<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:48:35 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Royal Orchid Hotels: Revenue Jumps 24%, But Profit Halves Amidst Accounting Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Royal-Orchid-Hotels-Revenue-Jumps-24percent-But-Profit-Halves-Amidst-Accounting-Shift/6992e5492e6a0b8ae17cec0d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Royal-Orchid-Hotels-Revenue-Jumps-24percent-But-Profit-Halves-Amidst-Accounting-Shift/6992e5492e6a0b8ae17cec0d</guid><description>Royal Orchid Hotels reported a strong 24.3% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹117.9 Cr in Q3 FY26. However, Profit After Tax (PAT) saw a significant drop of 52.9% YoY to ₹7.7 Cr. This decline is largely attributed to the adoption of new accounting standards (IND-AS), which increased depreciation and finance costs. The company also added 4 new hotels and outlined an ambitious 'Vision 2030' focusing on an asset-light model. Standalone performance showed a marginal revenue increase but a dip in profitability. The company has a history of regulatory actions, including a SEBI penalty for misleading financial statements.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:37:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992e5492e6a0b8ae17cec0c_1771234806824.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alkem's Unit Clears USFDA Data Integrity Test; 6 Issues Noted</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alkems-Unit-Clears-USFDA-Data-Integrity-Test-6-Issues-Noted/6992e5462e6a0b8ae17cebf7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alkems-Unit-Clears-USFDA-Data-Integrity-Test-6-Issues-Noted/6992e5462e6a0b8ae17cebf7</guid><description>Alkem Laboratories' subsidiary, Enzene Biosciences, passed a USFDA Pre-Approval Inspection (PAI) at its Chakan, Pune facility on February 13, 2026. The inspection concluded with 6 procedural observations, but critically, zero findings related to data integrity, validating Enzene's quality systems. The company is preparing its response and corrective actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:37:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992e5462e6a0b8ae17cebf6_1771234774158.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mufti Sales Dip, Firm Bets Big on Brand Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Mufti-Sales-Dip-Firm-Bets-Big-on-Brand-Overhaul/6992e5412e6a0b8ae17cebde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Mufti-Sales-Dip-Firm-Bets-Big-on-Brand-Overhaul/6992e5412e6a0b8ae17cebde</guid><description>Credo Brands Marketing, the maker of MUFTI, saw its Q3 FY'26 revenue drop 6.4% year-on-year to ₹146.1 crore. For the nine months, revenue fell 7.5% to ₹430 crore. The company is banking on its MUFTI 2.0 strategy, involving store premiumization and a planned increase in advertising spend, to revive growth. However, current performance shows margin pressures and a significant increase in marketing investment is expected to impact short-term profits.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:37:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992e5412e6a0b8ae17cebdd_1771234756172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW MG India Bets ₹40B on EVs Amid Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-MG-India-Bets-40B-on-EVs-Amid-Profit-Slump/6992e5402e6a0b8ae17cebc8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-MG-India-Bets-40B-on-EVs-Amid-Profit-Slump/6992e5402e6a0b8ae17cebc8</guid><description>JSW MG India is injecting up to ₹40 billion (approx. $441 million) over the next few years to significantly expand its manufacturing capacity and pivot its product lineup towards New Energy Vehicles (NEVs). This aggressive push aims to double production capacity to 300,000 units annually and capture a dominant share in India's burgeoning EV market. The investment follows a substantial jump in 2025 sales and revenue, yet it unfolds against a backdrop of doubled losses and intense competitive pressure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:37:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992e5402e6a0b8ae17cebc7_1771234797082.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Moneyboxx Finance Pivots to Secured Loans, PAT Jumps 77%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Moneyboxx-Finance-Pivots-to-Secured-Loans-PAT-Jumps-77percent/6992e3d72e6a0b8ae17ceaab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Moneyboxx-Finance-Pivots-to-Secured-Loans-PAT-Jumps-77percent/6992e3d72e6a0b8ae17ceaab</guid><description>Moneyboxx Finance has reported a strong 77.6% year-on-year jump in Profit After Tax (PAT) to INR 0.35 crore for Q3 FY'26. This growth is driven by a strategic shift towards secured lending, which now forms 60% of its Assets Under Management (AUM). While Net Interest Margins (NIMs) moderated to 14% due to this pivot, asset quality saw significant improvement with Gross Non-Performing Assets (GNPA) falling sharply to 1.43% from 5.6% a year ago. The company plans an equity raise of INR 43.3 crore to support its growth ambitions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:31:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992e3d72e6a0b8ae17ceaaa_1771234404402.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TRSL Q3 Results: Passenger Rail Booms, Freight Slips; Order Book Strong</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TRSL-Q3-Results-Passenger-Rail-Booms-Freight-Slips-Order-Book-Strong/6992e36a2e6a0b8ae17cea44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TRSL-Q3-Results-Passenger-Rail-Booms-Freight-Slips-Order-Book-Strong/6992e36a2e6a0b8ae17cea44</guid><description>Titagarh Rail Systems (TRSL) reported mixed Q3 FY26 results. While overall revenue dipped year-on-year, its Passenger Rail Systems (PRS) segment surged over 230%, boosting margins QoQ. The company maintains a robust ₹14,455 crore order book, with strong strategic alignment with the Union Budget's railway allocation bolstering its future outlook, especially in PRS and metro rolling stock.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:29:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992e36a2e6a0b8ae17cea43_1771234256576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Company Eyes Revenue as Pune Drone and Solar Plants Ready</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Company-Eyes-Revenue-as-Pune-Drone-and-Solar-Plants-Ready/6992e0bc2e6a0b8ae17ce89f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Company-Eyes-Revenue-as-Pune-Drone-and-Solar-Plants-Ready/6992e0bc2e6a0b8ae17ce89f</guid><description>A significant corporate update reveals the company's Pune facility is now operationally ready for defence drone and solar manufacturing. This marks a strategic transition from infrastructure development to revenue generation. Key initiatives include commencing solar production and assembling UAV platforms imported in SKD format, with a target for drone manufacturing infrastructure to be commissioned by March 2026. The company has also secured international procurement agreements for MALE UAV and loitering munition platforms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:17:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992e0bc2e6a0b8ae17ce89e_1771233542992.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gaudium IVF IPO: Growth Amidst Critical Workforce Chasm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Gaudium-IVF-IPO-Growth-Amidst-Critical-Workforce-Chasm/6992e0a32e6a0b8ae17ce889</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Gaudium-IVF-IPO-Growth-Amidst-Critical-Workforce-Chasm/6992e0a32e6a0b8ae17ce889</guid><description>Gaudium IVF &amp; Women Health is set to launch its IPO on February 20, 2026, capitalizing on India's rapidly expanding IVF sector. Despite strong market tailwinds, the company grapples with alarming employee attrition rates exceeding 60% in FY25, alongside rising professional fees and substantial contingent liabilities. These internal challenges pose a material risk to its growth trajectory, potentially overshadowing the sector's robust expansion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:17:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992e0a32e6a0b8ae17ce888_1771233591757.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Engineers India Surges on Strong Q3, But High Forward P/E Casts Shadow</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Engineers-India-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-But-High-Forward-PE-Casts-Shadow/6992e0952e6a0b8ae17ce872</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Engineers-India-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-But-High-Forward-PE-Casts-Shadow/6992e0952e6a0b8ae17ce872</guid><description>Engineers India Limited (EIL) shares climbed to a six-month high, driven by a substantial multi-fold jump in Q3 FY26 profit and robust revenue growth. The company also secured a significant consultancy project from Dangote Refinery. However, the stock's forward valuation multiples are approaching premium levels, raising questions about the sustainability of its recent ascent despite a positive analyst consensus.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:17:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992e0952e6a0b8ae17ce871_1771233646461.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UK's BII Bets Big on India's Green Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UKs-BII-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Green-Future/6992dfcd2e6a0b8ae17ce76a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UKs-BII-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Green-Future/6992dfcd2e6a0b8ae17ce76a</guid><description>British International Investment (BII), the UK's development finance institution, is cementing India as its largest single-country exposure, deploying $2.5 billion across over 600 companies. The focus is squarely on private sector-led climate and inclusion initiatives, with substantial capital earmarked for electric mobility and renewable energy. A key strategic pivot involves bolstering supply chain resilience in critical areas like battery manufacturing and EV components, reflecting government policy alignment and a proactive approach to emerging global economic trends.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:13:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992dfcd2e6a0b8ae17ce769_1771233340056.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Properties Buys Bengaluru Land for ₹600Cr Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Shriram-Properties-Buys-Bengaluru-Land-for-600Cr-Project/6992df292e6a0b8ae17ce689</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Shriram-Properties-Buys-Bengaluru-Land-for-600Cr-Project/6992df292e6a0b8ae17ce689</guid><description>Shriram Properties Ltd has acquired a 4-acre land parcel on Sarjapur Main Road, South-East Bengaluru, for an estimated ₹550-600 crore Gross Development Value (GDV) project. The acquisition signifies a strategic move to bolster its premium residential offerings. The project, slated for launch in late 2026, adds to the developer's substantial existing pipeline of 42 projects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:11:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992df292e6a0b8ae17ce688_1771233233161.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIC Re profit dips 6%, but underwriting ratio improves</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-profit-dips-6percent-but-underwriting-ratio-improves/6992df272e6a0b8ae17ce672</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-profit-dips-6percent-but-underwriting-ratio-improves/6992df272e6a0b8ae17ce672</guid><description>General Insurance Corporation of India (GIC Re) reported a 6.3% year-on-year decline in net profit for Q3 FY26, settling at ₹1,518.92 crore, even as gross premium income rose 10.2%. The company's combined ratio improved to 105.32% from 107.83% YoY, though it remains above 100%, indicating ongoing underwriting losses. GIC Re is focusing on portfolio optimization and a strategic shift towards domestic business, aiming for 8-10% medium-term growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992df272e6a0b8ae17ce671_1771233189193.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Power Seeks Green Light for Massive ₹45,000 Crore Deals with Group Firms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Power-Seeks-Green-Light-for-Massive-45000-Crore-Deals-with-Group-Firms/6992deb22e6a0b8ae17ce593</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Power-Seeks-Green-Light-for-Massive-45000-Crore-Deals-with-Group-Firms/6992deb22e6a0b8ae17ce593</guid><description>Tata Power is asking shareholders to approve six major deals worth a combined ₹45,000 crore for the upcoming financial year, FY27. These proposed transactions involve business dealings with other Tata Group companies like Tata Projects and Tata Steel, as well as with state-owned GRIDCO for power distribution. Shareholders will vote on these plans through a postal ballot and e-voting process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:09:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992deb22e6a0b8ae17ce592_1771233054676.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Davin Sons Retail Partners With Adidas, Skechers, Crocs For New Outlets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Davin-Sons-Retail-Partners-With-Adidas-Skechers-Crocs-For-New-Outlets/6992deaf2e6a0b8ae17ce57d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Davin-Sons-Retail-Partners-With-Adidas-Skechers-Crocs-For-New-Outlets/6992deaf2e6a0b8ae17ce57d</guid><description>Davin Sons Retail Limited has signed Memoranda of Understanding (MOUs) with global sportswear giants Skechers, Reebok, Adidas, New Balance, and Crocs. These agreements aim to establish multi-brand outlets in agreed territories, signalling a significant strategic move for the company to expand its retail presence and product offerings in the booming Indian sportswear market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:09:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992deaf2e6a0b8ae17ce57c_1771233053353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TTI Enterprise Mulls Quitting NBFC Business Amid Steep Financial Fall</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/TTI-Enterprise-Mulls-Quitting-NBFC-Business-Amid-Steep-Financial-Fall/6992dd462e6a0b8ae17ce40c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/TTI-Enterprise-Mulls-Quitting-NBFC-Business-Amid-Steep-Financial-Fall/6992dd462e6a0b8ae17ce40c</guid><description>TTI Enterprise Limited is set to consider surrendering its NBFC license to the RBI on February 20, 2026, amid a severe financial downturn. The company has seen a drastic fall in revenue and profits, prompting a strategic shift towards retail ventures. The trading window for its shares is closed from February 16 to February 23.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:03:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992dd462e6a0b8ae17ce40b_1771232723875.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Investor Bairagi Launches ₹40 Crore Open Offer for JIMG Corp Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Investor-Bairagi-Launches-40-Crore-Open-Offer-for-JIMG-Corp-Stake/6992dcf52e6a0b8ae17ce38a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Investor-Bairagi-Launches-40-Crore-Open-Offer-for-JIMG-Corp-Stake/6992dcf52e6a0b8ae17ce38a</guid><description>Investor Neerav Bairagi has launched an open offer to acquire up to 26% of JIMG Corporation Limited. The offer price is ₹65.30 per share. This move could significantly alter the company's ownership structure and control, as per a regulatory filing published on February 16, 2026. The offer is made under SEBI regulations, signaling a key corporate event for shareholders.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:01:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6992dcf52e6a0b8ae17ce389.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sky Gold Eyes Debt-Free Future with Bold '3.0' Vision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sky-Gold-Eyes-Debt-Free-Future-with-Bold-30-Vision/6992dcdc2e6a0b8ae17ce36c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sky-Gold-Eyes-Debt-Free-Future-with-Bold-30-Vision/6992dcdc2e6a0b8ae17ce36c</guid><description>Sky Gold and Diamonds unveils its 'Sky Gold 3.0' strategy, targeting 30-35% revenue CAGR and becoming net debt-free by 2030. The company is enhancing corporate governance, with promoters adopting a zero-salary model compensated via dividends, aligning interests with shareholders. Operational improvements and export expansion are key growth drivers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:01:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992dcdc2e6a0b8ae17ce36b_1771232595373.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GK Energy Powers Up: Q3 Profits Soar on Record Revenue &amp; New Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GK-Energy-Powers-Up-Q3-Profits-Soar-on-Record-Revenue-and-New-Strategy/6992dc582e6a0b8ae17ce2e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GK-Energy-Powers-Up-Q3-Profits-Soar-on-Record-Revenue-and-New-Strategy/6992dc582e6a0b8ae17ce2e2</guid><description>GK Energy Limited has delivered a stellar performance in Q3 FY26, with standalone net profit soaring 57.68% year-over-year to ₹58.83 crore. Revenue from operations surged 43.64% to ₹460.20 crore, driven by its core EPC business and a growing solar cell trading segment. The company also announced a strategic expansion into the Retail Solar Rooftop System (RTS) EPC segment to enhance cash flow and diversify.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:59:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992dc582e6a0b8ae17ce2e1_1771232461101.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Markolines Pavement Sees 72% Profit Jump on Infra Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Markolines-Pavement-Sees-72percent-Profit-Jump-on-Infra-Boom/6992db672e6a0b8ae17ce1f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Markolines-Pavement-Sees-72percent-Profit-Jump-on-Infra-Boom/6992db672e6a0b8ae17ce1f2</guid><description>Markolines Pavement Technologies reported a stellar Q3FY26 with a 72% surge in net profit to ₹7.00 Cr, fueled by strong revenue growth of 20% QoQ. For the nine months, net profit jumped 43% YoY to ₹14.87 Cr. The company attributes its robust performance to operational efficiencies, cost discipline, and a significant boost from government infrastructure development initiatives, positioning it well for future growth in the roads sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:55:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992db672e6a0b8ae17ce1f1_1771232217908.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Remsons Industries Surges on Q3 Results, Eyes ₹1000 Cr Revenue Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Remsons-Industries-Surges-on-Q3-Results-Eyes-1000-Cr-Revenue-Target/6992daf52e6a0b8ae17ce175</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Remsons-Industries-Surges-on-Q3-Results-Eyes-1000-Cr-Revenue-Target/6992daf52e6a0b8ae17ce175</guid><description>Remsons Industries posted a strong 20% year-on-year revenue growth in Q3 FY2026, reaching ₹123 Crores. The company is undergoing a major transformation into 'Remsons 2.0', aiming to become a technology-driven mobility solutions provider across the value chain. With significant order wins, including a multi-year ₹300+ crore contract with Stellantis, and aggressive expansion plans, Remsons aims for ₹900-1000 Crores revenue by FY2029-2030 and improved EBITDA margins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:53:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992daf52e6a0b8ae17ce174_1771232131688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Schneider Electric Sees Orders Surge 60% Amidst India's Infrastructure Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Schneider-Electric-Sees-Orders-Surge-60percent-Amidst-Indias-Infrastructure-Boom/6992daf12e6a0b8ae17ce15f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Schneider-Electric-Sees-Orders-Surge-60percent-Amidst-Indias-Infrastructure-Boom/6992daf12e6a0b8ae17ce15f</guid><description>Schneider Electric Infrastructure reported a strong Q3 FY26, with order booking soaring 60% year-on-year to ₹909 crore and sales climbing over 20% to ₹1,000 crore. The company's order backlog also grew by over 50% to ₹1,700 crore. Management cited strong government initiatives, rising capex, and growth in new sectors like data centers, semiconductors, and renewables as key drivers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:53:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992daf12e6a0b8ae17ce15e_1771232137094.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCLT Steps In: Jaypee Infratech Project Delays Under Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NCLT-Steps-In-Jaypee-Infratech-Project-Delays-Under-Scrutiny/6992d9122e6a0b8ae17ce02b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NCLT-Steps-In-Jaypee-Infratech-Project-Delays-Under-Scrutiny/6992d9122e6a0b8ae17ce02b</guid><description>The National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) has appointed a two-member committee to assess construction progress for Suraksha Group's Jaypee Infratech projects. This action stems from escalating homebuyer complaints regarding inordinate delays, signaling potential execution issues with the approved resolution plan. The committee will report on project status and grievances by April 1, 2026, raising concerns for thousands of affected buyers amidst a generally robust Indian real estate market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:45:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d9122e6a0b8ae17ce02a_1771231647935.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Arkade Developers: ₹700 Cr Project Amidst Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Arkade-Developers-700-Cr-Project-Amidst-Profit-Slump/6992d9112e6a0b8ae17ce014</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Arkade-Developers-700-Cr-Project-Amidst-Profit-Slump/6992d9112e6a0b8ae17ce014</guid><description>Arkade Developers has secured a significant ₹700 crore Gross Development Value (GDV) redevelopment project in Malad West, Mumbai. This initiative aims to modernize housing for the Shree Rani Sati Nagar Co-operative Housing Society Limited. However, the company is currently navigating a period of financial headwinds, reporting a 19.56% decrease in net profit for the third quarter, alongside declining net sales and EBITDA. The stock reflects this pressure, trading significantly below its IPO price.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:45:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d9112e6a0b8ae17ce013_1771231657193.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anthropic India Surge: Enterprise Focus Drives Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-India-Surge-Enterprise-Focus-Drives-Growth/6992d8222e6a0b8ae17cdf52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-India-Surge-Enterprise-Focus-Drives-Growth/6992d8222e6a0b8ae17cdf52</guid><description>Anthropic India has doubled its revenue run rate, with India now its second-largest market for Claude AI. Managing Director Irina Ghose highlights a strategy focused on co-building with enterprises and addressing "last mile" needs across sectors like education and healthcare. This deep localization, coupled with investments in Indic language capabilities, aims to foster trust and long-term impact. The company's growth mirrors a global surge to a $14 billion run rate, driven by enterprise adoption, while navigating a competitive landscape and addressing the unique demands of the Indian market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:41:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d8222e6a0b8ae17cdf51_1771231429012.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jainam Broking IPO Faces Regulatory Headwinds Amidst Derivatives Frenzy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Jainam-Broking-IPO-Faces-Regulatory-Headwinds-Amidst-Derivatives-Frenzy/6992d6e82e6a0b8ae17cdddf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Jainam-Broking-IPO-Faces-Regulatory-Headwinds-Amidst-Derivatives-Frenzy/6992d6e82e6a0b8ae17cdddf</guid><description>Jainam Broking has filed its Draft Red Herring Prospectus (DRHP) for an Initial Public Offering, aiming to tap into India's expanding financial services sector. However, the firm's future as a listed entity is intertwined with the volatile and increasingly regulated Indian derivatives market, where retail investors face significant losses and regulatory bodies are imposing stricter controls. This presents a complex environment for Jainam's growth trajectory and its ability to meet public market expectations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:35:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d6e82e6a0b8ae17cddde_1771231038255.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold ETFs Defy Downturn: Silver Faces Deeper Sell-off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-ETFs-Defy-Downturn-Silver-Faces-Deeper-Sell-off/6992d6b72e6a0b8ae17cddc5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-ETFs-Defy-Downturn-Silver-Faces-Deeper-Sell-off/6992d6b72e6a0b8ae17cddc5</guid><description>Precious metals faced downward pressure on February 16, 2026, with gold futures down 0.53% and silver futures down 1.45% on CME COMEX. This decline extended to domestic markets. Crucially, gold exchange-traded funds (ETFs) exhibited unexpected resilience, with several posting modest gains despite the softer futures market. In stark contrast, silver ETFs experienced broader and deeper losses, highlighting a divergence in market sentiment between the two metals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:35:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d6b72e6a0b8ae17cddc4_1771231045068.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hubtown Plans ₹600 Crore Share Sale for Realty Expansion, Debt Paydown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Hubtown-Plans-600-Crore-Share-Sale-for-Realty-Expansion-Debt-Paydown/6992d5522e6a0b8ae17cdcb8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Hubtown-Plans-600-Crore-Share-Sale-for-Realty-Expansion-Debt-Paydown/6992d5522e6a0b8ae17cdcb8</guid><description>Hubtown Limited has called an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) for March 10, 2026. Shareholders will vote on a proposal to raise up to ₹6,000 million (₹600 Crores) by issuing new securities. The funds are earmarked for expanding its real estate business, including land acquisition and development, and for repaying existing borrowings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:29:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d5522e6a0b8ae17cdcb7_1771230675878.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's F&amp;O Market: Global Scale Meets Retail Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-FandO-Market-Global-Scale-Meets-Retail-Risk/6992d1d12e6a0b8ae17cd9ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-FandO-Market-Global-Scale-Meets-Retail-Risk/6992d1d12e6a0b8ae17cd9ea</guid><description>India's futures and options market has ascended to global leadership in volume, fueled by rapid retail investor growth over two decades. However, this expansion masks a stark reality: 91% of individual traders incurred substantial net losses in FY25, totaling over ₹1.05 lakh crore. Recent stringent regulatory actions by SEBI aim to curb speculation and protect investors, leading to significant drops in trading volumes. The market faces a critical juncture, balancing its benchmark status with inherent risks for its burgeoning retail base.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:14:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d1d12e6a0b8ae17cd9e9_1771229908588.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titagarh Navigates Firema Risk Amidst Rail Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Titagarh-Navigates-Firema-Risk-Amidst-Rail-Boom/6992d1942e6a0b8ae17cd91a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Titagarh-Navigates-Firema-Risk-Amidst-Rail-Boom/6992d1942e6a0b8ae17cd91a</guid><description>Titagarh Rail Systems is navigating a crucial period, balancing a booming passenger rail business fueled by a ₹14,500 crore order book with the looming uncertainty of its Italian subsidiary, Firema Trasporti. The company faces a potential ₹300 crore exposure, including a worst-case investment write-off, even as it ramps up Vande Bharat train production and bids for new tenders.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:13:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d1942e6a0b8ae17cd919_1771229936042.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eris Lifesciences: Growth Bets Face Margin Scrutiny, Analysts Maintain Confidence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Eris-Lifesciences-Growth-Bets-Face-Margin-Scrutiny-Analysts-Maintain-Confidence/6992d1922e6a0b8ae17cd903</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Eris-Lifesciences-Growth-Bets-Face-Margin-Scrutiny-Analysts-Maintain-Confidence/6992d1922e6a0b8ae17cd903</guid><description>Eris Lifesciences' Q3 FY26 performance showed robust international segment growth offsetting subdued domestic sales, leading to a 6.36% stock price drop despite revenue increases. Prabhudas Lilladher reiterated a 'BUY' rating and ₹1800 target, citing future catalysts like the GLP-1 market and export ramp-up, even after revising EBITDA estimates down by 3%. The company's inorganic strategy aims for scale without margin dilution. However, concerns linger regarding high valuation, standalone financials, and sequential margin compression.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:13:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d1922e6a0b8ae17cd902_1771229816552.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises: Profit Jump Amid Debt Rise &amp; US Sanctions Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Enterprises-Profit-Jump-Amid-Debt-Rise-and-US-Sanctions-Probe/6992d14f2e6a0b8ae17cd7de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Enterprises-Profit-Jump-Amid-Debt-Rise-and-US-Sanctions-Probe/6992d14f2e6a0b8ae17cd7de</guid><description>Adani Enterprises reported a significant profit rebound and revenue growth, bolstered by acquisitions and a substantial rights issue. However, the company's debt-to-equity ratio has escalated, and it is now under a US investigation concerning potential Iran sanctions violations. These factors introduce considerable risk, overshadowing the positive financial metrics and a recent P/E ratio near 20.9, creating a complex investment outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:11:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6992d14f2e6a0b8ae17cd7dd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Dips Amid AI Fears, High Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Mahindra-Dips-Amid-AI-Fears-High-Valuation/6992d1492e6a0b8ae17cd7be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Mahindra-Dips-Amid-AI-Fears-High-Valuation/6992d1492e6a0b8ae17cd7be</guid><description>Tech Mahindra's stock experienced a significant downturn, reflecting broader sector-wide anxieties surrounding AI's impact on the IT services model. Despite recent revenue growth and improving profitability metrics, the company's higher valuation multiples compared to key peers, coupled with sector-wide risk aversion, has pressured its share price. Analyst sentiment remains largely optimistic with a 'Strong Buy' consensus, yet the market's immediate reaction points to a cautious stance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:11:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d1492e6a0b8ae17cd7bd_1771229800209.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Max Healthcare: Growth vs. Premium Valuation Battle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Growth-vs-Premium-Valuation-Battle/6992d1402e6a0b8ae17cd7a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Growth-vs-Premium-Valuation-Battle/6992d1402e6a0b8ae17cd7a5</guid><description>Max Healthcare Institute shares climbed 2% to ₹1,074.70 on Monday, defying a broader market downturn. This surge, despite a dip in the healthcare sector and benchmark indices on February 10th, was driven by robust revenue growth from ₹2,504 Crore in FY2021 to ₹7,028 Crore in FY2025 and a significant profit turnaround. However, the company's premium valuation, reflected in a high P/E ratio of approximately 72, is a point of concern, especially with a recent 'Sell' rating from MarketsMojo, contrasting with a generally positive sector outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:11:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d1402e6a0b8ae17cd7a4_1771229744576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indus Towers: 52-Week High Masking Quarterly Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indus-Towers-52-Week-High-Masking-Quarterly-Profit-Slump/6992d1352e6a0b8ae17cd78d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indus-Towers-52-Week-High-Masking-Quarterly-Profit-Slump/6992d1352e6a0b8ae17cd78d</guid><description>Indus Towers achieved a new 52-week high, yet its December 2025 quarter net profit plummeted by 55.6% year-on-year to ₹1,776 crore. While annual revenue and profit showed robust growth for the fiscal year ending March 2025, the sharp quarterly decline signals potential headwinds amidst expansion. The company's debt-to-equity ratio remains low at 0.07, and it operates within a growing Indian telecom tower market driven by 5G, though regulatory scrutiny and past receivable issues present challenges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:11:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d1352e6a0b8ae17cd78c_1771229711307.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Torrent Pharma JBCP Deal: Synergies or Strain?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Torrent-Pharma-JBCP-Deal-Synergies-or-Strain/6992d1322e6a0b8ae17cd776</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Torrent-Pharma-JBCP-Deal-Synergies-or-Strain/6992d1322e6a0b8ae17cd776</guid><description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals' Q3FY26 EBITDA rose 19% YoY, fueled by strong branded formulation sales. The acquisition of JB Chemicals &amp; Pharma aims to solidify its position as India's fifth-largest pharma player, enhancing chronic therapy offerings and adding a CDMO vertical. Analysts anticipate significant cost synergies, with Prabhudas Lilladher upgrading the stock to 'BUY' with a ₹4,750 target, citing projected combined entity EBITDA of ₹77-78 billion by FY28.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:11:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d1322e6a0b8ae17cd775_1771229701715.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CRISIL Stock Jumps on Robust FY25 Results; Valuation Premium Questioned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CRISIL-Stock-Jumps-on-Robust-FY25-Results-Valuation-Premium-Questioned/6992d1282e6a0b8ae17cd72e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CRISIL-Stock-Jumps-on-Robust-FY25-Results-Valuation-Premium-Questioned/6992d1282e6a0b8ae17cd72e</guid><description>CRISIL's stock advanced significantly following robust fiscal 2025 earnings and an increased dividend payout, underscoring financial resilience and a debt-free balance sheet. Annual revenue climbed 11.9% to ₹3,649.01 crore, and net profit rose 12.0% to ₹766.01 crore. The company's market leadership and consistent growth command a substantial valuation premium, however, raising questions about future sustainability against peer valuations and sector cyclicality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:11:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6992d1282e6a0b8ae17cd72d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSP Stock Hits New Highs Amid Profit Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSP-Stock-Hits-New-Highs-Amid-Profit-Plunge/6992d11c2e6a0b8ae17cd716</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSP-Stock-Hits-New-Highs-Amid-Profit-Plunge/6992d11c2e6a0b8ae17cd716</guid><description>Jindal Steel &amp; Power Ltd. (JSP) shares reached a new peak of ₹1,208.70 on February 16, 2026, buoyed by positive market sentiment and sector optimism. This ascent, however, starkly contrasts with the company's deteriorating financial performance. For fiscal year 2025, net profit plummeted by over 50% year-on-year to ₹2,854.75 Crore, accompanied by a significant drop in earnings per share and eroding profit margins. Quarterly results showed a similar trend, with net profit for the December 2025 quarter falling sharply to ₹193.30 Crore from ₹950.80 Crore in the prior year.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:11:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d11c2e6a0b8ae17cd715_1771229652056.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fine Organic: Margin Squeeze Amidst Ambitious Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fine-Organic-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Ambitious-Global-Expansion/6992d1192e6a0b8ae17cd6ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fine-Organic-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Ambitious-Global-Expansion/6992d1192e6a0b8ae17cd6ff</guid><description>Fine Organic Industries posted a 7.3% year-over-year revenue increase to ₹554.8 crore in Q3 FY26. However, profitability metrics faced severe pressure, with adjusted EBITDA margins contracting by 560 basis points QoQ to 17.0% due to higher raw material costs. The company is aggressively pursuing global expansion with new US and UAE facilities, alongside a large greenfield project slated for FY28 contribution, while analysts maintain a mixed outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:11:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d1192e6a0b8ae17cd6fe_1771229633258.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's RTI Faces Privacy Test as SC Declines Stay on Data Law</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-RTI-Faces-Privacy-Test-as-SC-Declines-Stay-on-Data-Law/6992d0a42e6a0b8ae17cd5d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-RTI-Faces-Privacy-Test-as-SC-Declines-Stay-on-Data-Law/6992d0a42e6a0b8ae17cd5d2</guid><description>The Supreme Court declined to stay the amendment to the Right to Information (RTI) Act, introduced by the Digital Personal Data Protection (DPDP) Act, which restricts the disclosure of personal information even in cases serving larger public interest. This pivotal decision sets the stage for further deliberations on balancing data privacy with transparency, while petitioners argue the move significantly curtails fundamental rights to information and free speech. The ruling implies immediate challenges for investigative journalism and public scrutiny of official actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:09:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d0a42e6a0b8ae17cd5d1_1771229477092.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Analyst Bullish on Fractal Analytics Amid Valuation Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Analyst-Bullish-on-Fractal-Analytics-Amid-Valuation-Debate/6992d0a12e6a0b8ae17cd5bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Analyst-Bullish-on-Fractal-Analytics-Amid-Valuation-Debate/6992d0a12e6a0b8ae17cd5bb</guid><description>Prabhudas Lilladher has initiated coverage on Fractal Analytics with a 'BUY' recommendation and a price target of Rs 1,260, citing consistent revenue growth and robust client retention. However, the AI analytics firm's recent market debut was met with caution, with shares trading below their IPO price. Fractal faces scrutiny over its premium valuation, particularly when compared to industry peers and broader market multiples, even as it targets significant margin expansion and revenue growth in the burgeoning AI sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:09:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992d0a12e6a0b8ae17cd5ba_1771229477358.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>