<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:36:35 +0000</pubDate><item><title>PIF Partnership Elevates Stride Ventures, Signals India's Credit Market Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/PIF-Partnership-Elevates-Stride-Ventures-Signals-Indias-Credit-Market-Rise/69a16280fa7d0695d1ab8769</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/PIF-Partnership-Elevates-Stride-Ventures-Signals-Indias-Credit-Market-Rise/69a16280fa7d0695d1ab8769</guid><description>Stride Ventures has secured a significant partnership with Saudi Arabia's Public Investment Fund (PIF) through its Jada Fund of Funds. This collaboration marks a critical step for the India-rooted Stride Ventures, positioning it as a globally trusted private credit platform. The deal underscores PIF's confidence in Stride's governance model and highlights the growing influence of Indian financial platforms on the international stage, while signaling PIF's strategic intent to bolster its exposure to emerging market credit ecosystems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:23:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a16280fa7d0695d1ab8768_1772184310147.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exato Technologies Q3 FY26 PAT Surges 191%; Revenue Up 63.23%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Exato-Technologies-Q3-FY26-PAT-Surges-191percent-Revenue-Up-6323percent/69a15dcafa7d0695d1ab84f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Exato-Technologies-Q3-FY26-PAT-Surges-191percent-Revenue-Up-6323percent/69a15dcafa7d0695d1ab84f5</guid><description>Exato Technologies reported robust Q3 FY26 results with PAT surging 191% and revenue growing 63.23% YoY for the nine months. The company is increasingly focusing on international markets, now contributing 28% of revenue, and holds a significant ₹348 crore order book, largely in healthcare. Key risks include high customer concentration and revenue lumpiness, but strategic international expansion and IP development are key growth drivers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a15dcafa7d0695d1ab84f4_1772183299876.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Energy Security Gambit: Deepwater Exploration, Reserve Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Security-Gambit-Deepwater-Exploration-Reserve-Boost/69a15d0bfa7d0695d1ab83d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Security-Gambit-Deepwater-Exploration-Reserve-Boost/69a15d0bfa7d0695d1ab83d0</guid><description>India is undertaking "Mission Samudra Manthan," a multi-pronged initiative to fortify its energy security against geopolitical shocks and import dependence. The plan accelerates deepwater exploration, aiming to quintuple annual well drilling to 100 by 2027, and expands strategic petroleum reserves by 6 MMT to approach a 90-day import buffer. This strategic push seeks to reduce the nation's 85% energy import reliance, targeting significant increases in domestic hydrocarbon production and refining capacity, while navigating substantial capital requirements and global market volatility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:59:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a15d0bfa7d0695d1ab83cf_1772182903386.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Storms Batter Equities, Exposing AI Hype</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Storms-Batter-Equities-Exposing-AI-Hype/69a15c6ffa7d0695d1ab82fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Storms-Batter-Equities-Exposing-AI-Hype/69a15c6ffa7d0695d1ab82fc</guid><description>Indian equity markets experienced a significant decline, propelled by escalating geopolitical tensions in West Asia and along the Pakistan-Afghanistan border. This, combined with persistent skepticism over the profitability of artificial intelligence investments, amplified concerns about stretched valuations, especially in small and midcap stocks. The selling pressure has led to a reassessment of near-term earnings visibility for the IT sector and a general risk-off sentiment across exchanges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:57:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a15c6ffa7d0695d1ab82fb_1772182939551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIFT City's Landmark IPO: XED Eyes Foreign Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/GIFT-Citys-Landmark-IPO-XED-Eyes-Foreign-Capital/69a15bf3fa7d0695d1ab8215</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/GIFT-Citys-Landmark-IPO-XED-Eyes-Foreign-Capital/69a15bf3fa7d0695d1ab8215</guid><description>XED Executive Development Ltd is launching India's inaugural equity IPO from GIFT City's International Financial Services Centre (IFSC) on March 6, seeking to raise $12 million. The dollar-denominated offering on NSE IX and India-INX targets foreign investors, aiming to fund global expansion and acquisitions. This debut represents a critical test for IFSC's ambitions in attracting offshore equity listings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:55:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a15bf3fa7d0695d1ab8214_1772182624930.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Jet Healthcare Bets ₹2,300 Cr on ESG-Driven Pharma Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Bets-2300-Cr-on-ESG-Driven-Pharma-Expansion/69a15be9fa7d0695d1ab81fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Bets-2300-Cr-on-ESG-Driven-Pharma-Expansion/69a15be9fa7d0695d1ab81fe</guid><description>Blue Jet Healthcare is investing ₹2,300 crore to establish a new pharmaceutical manufacturing facility in Andhra Pradesh, slated for operation by FY2028-29. The project emphasizes advanced environmental technologies, including Zero Liquid Discharge and significant energy/water recovery, aiming to meet stringent global ESG benchmarks. This expansion is designed to boost production of contrast media intermediates and high-intensity sweeteners, positioning the company to capture growing demand in the specialized CDMO sector and enhance its international market competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:55:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a15be9fa7d0695d1ab81fd_1772182676174.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GMDC secures Kutch mine green nod; eyes 3 MTPA lignite, 30 MTPA limestone</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GMDC-secures-Kutch-mine-green-nod-eyes-3-MTPA-lignite-30-MTPA-limestone/69a1582bfa7d0695d1ab7ff4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GMDC-secures-Kutch-mine-green-nod-eyes-3-MTPA-lignite-30-MTPA-limestone/69a1582bfa7d0695d1ab7ff4</guid><description>Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation (GMDC) has received crucial environmental clearance from the Indian government for its Lakhpat-Punrajpur Lignite &amp; Limestone Mine in Kutch, Gujarat. The approval allows for a production capacity of 3.0 MTPA of lignite and 29.81 MTPA of limestone. This marks a significant milestone in GMDC's expansion strategy, bolstering its long-term production visibility and strengthening its mineral resource base within the state.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:39:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1582bfa7d0695d1ab7ff3_1772181855289.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sarda Energy Rally Masks Margin Woes Post-SKS Deal Clearance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Sarda-Energy-Rally-Masks-Margin-Woes-Post-SKS-Deal-Clearance/69a157b6fa7d0695d1ab7f36</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Sarda-Energy-Rally-Masks-Margin-Woes-Post-SKS-Deal-Clearance/69a157b6fa7d0695d1ab7f36</guid><description>Sarda Energy and Minerals Ltd. shares surged over 8% following the Supreme Court's dismissal of acquisition-related pleas, clearing the final obstacle for the SKS Power transaction. This strategic move is expected to reduce business cyclicality. However, the immediate financial picture remains weak, with Q3 net profit down 3.55% and revenue declining 3.3%. Earnings before interest, tax, depreciation, and amortisation (EBITDA) saw a steeper 15.7% drop, accompanied by a notable compression in operating margins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:37:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a157b6fa7d0695d1ab7f35_1772181575079.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>String Metaverse Appoints Tech Advisor, Eyes Global AI Workforce Platform</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/String-Metaverse-Appoints-Tech-Advisor-Eyes-Global-AI-Workforce-Platform/69a15797fa7d0695d1ab7eda</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/String-Metaverse-Appoints-Tech-Advisor-Eyes-Global-AI-Workforce-Platform/69a15797fa7d0695d1ab7eda</guid><description>String Metaverse Limited has appointed Mr. Sai Kotha Venkata as Technical Advisor and announced plans to establish a Singapore-based entity to develop a global Agentic Workforce Platform. This initiative aims to deploy AI agents across financial markets and payment systems, leveraging the company's 'String Payx' fintech platform. The move signifies a strategic push into advanced AI and global fintech infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:36:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a15797fa7d0695d1ab7ed9_1772181469392.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Wealth Surge Redefines Luxury Property as Strategic Asset</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Wealth-Surge-Redefines-Luxury-Property-as-Strategic-Asset/69a1576dfa7d0695d1ab7e5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Wealth-Surge-Redefines-Luxury-Property-as-Strategic-Asset/69a1576dfa7d0695d1ab7e5a</guid><description>India's private wealth has surged, adding over 33,000 millionaires and nearing $1.5 trillion, fundamentally altering capital behavior. Luxury real estate is shifting from an aspirational purchase to a strategic asset class. Affluent investors, including Non-Resident Indians (NRIs), now prioritize stability, inflation protection, and long-term value over mere status. This trend is supported by inherent market scarcity, disciplined development, and favorable currency dynamics, positioning premium properties as essential components of resilient portfolios.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:35:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1576dfa7d0695d1ab7e59_1772181624439.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Byju's Legal Tangle: SC Status Quo Clouds Creditor Rights</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Byjus-Legal-Tangle-SC-Status-Quo-Clouds-Creditor-Rights/69a156c1fa7d0695d1ab7d7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Byjus-Legal-Tangle-SC-Status-Quo-Clouds-Creditor-Rights/69a156c1fa7d0695d1ab7d7b</guid><description>The Supreme Court has mandated a status quo in the dispute over the legal standing of Byju's Committee of Creditors (CoC). This order intervenes in a complex legal battle where the National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) had ruled that a CoC, while not a traditional juristic person, can litigate under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC). The move introduces further ambiguity into Byju's restructuring efforts, potentially delaying resolution and impacting asset recovery for its creditors. The court's decision ensures the current composition and operational status of the CoC remain unchanged pending a comprehensive hearing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:33:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a156c1fa7d0695d1ab7d7a_1772181319341.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IIFL Home Finance Secures $300M ADB Deal for Housing Deficit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Home-Finance-Secures-300M-ADB-Deal-for-Housing-Deficit/69a155d8fa7d0695d1ab7bc1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Home-Finance-Secures-300M-ADB-Deal-for-Housing-Deficit/69a155d8fa7d0695d1ab7bc1</guid><description>IIFL Home Finance has secured a $300 million syndicated loan from the Asian Development Bank (ADB) and a consortium of international lenders, marking its inaugural external commercial borrowing. This significant financing is earmarked to expand affordable housing access for low-income borrowers, particularly women, and support green-certified homes, directly addressing India's substantial housing deficit. The funds will be deployed across semi-urban, urban, and lagging regions of India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:29:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a155d8fa7d0695d1ab7bc0_1772181096239.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hypersoft Technologies Approves ₹2002 Crore Share Swap for Nexus Innovate Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hypersoft-Technologies-Approves-2002-Crore-Share-Swap-for-Nexus-Innovate-Acquisition/69a155d0fa7d0695d1ab7ba7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hypersoft-Technologies-Approves-2002-Crore-Share-Swap-for-Nexus-Innovate-Acquisition/69a155d0fa7d0695d1ab7ba7</guid><description>Hypersoft Technologies' Board has approved a ₹2002.35 crore share swap, allotting 6.82 crore equity shares to make Nexus Innovate Pte. Ltd. a wholly-owned subsidiary. The move signals a significant strategic integration. Concurrently, the company noted a delay in submitting shareholder complaint data for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, and has been advised to enhance its internal compliance mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:29:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a155d0fa7d0695d1ab7ba6_1772181092653.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Investment Push: Ambition Meets Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Investment-Push-Ambition-Meets-Execution-Hurdles/69a1556bfa7d0695d1ab7b2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Investment-Push-Ambition-Meets-Execution-Hurdles/69a1556bfa7d0695d1ab7b2a</guid><description>Prime Minister Modi has urged a significant ramp-up in private investment and innovation to propel India towards its 'Viksit Bharat' 2047 goal. While public capital expenditure is surging and foreign direct investment shows robust inflow, persistent financing gaps in infrastructure and recent market volatility highlight execution risks. Concurrently, intensified India-Israel trade talks aim to unlock new economic corridors, but the nation's developmental aspirations require a shift from scale to productivity to bridge the gap between ambitious targets and tangible results.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:27:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1556bfa7d0695d1ab7b29_1772181015783.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BCC Fuba India Plans ₹35 Cr Rights Issue; Board Meets March 5 to Finalise Terms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/BCC-Fuba-India-Plans-35-Cr-Rights-Issue-Board-Meets-March-5-to-Finalise-Terms/69a15198fa7d0695d1ab7932</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/BCC-Fuba-India-Plans-35-Cr-Rights-Issue-Board-Meets-March-5-to-Finalise-Terms/69a15198fa7d0695d1ab7932</guid><description>BCC Fuba India announced its board will meet on March 5, 2026, to approve terms for a rights issue aiming to raise up to ₹35 crore. BSE has provided in-principle approval for this capital infusion, which follows a recent acquisition and aims to support the company's financial requirements. The trading window for company securities is closed until March 4, 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:11:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a15198fa7d0695d1ab7931_1772179997135.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Market Slumps: Geopolitics, FPIs Spark Broad Sell-off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Market-Slumps-Geopolitics-FPIs-Spark-Broad-Sell-off/69a15127fa7d0695d1ab78b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Market-Slumps-Geopolitics-FPIs-Spark-Broad-Sell-off/69a15127fa7d0695d1ab78b8</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks, the Sensex and Nifty, plunged on Friday, February 27, 2026, as geopolitical tensions and significant foreign portfolio investor (FPI) selling pressured sentiment. The Sensex fell over 650 points to 81,589, and the Nifty dropped 228 points to 25,268. Real Estate and Auto sectors led the decline, while IT and Oil &amp; Gas showed resilience. Persistent FPI outflows, amounting to ₹3,466 crore on Thursday, contrasted with strong domestic institutional buying, indicating market bifurcation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:09:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a15127fa7d0695d1ab78b7_1772180072876.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SpiceJet Faces Court Costs Amidst Deepening Financial Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SpiceJet-Faces-Court-Costs-Amidst-Deepening-Financial-Strain/69a14fbbfa7d0695d1ab7757</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SpiceJet-Faces-Court-Costs-Amidst-Deepening-Financial-Strain/69a14fbbfa7d0695d1ab7757</guid><description>SpiceJet and its chairman Ajay Singh suffered a setback as the Supreme Court dismissed their plea against a Delhi High Court order to deposit ₹144.5 crore in an arbitration dispute with Kalanithi Maran. The court also imposed ₹1 lakh in costs on Singh. This ruling underscores the airline's persistent financial difficulties and its ongoing struggle to resolve long-standing liabilities, adding to its operational and market pressures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:03:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14fbbfa7d0695d1ab7756_1772179534357.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Coal Import Cut: Power Plants Face Costly Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Coal-Import-Cut-Power-Plants-Face-Costly-Overhaul/69a14f65fa7d0695d1ab76af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Coal-Import-Cut-Power-Plants-Face-Costly-Overhaul/69a14f65fa7d0695d1ab76af</guid><description>India aims to slash thermal coal imports by at least 30%, or 15 million tons annually, by increasing reliance on domestic production. While this bolsters state-owned Coal India's large inventories, power producers signal significant costs associated with recalibrating boilers to handle lower-quality local coal. This strategic shift occurs as renewable energy sources rapidly gain market share, presenting a complex energy transition for the nation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:01:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14f65fa7d0695d1ab76ae_1772179587305.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget: Growth Fuel vs. Execution Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Growth-Fuel-vs-Execution-Risk/69a14ecffa7d0695d1ab75b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Growth-Fuel-vs-Execution-Risk/69a14ecffa7d0695d1ab75b2</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 outlines a robust 'Viksit Bharat' roadmap driven by a record capital expenditure push, advanced technology integration, and significant bond market reforms. While aiming to stimulate growth and attract foreign investment, the true impact hinges on effective execution, fiscal prudence, and navigating global economic uncertainties. Investors face a landscape balancing ambitious projections with inherent implementation risks and potential shifts in borrowing costs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:59:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14ecffa7d0695d1ab75b1_1772179271308.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gen X Leads India's Premium Shift: The Outcome-Driven Consumer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Gen-X-Leads-Indias-Premium-Shift-The-Outcome-Driven-Consumer/69a14ec9fa7d0695d1ab759b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Gen-X-Leads-Indias-Premium-Shift-The-Outcome-Driven-Consumer/69a14ec9fa7d0695d1ab759b</guid><description>India's Generation X is emerging as a potent, yet often underestimated, consumer force, poised to drive over $500 billion in spending by FY30. Unlike younger demographics, Gen X prioritizes outcomes, efficacy, and long-term value over fleeting trends, fueling premiumization in sectors like healthcare, wellness, and specialized travel. This cohort's financial security and digital savviness, combined with a deliberate approach to purchases, positions them as key architects of substantive brand loyalty and premium market evolution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:59:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14ec9fa7d0695d1ab759a_1772179308860.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sarda Energy Secures SKS Power Acquisition as SC Rejects All Appeals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Sarda-Energy-Secures-SKS-Power-Acquisition-as-SC-Rejects-All-Appeals/69a14bf8fa7d0695d1ab73bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Sarda-Energy-Secures-SKS-Power-Acquisition-as-SC-Rejects-All-Appeals/69a14bf8fa7d0695d1ab73bc</guid><description>Sarda Energy &amp; Minerals Ltd. has received a decisive nod from the Supreme Court, which dismissed all appeals challenging its acquisition of SKS Power Generation (Chhattisgarh) Ltd. The apex court's ruling on February 27, 2026, validates the National Company Law Tribunal's (NCLT) approval of Sarda Energy's Rs 2,657 crore resolution plan, bringing a significant end to the legal challenges. This clears the path for Sarda Energy to integrate the 1200 MW thermal power asset, bolstering its energy security and diversification strategy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:47:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14bf8fa7d0695d1ab73bb_1772178751248.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ElevenLabs Bets Big on Google Cloud for Enterprise AI Voice Supremacy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ElevenLabs-Bets-Big-on-Google-Cloud-for-Enterprise-AI-Voice-Supremacy/69a14a3cfa7d0695d1ab71a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ElevenLabs-Bets-Big-on-Google-Cloud-for-Enterprise-AI-Voice-Supremacy/69a14a3cfa7d0695d1ab71a1</guid><description>ElevenLabs has significantly deepened its partnership with Google Cloud through a multi-year agreement, securing access to advanced NVIDIA Blackwell GPUs and Google's AI models. This strategic move aims to bolster ElevenLabs' capabilities for scaling enterprise AI voice tools and positions the company as a key player in AI infrastructure, moving beyond creative applications to offer robust, globally scalable voice solutions for large organizations. The expanded infrastructure will enable faster inference, enhanced reliability, and broader deployment capabilities across numerous industries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:39:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14a3cfa7d0695d1ab71a0_1772178150341.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bihar MFI Bill Triggers Sector Shake-up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bihar-MFI-Bill-Triggers-Sector-Shake-up/69a14a37fa7d0695d1ab7186</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bihar-MFI-Bill-Triggers-Sector-Shake-up/69a14a37fa7d0695d1ab7186</guid><description>Bihar's recent passage of the Microfinance Institutions Bill 2026 introduces stringent operational and registration mandates for lenders. This regulatory tightening, impacting approximately 15% of India's microfinance loan book, is expected to increase compliance burdens and could lead to a divergence in sector performance. Analysts suggest that well-capitalized, diversified entities such as Ujjivan Small Finance Bank are better positioned to navigate these changes than those with higher regional exposure or weaker balance sheets, potentially reshaping competitive dynamics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:39:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14a37fa7d0695d1ab7185_1772178093217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lupin Goa Facility Receives Satisfactory US FDA EIR, VAI Status</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Goa-Facility-Receives-Satisfactory-US-FDA-EIR-VAI-Status/69a14a37fa7d0695d1ab716f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Goa-Facility-Receives-Satisfactory-US-FDA-EIR-VAI-Status/69a14a37fa7d0695d1ab716f</guid><description>Lupin Limited has announced receiving a satisfactory Establishment Inspection Report (EIR) from the US FDA for its Goa manufacturing facility. The inspection, conducted in November 2025, concluded with a Voluntary Action Indicated (VAI) classification, signifying compliance with regulatory standards. This positive outcome is crucial for the facility's continued operations and market access in the United States.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:39:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14a37fa7d0695d1ab716e_1772178268114.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sarvam AI Powers SBI Life's Nationwide AI Rollout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Sarvam-AI-Powers-SBI-Lifes-Nationwide-AI-Rollout/69a14a2ffa7d0695d1ab713b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Sarvam-AI-Powers-SBI-Lifes-Nationwide-AI-Rollout/69a14a2ffa7d0695d1ab713b</guid><description>AI startup Sarvam has partnered with SBI Life Insurance to deploy its advanced AI tools, Samvaad and Arya, across the insurer's nationwide network. This initiative targets over 8 crore customers and 3.5 lakh distributors, focusing on production-ready AI for enhanced customer engagement and sales support. The move signals Sarvam's ambition to scale its 'sovereign AI' solutions beyond pilots, aligning with India's accelerating adoption of AI in the financial services sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:39:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14a2ffa7d0695d1ab713a_1772178108059.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KFintech Subsidiary Obtains IFSCA License for Global Fintech Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KFintech-Subsidiary-Obtains-IFSCA-License-for-Global-Fintech-Expansion/69a149b8fa7d0695d1ab708a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KFintech-Subsidiary-Obtains-IFSCA-License-for-Global-Fintech-Expansion/69a149b8fa7d0695d1ab708a</guid><description>KFin Technologies Limited's wholly-owned subsidiary, KFin Global Technologies (IFSC) Limited, has secured a Certificate of Registration from the International Financial Services Centres Authority (IFSCA). This license allows the subsidiary to operate as a TechFin and Ancillary Services Provider within India's International Financial Services Centres (IFSC), marking a strategic move to deepen its global fintech presence and diversify service offerings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:37:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a149b8fa7d0695d1ab7089_1772177968138.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver's Consolidation Tests Resilience Amid Macro Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silvers-Consolidation-Tests-Resilience-Amid-Macro-Shifts/69a14930fa7d0695d1ab6fe8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silvers-Consolidation-Tests-Resilience-Amid-Macro-Shifts/69a14930fa7d0695d1ab6fe8</guid><description>Silver prices are in a consolidation phase, hovering near $90 per ounce, following a significant rally in 2025. Despite persistent supply shortages and robust industrial demand, a strengthening U.S. dollar and evolving macroeconomic conditions, especially within India, introduce short-term headwinds. Analysts offer divergent 2026 price forecasts, underscoring the commodity's complex outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:35:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14930fa7d0695d1ab6fe7_1772177906431.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyatt Targets 5X India Growth Amidst Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Hyatt-Targets-5X-India-Growth-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/69a147cffa7d0695d1ab6e91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Hyatt-Targets-5X-India-Growth-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/69a147cffa7d0695d1ab6e91</guid><description>Hyatt Hotels aims to quintuple its India presence within five years, operating 55 hotels currently and targeting over 275. This aggressive strategy leverages India's burgeoning travel market, projected to double by 2031, driven by population growth and rising consumer spending. However, Hyatt faces formidable competition from global giants like Marriott and IHG, alongside execution hurdles and capital demands. The company's stock has seen recent volatility, trading near its 52-week high but with a negative P/E ratio reflecting current losses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:29:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a147cffa7d0695d1ab6e90_1772177669562.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Astra Microwave gets nod to demerge Space, Geo businesses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astra-Microwave-gets-nod-to-demerge-Space-Geo-businesses/69a1476ffa7d0695d1ab6dc4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astra-Microwave-gets-nod-to-demerge-Space-Geo-businesses/69a1476ffa7d0695d1ab6dc4</guid><description>Astra Microwave Products Limited's Board of Directors has granted in-principle approval for demerging its Space, Meteorology, and Hydrology business undertakings into a separate entity. This strategic move aims to foster focused management, enhance operational efficiency, and tailor growth strategies for these specific sectors. The demerger is expected to unlock shareholder value, though final structure and terms are subject to further approvals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:27:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1476ffa7d0695d1ab6dc3_1772177365346.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Assures Summer Supply with 175.5 MT Coal Stock</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Assures-Summer-Supply-with-1755-MT-Coal-Stock/69a1465bfa7d0695d1ab6c11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Assures-Summer-Supply-with-1755-MT-Coal-Stock/69a1465bfa7d0695d1ab6c11</guid><description>Coal India Limited (CIL) has assured ample coal availability to meet projected summer demand, holding approximately 175.5 million tonnes (MTs) of accessible coal. This robust position, including 115 MTs of pithead coal, could significantly reduce India's reliance on imports, supporting domestic energy security throughout the peak demand season.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:23:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1465bfa7d0695d1ab6c10_1772177354506.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IOB Assigned BBB Global Rating; ₹4,000 Cr Capital Raise Planned for Public Float</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IOB-Assigned-BBB-Global-Rating-4000-Cr-Capital-Raise-Planned-for-Public-Float/69a1465bfa7d0695d1ab6bfa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IOB-Assigned-BBB-Global-Rating-4000-Cr-Capital-Raise-Planned-for-Public-Float/69a1465bfa7d0695d1ab6bfa</guid><description>S&amp;P Global Ratings has assigned Indian Overseas Bank (IOB) an initial long-term issuer credit rating of 'BBB' with a stable outlook, alongside a short-term rating of 'A-2'. This marks a significant assessment of IOB's creditworthiness by a major global agency. The bank plans to raise approximately ₹4,000 crore by the end of fiscal 2026, primarily to comply with SEBI's minimum public float requirement of 25%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:23:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1465bfa7d0695d1ab6bf9_1772177133384.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mastek Wins £49M UK Home Office Contract for Biometrics Systems</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mastek-Wins-49M-UK-Home-Office-Contract-for-Biometrics-Systems/69a1465afa7d0695d1ab6be4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mastek-Wins-49M-UK-Home-Office-Contract-for-Biometrics-Systems/69a1465afa7d0695d1ab6be4</guid><description>Mastek's UK subsidiary has secured a 5-year contract with the UK Home Office, valued at approximately £49 million. The deal covers engineering, integration, and product development for vital biometrics systems, including the National DNA Database, supporting services like Passports, Visas, and Justice. This win underscores Mastek's deep expertise in the UK public sector and its capabilities in critical government technology solutions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1465afa7d0695d1ab6be3_1772177148389.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Active Clothing Shareholders Approve ₹23 Cr Preferential Warrant Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Active-Clothing-Shareholders-Approve-23-Cr-Preferential-Warrant-Issue/69a14658fa7d0695d1ab6bce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Active-Clothing-Shareholders-Approve-23-Cr-Preferential-Warrant-Issue/69a14658fa7d0695d1ab6bce</guid><description>Active Clothing Co. Limited shareholders have given the green light to a preferential issue of convertible warrants, backing plans to raise ₹23 crore. The EGM on February 26, 2026, saw unanimous approval, signalling confidence in the company's strategy to fund growth initiatives and operational expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:23:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14658fa7d0695d1ab6bcd_1772177092355.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fusion Finance Hits Profitability, Reaffirms UP Focus with ₹1837 Cr Portfolio</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fusion-Finance-Hits-Profitability-Reaffirms-UP-Focus-with-1837-Cr-Portfolio/69a14402fa7d0695d1ab6a2e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fusion-Finance-Hits-Profitability-Reaffirms-UP-Focus-with-1837-Cr-Portfolio/69a14402fa7d0695d1ab6a2e</guid><description>Fusion Finance Limited has reaffirmed its strong strategic focus on Uttar Pradesh, reporting a net profit of ₹31.6 Crore in Q3 FY26. The company's portfolio in the state reached INR 1837 Crore, comprising ₹1543 Crore in microfinance and ₹294 Crore in MSME lending, serving over 5.6 lakh loan accounts in UP. This renewed focus leverages an extensive branch network and digital capabilities to deepen financial inclusion and support sustainable growth in the key northern state.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:13:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14402fa7d0695d1ab6a2d_1772176500220.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Retail, AI, IT Sectors Ignite Opportunities Amidst Valuation Puzzles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Retail-AI-IT-Sectors-Ignite-Opportunities-Amidst-Valuation-Puzzles/69a14321fa7d0695d1ab6894</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Retail-AI-IT-Sectors-Ignite-Opportunities-Amidst-Valuation-Puzzles/69a14321fa7d0695d1ab6894</guid><description>Siddhartha Khemka, Head of Research at Motilal Oswal Wealth Management, identifies robust investment avenues in India's value retail and AI-driven engineering sectors. While consumption recovery bolsters retailers like Vishal Mega Mart and V2 Retail, and data center demand propels MTAR Technologies, questions linger regarding their high valuations. The IT sector faces a dual challenge: AI-led disruption to legacy services, balanced by new opportunities for giants like Infosys and HCLTech.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:09:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14321fa7d0695d1ab6893_1772176738328.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MSCI Rejig Sparks Outflows, Stocks Dip Despite Inflow Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MSCI-Rejig-Sparks-Outflows-Stocks-Dip-Despite-Inflow-Hopes/69a14318fa7d0695d1ab687d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MSCI-Rejig-Sparks-Outflows-Stocks-Dip-Despite-Inflow-Hopes/69a14318fa7d0695d1ab687d</guid><description>MSCI's February 2026 index review will see a net outflow of approximately $260 million from Indian equities, effective February 27th. While Aditya Birla Capital and L&amp;T Finance are added, and AU Small Finance Bank's weight increases, IRCTC is excluded. Despite projected inflows for additions, all four affected stocks are trading down today, signaling investor caution amidst broader market pressures. India's overall weight in the MSCI Standard Index remains stable at 14.1%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:09:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14318fa7d0695d1ab687c_1772176299372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Investment Influx Amidst Global Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Investment-Influx-Amidst-Global-Caution/69a14316fa7d0695d1ab6866</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Investment-Influx-Amidst-Global-Caution/69a14316fa7d0695d1ab6866</guid><description>India's economic indicators suggest potential for increased foreign investment, buoyed by moderating Chinese momentum and lower oil prices. However, a significant catalyst is still required to attract substantial capital. Meanwhile, the artificial intelligence sector, despite robust growth projections, faces structural concerns and heightened market volatility, tempering expectations for universal gains in 2026. Geopolitical tensions are also injecting uncertainty into energy markets, influencing broader investor sentiment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:09:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14316fa7d0695d1ab6865_1772176306498.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>STT Hike Rattles Capital Stocks: F&amp;O Volume Outlook Dims</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/STT-Hike-Rattles-Capital-Stocks-FandO-Volume-Outlook-Dims/69a14248fa7d0695d1ab664d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/STT-Hike-Rattles-Capital-Stocks-FandO-Volume-Outlook-Dims/69a14248fa7d0695d1ab664d</guid><description>Capital market-linked stocks experienced a downturn Friday, with Angel One and BSE shares falling. The pressure stems from the recently increased Securities Transaction Tax (STT) and concerns voiced by NSE CEO Ashishkumar Chauhan regarding a potential decline in futures and options (F&amp;O) trading volumes. Chauhan also advocated for stricter eligibility criteria for derivatives trading, suggesting a regulatory move to curb speculation and potentially reshape revenue streams for exchanges and brokers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:05:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14248fa7d0695d1ab664c_1772176263847.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Trade Doctrine: Sovereignty, Supply Chains, and Digital Guardrails</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Doctrine-Sovereignty-Supply-Chains-and-Digital-Guardrails/69a14241fa7d0695d1ab6636</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Doctrine-Sovereignty-Supply-Chains-and-Digital-Guardrails/69a14241fa7d0695d1ab6636</guid><description>India is shifting its trade strategy from politically driven caution to economic logic, leveraging comparative advantage and calibrated openness. Recent FTAs and an interim India-US BTA signal a doctrine of market access for FDI and technology, positioning India as a reliable supply chain partner. The nation is prioritizing fundamental economic strengths over temporary tariff advantages, especially in light of global policy volatility. This includes strategic digital trade guardrails and robust protection for sensitive domestic sectors like agriculture and dairy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:05:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a14241fa7d0695d1ab6635_1772176137041.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Beyond AI: Geopolitics Fuels Value in Defense, Metals, Pharma</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Beyond-AI-Geopolitics-Fuels-Value-in-Defense-Metals-Pharma/69a1422bfa7d0695d1ab65fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Beyond-AI-Geopolitics-Fuels-Value-in-Defense-Metals-Pharma/69a1422bfa7d0695d1ab65fa</guid><description>Veteran investor Ramesh Damani argues that the market's intense focus on Artificial Intelligence is obscuring significant investment opportunities in traditional sectors like defense, metals, and pharmaceuticals. These sectors are poised for growth driven by a global push for localized manufacturing, resilient supply chains, and increased defense spending spurred by geopolitical realignments. Damani views this as a natural sectoral rotation, suggesting value lies in physical capabilities and domestic production rather than solely in digital innovation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:05:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1422bfa7d0695d1ab65f9_1772176216269.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>