<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:55:43 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Jefferies Unleashes FIRST 'Buy' Rating on Pine Labs! Target ₹300 – Massive Surge Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Jefferies-Unleashes-FIRST-Buy-Rating-on-Pine-Labs-Target-300-Massive-Surge-Ahead/694b63cbe10c98d0787a774e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Jefferies-Unleashes-FIRST-Buy-Rating-on-Pine-Labs-Target-300-Massive-Surge-Ahead/694b63cbe10c98d0787a774e</guid><description>Brokerage firm Jefferies has initiated coverage on Pine Labs shares with a 'buy' rating and a price target of ₹300, projecting a 28.5% upside. Jefferies highlights Pine Labs' leadership in digital payments, strong revenue growth potential (23% CAGR FY25-28), and expected margin expansion from 15% to 27% by FY28. The report notes current valuations are a discount to peers, suggesting potential for re-rating with consistent growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:44:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b63cbe10c98d0787a774d_1766548505533.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>8th Pay Commission Takes Shape: Millions of Govt Employees &amp; Pensioners Eye Salary, Pension Hikes Soon!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8th-Pay-Commission-Takes-Shape-Millions-of-Govt-Employees-and-Pensioners-Eye-Salary-Pension-Hikes-Soon/694b63ace10c98d0787a771e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8th-Pay-Commission-Takes-Shape-Millions-of-Govt-Employees-and-Pensioners-Eye-Salary-Pension-Hikes-Soon/694b63ace10c98d0787a771e</guid><description>The 8th Central Pay Commission has been officially constituted, set to revise pay and pensions for over 50 lakh central government employees and 69 lakh pensioners. Recommendations are expected within 18 months, with potential payouts effective January 1, 2026. The 'fitment factor' will guide salary increases, while Dearness Allowance (DA) will remain separate. Estimated fiscal implications are substantial, potentially exceeding ₹4 lakh crore.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:44:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b63ace10c98d0787a771d_1766548463792.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Creator Economy Explodes: ₹4,500 Crore Boom &amp; The Rise of Commerce Powerhouses in 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Creator-Economy-Explodes-4500-Crore-Boom-and-The-Rise-of-Commerce-Powerhouses-in-2026/694b627ee10c98d0787a75a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Creator-Economy-Explodes-4500-Crore-Boom-and-The-Rise-of-Commerce-Powerhouses-in-2026/694b627ee10c98d0787a75a5</guid><description>India's creator economy surged 25% to ₹4,500 crore in 2025, fueled by digital content and niche creators. By 2026, it's set for maturity, driven by deeper e-commerce integration, global format shows, AI adoption, and stronger legal protections like personality rights. Brands are increasingly relying on data-driven strategies and personalized community building, indicating a significant shift towards creator-driven commerce and strategic scaling.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Market Meltdown Alert: 75% Stocks Plummet as 2025 Woes Deepen! Are Your Investments Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Meltdown-Alert-75percent-Stocks-Plummet-as-2025-Woes-Deepen-Are-Your-Investments-Safe/694b6206e10c98d0787a751a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Meltdown-Alert-75percent-Stocks-Plummet-as-2025-Woes-Deepen-Are-Your-Investments-Safe/694b6206e10c98d0787a751a</guid><description>Indian stock market faces severe downturn in 2025, with 75% of actively traded shares (2,774 out of 3,677) falling into negative territory. This broad weakness, significantly worse than 2024's 33% decline, is driven by uncertainty over US tariff policies and geopolitical tensions. Mid-cap and small-cap stocks are particularly hard-hit, testing investor patience.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:35:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b6206e10c98d0787a7519_1766548214494.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Securities Initiates 'Buy' on Orkla India! ₹800 Target Sparks Investor Frenzy – Regional Brands &amp; Exports Set to Soar?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ICICI-Securities-Initiates-Buy-on-Orkla-India-800-Target-Sparks-Investor-Frenzy-Regional-Brands-and-Exports-Set-to-Soar/694b5d1be10c98d0787a6bf1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ICICI-Securities-Initiates-Buy-on-Orkla-India-800-Target-Sparks-Investor-Frenzy-Regional-Brands-and-Exports-Set-to-Soar/694b5d1be10c98d0787a6bf1</guid><description>ICICI Securities has launched coverage on Orkla India with a 'Buy' rating and a ₹800 target price. Analysts highlight the company's strong foothold in regional markets with brands like MTR and Eastern, its significant share in India's growing spices and convenience foods segments, and a robust export business. The brokerage anticipates steady growth driven by operational improvements, product innovation, and strategic acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:11:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b5d1be10c98d0787a6bf0_1766546790240.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nuvama Wealth, DCM Shriram &amp; 2 More: Stocks to Watch as Ex-Dates Trigger Major Corporate Actions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nuvama-Wealth-DCM-Shriram-and-2-More-Stocks-to-Watch-as-Ex-Dates-Trigger-Major-Corporate-Actions/694b5cc1e10c98d0787a6b3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nuvama-Wealth-DCM-Shriram-and-2-More-Stocks-to-Watch-as-Ex-Dates-Trigger-Major-Corporate-Actions/694b5cc1e10c98d0787a6b3b</guid><description>Four Indian companies, including Nuvama Wealth Management and DCM Shriram Industries, are in focus as they trade ex-date on December 26. This follows significant corporate actions: DCM Shriram Industries is demerging its chemical and rayon businesses; Nuvama Wealth Management is executing a 1:5 stock split; Hilton Metal Forging is undertaking a rights issue; and Ram Ratna Wires is issuing a 1:1 bonus share. Investors should note the market closure on December 25 for Christmas.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:11:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b5cc1e10c98d0787a6b3a_1766546704172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-NZ FTA: Kiwi, Meat, Wine Now Cheaper! Dairy Prices to Remain High.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-NZ-FTA-Kiwi-Meat-Wine-Now-Cheaper-Dairy-Prices-to-Remain-High/694b5c5ee10c98d0787a6ac8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-NZ-FTA-Kiwi-Meat-Wine-Now-Cheaper-Dairy-Prices-to-Remain-High/694b5c5ee10c98d0787a6ac8</guid><description>India and New Zealand have signed a Free Trade Agreement (FTA) set to reduce import duties on key New Zealand products including meat, seafood, fruits, honey, and wine, making them more affordable in India. However, dairy items like milk, cheese, and yogurt will continue to face tariffs. The agreement includes staggered duty reductions over several years and aims to boost bilateral trade, while India will facilitate geographical indications for its own products in New Zealand.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:10:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b5c5ee10c98d0787a6ac7_1766546695804.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nuvama's Bold Call: Knowledge Marine Stock Poised for 40% Surge - Is This the Next Big Maritime Play?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nuvamas-Bold-Call-Knowledge-Marine-Stock-Poised-for-40percent-Surge-Is-This-the-Next-Big-Maritime-Play/694b5bfce10c98d0787a6a1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nuvamas-Bold-Call-Knowledge-Marine-Stock-Poised-for-40percent-Surge-Is-This-the-Next-Big-Maritime-Play/694b5bfce10c98d0787a6a1a</guid><description>Brokerage firm Nuvama has initiated coverage on Knowledge Marine and Engineering Ltd., assigning a "buy" rating and a ₹2,500 price target. This suggests a potential 40% upside from current levels. Nuvama highlights India's maritime sector growth and Knowledge Marine's strong order book, diversified business, high EBITDA margins, and robust revenue growth projections (58% CAGR).</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:10:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b5bfce10c98d0787a6a19_1766547425071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Credit Card Growth Slows Sharply: What This Means for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Credit-Card-Growth-Slows-Sharply-What-This-Means-for-Your-Investments/694b5bb7e10c98d0787a69bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Credit-Card-Growth-Slows-Sharply-What-This-Means-for-Your-Investments/694b5bb7e10c98d0787a69bc</guid><description>A JM Financial report reveals India's consumption credit market is recovering, but credit card issuance has notably slowed down by 28% year-on-year in Q3 FY26 due to lenders' caution on unsecured loans. While personal loans and consumer durables are rebounding, this slowdown in credit cards signals a shift in lending strategies. Investors should watch how this impacts financial sector performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:09:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b5bb7e10c98d0787a69bb_1766547213006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Robin Raina REJECTS Eraaya Allegations: Legal War Over 50% Stake Rages On!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Robin-Raina-REJECTS-Eraaya-Allegations-Legal-War-Over-50percent-Stake-Rages-On/694b5ae2e10c98d0787a68e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Robin-Raina-REJECTS-Eraaya-Allegations-Legal-War-Over-50percent-Stake-Rages-On/694b5ae2e10c98d0787a68e5</guid><description>Former Ebix Chairman Robin Raina has denied claims by Eraaya Lifespaces Limited regarding ongoing legal disputes. Raina states Eraaya is misrepresenting a Supreme Court order from August 2024, which he says did not rule on the merits of his 50% shareholding claim. Multiple lawsuits filed by Raina against Eraaya and its promoter Vikas Garg, alleging fraud and other offenses, are active in India and the US.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:08:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b5ae2e10c98d0787a68e4_1766546344778.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MNC Employees Brace for Tax Trouble: Foreign ESOPs Trigger Income Tax Alerts!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/MNC-Employees-Brace-for-Tax-Trouble-Foreign-ESOPs-Trigger-Income-Tax-Alerts/694b5a80e10c98d0787a6816</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/MNC-Employees-Brace-for-Tax-Trouble-Foreign-ESOPs-Trigger-Income-Tax-Alerts/694b5a80e10c98d0787a6816</guid><description>Multinational company employees holding foreign Employee Stock Option Plans (ESOPs) or Restricted Stock Units (RSUs) are receiving income tax alerts. India's enhanced data-matching capabilities, fueled by global information sharing agreements like CRS and FATCA, are identifying discrepancies in reporting foreign assets and income. Employees must ensure correct disclosure in their Income Tax Returns (ITR), particularly in Schedule FA and Schedule CG, upon exercise of these options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:05:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b5a80e10c98d0787a6815_1766546597371.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Excluded from Key US-Led Chip Alliance: Global Tech Reality Check!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Excluded-from-Key-US-Led-Chip-Alliance-Global-Tech-Reality-Check/694b5ac1e10c98d0787a689e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Excluded-from-Key-US-Led-Chip-Alliance-Global-Tech-Reality-Check/694b5ac1e10c98d0787a689e</guid><description>India's ambition to lead in semiconductors faces a reality check after being excluded from Pax Silica, a US-led technology coalition. This group comprises nations controlling critical chip supply chain chokepoints, highlighting India's current perception as a technology consumer. The exclusion may lead to higher capital costs and restricted access to future technologies, impacting India's strategic position in the global industry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:05:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b5ac1e10c98d0787a689d_1766546197807.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Poised for Positive Start: FIIs Sell, Earnings Cheer, and Derivatives Signal Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Poised-for-Positive-Start-FIIs-Sell-Earnings-Cheer-and-Derivatives-Signal-Gains/694b5892e10c98d0787a6578</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Poised-for-Positive-Start-FIIs-Sell-Earnings-Cheer-and-Derivatives-Signal-Gains/694b5892e10c98d0787a6578</guid><description>Indian stock markets are expected to open with a positive bias, influenced by steady global cues and strong domestic fundamentals. Despite Foreign Portfolio Investors (FPIs) turning net sellers, market participants are watching closely. Motilal Oswal Financial Services reports an encouraging trend of earnings upgrades for India Inc, especially in mid-caps, signalling potential upside. Derivatives data also reflects a growing optimistic outlook, with improved Put-Call Ratio and easing volatility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:58:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b5892e10c98d0787a6577_1766545740001.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Secret to 2026 Wealth? These 3 Indian Value Stocks Could Skyrocket!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Secret-to-2026-Wealth-These-3-Indian-Value-Stocks-Could-Skyrocket/694b54a4e10c98d0787a6275</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Secret-to-2026-Wealth-These-3-Indian-Value-Stocks-Could-Skyrocket/694b54a4e10c98d0787a6275</guid><description>Discover the power of value investing for long-term wealth with three promising Indian stocks for your 2026 watchlist. Learn how to identify companies trading below their intrinsic value. The article highlights Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC), Power Finance Corporation (PFC), and Gujarat State Fertilisers and Chemicals (GSFC), explaining their current market pressures and potential upside based on fundamental strengths and future plans. These picks are based on metrics like low Price-to-Earnings and Price-to-Book ratios, along with dividend yields.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:39:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b54a4e10c98d0787a6274_1766544692596.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerage Buzz: Angel One Flags Welspun Corp for 29% Upside – Buy Signal Issued!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Brokerage-Buzz-Angel-One-Flags-Welspun-Corp-for-29percent-Upside-Buy-Signal-Issued/694b5402e10c98d0787a6187</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Brokerage-Buzz-Angel-One-Flags-Welspun-Corp-for-29percent-Upside-Buy-Signal-Issued/694b5402e10c98d0787a6187</guid><description>Brokerage firm Angel One has issued a 'Buy' rating for Welspun Corp, setting a target price of ₹1,050, indicating a potential 29% increase from its previous close. The upgrade is driven by Welspun Corp's leadership in large-diameter pipes, strong US operational visibility through FY28, diversification into ductile iron pipes and building materials, and the introduction of value-added products expected to boost margins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:35:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b5402e10c98d0787a6186_1766545265600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stocks to Watch: Adani Ports Seals Overseas Deal, Coal India Eyes Subsidiary Listings, &amp; More Big Moves!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stocks-to-Watch-Adani-Ports-Seals-Overseas-Deal-Coal-India-Eyes-Subsidiary-Listings-and-More-Big-Moves/694b5470e10c98d0787a6201</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stocks-to-Watch-Adani-Ports-Seals-Overseas-Deal-Coal-India-Eyes-Subsidiary-Listings-and-More-Big-Moves/694b5470e10c98d0787a6201</guid><description>Investors will track several key developments today. Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone is set to acquire Australia's Abbot Point Port. Coal India's board approved the potential listing of its subsidiaries, MCL and South Eastern Coalfields Limited. Other notable movements include Ajanta Pharma and Biocon's in-licensing agreement, Vikran Engineering securing a ₹2,035 crore solar project order, and GPT Infraprojects receiving a ₹199 crore railway contract. Global markets show mixed trends, with gold prices continuing their record rally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:35:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b5470e10c98d0787a6200_1766544568112.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Modi-Putin Summit: Optics Over Outcomes? India's Strategic Dilemma Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Modi-Putin-Summit-Optics-Over-Outcomes-Indias-Strategic-Dilemma-Revealed/694b52fce10c98d0787a602f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Modi-Putin-Summit-Optics-Over-Outcomes-Indias-Strategic-Dilemma-Revealed/694b52fce10c98d0787a602f</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi's recent summit with Russian President Vladimir Putin in Delhi yielded modest outcomes, including a revised trade target of $100 billion by 2030 and pledges for crude oil supplies. Analysts suggest the visit's primary success was for Moscow, signalling Russia is not a pariah in Asia. However, for India, the partnership faces significant constraints given its adversarial relationship with China, a struggling domestic economy, and increasing reliance on US-led technology and supply chains. The summit did little to address these core challenges, raising concerns about India's strategic direction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:34:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b52fce10c98d0787a602e_1766544910060.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LG India Stock Faces Major Downgrade: Investec Warns of Market Share Loss Amidst Fierce Competition!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Stock-Faces-Major-Downgrade-Investec-Warns-of-Market-Share-Loss-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/694b539ee10c98d0787a60b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Stock-Faces-Major-Downgrade-Investec-Warns-of-Market-Share-Loss-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/694b539ee10c98d0787a60b1</guid><description>Investec has initiated coverage on LG Electronics India with a 'reduce' rating and a price target of ₹1,536, a significant shift from its previous 'consensus buy' status. The brokerage warns of potential market share erosion and challenges in premium categories due to new market entrants, despite acknowledging the company's strong reach and manufacturing capabilities. The stock closed near this target price, reflecting investor concerns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:33:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b539ee10c98d0787a60b0_1766544365594.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LG India Stock Faces Major Downgrade: Investec Warns of Market Share Loss Amidst Fierce Competition!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Stock-Faces-Major-Downgrade-Investec-Warns-of-Market-Share-Loss-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/694b52ede10c98d0787a5fd8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Stock-Faces-Major-Downgrade-Investec-Warns-of-Market-Share-Loss-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/694b52ede10c98d0787a5fd8</guid><description>Investec has initiated coverage on LG Electronics India with a 'reduce' rating and a price target of ₹1,536, a significant shift from its previous 'consensus buy' status. The brokerage warns of potential market share erosion and challenges in premium categories due to new market entrants, despite acknowledging the company's strong reach and manufacturing capabilities. The stock closed near this target price, reflecting investor concerns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:33:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b52ede10c98d0787a5fd7_1766544180412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Monte Carlo Fashions Lands HUGE ₹147 Crore Solar Contracts: Is This Your Next Big Investment?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Monte-Carlo-Fashions-Lands-HUGE-147-Crore-Solar-Contracts-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Investment/694b51f5e10c98d0787a5f09</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Monte-Carlo-Fashions-Lands-HUGE-147-Crore-Solar-Contracts-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Investment/694b51f5e10c98d0787a5f09</guid><description>Monte Carlo Fashions is making headlines after securing multiple Letters of Award worth approximately ₹147 crore from Madhya Pradesh Urja Vikas Nigam Ltd. The contracts are for developing 35 MW (AC) of grid-connected solar PV power plants under the 'Surya Mitra Krishi Feeders Scheme - PM KUSUM-C'. These projects are slated for execution within 18 months and come with a significant 25-year operational period, promising long-term revenue. This news follows a period where the company's stock saw a 23% rise in the last six months.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:29:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b51f5e10c98d0787a5f08_1766544300758.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Consumer Sector Sees Record CEO Shake-up: Boards Demand Digital-First Leaders for Growth Amidst Fierce Competition!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Consumer-Sector-Sees-Record-CEO-Shake-up-Boards-Demand-Digital-First-Leaders-for-Growth-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/694b4fdce10c98d0787a409f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Consumer-Sector-Sees-Record-CEO-Shake-up-Boards-Demand-Digital-First-Leaders-for-Growth-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/694b4fdce10c98d0787a409f</guid><description>Indian consumer companies are experiencing a significant increase in CEO changes in 2025, driven by intense competition, slowing growth, and the rise of digital-first brands. Analysts note that boards are proactively seeking leaders with digital expertise and a focus on omni-channel growth to navigate the complex market landscape. Key firms like Hindustan Unilever, Britannia, and Reliance Retail are making strategic leadership shifts to adapt and accelerate their business strategies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:18:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b4fdce10c98d0787a409e_1766543395505.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump's Ultimatum: Cut Rates If Market Soars, Or Forget Fed Chair Job!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trumps-Ultimatum-Cut-Rates-If-Market-Soars-Or-Forget-Fed-Chair-Job/694b4fcce10c98d0787a4070</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trumps-Ultimatum-Cut-Rates-If-Market-Soars-Or-Forget-Fed-Chair-Job/694b4fcce10c98d0787a4070</guid><description>Donald Trump has publicly stated his expectation for the next Federal Reserve Chair to lower interest rates during periods of strong market performance. He warned potential nominees against disagreeing with his views, emphasizing his desire for rate cuts to boost the economy and prevent market downturns on positive economic news. Trump is finalizing his choice for the next Fed chair, indicating a desire for a leader aligned with his monetary policy preferences.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:14:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b4fcce10c98d0787a406f_1766543711238.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Platinum Shatters Records: Price Surges Past $2,300 Amidst Crippling Supply Shortages!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Platinum-Shatters-Records-Price-Surges-Past-2300-Amidst-Crippling-Supply-Shortages/694b4f09e10c98d0787a3f5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Platinum-Shatters-Records-Price-Surges-Past-2300-Amidst-Crippling-Supply-Shortages/694b4f09e10c98d0787a3f5f</guid><description>Platinum has reached an unprecedented all-time high, surpassing $2,300 per ounce. This surge is driven by severely restricted global supplies, historically high borrowing costs, and strategic metal positioning in US warehouses due to potential tariffs. Robust demand from China, coupled with supply disruptions in South Africa, is further fueling the rally, marking platinum's longest winning streak since 2017 and a significant annual gain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:13:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b4f09e10c98d0787a3f5e_1766543584250.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Rockets Past $4500! Global Surge Ignites Indian Markets - What Investors NEED to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Gold-Rockets-Past-4500-Global-Surge-Ignites-Indian-Markets-What-Investors-NEED-to-Know/694b492ee10c98d0787a3af8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Gold-Rockets-Past-4500-Global-Surge-Ignites-Indian-Markets-What-Investors-NEED-to-Know/694b492ee10c98d0787a3af8</guid><description>Indian markets are poised for a positive opening on December 24, influenced by strong global cues. The US economy showed its fastest growth in two years, pushing US stocks to record highs. Gold prices surged past $4,500 per ounce due to safe-haven demand and anticipated rate cuts. While the previous day saw a mixed close for Indian indices, robust domestic institutional investor buying countered foreign institutional investor selling, providing support for today's trade.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:47:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b492ee10c98d0787a3af7_1766541729564.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Smashes $4,500 Barrier! Asian Markets Surge on US Growth Boom; India Bolsters Rupee</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Smashes-4500-Barrier-Asian-Markets-Surge-on-US-Growth-Boom-India-Bolsters-Rupee/694b487ce10c98d0787a3a3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Smashes-4500-Barrier-Asian-Markets-Surge-on-US-Growth-Boom-India-Bolsters-Rupee/694b487ce10c98d0787a3a3a</guid><description>Asian stocks climbed to a four-day high, mirroring Wall Street's record gains, as US economic growth hit a two-year peak of 4.3%. Gold prices soared past $4,500 per ounce, with silver and copper also reaching all-time highs amid geopolitical tensions. India's central bank announced measures to boost banking liquidity and support the weakening rupee.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:47:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b487ce10c98d0787a3a39_1766541901912.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Trade War BACKFIRES! US &amp; China Learn Hard Lesson As India Charts New Course</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Trade-War-BACKFIRES-US-and-China-Learn-Hard-Lesson-As-India-Charts-New-Course/694b47d1e10c98d0787a3964</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Trade-War-BACKFIRES-US-and-China-Learn-Hard-Lesson-As-India-Charts-New-Course/694b47d1e10c98d0787a3964</guid><description>Export curbs by the US and China aimed at strategic leverage have backfired. Instead of slowing rivals, these policies accelerated their self-reliance efforts while hurting domestic exporters. India is taking note, implementing schemes to build domestic capacity for critical minerals and magnets to reduce vulnerability and enhance its role in global supply chains.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:46:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b47d1e10c98d0787a3963_1766541422468.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>This Kotak bet delivered 18x return in 11 years—and it's still compounding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/This-Kotak-bet-delivered-18x-return-in-11-yearsand-its-still-compounding/694b4679e10c98d0787a3869</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/This-Kotak-bet-delivered-18x-return-in-11-yearsand-its-still-compounding/694b4679e10c98d0787a3869</guid><description /><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:39:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b4679e10c98d0787a3868_1766540992848.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US H-1B Visa Shift: Indian IT Stocks Brace for Major Impact as New Rules Favor High-Skilled Workers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-H-1B-Visa-Shift-Indian-IT-Stocks-Brace-for-Major-Impact-as-New-Rules-Favor-High-Skilled-Workers/694b4171e10c98d0787a35a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-H-1B-Visa-Shift-Indian-IT-Stocks-Brace-for-Major-Impact-as-New-Rules-Favor-High-Skilled-Workers/694b4171e10c98d0787a35a2</guid><description>The U.S. Department of Homeland Security is changing the H-1B visa selection process, moving from a random lottery to a weighted system prioritizing higher-skilled and higher-paid workers. This new approach, effective February 27, 2026, aims to protect American jobs. Major Indian IT companies like Infosys, TCS, Wipro, and Tech Mahindra are expected to be significantly impacted, as the shift could affect talent acquisition and operational costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:18:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b4171e10c98d0787a35a1_1766540228602.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Chip Boom: 3 'Hidden Gems' Quietly Powering ₹10 Lakh Crore Semiconductor Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Chip-Boom-3-Hidden-Gems-Quietly-Powering-10-Lakh-Crore-Semiconductor-Surge/694b3f91e10c98d0787a3428</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Chip-Boom-3-Hidden-Gems-Quietly-Powering-10-Lakh-Crore-Semiconductor-Surge/694b3f91e10c98d0787a3428</guid><description>India's semiconductor market is projected to hit $100-110 billion by 2030. Beyond large fabs, crucial growth lies in the supply chain for essential chemicals and gases. Three Indian companies, Acutaas Chemicals, Archean Chemicals Industries, and Stallion India, are emerging as key players by developing and supplying these critical inputs, positioning themselves to benefit from the global diversification away from China and India's own manufacturing push.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:09:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3f91e10c98d0787a3427_1766539504217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Forget SBI! This Unsung PSU Bank is Your 2026 Value Goldmine - 3 Reasons Why!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Forget-SBI-This-Unsung-PSU-Bank-is-Your-2026-Value-Goldmine-3-Reasons-Why/694b4021e10c98d0787a34aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Forget-SBI-This-Unsung-PSU-Bank-is-Your-2026-Value-Goldmine-3-Reasons-Why/694b4021e10c98d0787a34aa</guid><description>Central Bank of India, often overlooked, is emerging as a compelling value investment for 2026. Trading at a significantly lower valuation (0.9x book value) compared to State Bank of India (1.7x book value), it has demonstrated robust operational improvements. The bank reported strong Q2FY26 results, including 17.7% loan growth and a 32.9% rise in net profit, coupled with falling non-performing assets. With a positive growth outlook and potential for valuation re-rating, it's attracting attention from savvy investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:09:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b4021e10c98d0787a34a9_1766539369686.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economic Surge: RBI Deputy Governor Predicts Stronger Growth Driven by Reforms!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Surge-RBI-Deputy-Governor-Predicts-Stronger-Growth-Driven-by-Reforms/694b3d52e10c98d0787a32a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Surge-RBI-Deputy-Governor-Predicts-Stronger-Growth-Driven-by-Reforms/694b3d52e10c98d0787a32a8</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India Deputy Governor Poonam Gupta is optimistic about India's economic future, citing rapid reforms that are expected to fuel stronger growth, potentially reaching 7-7.5% annually with limited downside. She also noted benign inflation trends, forecasting it to remain low and stable. Gupta expressed confidence in the rupee's resilience and the economy's ability to withstand global uncertainties, emphasizing the positive impact of Free Trade Agreements (FTAs).</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:02:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3d52e10c98d0787a32a7_1766538649364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dalal Street Buzz: Nifty Bulls Eyeing Santa Rally as Christmas Nears! 🎅🎁</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dalal-Street-Buzz-Nifty-Bulls-Eyeing-Santa-Rally-as-Christmas-Nears/694b3b61e10c98d0787a31be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dalal-Street-Buzz-Nifty-Bulls-Eyeing-Santa-Rally-as-Christmas-Nears/694b3b61e10c98d0787a31be</guid><description>Indian stock markets, including the Sensex and Nifty, are showing signs of anticipation for a 'Santa rally' as the Christmas holiday approaches. Investors are looking for a year-end boost on Dalal Street, seeking positive momentum before the festive season concludes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:52:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3b61e10c98d0787a31bd_1766539266706.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Flat: Analyst Raja Venkatraman Reveals 3 Must-Buy Stocks for Big Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Flat-Analyst-Raja-Venkatraman-Reveals-3-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-Big-Gains/694b3af8e10c98d0787a3143</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Flat-Analyst-Raja-Venkatraman-Reveals-3-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-Big-Gains/694b3af8e10c98d0787a3143</guid><description>Indian stock markets, Sensex and Nifty 50, closed nearly flat on December 23rd due to profit booking, while mid and small-cap stocks saw modest gains. Amidst mixed global cues, analyst Raja Venkatraman of NeoTrader recommended three stocks for potential upside: Ashok Leyland, HDFC AMC, and Dalmia Bharat, detailing buy levels, stop losses, and target prices based on technical analysis.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:46:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3af8e10c98d0787a3142_1766538044926.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Flat, But 2 Stocks Could Soar: MarketSmith India's Bold Buy Picks Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Market-Flat-But-2-Stocks-Could-Soar-MarketSmith-Indias-Bold-Buy-Picks-Revealed/694b3a65e10c98d0787a3064</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Market-Flat-But-2-Stocks-Could-Soar-MarketSmith-Indias-Bold-Buy-Picks-Revealed/694b3a65e10c98d0787a3064</guid><description>Indian stock markets closed flat on Tuesday with the Sensex and Nifty 50 showing minimal changes, despite modest gains in mid and small-cap segments. MarketSmith India has issued buy recommendations for Bajaj Auto Ltd and S.J.S. Enterprises Ltd, citing strong fundamentals, brand leadership, and growth potential. The advisory service also provided specific target prices and risk factors for both stocks, alongside a technical analysis of the broader market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:46:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3a65e10c98d0787a3063_1766537976006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Post Postmen to Sell Mutual Funds: Can Their Trust Overcome Market Risks?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/India-Post-Postmen-to-Sell-Mutual-Funds-Can-Their-Trust-Overcome-Market-Risks/694b3a2ce10c98d0787a302a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/India-Post-Postmen-to-Sell-Mutual-Funds-Can-Their-Trust-Overcome-Market-Risks/694b3a2ce10c98d0787a302a</guid><description>The Association of Mutual Funds in India (Amfi) plans to train one lakh postmen to sell mutual funds, leveraging India Post's vast network of 1.6 lakh branches. However, experts express skepticism due to challenges in training for complex products, potential mis-selling risks, and the need for robust digital KYC. The initiative is starting with simpler funds in a pilot phase.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:46:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3a2ce10c98d0787a3029_1766538548576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rare Earth Powerhouse: Attero Plans Massive ₹2,000 Crore Expansion to Secure Critical Minerals!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rare-Earth-Powerhouse-Attero-Plans-Massive-2000-Crore-Expansion-to-Secure-Critical-Minerals/694b397be10c98d0787a2f3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rare-Earth-Powerhouse-Attero-Plans-Massive-2000-Crore-Expansion-to-Secure-Critical-Minerals/694b397be10c98d0787a2f3a</guid><description>E-waste recycler Attero plans a significant ₹2,000 crore expansion over three years to boost battery recycling and critical minerals refining capacity. The move aims to enhance India's self-reliance in rare earths and support government missions, with the company also eyeing a public listing in two to three years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:46:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b397be10c98d0787a2f39_1766538418811.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto's Bold KTM Rescue Plan: Can It Save the Premium Bike Giant Amidst Domestic Woes?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Autos-Bold-KTM-Rescue-Plan-Can-It-Save-the-Premium-Bike-Giant-Amidst-Domestic-Woes/694b397be10c98d0787a2f65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Autos-Bold-KTM-Rescue-Plan-Can-It-Save-the-Premium-Bike-Giant-Amidst-Domestic-Woes/694b397be10c98d0787a2f65</guid><description>Bajaj Auto is launching a comprehensive revival plan for its major acquisition, KTM, which is undergoing judicial restructuring. The strategy includes discontinuing smaller brands, optimizing operations, and leveraging supply chain synergies to boost profitability. This comes as Bajaj Auto faces declining domestic market share, making KTM's turnaround crucial for its premium offerings and overall financial health. Efforts will ramp up in early 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:46:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b397be10c98d0787a2f64_1766537665830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Skyrockets Past Apple's Value: Is This The Ultimate Safe Haven?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-Past-Apples-Value-Is-This-The-Ultimate-Safe-Haven/694b353ce10c98d0787a2d62</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-Past-Apples-Value-Is-This-The-Ultimate-Safe-Haven/694b353ce10c98d0787a2d62</guid><description>Silver prices have surged dramatically, pushing its market capitalization to $4.04 trillion, now exceeding tech giant Apple Inc.'s $4.02 trillion. This unprecedented rally makes silver the third most valuable asset globally, trailing only gold and Nvidia, signaling a significant shift in investor preferences towards precious metals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:25:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b353ce10c98d0787a2d61_1766536861794.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coca-Cola India's Big Shake-Up: Hundreds of Jobs Cut as Bottler Targets Profit Boost!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Coca-Cola-Indias-Big-Shake-Up-Hundreds-of-Jobs-Cut-as-Bottler-Targets-Profit-Boost/694b3317e10c98d0787a2c6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Coca-Cola-Indias-Big-Shake-Up-Hundreds-of-Jobs-Cut-as-Bottler-Targets-Profit-Boost/694b3317e10c98d0787a2c6e</guid><description>Hindustan Coca-Cola Beverages (HCCB), Coca-Cola's bottling arm in India, is laying off approximately 300 employees across various functions like sales, supply chain, and plant operations. This move, affecting about 4-6% of its 5,000-strong workforce, aims to enhance profitability and streamline operations under its new CEO, Hemant Rupani. The company reported a significant 73% drop in net profit for FY25 to ₹756.64 crore and a 9% decline in revenue, partly due to selling bottling operations and muted demand.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:17:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3317e10c98d0787a2c6d_1766536174973.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>