<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:20:08 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Pharma Exports Surge 9.4%, Trade Deals Boost Global Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Exports-Surge-94percent-Trade-Deals-Boost-Global-Ambitions/6999c73f730b6847a5178108</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Exports-Surge-94percent-Trade-Deals-Boost-Global-Ambitions/6999c73f730b6847a5178108</guid><description>India's pharmaceutical exports reached $30.47 billion in fiscal year 2024-25, a 9.4% increase, reinforcing its position as a global generic leader. While the US and Europe remain dominant markets, new trade agreements with the EU and US are poised to improve market access and price competitiveness. The sector, valued at approximately $60 billion, is targeting double-digit export growth by 2026-27, supported by government initiatives and strategic investments in high-value segments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:54:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999c73f730b6847a5178107_1771685795110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SER Industries EGM Greenlights Name Change, Acquisitions &amp; Borrowing Powers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/SER-Industries-EGM-Greenlights-Name-Change-Acquisitions-and-Borrowing-Powers/6999c56b730b6847a5178058</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/SER-Industries-EGM-Greenlights-Name-Change-Acquisitions-and-Borrowing-Powers/6999c56b730b6847a5178058</guid><description>SER Industries Limited's Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) on February 20, 2026, concluded with shareholders unanimously approving all 13 resolutions. This includes a name change to 'Desi Farms India Limited', enhanced borrowing powers, and crucial approvals for preferential share and debenture issuances. These measures facilitate the company's strategic pivot into the food and dairy sector through the acquisition of SNA Milk and Milk Products Ltd. and DFSU Farmer Connect Private Ltd., signaling a major corporate restructuring.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:47:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999c56b730b6847a5178057_1771685372435.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Taylormade Renewables Board to Consider Fundraising on Feb 24</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Taylormade-Renewables-Board-to-Consider-Fundraising-on-Feb-24/6999c400730b6847a5177f9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Taylormade-Renewables-Board-to-Consider-Fundraising-on-Feb-24/6999c400730b6847a5177f9e</guid><description>Taylormade Renewables has scheduled a board meeting for February 24, 2026, to evaluate a proposal for raising funds. The company may opt for equity shares, debt securities, or other instruments, subject to necessary regulatory and shareholder approvals. This comes amid recent financial headwinds and a shift towards a recurring revenue model.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:41:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6999c400730b6847a5177f9d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Equities poised to reclaim leadership over precious metals in 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Equities-poised-to-reclaim-leadership-over-precious-metals-in-2026/6999bfd7730b6847a5177e20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Equities-poised-to-reclaim-leadership-over-precious-metals-in-2026/6999bfd7730b6847a5177e20</guid><description>Following a year where gold and silver significantly outpaced Indian equities, analysts predict a reversal in 2026. Precious metals benefited from geopolitical uncertainty and central bank buying, but Indian equity valuations are now presenting a more compelling case for growth. While gold and silver will remain important portfolio hedges, equities are expected to drive long-term wealth creation. Diversification and disciplined rebalancing are key.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:23:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6999bfd7730b6847a5177e1f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prestige Group Signs ₹115 Cr Deal for Bellandur Metro Station Co-Branding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Prestige-Group-Signs-115-Cr-Deal-for-Bellandur-Metro-Station-Co-Branding/6999b9b1730b6847a5177c38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Prestige-Group-Signs-115-Cr-Deal-for-Bellandur-Metro-Station-Co-Branding/6999b9b1730b6847a5177c38</guid><description>Prestige Group has entered a significant public-private partnership with BMRCL to adopt and co-brand the Bellandur Metro Station in Bengaluru for ₹115 crore. The 30-year agreement grants exclusive naming rights, commercial, and advertising entitlements, aiming to enhance brand visibility and integrate with urban transport infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:57:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b9b1730b6847a5177c37_1771682361957.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's CAG to Convene Power Sector Audit Conference</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-CAG-to-Convene-Power-Sector-Audit-Conference/6999b760730b6847a5177b2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-CAG-to-Convene-Power-Sector-Audit-Conference/6999b760730b6847a5177b2a</guid><description>India's Comptroller and Auditor General (CAG) is convening a national conference on February 23 to address evolving trends in the nation's power sector. The event will gather central and state government officials, alongside public sector power companies, to discuss emerging challenges and guide future audit strategies for generation, transmission, and distribution. Key areas for deliberation include digitalization, renewable energy integration, and the financial health of distribution companies (DISCOMs).</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:47:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b760730b6847a5177b29_1771681751751.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Life Board to Decide Interim Dividend Feb 25; Record Date March 6</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/SBI-Life-Board-to-Decide-Interim-Dividend-Feb-25-Record-Date-March-6/6999b675730b6847a5177a82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/SBI-Life-Board-to-Decide-Interim-Dividend-Feb-25-Record-Date-March-6/6999b675730b6847a5177a82</guid><description>SBI Life Insurance's Board of Directors will convene on February 25, 2026, to consider declaring an interim dividend for the Financial Year 2025-26. The record date for determining dividend eligibility is set for March 06, 2026. The company also tightened its insider trading window for designated persons from February 21 to February 27, 2026.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:43:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b675730b6847a5177a81_1771681531692.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Growth Pivot: Opportunity hinges on execution amid structural gaps</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Pivot-Opportunity-hinges-on-execution-amid-structural-gaps/6999b490730b6847a51779bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Pivot-Opportunity-hinges-on-execution-amid-structural-gaps/6999b490730b6847a51779bc</guid><description>India is positioned for economic growth, leveraging a demographic dividend until approximately 2047. However, realizing this potential requires focused investment in human capital, advanced manufacturing, and bridging deep-rooted regional economic disparities. The nation targets substantial foreign direct investment, even as global trends favor developed economies, and faces the dual challenge of attracting AI-driven innovation while potentially disrupting its established IT services sector. Success hinges on effective state-level execution and skilled workforce development.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:35:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b490730b6847a51779bb_1771681074485.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fusion Finance Promoters Seek Reclassification to Public Shareholder Status</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fusion-Finance-Promoters-Seek-Reclassification-to-Public-Shareholder-Status/6999b2a8730b6847a51778e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fusion-Finance-Promoters-Seek-Reclassification-to-Public-Shareholder-Status/6999b2a8730b6847a51778e6</guid><description>Fusion Finance Limited is processing requests from key shareholders, including Devesh Sachdev and Mini Sachdev, to reclassify their shares from 'Promoter/Promoter Group' to 'Public' shareholder category. This move involves 45,34,863 shares and requires approvals from the company's Board, shareholders, and stock exchanges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:27:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b2a8730b6847a51778e5_1771680538953.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE goes nanosecond: Speed race intensifies globally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-goes-nanosecond-Speed-race-intensifies-globally/6999b17f730b6847a51777fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-goes-nanosecond-Speed-race-intensifies-globally/6999b17f730b6847a51777fa</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange of India is set to achieve nanosecond trading response times for equities and derivatives by April 2026, a move that propels it to the forefront of global market speed. This upgrade significantly boosts order handling capacity and expands co-location infrastructure, aiming to accommodate escalating high-frequency trading volumes. However, the pursuit of extreme speed intensifies the competitive race among exchanges and amplifies concerns regarding market volatility and systemic risks, particularly for retail investors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:22:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b17f730b6847a51777f9_1771680277261.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Life Board to Consider Interim Dividend for FY26 on Feb 25</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/SBI-Life-Board-to-Consider-Interim-Dividend-for-FY26-on-Feb-25/6999b147730b6847a5177786</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/SBI-Life-Board-to-Consider-Interim-Dividend-for-FY26-on-Feb-25/6999b147730b6847a5177786</guid><description>SBI Life Insurance's Board of Directors will convene on February 25, 2026, to deliberate on declaring an interim dividend for the Financial Year 2025-26. The company has also set March 06, 2026, as the record date for this potential payout. This announcement signals a potential return of capital to shareholders, contingent on the board's approval.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:21:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b147730b6847a5177785_1771680223496.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Peptris Lands $7.7M Series A for AI Drug Discovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Peptris-Lands-77M-Series-A-for-AI-Drug-Discovery/6999b105730b6847a5177752</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Peptris-Lands-77M-Series-A-for-AI-Drug-Discovery/6999b105730b6847a5177752</guid><description>Bengaluru-based Peptris has closed a Rs 70 crore ($7.7 million) Series A funding round, co-led by IAN Alpha Fund and Speciale Invest. The capital will accelerate its AI-powered drug discovery programs towards clinical readiness. Peptris targets critical bottlenecks in the early stages of drug development, aiming to reduce failure rates and costs. This funding aligns with a significant global surge in AI adoption within the pharmaceutical R&amp;D sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:20:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b105730b6847a5177751_1771680131950.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Raymond Realty Shareholders Greenlight ESOP 2025 with Overwhelming 99.71% Approval</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Raymond-Realty-Shareholders-Greenlight-ESOP-2025-with-Overwhelming-9971percent-Approval/6999ad45730b6847a5177618</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Raymond-Realty-Shareholders-Greenlight-ESOP-2025-with-Overwhelming-9971percent-Approval/6999ad45730b6847a5177618</guid><description>Raymond Realty Limited shareholders have overwhelmingly approved the 'Raymond Realty Employees Stock Option Plan 2025' and related resolutions via postal ballot, with the primary ESOP approval receiving 99.71% in favour. This move facilitates employee incentives and aligns with the company's strategy as it prepares for an independent listing, reinforcing its commitment to retaining talent.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:04:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999ad45730b6847a5177617_1771679198572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Foxconn-HCL Chip Fab: India's Hardware Ambition Ignites</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Foxconn-HCL-Chip-Fab-Indias-Hardware-Ambition-Ignites/6999aab6730b6847a517748e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Foxconn-HCL-Chip-Fab-Indias-Hardware-Ambition-Ignites/6999aab6730b6847a517748e</guid><description>In Jewar, Uttar Pradesh, Foxconn and HCL Technologies have initiated a joint venture semiconductor manufacturing plant. This project, blessed by Prime Minister Narendra Modi, signifies India's accelerated push into sophisticated hardware production, aiming to bolster 'Make in India' and national self-reliance amidst evolving global supply chains. The venture underscores a strategic pivot, leveraging India's strengths in software and design to conquer complex chip fabrication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:53:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999aab6730b6847a517748d_1771678547828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bizotic Commercial Approves ₹364 Cr Promoter Warrant Allotment; Upfront ₹91 Cr Received</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Bizotic-Commercial-Approves-364-Cr-Promoter-Warrant-Allotment-Upfront-91-Cr-Received/6999aaaf730b6847a5177477</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Bizotic-Commercial-Approves-364-Cr-Promoter-Warrant-Allotment-Upfront-91-Cr-Received/6999aaaf730b6847a5177477</guid><description>Bizotic Commercial Limited's board approved a preferential allotment of 12.58 lakh convertible warrants to promoters, potentially raising ₹364.82 crore. The company has received an upfront payment of ₹91.21 crore. This move signals future capital infusion, though it comes with compliance requirements and a risk of dilution for existing shareholders if warrants are exercised.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:53:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999aaaf730b6847a5177476_1771678504000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mawana Sugars Shareholders Greenlight Mawana Foods Amalgamation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Mawana-Sugars-Shareholders-Greenlight-Mawana-Foods-Amalgamation/6999a7a4730b6847a517730d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Mawana-Sugars-Shareholders-Greenlight-Mawana-Foods-Amalgamation/6999a7a4730b6847a517730d</guid><description>Mawana Sugars Limited shareholders have overwhelmingly approved a scheme of amalgamation to merge Mawana Foods Private Limited into the company. The resolution passed with over 99.99% in favour, signalling strong support for the consolidation. The move now awaits final approval from the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT).</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:40:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a7a4730b6847a517730c_1771677722941.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cipla Faces USFDA OAI at Supplier; Lanreotide Injection Supply Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cipla-Faces-USFDA-OAI-at-Supplier-Lanreotide-Injection-Supply-Risk/6999a49e730b6847a517713e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cipla-Faces-USFDA-OAI-at-Supplier-Lanreotide-Injection-Supply-Risk/6999a49e730b6847a517713e</guid><description>Cipla announced a USFDA inspection at its key supplier Pharmathen International S.A.'s facility in Greece resulted in an 'Official Action Indicated' (OAI) classification. This finding suggests significant regulatory violations, potentially disrupting the supply chain for Lanreotide Injection, a critical product for Cipla USA Inc. The company is awaiting Pharmathen's corrective actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:27:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a49e730b6847a517713d_1771676973131.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rudra Ecovation Shareholders Meet on Shiva Texfabs Amalgamation Scheme</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rudra-Ecovation-Shareholders-Meet-on-Shiva-Texfabs-Amalgamation-Scheme/6999a497730b6847a5177128</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rudra-Ecovation-Shareholders-Meet-on-Shiva-Texfabs-Amalgamation-Scheme/6999a497730b6847a5177128</guid><description>Rudra Ecovation Limited shareholders met virtually on February 21, 2026, to vote on its amalgamation with Shiva Texfabs Limited. The scheme, approved by boards and progressing through regulatory steps including NCLT orders, aims to leverage synergies and strengthen market position in sustainable textiles. E-voting results are awaited, marking a crucial step before final approvals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:27:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a497730b6847a5177127_1771676937551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE IPO Legal Roadblock Cleared, Substantive Claims Unresolved</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NSE-IPO-Legal-Roadblock-Cleared-Substantive-Claims-Unresolved/6999a464730b6847a51770e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NSE-IPO-Legal-Roadblock-Cleared-Substantive-Claims-Unresolved/6999a464730b6847a51770e7</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange's (NSE) long-awaited initial public offering (IPO) has overcome a significant legal hurdle as the Delhi High Court dismissed a petition challenging the Securities and Exchange Board of India's (SEBI) no-objection certificate (NOC). The court's decision, however, was based on territorial jurisdiction rather than the merits of the petitioner's serious allegations concerning corporate action adjustments and potential financial improprieties. This procedural victory clears the path for an Offer for Sale (OFS), but the unaddressed claims introduce a lingering risk profile.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:26:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a464730b6847a51770e6_1771676895106.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exhicon subsidiary UHPL secures DGCA AOP for helicopter operations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Exhicon-subsidiary-UHPL-secures-DGCA-AOP-for-helicopter-operations/6999a420730b6847a517705e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Exhicon-subsidiary-UHPL-secures-DGCA-AOP-for-helicopter-operations/6999a420730b6847a517705e</guid><description>Exhicon Events Media Solutions is expanding into active helicopter flying operations via its subsidiary, United Helicharters Private Limited (UHPL). UHPL has received an Air Operator Permit (AOP) from the DGCA, valid for five years, marking a strategic pivot from aviation support to commercial charter services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:25:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a420730b6847a517705d_1771676858836.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chrome Silicon Q3 Loss Widens as Operations Remain Suspended, Audit Flags Mount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Chrome-Silicon-Q3-Loss-Widens-as-Operations-Remain-Suspended-Audit-Flags-Mount/6999a420730b6847a5177048</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Chrome-Silicon-Q3-Loss-Widens-as-Operations-Remain-Suspended-Audit-Flags-Mount/6999a420730b6847a5177048</guid><description>Chrome Silicon Limited reported a net loss of ₹2.13 crore for the quarter ending December 31, 2025, on a total income of ₹5.34 crore. Total income plummeted 77.32% year-on-year. Crucially, manufacturing operations have been suspended since May 2025 due to market volatility. The company's auditors have raised significant qualifications regarding the accuracy of financial statements, including unverified inventories and assets, unconfirmed liabilities, and uncertain loan recoverability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:25:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a420730b6847a5177047_1771676826623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pharma: Td Vaccine Launch Signals Sector Maturation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Td-Vaccine-Launch-Signals-Sector-Maturation/6999a3aa730b6847a5176f9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Td-Vaccine-Launch-Signals-Sector-Maturation/6999a3aa730b6847a5176f9b</guid><description>Union Health Minister J.P. Nadda launched India's indigenously manufactured Tetanus and adult Diphtheria (Td) vaccine, a significant step for national health security and the 'Atmanirbhar Bharat' vision. The Central Research Institute will supply 55 lakh doses to the Universal Immunization Programme by April 2026, bolstering domestic production capabilities. This event aligns with robust growth projections for India's pharmaceutical sector, driven by strong domestic demand and government incentives, reinforcing its global "pharmacy of the world" status, though challenges in scaling and market competition persist for the broader industry.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a3aa730b6847a5176f9a_1771676717908.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-France Strategic Partnership Deepens: Defense, Tech Deals Signal New Era</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-France-Strategic-Partnership-Deepens-Defense-Tech-Deals-Signal-New-Era/6999a1c5730b6847a5176e53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-France-Strategic-Partnership-Deepens-Defense-Tech-Deals-Signal-New-Era/6999a1c5730b6847a5176e53</guid><description>The India-France relationship has been elevated to a "Special Global Strategic Partnership," marked by significant defense agreements, including a substantial Rafale jet contract and helicopter production, alongside increased cooperation in critical minerals, AI, and innovation. This strategic deepening aims to bolster industrial self-reliance, enhance regional security in the Indo-Pacific, and navigate a complex global order, reflecting a long-term co-development vision.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:15:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a1c5730b6847a5176e52_1771676273656.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Ruling Sparks Volatility; India Rallies AI &amp; Defence Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Ruling-Sparks-Volatility-India-Rallies-AI-and-Defence-Investments/6999a159730b6847a5176df4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Ruling-Sparks-Volatility-India-Rallies-AI-and-Defence-Investments/6999a159730b6847a5176df4</guid><description>Indian equity markets experienced their sharpest decline since Budget Day on February 19, 2026, with the Nifty 50 falling 1.6% and the Sensex dropping 1.5%. This came after a US Supreme Court ruling struck down President Trump's tariffs, though he quickly announced new ones. Simultaneously, India hosted its AI Impact Summit, securing over $360 billion in investment commitments, and advanced talks on the Rafale jet deal, signaling robust domestic growth potential amidst global trade uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:13:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a159730b6847a5176df3_1771676122265.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rishab Special Yarns to become IMPERA WORLDWIDE; approves Rights Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rishab-Special-Yarns-to-become-IMPERA-WORLDWIDE-approves-Rights-Issue/69999fea730b6847a5176d40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rishab-Special-Yarns-to-become-IMPERA-WORLDWIDE-approves-Rights-Issue/69999fea730b6847a5176d40</guid><description>Rishab Special Yarns Limited has announced a significant board resolution to change its name to IMPERA WORLDWIDE LIMITED, subject to shareholder approval. The company also greenlit an increase in its authorised share capital and a proposal for a Rights Issue to raise funds. The board appointed SHRAVAN A. GUPTA &amp; ASSOCIATES as scrutinizer for the upcoming postal ballot process.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:07:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69999fea730b6847a5176d3f_1771675731949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Manufacturing Ambition Meets US Tariff Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Manufacturing-Ambition-Meets-US-Tariff-Volatility/69999e0a730b6847a5176c1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Manufacturing-Ambition-Meets-US-Tariff-Volatility/69999e0a730b6847a5176c1c</guid><description>Despite ongoing volatility from US trade tariff announcements, India's manufacturing sector is poised for significant expansion, driven by government initiatives and a strategic focus on domestic production and global supply chain diversification. Companies like Kirloskar Brothers demonstrate resilience against prior tariff pressures, while financial entities like JM Financial navigate market flux. Current valuations and mixed analyst sentiment for key players underscore the dynamic operational environment as India aims to leverage global shifts into a manufacturing powerhouse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:59:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69999e0a730b6847a5176c1b_1771675282301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Triveni Turbine Faces Tariff Headwinds, Valuation in Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triveni-Turbine-Faces-Tariff-Headwinds-Valuation-in-Focus/69999e07730b6847a5176c05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triveni-Turbine-Faces-Tariff-Headwinds-Valuation-in-Focus/69999e07730b6847a5176c05</guid><description>Triveni Turbine confronts challenges from fluctuating US tariff policies, impacting its global supply chain visibility and cross-border pricing. Despite a 150-day tariff window, long-term planning remains difficult. The company's stock has fallen over 17% in the past year, with a market capitalization of approximately ₹15,608.42 crore. While the Indian manufacturing sector shows resilience, Triveni Turbine's valuation is under review amidst these trade uncertainties and varying analyst outlooks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:59:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69999e07730b6847a5176c04_1771675309036.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power &amp; Instrumentation Q3 FY26 Revenue Surges 43%; Bags ₹124 Cr Orders</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-and-Instrumentation-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Surges-43percent-Bags-124-Cr-Orders/69999ca0730b6847a5176b11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-and-Instrumentation-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Surges-43percent-Bags-124-Cr-Orders/69999ca0730b6847a5176b11</guid><description>Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Limited posted robust Q3 FY26 results with consolidated income up 43.18% YoY to ₹48.89 Cr, boosted by ₹124.17 Cr in new contracts, including significant RDSS projects. The company targets 30-35% revenue growth over five years and is expanding into specialized manufacturing like busduct systems. Strong order book provides visibility, though working capital remains a monitor point.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69999ca0730b6847a5176b10_1771674961413.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCC Limited gets Delhi HC interim relief on NHAI debarment order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Limited-gets-Delhi-HC-interim-relief-on-NHAI-debarment-order/6999959a730b6847a5176903</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Limited-gets-Delhi-HC-interim-relief-on-NHAI-debarment-order/6999959a730b6847a5176903</guid><description>NCC Limited has received a significant reprieve as the Delhi High Court granted interim protection, putting a debarment order from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) on hold. This interim relief is effective until March 10, 2026, allowing NCC to continue its operations without immediate restrictions while it pursues further legal recourse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999959a730b6847a5176902_1771673143662.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Navigates US Tariffs With Strategic Trade Realignment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Navigates-US-Tariffs-With-Strategic-Trade-Realignment/699994b6730b6847a5176837</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Navigates-US-Tariffs-With-Strategic-Trade-Realignment/699994b6730b6847a5176837</guid><description>New Delhi is meticulously assessing the implications of recent US Supreme Court tariff rulings and President Trump's subsequent announcements. The Indian government's commerce ministry is studying these developments to understand potential impacts on the nation's export competitiveness and overall trade balance. This strategic review signals India's intent to adapt its economic policies and safeguard national interests in response to evolving international trade regulations. The move underscores a broader effort to enhance economic resilience through proactive trade recalibrations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:19:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699994b6730b6847a5176836_1771672867408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>R&amp;B Denims Bags ₹216 Cr Orders; 12M Meters Denim Fabric to be Supplied</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RandB-Denims-Bags-216-Cr-Orders-12M-Meters-Denim-Fabric-to-be-Supplied/6999942f730b6847a51767d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RandB-Denims-Bags-216-Cr-Orders-12M-Meters-Denim-Fabric-to-be-Supplied/6999942f730b6847a51767d4</guid><description>R&amp;B Denims Limited announced a significant win with new sales orders worth ₹215.88 crore for approximately 12 million meters of denim fabric. These orders are slated for execution within the next six months, significantly boosting the company's revenue visibility and order book position. The development underscores strong demand traction and the company's growing execution capabilities in the competitive textile market.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999942f730b6847a51767d3_1771672764171.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gulf Oil Lubricants Secures Mahindra Deal, Fuels EV Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Gulf-Oil-Lubricants-Secures-Mahindra-Deal-Fuels-EV-Ambitions/699990ed730b6847a517669a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Gulf-Oil-Lubricants-Secures-Mahindra-Deal-Fuels-EV-Ambitions/699990ed730b6847a517669a</guid><description>Gulf Oil Lubricants India Limited (GOLIL) has inked its longest-ever multi-year partnership renewal with Mahindra &amp; Mahindra's Farm Equipment Sector. This strategic alliance solidifies GOLIL's dominant position in the agricultural lubricant market, providing a stable revenue stream. The deepened bond is crucial for funding the company's aggressive diversification into electric vehicle (EV) mobility solutions and battery replacement segments, signaling a dual-pronged growth strategy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:03:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699990ed730b6847a5176699_1771671917922.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motherson Group Bets Big on $108B Target Amidst Diversification Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Motherson-Group-Bets-Big-on-108B-Target-Amidst-Diversification-Risks/69998e1a730b6847a517655d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Motherson-Group-Bets-Big-on-108B-Target-Amidst-Diversification-Risks/69998e1a730b6847a517655d</guid><description>Motherson Group Chairman Vivek Chaand Sehgal has reiterated the ambitious goal of achieving $108 billion in revenue by 2030, coupled with a challenging 40% return on capital employed (ROCE). The conglomerate reported ₹1.13 trillion (approximately $13.6 billion) in revenue for FY25, a 15% increase year-on-year. This expansion strategy involves a significant pivot beyond its core automotive components business into consumer electronics, medical equipment, and drone parts manufacturing. The company's largest factory has already shifted production to consumer electronics, signaling a major operational realignmen t. This aggressive push, however, introduces substantial execution risks and a heightened competitive profile in new markets, even as analysts maintain a generally positive outlook.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69998e1a730b6847a517655c_1771671204862.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hilltone Gases Adds CO2, Argon; Targets 25% Margin Boost and 15% Logistics Cut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hilltone-Gases-Adds-CO2-Argon-Targets-25percent-Margin-Boost-and-15percent-Logistics-Cut/69998e19730b6847a5176546</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hilltone-Gases-Adds-CO2-Argon-Targets-25percent-Margin-Boost-and-15percent-Logistics-Cut/69998e19730b6847a5176546</guid><description>Hilltone Software &amp; Gases Limited is expanding its Industrial Gases division by adding Carbon Dioxide (CO2) and Argon, investing in new storage and bottling infrastructure. The company expects this move to improve supply reliability, enhance customer service, and control procurement, with a target of a 25% gross profit margin improvement in the vertical and a 15% reduction in logistics costs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69998e19730b6847a5176545_1771671173510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tax Savings: ELSS, ULIPs, NPS Costs &amp; Risks Revealed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Tax-Savings-ELSS-ULIPs-NPS-Costs-and-Risks-Revealed/69998c65730b6847a5176457</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Tax-Savings-ELSS-ULIPs-NPS-Costs-and-Risks-Revealed/69998c65730b6847a5176457</guid><description>With the financial year-end approaching, high-income earners find the Old Tax Regime (OTR) appealing due to various deductions. However, a critical examination of investment vehicles like Equity Linked Savings Schemes (ELSS), Unit Linked Insurance Plans (ULIPs), and the National Pension System (NPS) is essential. While offering tax advantages, these instruments carry distinct risks, significant charges, and evolving regulatory landscapes that can dilute net returns, making a 'penny saved' potentially costlier than anticipated.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:43:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69998c65730b6847a5176456_1771670795195.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fineotex Chemical Q3 Revenue Surges 46%; Acquires US Oilfield Firm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fineotex-Chemical-Q3-Revenue-Surges-46percent-Acquires-US-Oilfield-Firm/699989e0730b6847a5176353</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fineotex-Chemical-Q3-Revenue-Surges-46percent-Acquires-US-Oilfield-Firm/699989e0730b6847a5176353</guid><description>Fineotex Chemical Limited reported a robust 46% year-on-year revenue growth to INR 190.46 crore for Q3 FY26. This surge was driven by its strategic acquisition of US-based CrudeChem Technologies (CCT), which significantly expanded its presence in the oil and gas sector. Despite the strong top-line performance, gross margins compressed to approximately 36% due to integration costs and temporary pricing adjustments. The company, however, remains debt-free with strong cash reserves, positioning it for future expansion and a target of INR 1,000 crore revenue in FY27.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:33:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699989e0730b6847a5176352_1771670095032.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global AI Accord: India Summit Sparks $270B Investment, Risks Remain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-AI-Accord-India-Summit-Sparks-270B-Investment-Risks-Remain/6999853c730b6847a517619a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-AI-Accord-India-Summit-Sparks-270B-Investment-Risks-Remain/6999853c730b6847a517619a</guid><description>The India AI Impact Summit concluded with 86 nations signing a declaration for responsible AI, signaling broad global agreement. Over $270 billion in investment commitments, split between infrastructure ($250B+) and venture capital ($20B), highlight strong global confidence in India's AI ecosystem. Despite the accord, significant hurdles remain in truly democratizing AI and bridging the global 'AI divide'.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:13:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999853c730b6847a5176199_1771668912894.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashoka Buildcon-Railtel Bags ₹1136 Cr Maharashtra IGR IT Project LOI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ashoka-Buildcon-Railtel-Bags-1136-Cr-Maharashtra-IGR-IT-Project-LOI/69998318730b6847a51760c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ashoka-Buildcon-Railtel-Bags-1136-Cr-Maharashtra-IGR-IT-Project-LOI/69998318730b6847a51760c2</guid><description>Ashoka Buildcon, in consortium with Railtel Corporation of India, has received a Letter of Intent (LOI) from the Maharashtra government for a project valued at an estimated ₹1136.18 crore. The five-year contract will focus on the modernization, operation, and maintenance of IT infrastructure for the state's Inspector General of Registration (IGR) offices. This award marks a significant expansion of Ashoka Buildcon's service offerings into government IT infrastructure management.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:04:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69998318730b6847a51760c1_1771668352225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Valuations Face Pressure Amid Growth Slowdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Valuations-Face-Pressure-Amid-Growth-Slowdown/699981b5730b6847a5175fa9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Valuations-Face-Pressure-Amid-Growth-Slowdown/699981b5730b6847a5175fa9</guid><description>Nilesh Shah of Envision Capital suggests Indian IT companies trading at 19-20 times earnings should adjust to around 15 times, reflecting projected 5-8% rupee growth. Current sector valuations are seen as disconnected from this muted outlook, with a potential need for further multiple contraction to align with historical norms and peer growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:58:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699981b5730b6847a5175fa8_1771668029133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Brazil Trade Surge: Critical Minerals &amp; Global South Power</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Brazil-Trade-Surge-Critical-Minerals-and-Global-South-Power/699981b3730b6847a5175f92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Brazil-Trade-Surge-Critical-Minerals-and-Global-South-Power/699981b3730b6847a5175f92</guid><description>India and Brazil are forging a new strategic economic alliance, setting an ambitious target to exceed $20 billion in bilateral trade within five years. This collaboration centers on critical minerals, aiming to diversify supply chains and reduce reliance on dominant global processors. Discussions also encompass artificial intelligence and strengthening the collective voice of the Global South amidst evolving geopolitical dynamics. The partnership underscores a move towards greater South-South economic cooperation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:58:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699981b3730b6847a5175f91_1771668019585.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>