<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:50:29 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Catalytic CSR: India's Growth Engine or Gilded Mirage?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Catalytic-CSR-Indias-Growth-Engine-or-Gilded-Mirage/699c206aee97f501b0eb665a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Catalytic-CSR-Indias-Growth-Engine-or-Gilded-Mirage/699c206aee97f501b0eb665a</guid><description>India's ambition to become a developed nation by 2047 requires vast capital, yet a significant credit gap persists for its 60 million informal entrepreneurs. The concept of 'Catalytic CSR,' using corporate funds to de-risk lending via credit guarantees, emerges as a proposed solution. While promising, this approach faces scrutiny over its scale relative to the need, potential for mission dilution, and implementation complexities. Existing credit guarantee schemes have facilitated substantial lending, but often fall short for the smallest nano-enterprises, highlighting the deep-seated challenges in bridging India's informal credit crisis.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:39:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c206aee97f501b0eb6659_1771839742909.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Fraud: Governance Fears Spark 20% Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Governance-Fears-Spark-20percent-Plunge/699c205aee97f501b0eb6641</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Governance-Fears-Spark-20percent-Plunge/699c205aee97f501b0eb6641</guid><description>IDFC First Bank disclosed a ₹590 crore fraud at its Chandigarh branch, triggering a 20% stock price collapse and its de-empanelment by the Haryana government. The fraud amount exceeds the bank's quarterly net profit, intensifying scrutiny on governance and internal controls. While the RBI downplayed systemic risks, the incident has led to significant investor wealth erosion and heightened caution, overshadowing the generally robust health of the Indian banking sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:39:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c205aee97f501b0eb6640_1771839756542.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CONCOR inks VISL MOU for Vizhinjam port CFS; boosts Kerala logistics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CONCOR-inks-VISL-MOU-for-Vizhinjam-port-CFS-boosts-Kerala-logistics/699c1fc5ee97f501b0eb659e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CONCOR-inks-VISL-MOU-for-Vizhinjam-port-CFS-boosts-Kerala-logistics/699c1fc5ee97f501b0eb659e</guid><description>Container Corporation of India (CONCOR) has signed a non-binding Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) with Vizhinjam International Seaport Ltd (VISL) to develop a Container Freight Station (CFS) near the Vizhinjam International Seaport in Thiruvananthapuram, Kerala. This collaboration aims to enhance multimodal logistics capabilities and support cargo handling efficiency at the strategic port, reinforcing CONCOR's role in expanding India's EXIM trade infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:37:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1fc5ee97f501b0eb659d_1771839533047.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nippon India MF Crosses 5.35% Stake in ESAB India via Open Market Buys</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nippon-India-MF-Crosses-535percent-Stake-in-ESAB-India-via-Open-Market-Buys/699c1e58ee97f501b0eb64c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nippon-India-MF-Crosses-535percent-Stake-in-ESAB-India-via-Open-Market-Buys/699c1e58ee97f501b0eb64c1</guid><description>Nippon India Mutual Fund, through Nippon Life India Asset Management, has significantly increased its shareholding in ESAB India Limited. The fund's total stake now stands at 5.35%, acquired through consistent open market transactions over nearly six years. This substantial accumulation signals institutional confidence in ESAB India's long-term prospects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1e58ee97f501b0eb64c0_1771839213900.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Banks Face Trust Crisis as FM Decries Mis-selling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Face-Trust-Crisis-as-FM-Decries-Mis-selling/699c1d99ee97f501b0eb632b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Face-Trust-Crisis-as-FM-Decries-Mis-selling/699c1d99ee97f501b0eb632b</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has sharply criticized banks for product mis-selling, labeling it a "pet peeve" and urging a return to core deposit mobilization and lending. She welcomed RBI guidelines aimed at curbing these practices, emphasizing that banks can no longer rely on government capital infusions. The absence of a bank consolidation roadmap was also clarified, with a focus shifting to a high-level panel for sector strengthening. This directive signals a critical shift towards rebuilding customer trust and operational prudence within the Indian banking system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:27:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1d99ee97f501b0eb632a_1771839020785.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Banks Face Fee Income Squeeze as Mis-selling Crackdown Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Face-Fee-Income-Squeeze-as-Mis-selling-Crackdown-Intensifies/699c1d7dee97f501b0eb6312</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Face-Fee-Income-Squeeze-as-Mis-selling-Crackdown-Intensifies/699c1d7dee97f501b0eb6312</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman and the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) are enacting stringent measures against banks for mis-selling financial products, designating it an offense under the Bharatiya Nyaya Sanhita (BNS). New RBI guidelines, effective July 1, 2026, mandate explicit customer consent, prohibit bundling, and require refunds and compensation for proven mis-selling. This regulatory tightening aims to curb a long-standing issue and could significantly impact banks' fee-based income, which constitutes a substantial portion of their revenue, forcing a strategic pivot towards core banking operations and customer-centricity amidst evolving funding dynamics and profitability pressures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:27:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1d7dee97f501b0eb6311_1771838965230.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BLS International Surge: Volume Lifts Stock Amid Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BLS-International-Surge-Volume-Lifts-Stock-Amid-Margin-Pressures/699c1d68ee97f501b0eb62fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BLS-International-Surge-Volume-Lifts-Stock-Amid-Margin-Pressures/699c1d68ee97f501b0eb62fb</guid><description>BLS International experienced an intraday surge, propelled by an eightfold increase in trading volume. This move follows robust Q3 results, yet underlying concerns persist: the company has significantly underperformed the Nifty 50 over the past year, and recent margin compression, particularly in its digital segment, signals potential headwinds despite healthy revenue growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:27:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1d68ee97f501b0eb62fa_1771838994867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TD Power Systems Hits New High Amidst Conflicting Signals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TD-Power-Systems-Hits-New-High-Amidst-Conflicting-Signals/699c1d67ee97f501b0eb62e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TD-Power-Systems-Hits-New-High-Amidst-Conflicting-Signals/699c1d67ee97f501b0eb62e4</guid><description>TD Power Systems shares have soared to a new peak, propelled by record export-driven order inflows and robust Q3 FY26 earnings. Revenue and profits climbed significantly year-over-year, with EBITDA margins improving. The company has raised its FY27 revenue guidance. However, the stock's valuation appears stretched compared to industry averages, and a significant number of analysts maintain bearish ratings and price targets, signaling potential divergence between market sentiment and fundamental outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:27:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1d67ee97f501b0eb62e3_1771838991508.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nayara Energy's Sanctioned Status Creates Unique Operational Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Nayara-Energys-Sanctioned-Status-Creates-Unique-Operational-Crisis/699c1c7aee97f501b0eb61b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Nayara-Energys-Sanctioned-Status-Creates-Unique-Operational-Crisis/699c1c7aee97f501b0eb61b1</guid><description>Nayara Energy is confronting substantial operational headwinds, primarily stemming from its direct EU sanctions that critically limit its access to alternative crude supplies. This unique vulnerability, unlike that of its peers, forces a continued reliance on Russian crude, exacerbating risks associated with an impending refinery maintenance shutdown. European contractors have already refused to work, postponing critical overhauls and raising concerns about safety and sustained economic viability, potentially forcing the company into prolonged periods of suboptimal capacity utilization. Competitors are actively diversifying, highlighting Nayara's structurally compromised position in the evolving energy market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1c7aee97f501b0eb61b0_1771838726874.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RPSG Ventures Seeks ₹800 Cr Loan Approval for Sports Unit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RPSG-Ventures-Seeks-800-Cr-Loan-Approval-for-Sports-Unit/699c1c03ee97f501b0eb6107</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RPSG-Ventures-Seeks-800-Cr-Loan-Approval-for-Sports-Unit/699c1c03ee97f501b0eb6107</guid><description>RPSG Ventures is initiating a postal ballot and e-voting process for members to approve loans of up to ₹800 crore to its subsidiary, RPSG Sports Private Limited. This move aims to provide financial support for the subsidiary's business activities. The e-voting period is from February 24, 2026, to March 25, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:21:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1c03ee97f501b0eb6106_1771838571492.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LWS Knitwear EGM March 20 to Seek Nod for ₹44 Cr Capital Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/LWS-Knitwear-EGM-March-20-to-Seek-Nod-for-44-Cr-Capital-Hike/699c19a7ee97f501b0eb5f4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/LWS-Knitwear-EGM-March-20-to-Seek-Nod-for-44-Cr-Capital-Hike/699c19a7ee97f501b0eb5f4f</guid><description>LWS Knitwear Limited will convene an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on March 20, 2026, seeking shareholder approval to significantly increase its authorised share capital from ₹15.50 crore to ₹44.00 crore. This move aims to create 2.85 crore additional equity shares, providing the company with enhanced flexibility for future capital raising initiatives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c19a7ee97f501b0eb5f4e_1771838181813.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Switching Technologies Q4 Loss Widens; Net Worth Eroded; Auditors Flag Going Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Switching-Technologies-Q4-Loss-Widens-Net-Worth-Eroded-Auditors-Flag-Going-Concern/699c17c7ee97f501b0eb5e0f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Switching-Technologies-Q4-Loss-Widens-Net-Worth-Eroded-Auditors-Flag-Going-Concern/699c17c7ee97f501b0eb5e0f</guid><description>Switching Technologies Gunther Limited reported a significant deepening of its net loss to ₹6.69 crore for the fiscal year ended March 31, 2025. The company's net worth has been completely eroded by accumulated losses, and auditors have raised substantial concerns about its ability to continue as a going concern. Liquidity pressures are severe, with current liabilities significantly exceeding assets, signalling an immediate financial crisis.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:03:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c17c7ee97f501b0eb5e0e_1771837696865.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC Hotels Surges: Rally Faces Peak Test Amid Sector Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/ITC-Hotels-Surges-Rally-Faces-Peak-Test-Amid-Sector-Consolidation/699c166dee97f501b0eb5ca9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/ITC-Hotels-Surges-Rally-Faces-Peak-Test-Amid-Sector-Consolidation/699c166dee97f501b0eb5ca9</guid><description>ITC Hotels shares surged 5% on heavy volumes, breaking a three-day losing streak following robust Q3 FY26 results showing a near 10% profit increase to ₹236.83 crore. Analysts maintain a 'Strong Buy' consensus with an average target of ₹237.40, signaling potential upside. However, the stock remains significantly below its post-demerger high of ₹261.62, while its P/E ratio trades at a premium compared to peers, in a hospitality sector focused on discipline and sustained, measured growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:57:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c166dee97f501b0eb5ca8_1771837190404.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reva Diamond IPO: High Margin Play Faces SIS Model Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Reva-Diamond-IPO-High-Margin-Play-Faces-SIS-Model-Risk/699c1663ee97f501b0eb5c8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Reva-Diamond-IPO-High-Margin-Play-Faces-SIS-Model-Risk/699c1663ee97f501b0eb5c8f</guid><description>PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery is set to launch its ₹380 crore IPO on February 24, 2026. The retail brand aims to capitalize on India's growing organized diamond jewelry market with a 100% diamond focus, promising high margins. However, its business model, heavily reliant on the Shop-in-Shop (SIS) format for most stores, presents significant structural risks, leading to a divergence in brokerage outlooks. SBI Securities maintains a neutral stance citing promoter dependency, while Arihant Capital recommends a long-term 'Subscribe'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:57:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1663ee97f501b0eb5c8e_1771837191337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kome-On Communication FY24: ₹13.28 Cr Loss, Zero Revenue, Assets Collapse</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kome-On-Communication-FY24-1328-Cr-Loss-Zero-Revenue-Assets-Collapse/699c157bee97f501b0eb5b3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kome-On-Communication-FY24-1328-Cr-Loss-Zero-Revenue-Assets-Collapse/699c157bee97f501b0eb5b3e</guid><description>Kome-On Communication Limited has reported a devastating financial performance for FY24, with zero revenue from operations and a staggering net loss of ₹13.28 Crores. The company's assets have virtually vanished, shrinking to ₹1.13 Lakhs from ₹13.27 Crores, leading to a negative net worth of (₹12.74) Lakhs. This signals a complete operational breakdown and severe financial distress.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:53:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c157bee97f501b0eb5b3d_1771836892788.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fraud Stains IDFC First Bank's Q3 Glow, Stock Plunges 16%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fraud-Stains-IDFC-First-Banks-Q3-Glow-Stock-Plunges-16percent/699c1574ee97f501b0eb5b25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fraud-Stains-IDFC-First-Banks-Q3-Glow-Stock-Plunges-16percent/699c1574ee97f501b0eb5b25</guid><description>IDFC First Bank's stock plummeted nearly 16% following a ₹590 crore fraud disclosure involving Haryana government accounts. Despite reporting a 41% rise in Q3 profit to ₹479 crore, the incident has triggered enhanced security protocols, internal suspensions, and a KPMG forensic audit. Analysts question governance and potential earnings impact, contrasting the bank's high P/E ratio with that of its peers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:53:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1574ee97f501b0eb5b24_1771837194795.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Surge: $1.7T Economic Prize Amidst Digital Backbone</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Surge-17T-Economic-Prize-Amidst-Digital-Backbone/699c140dee97f501b0eb59a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Surge-17T-Economic-Prize-Amidst-Digital-Backbone/699c140dee97f501b0eb59a0</guid><description>India's AI sector is rapidly maturing, with projections indicating nearly $1.7 trillion in economic value by 2035, driven by deep enterprise integration and a strong digital public infrastructure. Over 70% of organizations report a clear AI strategy. Key growth drivers include a rapidly expanding AI talent pool, government initiatives like the IndiaAI Mission bolstering compute access, and a focus on domain-specific, multilingual models. This approach emphasizes inclusive innovation, positioning India for sustained economic leadership.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:47:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c140dee97f501b0eb599f_1771836588473.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Arrow Greentech Wins India Patent for Anti-Counterfeiting Security Paper Tech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Arrow-Greentech-Wins-India-Patent-for-Anti-Counterfeiting-Security-Paper-Tech/699c1407ee97f501b0eb5986</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Arrow-Greentech-Wins-India-Patent-for-Anti-Counterfeiting-Security-Paper-Tech/699c1407ee97f501b0eb5986</guid><description>Arrow Greentech Limited has been granted an Indian patent (No. 580835) for "Multicolour Security Fibers/Planchettes for High Security Paper". This technology aims to significantly enhance security features in paper products, making them resistant to counterfeiting. With applications spanning banknotes, cheques, and official documents, the patent leverages the company's R&amp;D expertise in chemistry and security printing, potentially opening new avenues for its Hightech Products segment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:47:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1407ee97f501b0eb5985_1771836653560.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kome-On Communication Q3 FY24: Zero Revenue, ₹0.00 Cr Loss; Reporting Delayed Over 2 Years</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kome-On-Communication-Q3-FY24-Zero-Revenue-000-Cr-Loss-Reporting-Delayed-Over-2-Years/699c1319ee97f501b0eb5879</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kome-On-Communication-Q3-FY24-Zero-Revenue-000-Cr-Loss-Reporting-Delayed-Over-2-Years/699c1319ee97f501b0eb5879</guid><description>Kome-On Communication reported zero revenue for Q3 FY24 and the nine-month period ended December 31, 2023. The company incurred a net loss of ₹0.35 lakh for the quarter and ₹5.79 lakhs for the nine months, marking a widening loss. A significant concern is the over two-year delay in reporting these financial results, raising red flags for operational dormancy and governance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:43:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1319ee97f501b0eb5878_1771836292021.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-France Tax Treaty Overhaul Signals Investment Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-France-Tax-Treaty-Overhaul-Signals-Investment-Shift/699c1241ee97f501b0eb57a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-France-Tax-Treaty-Overhaul-Signals-Investment-Shift/699c1241ee97f501b0eb57a3</guid><description>India and France have updated their Double Taxation Avoidance Convention, reshaping dividend taxation with tiered rates (5%/15%) and significantly expanding India's capital gains taxing rights by removing ownership thresholds for French investors. The protocol also revises technical services taxation and removes the Most-Favoured-Nation clause, aiming to enhance tax certainty and align with global standards for cross-border transactions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:39:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c1241ee97f501b0eb57a2_1771836098500.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auto Sector Gears Up: Growth Signals Amidst Ancillary Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Sector-Gears-Up-Growth-Signals-Amidst-Ancillary-Challenges/699c0fa8ee97f501b0eb557e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Sector-Gears-Up-Growth-Signals-Amidst-Ancillary-Challenges/699c0fa8ee97f501b0eb557e</guid><description>Axis Securities forecasts FY26 growth for Indian auto and ancillary sectors, citing stable margins and improving volumes. However, a deeper analysis reveals potential margin compression for ancillaries amid commodity costs and a mixed outlook for OEMs, especially with evolving regulations and global economic uncertainties. Key players like Eicher Motors and Bajaj Auto show strength, while Ashok Leyland navigates segment-specific trends.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:28:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0fa8ee97f501b0eb557d_1771835498337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Olectra Greentech Wins ₹1,800 Cr EV Bus Order for Telangana</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Olectra-Greentech-Wins-1800-Cr-EV-Bus-Order-for-Telangana/699c0f9bee97f501b0eb5564</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Olectra-Greentech-Wins-1800-Cr-EV-Bus-Order-for-Telangana/699c0f9bee97f501b0eb5564</guid><description>Olectra Greentech has secured a substantial ₹1,800 crore order for 1,085 electric buses from the Telangana State Road Transport Corporation (TGSRTC) through its subsidiary Evey Trans Private Limited (EVEY). This 12-year Gross Cost Contract (GCC) / OPEX deal for supply, operation, and maintenance signifies significant revenue visibility and an expansion in Olectra's service-based business model.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:28:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0f9bee97f501b0eb5563_1771835606593.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dixon Tech Stock Dips Amid Memory Price Surge, Analysts Divided</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Dixon-Tech-Stock-Dips-Amid-Memory-Price-Surge-Analysts-Divided/699c0efdee97f501b0eb53eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Dixon-Tech-Stock-Dips-Amid-Memory-Price-Surge-Analysts-Divided/699c0efdee97f501b0eb53eb</guid><description>Dixon Technologies' stock declined over 3% as global memory prices, particularly DRAM, surged, impacting the cost-sensitive Indian smartphone market. Analysts are divided, with Morgan Stanley maintaining a bearish 'Underweight' rating and the lowest price target of ₹8,157, while others maintain 'Buy' ratings and higher targets. The company's reliance on imported components and its focus on the budget segment place it directly in the path of this cost inflation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:25:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0efdee97f501b0eb53ea_1771835300234.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LTIMindtree: Deal Win Meets Analyst Downgrade and Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/LTIMindtree-Deal-Win-Meets-Analyst-Downgrade-and-Profit-Slump/699c0ee9ee97f501b0eb53d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/LTIMindtree-Deal-Win-Meets-Analyst-Downgrade-and-Profit-Slump/699c0ee9ee97f501b0eb53d2</guid><description>LTIMindtree Limited has inked a $100 million, seven-year contract with a European MedTech firm, signaling a strategic push into healthcare technology. The deal encompasses product development and support for hearing solutions, leveraging LTIMindtree's iNXT platform. However, this positive development is overshadowed by a sharp downgrade from Jefferies to "underperform" with a slashed price target of ₹4,300, and a mixed Q4 performance where net profit declined significantly due to a one-time impact from new labor codes, despite revenue and margin beats. The company's stock is currently trading lower, reflecting broader investor concerns about profitability and market sentiment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:25:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0ee9ee97f501b0eb53d1_1771835300465.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC Criticizes RERA: Enforcement Gaps Fuel Abolition Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/SC-Criticizes-RERA-Enforcement-Gaps-Fuel-Abolition-Debate/699c0e90ee97f501b0eb52d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/SC-Criticizes-RERA-Enforcement-Gaps-Fuel-Abolition-Debate/699c0e90ee97f501b0eb52d2</guid><description>India's Supreme Court has sharply criticized the Real Estate (Regulation and Development) Act (RERA), suggesting abolition due to perceived favoritism towards builders and failure to protect homebuyers. Experts argue the law's intent remains sound, but inconsistent enforcement, jurisdictional conflicts with the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC), and uneven state implementation have hampered its efficacy. Reforms focused on bolstering recovery powers and inter-law coherence are proposed over dismantling the decade-old regulator.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:23:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0e90ee97f501b0eb52d1_1771835227684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises: High Growth Story Faces Valuation Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Amber-Enterprises-High-Growth-Story-Faces-Valuation-Test/699c0e78ee97f501b0eb52aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Amber-Enterprises-High-Growth-Story-Faces-Valuation-Test/699c0e78ee97f501b0eb52aa</guid><description>Amber Enterprises India is positioned for robust growth, buoyed by a strong Indian Room Air Conditioner (RAC) market projected at 19% CAGR and its expanding Electronics Manufacturing Services (EMS) portfolio. Analyst consensus is overwhelmingly 'Buy,' citing market leadership and a diversified strategy. However, a premium forward P/E of 55x, coupled with rising commodity costs and evolving energy efficiency norms, warrants careful scrutiny of its valuation amidst significant expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:23:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0e78ee97f501b0eb52a9_1771835197293.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPL Restructuring: Market Skepticism Overshadows Pure-Play Vision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/UPL-Restructuring-Market-Skepticism-Overshadows-Pure-Play-Vision/699c0e77ee97f501b0eb5293</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/UPL-Restructuring-Market-Skepticism-Overshadows-Pure-Play-Vision/699c0e77ee97f501b0eb5293</guid><description>UPL Ltd. is undergoing a three-phase restructuring to create a standalone, listed crop protection company, UPL Global, alongside its diversified entity. While analysts like Anand Rathi maintain a 'BUY' rating and an Rs860 target price, the market has reacted negatively, with shares dropping nearly 7% on February 23, 2026. This sentiment highlights investor concerns about leverage, dilution, and the execution of the demerger, which is expected to take 12-15 months. The company aims to streamline operations and facilitate deleveraging, but immediate market reception suggests a disconnect between strategic intent and investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:23:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0e77ee97f501b0eb5292_1771835532475.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's MTF Boom Faces Headwinds: Leverage &amp; Risk Concerns Mount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-MTF-Boom-Faces-Headwinds-Leverage-and-Risk-Concerns-Mount/699c0e06ee97f501b0eb51b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-MTF-Boom-Faces-Headwinds-Leverage-and-Risk-Concerns-Mount/699c0e06ee97f501b0eb51b4</guid><description>India's Margin Trading Facility (MTF) book has ballooned to ₹1.2 lakh crore as of January 2026, a 43% increase year-on-year. This growth, fueled by customer demand and F&amp;O restrictions, has seen major brokers like Groww report fourfold increases in their MTF portfolios. Despite recent Reserve Bank of India (RBI) curbs on bank lending to brokers for MTF, firms are largely relying on internal accruals and non-banking financial company (NBFC) funding, which are less affected by the directives. However, concerns are mounting over escalating leverage within a flat market, with the Nifty 50 experiencing its weakest January in over a decade. Analysts and industry insiders point to potential systemic risks, particularly if market volatility increases, as leveraged positions could trigger synchronized liquidations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:21:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0e06ee97f501b0eb51b3_1771835128752.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mangaluru Tech Ambition: Balancing Growth With Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mangaluru-Tech-Ambition-Balancing-Growth-With-Risks/699c0df3ee97f501b0eb518c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mangaluru-Tech-Ambition-Balancing-Growth-With-Risks/699c0df3ee97f501b0eb518c</guid><description>Mangaluru is positioning itself as a key tech hub, attracting over 40 firms and 8,000 jobs with its cost-effectiveness, talent pool, and quality of life. The IT workforce has reached nearly 26,000. While this growth aligns with India's decentralization trend, concerns over safety due to communal tensions and the need for rapid infrastructure scaling pose significant risks to its continued ascent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:21:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0df3ee97f501b0eb518b_1771835141589.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gurugram Luxury Homes Surge, Overtaking Mumbai in Sales Value</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Gurugram-Luxury-Homes-Surge-Overtaking-Mumbai-in-Sales-Value/699c0d89ee97f501b0eb508c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Gurugram-Luxury-Homes-Surge-Overtaking-Mumbai-in-Sales-Value/699c0d89ee97f501b0eb508c</guid><description>Gurugram's primary luxury housing market achieved a record sales value of ₹24,120 crore in 2025, an 80% year-on-year increase driven by higher volumes and price appreciation. The city sold 1,494 units priced at ₹10 crore and above, outperforming Mumbai's ₹21,902 crore in this segment. This growth is attributed to emerging micro-markets, infrastructure development, and a strong influx of high-net-worth individuals, signaling a significant shift in India's premium real estate landscape.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:19:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0d89ee97f501b0eb508b_1771834885865.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharat Taxi's Cooperative Drive Challenges Ola, Uber Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Bharat-Taxis-Cooperative-Drive-Challenges-Ola-Uber-Dominance/699c0d88ee97f501b0eb5075</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Bharat-Taxis-Cooperative-Drive-Challenges-Ola-Uber-Dominance/699c0d88ee97f501b0eb5075</guid><description>Union Home Minister Amit Shah launched Bharat Taxi, a cooperative ride-hailing platform where drivers are owners with equity participation and profit-sharing benefits, challenging the commission-heavy models of Ola and Uber. Drivers can become shareholders with a ₹500 investment, aiming for profit distribution based on kilometers driven after three years. The platform eschews commissions and surge pricing, contrasting with incumbents facing financial pressures and market share erosion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:19:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0d88ee97f501b0eb5074_1771834881960.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SPML Infra Q3 FY26 Profit ₹20.5 Cr; BESS Expansion and ₹4,358 Cr Order Book Drive Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SPML-Infra-Q3-FY26-Profit-205-Cr-BESS-Expansion-and-4358-Cr-Order-Book-Drive-Growth/699c0c8fee97f501b0eb4f46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SPML-Infra-Q3-FY26-Profit-205-Cr-BESS-Expansion-and-4358-Cr-Order-Book-Drive-Growth/699c0c8fee97f501b0eb4f46</guid><description>SPML Infra reported a profit after tax (PAT) of ₹20.5 crore for the third quarter of FY26, driven by a robust order book of ₹4,358 crore and strategic expansion into Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS). The company is targeting significant revenue and PAT growth for FY26 and is actively de-leveraging its balance sheet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:15:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0c8fee97f501b0eb4f45_1771834611652.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coulomb Litech Secures ₹20 Cr for Heavy EV Battery Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coulomb-Litech-Secures-20-Cr-for-Heavy-EV-Battery-Expansion/699c0c14ee97f501b0eb4eb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coulomb-Litech-Secures-20-Cr-for-Heavy-EV-Battery-Expansion/699c0c14ee97f501b0eb4eb2</guid><description>Battery technology startup Coulomb Litech has secured ₹20 crore in seed funding, earmarked for expanding its manufacturing capabilities and market presence within India's burgeoning electric vehicle ecosystem. Founded by IIT Kanpur alumni, the company specializes in fast-charging, long-life battery systems tailored for medium and heavy electric vehicles, addressing critical segments like electric tractors, construction equipment, and three-wheelers. This capital infusion is poised to accelerate the establishment of a state-of-the-art manufacturing facility and bolster research and development efforts, positioning Coulomb Litech to support India's ambitious electrification goals for commercial transport.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:13:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0c14ee97f501b0eb4eb1_1771834703806.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Garnet Construction MD &amp; CFO Kishankumar Kedia Dies; Promotes Family Leadership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Garnet-Construction-MD-and-CFO-Kishankumar-Kedia-Dies-Promotes-Family-Leadership/699c0760ee97f501b0eb4cf5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Garnet-Construction-MD-and-CFO-Kishankumar-Kedia-Dies-Promotes-Family-Leadership/699c0760ee97f501b0eb4cf5</guid><description>Garnet Construction Limited has announced the deeply unfortunate demise of its Promoter, Managing Director, and Chief Financial Officer, Mr. Kishankumar Jugalkishore Kedia, on February 22, 2026. Mr. Kedia, who held a significant 29.37% stake in the company, was instrumental in its leadership for years. The company faces the challenge of navigating a leadership transition following this irreparable loss.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0760ee97f501b0eb4cf4_1771833320987.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pine Labs Secures Major OMC Contracts, Eyes Turnaround</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Pine-Labs-Secures-Major-OMC-Contracts-Eyes-Turnaround/699c068dee97f501b0eb4b7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Pine-Labs-Secures-Major-OMC-Contracts-Eyes-Turnaround/699c068dee97f501b0eb4b7a</guid><description>Pine Labs Ltd. has secured multi-year contracts with India's top three Oil Marketing Companies (OMCs) to modernize digital payment infrastructure, involving approximately 130,000 devices. This strategic win coincides with a significant Q3 FY26 financial rebound, reporting a net profit of ₹42.4 crore against a prior-year loss, and revenue growth of 23.7%. Despite this positive momentum, the company's stock remains down 12.6% year-to-date, trading below its 52-week high.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:49:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c068dee97f501b0eb4b79_1771833136600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BF Utilities Posts Growth Amid Severe Auditor Concerns &amp; ₹500 Cr Claim</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Posts-Growth-Amid-Severe-Auditor-Concerns-and-500-Cr-Claim/699c0685ee97f501b0eb4b62</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Posts-Growth-Amid-Severe-Auditor-Concerns-and-500-Cr-Claim/699c0685ee97f501b0eb4b62</guid><description>BF Utilities reported a 4.71% revenue and 8.15% profit growth for Q2 FY26. However, the company faces significant headwinds, including an 'Adverse Conclusion' from its auditors for non-compliance with accounting standards, a ₹500 crore arbitration claim, and the cessation of toll operations at its material subsidiary, NHDL. These factors cast a shadow over the reported financial performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:49:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0685ee97f501b0eb4b61_1771833053169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bacil Pharma: Vicky Shah hikes stake to 16.60% via Off-Market deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Bacil-Pharma-Vicky-Shah-hikes-stake-to-1660percent-via-Off-Market-deal/699c0671ee97f501b0eb4b14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Bacil-Pharma-Vicky-Shah-hikes-stake-to-1660percent-via-Off-Market-deal/699c0671ee97f501b0eb4b14</guid><description>Mr. Vicky Shah has substantially increased his stake in Bacil Pharma Limited by acquiring 2,075,000 shares off-market. His holding has risen from 2.14% to 16.60% of the company's total equity share capital. This significant shift in shareholding could signal potential changes in the company's strategic direction or management.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0671ee97f501b0eb4b13_1771833076338.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT, EV Stocks Dive as AI Fears and Operational Woes Hit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-EV-Stocks-Dive-as-AI-Fears-and-Operational-Woes-Hit/699c0630ee97f501b0eb4a93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-EV-Stocks-Dive-as-AI-Fears-and-Operational-Woes-Hit/699c0630ee97f501b0eb4a93</guid><description>On Monday, February 23, 2026, a broad market uplift saw the BSE Sensex gain 0.4%, yet prominent IT and electric vehicle (EV) stocks plummeted to 52-week lows. Wipro, L&amp;T Technology Services, and Hexaware Technologies among IT firms, and Ola Electric Mobility in the EV segment, experienced significant sell-offs. This divergence highlights deep sectoral headwinds, including the disruptive potential of artificial intelligence on IT services and severe financial and operational challenges plaguing Ola Electric, overshadowing a seemingly stable broader market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0630ee97f501b0eb4a92_1771833050981.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Fraud Probe: RBI Assurances vs. Investor Skepticism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Probe-RBI-Assurances-vs-Investor-Skepticism/699c0620ee97f501b0eb4a55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Probe-RBI-Assurances-vs-Investor-Skepticism/699c0620ee97f501b0eb4a55</guid><description>IDFC First Bank's stock plummeted up to 20% after a ₹590 crore fraud probe involving its Chandigarh branch surfaced. Four employees have been suspended, and KPMG appointed for a forensic audit. The Haryana government de-empanelled the bank for government business. RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra stated there is no systemic risk, calling it an isolated incident and reassuring the broader banking sector. Despite these assurances, the market reaction highlights investor apprehension regarding governance issues. The bank's management claims internal checks were intact. IDFC First Bank has no promoter holding, with stakes held by mutual funds, insurance companies, and retail investors. The stock closed down 15.5% on NSE amidst significant trading volumes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:47:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0620ee97f501b0eb4a54_1771832950817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Supreme Court Flags Airfare Surges, Sparking Regulatory Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Supreme-Court-Flags-Airfare-Surges-Sparking-Regulatory-Risk/699c0541ee97f501b0eb4892</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Supreme-Court-Flags-Airfare-Surges-Sparking-Regulatory-Risk/699c0541ee97f501b0eb4892</guid><description>The Supreme Court of India has flagged 'serious concern' regarding unpredictable fluctuations in airfare and additional charges imposed by private airlines, particularly during peak seasons. In response to a petition seeking regulatory guidelines, the government has assured the court it is examining the issue at the highest level and will file a comprehensive response within four weeks. This intervention signals potential new regulatory oversight on dynamic pricing and ancillary revenue streams within the Indian aviation industry, a sector historically operating with significant market-driven freedom.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c0541ee97f501b0eb4891_1771832797435.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>