<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:39:13 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Eyes Energy Diversification Amid US Trade Pact; Russia Disputes Oil Halt Claims</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Eyes-Energy-Diversification-Amid-US-Trade-Pact-Russia-Disputes-Oil-Halt-Claims/6983115bf5a3f0ebac99c693</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Eyes-Energy-Diversification-Amid-US-Trade-Pact-Russia-Disputes-Oil-Halt-Claims/6983115bf5a3f0ebac99c693</guid><description>India is strategizing to diversify its energy portfolio amid global shifts, according to Trade Minister Piyush Goyal. This comes after reports of a US trade deal involving India halting Russian oil purchases, a move Russia disputes. Refiners await official directives, with existing contracts needing wind-down periods. The trade agreement also reportedly secured India's agricultural sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra Lands Landmark Indonesia LCV Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-Lands-Landmark-Indonesia-LCV-Order/6983112ef5a3f0ebac99c58f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-Lands-Landmark-Indonesia-LCV-Order/6983112ef5a3f0ebac99c58f</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra has finalized a landmark agreement to supply 35,000 Scorpio Pik Up light commercial vehicles to Indonesia’s state-owned Agrinas Pangan Nusantara in 2026. This single order surpasses Mahindra's total vehicle exports for FY25, marking a substantial acceleration in international operations and targeting agricultural logistics within Indonesia's Koperasi Desa/Kelurahan Merah Putih initiative.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PSP Projects: Adani Deal Boosts Orders, But High Valuation Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PSP-Projects-Adani-Deal-Boosts-Orders-But-High-Valuation-Looms/69830936f5a3f0ebac99a6fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PSP-Projects-Adani-Deal-Boosts-Orders-But-High-Valuation-Looms/69830936f5a3f0ebac99a6fe</guid><description>PSP Projects Ltd. (PSPPL) posted a significant 24% year-on-year revenue increase to Rs 7.7 billion for Q3 FY26, recovering from earlier flat growth. The company secured substantial order inflows, bolstering its order book to Rs 91 billion, largely driven by strategic partnerships with the Adani Group, which now includes a significant equity stake. Despite robust project execution and revenue visibility, PSPPL's current market valuation appears stretched when compared to peers and its own historical metrics, raising questions about sustainability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:28:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69830936f5a3f0ebac99a6fd_1770197278287.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sun Pharma Bets Big: Cricket Sponsorship Sparks Brand Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sun-Pharma-Bets-Big-Cricket-Sponsorship-Sparks-Brand-Debate/698310ccf5a3f0ebac99c3ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sun-Pharma-Bets-Big-Cricket-Sponsorship-Sparks-Brand-Debate/698310ccf5a3f0ebac99c3ff</guid><description>Sun Pharma, India's largest pharmaceutical company, has entered its first major cricket partnership, becoming the principal sponsor for Royal Challengers Bengaluru (RCB) for the 2026 T20 season. This three-year agreement, a significant strategic shift, includes prominent logo placement on team apparel and stadium branding. While aiming to bolster consumer connection, this substantial investment raises questions about resource allocation within the pharmaceutical sector and its long-term return on investment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Resonance Specialties Q3 Profit Surges 125% on Strong Revenue, Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Resonance-Specialties-Q3-Profit-Surges-125percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Margin-Gains/698308f6f5a3f0ebac99a533</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Resonance-Specialties-Q3-Profit-Surges-125percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Margin-Gains/698308f6f5a3f0ebac99a533</guid><description>Resonance Specialties Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26, with net profit soaring 125.27% YoY to ₹251.28 Lakhs. Revenue climbed 25.90% YoY to ₹2,296.27 Lakhs, while PBT margins expanded significantly to 14.53%. The company also saw a strong 55.51% growth in international revenue, now comprising 54.23% of the total. New board appointments were also announced.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:26:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698308f6f5a3f0ebac99a532_1770197178886.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian E2W Market Consolidation: Legacy Players Dominate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-E2W-Market-Consolidation-Legacy-Players-Dominate/698308bdf5a3f0ebac99a44b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-E2W-Market-Consolidation-Legacy-Players-Dominate/698308bdf5a3f0ebac99a44b</guid><description>India's electric two-wheeler (E2W) market is poised for robust growth, projected at 16-18% next fiscal, recovering from supply chain disruptions that moderated growth to 12-13% in the current fiscal. However, the market is undergoing significant consolidation, with legacy manufacturers like TVS Motor and Bajaj Auto extending their lead, while new-age players like Ola Electric face substantial market share declines due to weak unit economics and service concerns. Reliability and service are emerging as key differentiators, further bolstering established players.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698308bdf5a3f0ebac99a44a_1770197053515.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Great Eastern Shipping Posts Strong Profit, Dividend; Cautions on High Asset Prices</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Great-Eastern-Shipping-Posts-Strong-Profit-Dividend-Cautions-on-High-Asset-Prices/69831046f5a3f0ebac99c241</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Great-Eastern-Shipping-Posts-Strong-Profit-Dividend-Cautions-on-High-Asset-Prices/69831046f5a3f0ebac99c241</guid><description>Great Eastern Shipping reported a robust Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit at INR 813 crores and standalone at INR 650 crores. The company celebrated its 16th consecutive quarterly dividend, driven by strong market conditions across crude, product tanker, dry bulk, and LPG segments. Management, however, expressed caution on new fleet investments amid high asset prices, preferring to deploy capital during market downturns and maintaining a strong net cash position exceeding $500 million.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMB Bank Surges on Robust Q3FY26 Growth &amp; Asset Quality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/TMB-Bank-Surges-on-Robust-Q3FY26-Growth-and-Asset-Quality/69831038f5a3f0ebac99c1a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/TMB-Bank-Surges-on-Robust-Q3FY26-Growth-and-Asset-Quality/69831038f5a3f0ebac99c1a1</guid><description>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank (TMB) reported a strong Q3FY26, with total business growing 14.28% YoY to ₹1,07,470 Cr. Net Profit rose 13.74% YoY to ₹341.50 Cr, driven by a 13.28% YoY increase in Net Interest Income to ₹646.14 Cr. The bank significantly improved asset quality, with Gross NPA falling to 0.91% and Net NPA to 0.20%. Net Interest Margin (NIM) expanded to 4.04%, and ROA/ROE saw an uptick. TMB is investing ₹250 Cr in strategic IT initiatives and expanding its digital capabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India-US Trade Pact: Strategic Resilience Amidst Global Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Strategic-Resilience-Amidst-Global-Volatility/6983084af5a3f0ebac99a2cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Strategic-Resilience-Amidst-Global-Volatility/6983084af5a3f0ebac99a2cf</guid><description>India's newly finalized trade agreement with the United States reduces US tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, a significant shift from previous highs. This pact, which safeguards key domestic sectors like agriculture and energy, underscores India's strategic pivot towards economic self-reliance and de-risking from global trade uncertainties. The deal is projected to bolster GDP growth and improve export competitiveness across various industries, including MSMEs and textiles, while demonstrating a calculated approach to international economic diplomacy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983084af5a3f0ebac99a2ce_1770196998997.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wealth First Profit Plunges 93% Despite Sales Rise; Dividend Declared</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Wealth-First-Profit-Plunges-93percent-Despite-Sales-Rise-Dividend-Declared/698307fcf5a3f0ebac99a097</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Wealth-First-Profit-Plunges-93percent-Despite-Sales-Rise-Dividend-Declared/698307fcf5a3f0ebac99a097</guid><description>Wealth First's Q3 consolidated profit plunged 93% YoY to Rs. 76.77 Cr, sharply contrasting with a 19% revenue increase. Standalone profit also dropped 84%. However, the nine-month consolidated profit surged 2,414%. The company declared a 40% interim dividend.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:20:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698307fcf5a3f0ebac99a096_1770196852774.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Positron's $230M Boost: Qatar Bets on AI Chip Challenger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Positrons-230M-Boost-Qatar-Bets-on-AI-Chip-Challenger/69830f52f5a3f0ebac99bf7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Positrons-230M-Boost-Qatar-Bets-on-AI-Chip-Challenger/69830f52f5a3f0ebac99bf7f</guid><description>Semiconductor startup Positron raised $230 million in Series B funding, led by Qatar Investment Authority (QIA), to accelerate its AI memory chip deployment. This capital infusion supports Positron's challenge to Nvidia's dominance, particularly in the burgeoning AI inference market. The investment also aligns with Qatar's strategic push to build sovereign AI infrastructure and position itself as a regional AI hub. Positron's Atlas chip aims to match Nvidia H100 performance with significantly lower power consumption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TII Surges on Revenue Growth, Consolidated PAT Dips Due to One-Offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TII-Surges-on-Revenue-Growth-Consolidated-PAT-Dips-Due-to-One-Offs/69830efff5a3f0ebac99bebd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TII-Surges-on-Revenue-Growth-Consolidated-PAT-Dips-Due-to-One-Offs/69830efff5a3f0ebac99bebd</guid><description>Tube Investments of India (TII) posted a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue climbing 20.55% year-on-year to ₹5,800.99 Cr. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) saw a marginal 0.43% decline to ₹278.97 Cr, impacted by a ₹56.99 Cr exceptional item related to New Labour Codes. Standalone operations fared better, with PAT growing 17.58% to ₹188.99 Cr and ROIC improving to 49%. The company also declared an interim dividend of ₹2 per share.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Aptus Housing Finance Q3 Profit Soars 26% on 21% AUM Jump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Aptus-Housing-Finance-Q3-Profit-Soars-26percent-on-21percent-AUM-Jump/69830ef9f5a3f0ebac99be89</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Aptus-Housing-Finance-Q3-Profit-Soars-26percent-on-21percent-AUM-Jump/69830ef9f5a3f0ebac99be89</guid><description>Aptus Value Housing Finance India Ltd. delivered a robust Q3 FY26, posting a 26% YoY surge in Net Profit to ₹239 Cr, driven by a 21% jump in Assets Under Management (AUM) to ₹12,330 Cr. Total income rose 22% YoY to ₹569 Cr. The company reaffirmed its outlook for sustained 22-24% AUM growth, leveraging network expansion and a strategic pivot towards higher-ticket loans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Symphony Reverses Divestment Plan, Q3 Profit Jumps on Write-back</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Symphony-Reverses-Divestment-Plan-Q3-Profit-Jumps-on-Write-back/69830ed9f5a3f0ebac99bdb7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Symphony-Reverses-Divestment-Plan-Q3-Profit-Jumps-on-Write-back/69830ed9f5a3f0ebac99bdb7</guid><description>Symphony Limited's Q3 FY26 reported flat standalone revenue at ₹182 Cr YoY, with EBITDA down to ₹31 Cr due to higher ad spend. Standalone PAT surged to ₹34 Cr from negative territory, driven by a ₹4 Cr write-off recovery. Crucially, the company reversed its proposed divestment of IMPCO Mexico and Climate Holdings Australia, citing unmet valuation expectations, and plans to nurture these businesses. Nine-month figures show declines across revenue and profit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SEBI: Trade Deals Spur Capital; Bond Market Push Lags Crypto Awareness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SEBI-Trade-Deals-Spur-Capital-Bond-Market-Push-Lags-Crypto-Awareness/698307cff5a3f0ebac999fc5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SEBI-Trade-Deals-Spur-Capital-Bond-Market-Push-Lags-Crypto-Awareness/698307cff5a3f0ebac999fc5</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey stated that trade agreement resolutions, such as the one with the US, reduce market uncertainties, thereby accelerating capital formation and spurring investment decisions. He emphasized the need to deepen India's corporate bond market, lamenting that public awareness of cryptocurrencies far exceeds that of bonds. Pandey also indicated that SEBI is not contemplating immediate changes to the existing regulatory framework for derivatives, including weekly expiries, despite increased transaction taxes proposed in the 2026 Budget. He urged stakeholders to collaborate on bond market development initiatives.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:17:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698307cff5a3f0ebac999fc4_1770196657131.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tube Investments Posts Strong Revenue Growth, But Consolidation Profits Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tube-Investments-Posts-Strong-Revenue-Growth-But-Consolidation-Profits-Dip/69830e5cf5a3f0ebac99bc60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tube-Investments-Posts-Strong-Revenue-Growth-But-Consolidation-Profits-Dip/69830e5cf5a3f0ebac99bc60</guid><description>Tube Investments of India reported robust Q3 FY26 consolidated revenue growth of 20.54% year-on-year to ₹5,800.99 Cr. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) saw a marginal decline of 0.42% to ₹278.97 Cr, primarily due to exceptional items totalling ₹68.29 Cr, including gratuity liabilities and fair value losses on investments in TI Clean Mobility. Standalone PAT grew a healthy 17.58% YoY. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹2 per share.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Saregama Profit Jumps 17% QoQ Fueled by IP Expansion and Film Releases</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Saregama-Profit-Jumps-17percent-QoQ-Fueled-by-IP-Expansion-and-Film-Releases/69830731f5a3f0ebac999deb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Saregama-Profit-Jumps-17percent-QoQ-Fueled-by-IP-Expansion-and-Film-Releases/69830731f5a3f0ebac999deb</guid><description>Saregama India posted a robust 17% quarter-on-quarter surge in profit after tax, reaching ₹51.2 crore for Q3 FY26. Revenue also climbed 13% QoQ to ₹260.4 crore. Growth was propelled by its music licensing and artiste management segments, bolstered by over 1,100 new track releases and strategic acquisitions, including a minority stake in Bhansali Productions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69830731f5a3f0ebac999dea_1770196507797.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Century Plyboards Eyes Rs 1130 Cr UP Unit for Plywood, MDF Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Century-Plyboards-Eyes-Rs-1130-Cr-UP-Unit-for-Plywood-MDF-Expansion/69830e21f5a3f0ebac99bb2f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Century-Plyboards-Eyes-Rs-1130-Cr-UP-Unit-for-Plywood-MDF-Expansion/69830e21f5a3f0ebac99bb2f</guid><description>Century Plyboards (India) Ltd. has proposed a significant ₹1130 Crores investment to establish an integrated manufacturing unit in Uttar Pradesh. The project aims to bolster Plywood capacity by 90,000 CBM and introduce a substantial 330,000 CBM MDF board production line. Commissioning is targeted between FY2027-28 and FY2028-29, with financing to be managed via debt and equity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tube Investments: Revenue Soars, Profit Flat, EPS Dips; Dividend Declared</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tube-Investments-Revenue-Soars-Profit-Flat-EPS-Dips-Dividend-Declared/69830e04f5a3f0ebac99ba2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tube-Investments-Revenue-Soars-Profit-Flat-EPS-Dips-Dividend-Declared/69830e04f5a3f0ebac99ba2c</guid><description>Tube Investments of India Limited announced its Q3 FY26 results, showcasing robust consolidated revenue growth of 20.5% YoY to Rs. 5,801 Cr. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) was flat at Rs. 279 Cr, down from Rs. 280 Cr in the prior year. Standalone PAT grew 17.4% to Rs. 189 Cr, but standalone basic EPS decreased to Rs. 8.57 from Rs. 9.65 YoY. The company declared an interim dividend of Rs. 2 per share. No forward-looking guidance or concall commentary was provided.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tube Investments Surges on Strong Q3 Growth, Declares ₹2 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tube-Investments-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Growth-Declares-2-Dividend/69830de2f5a3f0ebac99b990</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tube-Investments-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Growth-Declares-2-Dividend/69830de2f5a3f0ebac99b990</guid><description>Tube Investments of India Limited reported a strong financial performance for Q3 FY26. Consolidated revenue surged 20.55% YoY to ₹5,800.99 Cr, with PBT before exceptional items rising 17.62% to ₹501.67 Cr. Standalone revenue grew 12.67% YoY to ₹2,152.22 Cr, and PBT before exceptional items increased 26.47% to ₹268.08 Cr. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹2 per share and highlighted successful acquisitions and investments, though future guidance was not provided.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Aro Granite Q3 Revenue Plummets 51%, Net Loss Widens Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aro-Granite-Q3-Revenue-Plummets-51percent-Net-Loss-Widens-Sharply/69830714f5a3f0ebac999cf5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aro-Granite-Q3-Revenue-Plummets-51percent-Net-Loss-Widens-Sharply/69830714f5a3f0ebac999cf5</guid><description>Aro Granite Industries reported a severe financial downturn for Q3 FY26, with revenue from operations plummeting 51.2% year-on-year to ₹1,469.12 Lacs. The company also saw its net loss widen significantly to ₹297.43 Lacs from a marginal loss of ₹0.44 Lacs in the prior year. Basic EPS slipped to ₹(1.92) from ₹0.02. While the nine-month net loss reduced, the quarterly performance signals significant headwinds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:12:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69830714f5a3f0ebac999cf4_1770196375244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aptus Housing Finance Posts 26% PAT Growth, Eyes 24% AUM Jump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aptus-Housing-Finance-Posts-26percent-PAT-Growth-Eyes-24percent-AUM-Jump/69830d69f5a3f0ebac99b807</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aptus-Housing-Finance-Posts-26percent-PAT-Growth-Eyes-24percent-AUM-Jump/69830d69f5a3f0ebac99b807</guid><description>Aptus Value Housing Finance India Ltd. reported a strong Q3 FY26 with Profit After Tax (PAT) climbing 26% year-on-year to ₹239 crore. Assets Under Management (AUM) grew 21% YoY to ₹12,330 crore. The company is strategically shifting focus to higher-ticket loans and expanding its branch network to 335 locations, anticipating sustained AUM growth of 22-24%.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Bond Market Lag: Growth Goals Hinder by Structural Gaps</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Bond-Market-Lag-Growth-Goals-Hinder-by-Structural-Gaps/698306dcf5a3f0ebac999bd8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Bond-Market-Lag-Growth-Goals-Hinder-by-Structural-Gaps/698306dcf5a3f0ebac999bd8</guid><description>SEBI Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey is pushing for India's corporate bond market to lead economic growth, noting bank credit alone is insufficient. Despite a 7.8% average quarterly GDP growth, the corporate bond market remains underdeveloped at just 16% of GDP, far behind international peers. Key challenges include a narrow issuer base, low investor awareness compared to crypto, and poor secondary market liquidity, all hindering vital funding for infrastructure and green initiatives.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698306dcf5a3f0ebac999bd7_1770196259398.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tube Investments Posts Strong Q3 Growth, Declares ₹2 Interim Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tube-Investments-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Declares-2-Interim-Dividend/69830d09f5a3f0ebac99b676</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tube-Investments-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Declares-2-Interim-Dividend/69830d09f5a3f0ebac99b676</guid><description>Tube Investments of India Limited (TII) reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue surging 20.6% YoY to ₹5,801 Cr. Standalone revenue grew 12.7% to ₹2,152 Cr. Profit After Tax saw a 17.5% YoY increase standalone to ₹189 Cr. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹2 per share. Key segments like Engineering and Mobility demonstrated strong performance. No forward-looking guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Bond Market Lags Despite Trade Deal Optimism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Bond-Market-Lags-Despite-Trade-Deal-Optimism/69830cf5f5a3f0ebac99b5ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Bond-Market-Lags-Despite-Trade-Deal-Optimism/69830cf5f5a3f0ebac99b5ef</guid><description>Sebi Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey emphasized that while trade agreements like the one with the US reduce uncertainties and can spur capital formation, India's domestic bond market faces significant hurdles. Investor awareness for corporate bonds remains low at 10%, trailing even cryptocurrency awareness (15%). The market depth, measured as a percentage of GDP, lags behind key Asian peers like South Korea and Malaysia, despite recent regulatory efforts to democratize access and broaden the issuer base. Sebi maintains a status quo approach on derivatives, prioritizing stability over speculative fervor.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:10:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Andhra Petrochem Tanks on Q3 Loss Amid Plant Shutdown, VPA Dispute Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Andhra-Petrochem-Tanks-on-Q3-Loss-Amid-Plant-Shutdown-VPA-Dispute-Looms/69830661f5a3f0ebac9999a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Andhra-Petrochem-Tanks-on-Q3-Loss-Amid-Plant-Shutdown-VPA-Dispute-Looms/69830661f5a3f0ebac9999a8</guid><description>Andhra Petrochemicals Limited plunged into a net loss of ₹10.77 Cr in Q3 FY26, a sharp reversal from last year's profit, as revenue plummeted 45.87% to ₹67.39 Cr. The downturn was driven by a planned plant shutdown for maintenance and adverse market conditions. Operations have now resumed as of February 4, 2026, but a lingering land lease dispute with Visakhapatnam Port Authority adds significant uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:09:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69830661f5a3f0ebac9999a7_1770196138217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wonder Electricals Expands Beyond Fans, Fuels 30% Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Wonder-Electricals-Expands-Beyond-Fans-Fuels-30percent-Revenue-Growth/69830c7ef5a3f0ebac99b434</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Wonder-Electricals-Expands-Beyond-Fans-Fuels-30percent-Revenue-Growth/69830c7ef5a3f0ebac99b434</guid><description>Wonder Electricals Limited is strategically pivoting from its core fan manufacturing business to a diversified player in electrical appliances and industrial products. The company is entering new verticals like Electric Heaters and Ventilating Fans, supported by impressive financial growth from FY21 to FY25, with revenue and net profit growing at CAGRs of 30.8% and 39.6% respectively. This expansion, maintaining an 18.43% ROE, aims to position the company as a leader in India's evolving electrical solutions market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Geopolitics Fuels Energy Stocks; Value in Upstream?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitics-Fuels-Energy-Stocks-Value-in-Upstream/69830c12f5a3f0ebac99b34d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitics-Fuels-Energy-Stocks-Value-in-Upstream/69830c12f5a3f0ebac99b34d</guid><description>Escalating US-Iran tensions have driven crude oil prices to rally, propelling shares of Indian energy companies. Upstream players Oil India and ONGC have seen significant gains, hitting 52-week highs, outperforming some downstream oil marketing companies. Analysts highlight strong technicals, but current valuations warrant scrutiny amidst volatile geopolitical drivers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:06:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sebi Overhaul: Fit &amp; Proper Norms Shift Towards Fairness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Overhaul-Fit-and-Proper-Norms-Shift-Towards-Fairness/69830c06f5a3f0ebac99b2d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Overhaul-Fit-and-Proper-Norms-Shift-Towards-Fairness/69830c06f5a3f0ebac99b2d2</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) is proposing a substantial revision to its 'fit and proper person' criteria for market intermediaries. This strategic recalibration aims to mitigate compliance burdens by preventing automatic disqualifications arising solely from preliminary legal actions like FIRs or charge sheets. The move emphasizes procedural fairness, ensuring intermediaries have a right to be heard before being deemed unfit, and could offer relief to entities undergoing insolvency resolution, fostering a more predictable operating environment for India's financial sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Century Plyboards: Consolidated Profit Climbs 10.5%, Standalone Profit Drops 7.9%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Century-Plyboards-Consolidated-Profit-Climbs-105percent-Standalone-Profit-Drops-79percent/698305a4f5a3f0ebac99972d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Century-Plyboards-Consolidated-Profit-Climbs-105percent-Standalone-Profit-Drops-79percent/698305a4f5a3f0ebac99972d</guid><description>Century Plyboards (India) Ltd. reported mixed financial results for Q3 FY26. Consolidated revenue grew 18.38% YoY to ₹1,35,008.04 Lacs, and consolidated net profit rose 10.55% YoY to ₹6,504.64 Lacs. However, standalone revenue increased by a slower 14.25% YoY to ₹1,14,656.44 Lacs, and standalone net profit declined 7.94% YoY to ₹5,877.30 Lacs. An exceptional item of ₹717.89 Lacs (standalone) and ₹761.18 Lacs (consolidated) related to gratuity liability impacted profits. The company provided no future outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:05:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698305a4f5a3f0ebac99972c_1770195948103.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv: Provisions Mask Profit Surge, Analysts Upbeat</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finserv-Provisions-Mask-Profit-Surge-Analysts-Upbeat/69830baef5a3f0ebac99b135</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finserv-Provisions-Mask-Profit-Surge-Analysts-Upbeat/69830baef5a3f0ebac99b135</guid><description>Bajaj Finserv's Q3 FY26 saw total revenue climb 24% to ₹39,708.6 crore. Reported net profit remained stable at ₹2,230 crore due to ₹3,620 crore in loan loss provisions, including a ₹1,406 crore accelerated ECL charge. Excluding these, profit would have risen 32%. Bajaj Finance's AUM grew 22% to ₹4,84,477 crore, with stable asset quality. The company maintains robust capital buffers. Analysts largely favor the stock, citing underlying strength and prudent risk management.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:04:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Five Stocks Notch Major EPS Upgrades: What Drives Analyst Optimism?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Five-Stocks-Notch-Major-EPS-Upgrades-What-Drives-Analyst-Optimism/69830b8df5a3f0ebac99b043</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Five-Stocks-Notch-Major-EPS-Upgrades-What-Drives-Analyst-Optimism/69830b8df5a3f0ebac99b043</guid><description>A JM Financial report, citing Bloomberg data, reveals five Indian stocks have received substantial upgrades to their consensus earnings per share estimates. These upgrades, ranging from 9.2% to 19.7%, occurred over the year ending January 2026. The key questions now revolve around what fueled this optimism and how sustainable it will be for the market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Andhra Petro Hits ₹10.77 Cr Q3 Loss Amid Plant Shutdown, VPA Dispute</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Andhra-Petro-Hits-1077-Cr-Q3-Loss-Amid-Plant-Shutdown-VPA-Dispute/698304f9f5a3f0ebac999484</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Andhra-Petro-Hits-1077-Cr-Q3-Loss-Amid-Plant-Shutdown-VPA-Dispute/698304f9f5a3f0ebac999484</guid><description>Andhra Petrochemicals Limited reported a ₹10.77 Cr net loss for Q3 FY26, a sharp reversal from last year's profit, as revenue plunged 45.9% YoY to ₹67.39 Cr. Operations were disrupted by a prolonged plant shutdown for maintenance (Oct-Jan). The company faces ongoing challenges from adverse market conditions and a critical land lease dispute with Visakhapatnam Port Authority.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698304f9f5a3f0ebac999483_1770195746940.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indus Towers: Centrum Broking Maintains 'Buy' With Rs 523 Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Indus-Towers-Centrum-Broking-Maintains-Buy-With-Rs-523-Target/69830526f5a3f0ebac999548</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Indus-Towers-Centrum-Broking-Maintains-Buy-With-Rs-523-Target/69830526f5a3f0ebac999548</guid><description>Centrum Broking has reiterated its 'Buy' rating on Indus Towers Ltd., lifting the target price to ₹523. The brokerage cited improving revenue visibility, steady tenancy growth driven by data usage and 5G expansion as key factors. Strengthened balance sheets for Vodafone Idea Ltd. further enhance long-term earnings predictability, with core profitability improving despite optical margin pressures. Centrum projects a revenue CAGR of 9.3% over FY25-FY28E.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:03:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69830526f5a3f0ebac999547_1770195782270.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Sparks Strategic Shift, Budget Offers Stability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Strategic-Shift-Budget-Offers-Stability/69830b49f5a3f0ebac99af0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Strategic-Shift-Budget-Offers-Stability/69830b49f5a3f0ebac99af0a</guid><description>Bernstein retains a neutral stance and a Nifty target of 28,100 for the calendar year, emphasizing the strategic implications of the India-US trade deal over the recent Union Budget's near-term impact. The firm sees the trade pact as a catalyst for India's global supply chain integration and competitiveness, despite high market valuations. Key sectors like energy, electronics, and defense are poised for growth, while autos may see limited effects. The Union Budget is characterized as disciplined but neutral for immediate market upside.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:03:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BHEL Lands ₹1,500 Cr Hindalco Order, Stock Edges Up Modestly</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BHEL-Lands-1500-Cr-Hindalco-Order-Stock-Edges-Up-Modestly/69830b30f5a3f0ebac99ae8b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BHEL-Lands-1500-Cr-Hindalco-Order-Stock-Edges-Up-Modestly/69830b30f5a3f0ebac99ae8b</guid><description>Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited (BHEL) has secured a significant order valued between ₹1,200 crore and ₹1,500 crore from Hindalco Industries for the Aditya Expansion Project Phase II in Odisha. The contract entails a 2 × 150 MW Boiler Turbine Generator (BTG) package, with commissioning slated for 35-37 months post-contract. While the order book boost is substantial, BHEL shares saw a modest 0.95% increase, indicating investor focus on long-term revenue realization and profitability metrics in a competitive market.

This award aligns with Hindalco's strategic expansion in the high-growth aluminium sector, particularly in areas supporting India's electric vehicle and advanced manufacturing initiatives. The project scope highlights BHEL's comprehensive capabilities in supplying critical power generation equipment for industrial expansion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:02:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Emcure Pharma's Q3 Profit Surges 48%, Boosted by International Sales &amp; New Weight Loss Drug</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Emcure-Pharmas-Q3-Profit-Surges-48percent-Boosted-by-International-Sales-and-New-Weight-Loss-Drug/69830495f5a3f0ebac9992a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Emcure-Pharmas-Q3-Profit-Surges-48percent-Boosted-by-International-Sales-and-New-Weight-Loss-Drug/69830495f5a3f0ebac9992a0</guid><description>Emcure Pharmaceuticals has announced strong Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue growing 20.4% year-over-year to ₹2,363 Cr and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 48.2% to ₹231 Cr. The company reported improved EBITDA margins and significant growth in both domestic and international segments. Key strategic moves include the launch of Poviztra®, a semaglutide injection for weight management in partnership with Novo Nordisk, and the complete acquisition of Zuventus Healthcare Ltd. The results include an exceptional expense of ₹38 Cr related to new labour code changes, impacting QoQ PAT.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69830495f5a3f0ebac99929f_1770195636071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emcure Pharma Surges on 48% PAT Growth, Novo Nordisk Pact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Emcure-Pharma-Surges-on-48percent-PAT-Growth-Novo-Nordisk-Pact/69830432f5a3f0ebac99903c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Emcure-Pharma-Surges-on-48percent-PAT-Growth-Novo-Nordisk-Pact/69830432f5a3f0ebac99903c</guid><description>Emcure Pharmaceuticals reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue climbing 20.4% YoY to ₹2,363 Cr and Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 48.2% to ₹231 Cr. EBITDA margins expanded to 19.47% from 18.44%. The company also highlighted its strategic entry into the obesity segment via a Novo Nordisk partnership, launching Poviztra®, and the acquisition of Zuventus Healthcare, making it a wholly owned subsidiary. Management aims to further boost profitability and product portfolio.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69830432f5a3f0ebac99903b_1770195375467.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ajanta Pharma: Strategic Bets Fuel Diversified Growth Amidst Sector Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ajanta-Pharma-Strategic-Bets-Fuel-Diversified-Growth-Amidst-Sector-Valuation/698309adf5a3f0ebac99a912</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ajanta-Pharma-Strategic-Bets-Fuel-Diversified-Growth-Amidst-Sector-Valuation/698309adf5a3f0ebac99a912</guid><description>Ajanta Pharma reported a robust Q3FY26 with EBITDA growing 19% year-on-year to Rs 3.8 billion, exceeding expectations. Higher revenues from domestic and U.S. markets, coupled with a strategic in-licensing agreement with Biocon for semaglutide across Rest of World markets, underscore the company's diversified growth trajectory. Ajanta's established presence in branded generics, contributing 70% to 9MFY26 revenue, and strong annual free cash flow of Rs 8-10 billion support sustained investments and potential inorganic opportunities, reinforcing medium-term growth visibility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IDBI Bank Surges on Disinvestment Hopes, Analysts Cautious on Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDBI-Bank-Surges-on-Disinvestment-Hopes-Analysts-Cautious-on-Valuation/698303a7f5a3f0ebac998db8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDBI-Bank-Surges-on-Disinvestment-Hopes-Analysts-Cautious-on-Valuation/698303a7f5a3f0ebac998db8</guid><description>IDBI Bank shares surged 10% on February 4, 2026, driven by heavy trading volumes amidst a subdued market. The rally coincides with the final stages of the strategic disinvestment process by the Government of India and LIC. While the bank's improving fundamentals and a 12% year-over-year business growth are positive, a premium valuation and the complexities of the sale process present hurdles. The broader PSU banking sector is undergoing consolidation and reform discussions, adding a layer of market sentiment to IDBI's privatization trajectory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:56:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698303a7f5a3f0ebac998db7_1770195255710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>