<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:57:22 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Kwality Pharma Revenue Surges 46%, Margins Expand on Global Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Kwality-Pharma-Revenue-Surges-46percent-Margins-Expand-on-Global-Demand/698d7705ba46a4833be1383e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Kwality-Pharma-Revenue-Surges-46percent-Margins-Expand-on-Global-Demand/698d7705ba46a4833be1383e</guid><description>Kwality Pharmaceuticals Ltd. announced a strong Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue jumping 46% YoY to ₹123 crore and PAT surging 78% YoY to ₹16 crore. EBITDA margins improved to 24.3% driven by operational leverage and cost efficiencies. The company reaffirms its FY26 revenue target of ₹500 crore and projects ₹650 crore for FY27, aiming for ₹1,000-1,100 crore by FY29. Expansions are underway, funded by internal accruals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:45:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d7705ba46a4833be1383d_1770878971885.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SJVN Stock Surges on Q3 Profit Jump; Execution Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/SJVN-Stock-Surges-on-Q3-Profit-Jump-Execution-Risks-Loom/698d7620ba46a4833be132e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/SJVN-Stock-Surges-on-Q3-Profit-Jump-Execution-Risks-Loom/698d7620ba46a4833be132e4</guid><description>SJVN's stock climbed over 5% following robust Q3 FY26 results, which showed a 51% profit surge and 61% revenue jump year-over-year. The company also announced an interim dividend and plans to raise ₹1,000 crore. However, these positive developments are tempered by analyst concerns regarding slower project execution and the implications of increased leverage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Park Medi World Surges to 52-Week High Amid Expansion Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Park-Medi-World-Surges-to-52-Week-High-Amid-Expansion-Push/698d75daba46a4833be132c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Park-Medi-World-Surges-to-52-Week-High-Amid-Expansion-Push/698d75daba46a4833be132c9</guid><description>Park Medi World Ltd's stock price climbed 5.5% to a fresh 52-week high of ₹179.55 on Thursday, accompanied by a surge in trading volume. This advance follows the company's Rs 245 crore acquisition of the 360-bed KP Institute of Medical Sciences (KPIMS) in Agra, bolstering its Uttar Pradesh footprint. The hospital chain reported robust Q3 FY26 financial performance, with net sales up 18% to Rs 410 crore and net profit rising 16% to Rs 52.80 crore year-on-year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:40:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d75daba46a4833be132c8_1770878777230.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FMCG Stocks Tumble 6% on Slowing Demand, ITC Leads Slide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Stocks-Tumble-6percent-on-Slowing-Demand-ITC-Leads-Slide/698d75d7ba46a4833be132c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Stocks-Tumble-6percent-on-Slowing-Demand-ITC-Leads-Slide/698d75d7ba46a4833be132c1</guid><description>The Nifty FMCG index has fallen nearly 6% in 2026, lagging the broader market. This downturn is largely fueled by a significant 20% drop in ITC shares, with other key players like Varun Beverages and Patanjali Foods also experiencing declines. Analysts point to slowing consumption patterns and tepid volume growth as primary concerns for the sector, though some remain selectively bullish on specific stocks with clear earnings visibility. Hindustan Unilever posted a mixed quarterly result.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sector Surge Faces Scrutiny: Hotels, Metals, Autos Under Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Sector-Surge-Faces-Scrutiny-Hotels-Metals-Autos-Under-Pressure/698d758cba46a4833be1328e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Sector-Surge-Faces-Scrutiny-Hotels-Metals-Autos-Under-Pressure/698d758cba46a4833be1328e</guid><description>Market optimism surrounding hospitality, metals, and automotive sectors is tempered by underlying concerns. While hospitality firms like Indian Hotels and Lemon Tree benefit from strong demand, rising costs and valuations are key watchpoints. Hindalco Industries faces negative analyst sentiment and sector volatility. Mahindra &amp; Mahindra and Eicher Motors navigate EV transitions amidst divided analyst opinions, while Black Box's growth narrative faces scrutiny over revenue trends.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kwality Pharma Surges 46% YoY on Robust Q3 Earnings &amp; Strong Growth Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Kwality-Pharma-Surges-46percent-YoY-on-Robust-Q3-Earnings-and-Strong-Growth-Outlook/698d7576ba46a4833be13284</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Kwality-Pharma-Surges-46percent-YoY-on-Robust-Q3-Earnings-and-Strong-Growth-Outlook/698d7576ba46a4833be13284</guid><description>Kwality Pharmaceuticals Ltd. reported stellar Q3 FY26 results with consolidated revenue jumping 46.24% YoY to ₹123.44 Cr and PAT surging 87.46% to ₹16.01 Cr. EBITDA climbed 66.67% to ₹30 Cr, with margins expanding. Nine-month performance also showed strong YoY growth. Management reaffirms FY26 revenue target of ₹500 Cr and projects ₹650 Cr for FY27, aiming for ₹1,000-₹1,100 Cr by FY29, driven by global expansion and R&amp;D.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Seafood Stocks Rally: Trade Deal Boosts Avanti, Apex Sees Turnaround</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Seafood-Stocks-Rally-Trade-Deal-Boosts-Avanti-Apex-Sees-Turnaround/698d7553ba46a4833be13279</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Seafood-Stocks-Rally-Trade-Deal-Boosts-Avanti-Apex-Sees-Turnaround/698d7553ba46a4833be13279</guid><description>Avanti Feeds and Apex Frozen Foods experienced significant stock price rallies, hitting multi-year highs following robust third-quarter fiscal year 2026 earnings reports. The optimism is further amplified by a recent India-United States trade agreement that drastically reduces import tariffs. While Avanti Feeds benefits from its substantial US export exposure and margin expansion, Apex Frozen Foods' turnaround is underpinned by cost efficiencies. Despite the positive catalysts, investor scrutiny is warranted regarding Avanti Feeds' elevated valuation and Apex's historical performance metrics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Court Slams RERA; Real Estate Faces Regulatory Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Supreme-Court-Slams-RERA-Real-Estate-Faces-Regulatory-Test/698d7392ba46a4833be12f9d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Supreme-Court-Slams-RERA-Real-Estate-Faces-Regulatory-Test/698d7392ba46a4833be12f9d</guid><description>The Supreme Court has sharply criticized India's Real Estate Regulatory Authorities (RERA), questioning their effectiveness and suggesting potential abolition. This judicial review occurs as the Indian real estate market anticipates disciplined growth in 2026, with a focus on premium housing and increasing professionalism. The apex court's stance adds a layer of regulatory uncertainty to a sector otherwise showing resilience and strategic evolution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HUL Exits Wellbeing Nutrition for ₹307 Cr, Cashing In On Wellness Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Exits-Wellbeing-Nutrition-for-307-Cr-Cashing-In-On-Wellness-Boom/698d7307ba46a4833be12dcb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Exits-Wellbeing-Nutrition-for-307-Cr-Cashing-In-On-Wellness-Boom/698d7307ba46a4833be12dcb</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever (HUL) has divested its 19.8% stake in wellness supplement brand Wellbeing Nutrition for ₹307 crore to USV Pharma. This profitable exit, a more than fourfold return on its 2022 investment, underscores HUL's strategic approach to scaling and monetizing early-stage consumer health ventures. The deal values Wellbeing Nutrition at approximately ₹1,600 crore, a significant jump despite the company remaining loss-making, reflecting strong investor appetite for India's rapidly expanding nutraceutical market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bondada Engineering Partners for Green Data Centers in India, Boosting Digital Infra</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bondada-Engineering-Partners-for-Green-Data-Centers-in-India-Boosting-Digital-Infra/698d727cba46a4833be12d19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bondada-Engineering-Partners-for-Green-Data-Centers-in-India-Boosting-Digital-Infra/698d727cba46a4833be12d19</guid><description>Bondada Engineering Limited (BEL) has inked a strategic Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) with Dubai-based Bryanston Renewables FZCO to jointly develop green-powered data centres in India and select international markets. This collaboration leverages BEL's expertise in infrastructure, solar energy, and data centre MEP services, aligning with India's push for digital economy growth and sustainable energy solutions, as reinforced by Union Budget 2026 initiatives.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Muthoot Microfin Eyes ₹2000 Cr Capital Infusion Via NCDs for Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Microfin-Eyes-2000-Cr-Capital-Infusion-Via-NCDs-for-Growth/698d721eba46a4833be12c64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Microfin-Eyes-2000-Cr-Capital-Infusion-Via-NCDs-for-Growth/698d721eba46a4833be12c64</guid><description>Muthoot Microfin Limited is gearing up to raise ₹2000 crore through Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) via private placement, seeking shareholder approval through remote e-voting from February 13 to March 14, 2026. The funds will bolster its on-lending activities, refinance debt, strengthen working capital, and support general corporate needs, aligning with its growth strategy. This move falls within its existing ₹15,000 crore borrowing limit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Aavas Financiers Posts 16% Profit Surge, Eyes 25% Disbursement Growth in FY27</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Aavas-Financiers-Posts-16percent-Profit-Surge-Eyes-25percent-Disbursement-Growth-in-FY27/698d7113ba46a4833be12b83</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Aavas-Financiers-Posts-16percent-Profit-Surge-Eyes-25percent-Disbursement-Growth-in-FY27/698d7113ba46a4833be12b83</guid><description>Aavas Financiers reported a 16% year-on-year net profit increase to Rs 1.70 billion in Q3 FY26, supported by a robust 17% growth in Net Interest Income and expanding Net Interest Margins to 8.01%. Assets Under Management grew 15% to Rs 222 billion, with the balance sheet exceeding Rs 20,000 crore. The company has set an optimistic outlook for FY27, targeting over 25% growth in disbursements and 17-18% loan book growth, driven by branch expansion and digital strategies, while maintaining strong asset quality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:20:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Divi's Lab Q3: Custom Synthesis Fuels Growth, Peptide Power Beckons</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Divis-Lab-Q3-Custom-Synthesis-Fuels-Growth-Peptide-Power-Beckons/698d6fc6ba46a4833be125df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Divis-Lab-Q3-Custom-Synthesis-Fuels-Growth-Peptide-Power-Beckons/698d6fc6ba46a4833be125df</guid><description>Divi's Laboratories posted a steady Q3 FY26, with custom synthesis driving 12% top-line growth. A one-time Rs 74 crore labour code charge impacted net profit. Operating margins remained strong at 34.2% due to a better segmental mix. The company anticipates new custom synthesis projects commercializing in H2 CY27 and sees broadening peptide applications beyond GLP-1 drugs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lincoln Pharma Surges on Strong Q3 Profit Growth, Global Expansion Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Lincoln-Pharma-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-Growth-Global-Expansion-Drive/698d6f83ba46a4833be1253b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Lincoln-Pharma-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-Growth-Global-Expansion-Drive/698d6f83ba46a4833be1253b</guid><description>Lincoln Pharmaceuticals delivered robust Q3 FY26 results, with net profit soaring 37.7% year-over-year to ₹28.60 crore on 13.5% revenue growth. For the nine months, profit grew 7.8% to ₹76.26 crore. The company maintained a debt-free status and highlighted strong performance in key therapeutic areas. Management reiterated a target of ₹1,000 crore revenue within three years, backed by regulatory approvals for global market expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:13:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d6f83ba46a4833be1253a_1770877085528.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HUL Profit Plunge Masks Margin Squeeze, Stock Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Profit-Plunge-Masks-Margin-Squeeze-Stock-Dips/698d6f6cba46a4833be12534</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Profit-Plunge-Masks-Margin-Squeeze-Stock-Dips/698d6f6cba46a4833be12534</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever's Q3FY26 net profit fell 30% to ₹2,118 crore, overshadowing a 5.6% revenue increase to ₹16,441 crore. While reported profit after tax soared due to a business demerger, EBITDA margins compressed to 23.3%, signalling underlying operational pressures. The company's stock experienced a sell-off, and a significant acquisition of the remaining stake in Zywie for ₹824 crore adds to cost considerations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apollo Hospitals Surges Post-Q3, Demerger &amp; Expansion Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Apollo-Hospitals-Surges-Post-Q3-Demerger-and-Expansion-Risks-Loom/698d6f4bba46a4833be12526</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Apollo-Hospitals-Surges-Post-Q3-Demerger-and-Expansion-Risks-Loom/698d6f4bba46a4833be12526</guid><description>Apollo Hospitals delivered a robust Q3 FY26 with 17% revenue growth and 35% PAT increase, driven by all segments. The company plans to demerge its pharmacy and digital health businesses by Q4FY27 and is on track with ambitious bed capacity expansion. Despite positive results and reasonable valuation, scrutiny will focus on Apollo 24/7's delayed breakeven, demerger execution risks, and competitive pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Artemis Medicare Target: Brokerage Sees 45% Upside</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Artemis-Medicare-Target-Brokerage-Sees-45percent-Upside/698d6eeaba46a4833be124eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Artemis-Medicare-Target-Brokerage-Sees-45percent-Upside/698d6eeaba46a4833be124eb</guid><description>Artemis Medicare Services Ltd. shares surged Thursday following Antique Stock Broking's initiation of coverage with a 'Buy' rating and a ₹340 price target, signaling a potential 45% upside. The bullish stance is driven by expectations of increasing volumes and improved profitability, fueled by an ambitious plan to nearly double capacity by adding 1,300 beds over the next three to four years. The brokerage forecasts significant margin expansion and substantial revenue and profit growth through FY28, positioning Artemis Medicare for accelerated performance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Britannia: Q3 Margin Surge Masks Competitive Pricing Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannia-Q3-Margin-Surge-Masks-Competitive-Pricing-Risks/698d6ec4ba46a4833be123fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannia-Q3-Margin-Surge-Masks-Competitive-Pricing-Risks/698d6ec4ba46a4833be123fb</guid><description>Britannia Industries reported a robust Q3FY26, marked by a 9.5% YoY revenue increase to ₹4,880 crore, driven by 12% sales growth in November-December and significant margin expansion. Gross margin climbed 450 basis points to 43.3%, and Ebitda margin rose 230 basis points to 20.7%. Adjusted net profit surged 23% YoY to ₹620 crore. Despite tepid market sentiment, the stock gained 1.3% intraday. This performance positions Britannia to navigate evolving competitive pricing dynamics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India AIFs Shift to Realization as Domestic Capital Dominates</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-AIFs-Shift-to-Realization-as-Domestic-Capital-Dominates/698d6e2dba46a4833be122a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-AIFs-Shift-to-Realization-as-Domestic-Capital-Dominates/698d6e2dba46a4833be122a0</guid><description>India's Alternative Investment Funds (AIFs) are witnessing a significant shift, driven by a substantial increase in domestic capital contributions, which now represent over 55% of Category I and II AIF capital. This trend is reducing the industry's dependence on foreign investment. The market's maturation is evident as focus moves from capital raising to actual cash realisations, supported by robust growth in secondary market transactions. Cumulative AIF commitments have expanded rapidly, with top-quartile funds demonstrating strong returns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:07:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Zydus Secures Mirabegron Market Access with $120M Payout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Secures-Mirabegron-Market-Access-with-120M-Payout/698d6d53ba46a4833be12270</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Secures-Mirabegron-Market-Access-with-120M-Payout/698d6d53ba46a4833be12270</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences will pay Astellas Pharma $120 million to settle a patent dispute over the bladder drug Mirabegron. The agreement includes ongoing licensing fees for U.S. sales of Zydus's generic version until September 2027, effectively concluding litigation and enabling continued market access. Shares rose 2.30% on the news. This follows a similar $90 million settlement by competitor Lupin Ltd., potentially creating a temporary window of reduced competition for both firms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:04:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Near Record Highs: Fed Data Clashes With Central Bank Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Near-Record-Highs-Fed-Data-Clashes-With-Central-Bank-Demand/698d6c16ba46a4833be11eb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Near-Record-Highs-Fed-Data-Clashes-With-Central-Bank-Demand/698d6c16ba46a4833be11eb2</guid><description>Indian gold prices traded near record highs on February 12, 2026. Robust US jobs data tempered expectations for imminent Federal Reserve rate cuts, creating headwinds. However, sustained central bank purchases and geopolitical safe-haven demand continue to provide strong underlying support, keeping prices elevated. Meanwhile, Indian consumers face a persistent premium compared to international benchmarks like Dubai.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Agri Exports Surge: Zero Tariffs Boost Key Sectors in US Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-Agri-Exports-Surge-Zero-Tariffs-Boost-Key-Sectors-in-US-Market/698d6be1ba46a4833be11dc5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-Agri-Exports-Surge-Zero-Tariffs-Boost-Key-Sectors-in-US-Market/698d6be1ba46a4833be11dc5</guid><description>An SBI report indicates India's agricultural exports to the United States will see a substantial increase, with 75% of relevant commodities now entering the US duty-free. This development is projected to bolster India's existing $1.3 billion agricultural trade surplus. Key beneficiaries include rice, spices, tea, coffee, and fisheries, aiming to enhance farmer incomes and export volumes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HUL: Profit Surge Hides Sluggish Core Growth, Wellness Bet</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Profit-Surge-Hides-Sluggish-Core-Growth-Wellness-Bet/698d6b76ba46a4833be11d93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Profit-Surge-Hides-Sluggish-Core-Growth-Wellness-Bet/698d6b76ba46a4833be11d93</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever (HUL) reported a Q3 FY26 net profit leap to ₹6,607 crore, more than doubling year-on-year. However, this figure was heavily influenced by a one-off gain related to the ice cream business demerger. Excluding exceptional items, core profit grew a mere 1% to ₹2,652 crore, despite a 5.7% revenue increase driven by 4% volume growth. The company also finalized the acquisition of the remaining 49% in health and wellness player Zywie for ₹824 crore, signaling a strategic push into higher-growth categories.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Smartworks Coworking Sees Strong Q3: Revenue Jumps 34%, Posts First Profit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Smartworks-Coworking-Sees-Strong-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-34percent-Posts-First-Profit/698d6b4cba46a4833be11cf8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Smartworks-Coworking-Sees-Strong-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-34percent-Posts-First-Profit/698d6b4cba46a4833be11cf8</guid><description>Smartworks Coworking reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with normalized revenue reaching ₹472 Cr, a 34% year-over-year increase. The company achieved its first-ever positive Ind AS PAT of ₹1 Cr, alongside an 86% surge in EBITDA to ₹85 Cr and improved EBITDA margins to 17.9%. Operating cash flow grew 148% YoY to ₹101 Cr. With 15.3 Million sq ft under management and 84% occupancy, Smartworks is strategically positioned to capitalize on the growing demand for managed workspaces in India.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IREDA Eyes ₹2,994 Cr Capital Raise Via QIP for Green Energy Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Eyes-2994-Cr-Capital-Raise-Via-QIP-for-Green-Energy-Push/698d6a58ba46a4833be119ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Eyes-2994-Cr-Capital-Raise-Via-QIP-for-Green-Energy-Push/698d6a58ba46a4833be119ee</guid><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency (IREDA) has announced a postal ballot notice to its shareholders for approval to raise up to ₹2,994 Crore through a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP). This significant capital infusion is slated to augment the company's base for onward lending and meet future growth requirements in the renewable energy sector. Eligible shareholders can cast their votes remotely from February 13 to March 14, 2026, with potential dilution for the President of India capped at 3.76%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Titan Navigates Gold Volatility with Strategic Edge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Navigates-Gold-Volatility-with-Strategic-Edge/698d6a55ba46a4833be119be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Navigates-Gold-Volatility-with-Strategic-Edge/698d6a55ba46a4833be119be</guid><description>Titan Company Limited posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with overall revenues climbing 43% year-on-year, led by its jewellery division's 46% surge. Despite significant gold price increases, the company maintained EBITDA margins through strategic adjustments and product mix innovation. This performance highlights Titan's resilience and market leadership amidst industry-wide consolidation and regulatory shifts favoring organized players.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kernex Audit Flags ₹12.7 Cr Impairment Omission Amid Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kernex-Audit-Flags-127-Cr-Impairment-Omission-Amid-Revenue-Surge/698d6a4fba46a4833be119b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kernex-Audit-Flags-127-Cr-Impairment-Omission-Amid-Revenue-Surge/698d6a4fba46a4833be119b6</guid><description>Kernex Microsystems (India) Limited posted a dramatic 97.23% YoY revenue jump to ₹72.6 Cr for Q3 FY26. However, consolidated PAT declined 15.09% YoY to ₹6.1 Cr, with EPS falling to ₹3.61. A significant concern is the auditor's qualified opinion on standalone financials, noting a failure to recognize a ₹12.76 Cr impairment loss on a subsidiary investment, which overstated standalone profit. Auditors also highlighted long-standing receivables and other provisions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:51:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d6a4fba46a4833be119b5_1770875786769.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sudeep Pharma Posts 52% Revenue Surge, Eyes Battery Materials Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Sudeep-Pharma-Posts-52percent-Revenue-Surge-Eyes-Battery-Materials-Boom/698d693dba46a4833be1158b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Sudeep-Pharma-Posts-52percent-Revenue-Surge-Eyes-Battery-Materials-Boom/698d693dba46a4833be1158b</guid><description>Sudeep Pharma Limited reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with total income jumping 52% YoY to ₹179.2 crore and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 66% YoY to ₹47.7 crore. The company is aggressively expanding into specialty ingredients, battery-grade iron phosphate through its Sudeep Advanced Materials (SAM) division, and liposomal chemistry. Significant capacity expansions at Nandesari and Dahej are underway to fuel future growth, with management expressing confidence in sustaining momentum and margin expansion, particularly from the US market in FY27.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Almondz Global Surges 56% Revenue on Green Fuel, Advisory Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Almondz-Global-Surges-56percent-Revenue-on-Green-Fuel-Advisory-Growth/698d6939ba46a4833be11584</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Almondz-Global-Surges-56percent-Revenue-on-Green-Fuel-Advisory-Growth/698d6939ba46a4833be11584</guid><description>Almondz Global Securities Limited reported a strong 55.9% YoY jump in consolidated revenue to ₹52.3 crore and a 405.9% surge in profit to ₹12.9 crore for Q3 FY26. This stellar performance was propelled by its Green Fuel Business (JV) which saw revenue grow 13.4% YoY to ₹206.1 crore and profit by 1082.2% to ₹13.95 crore. The Infrastructure Advisory business also contributed with a 25.3% QoQ revenue increase to ₹31.5 crore and 20% growth outlook. However, the Financial Services segment reported a loss of ₹2.69 crore, primarily due to an ₹82.71 crore Mark-to-Market (MTM) loss on equity holdings. The company anticipates Q4 performance improvement with market sentiment recovery. A revised composite scheme of arrangement is under review by stock exchanges' legal departments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Pre-Open Rupee Push Signals New FX Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Pre-Open-Rupee-Push-Signals-New-FX-Strategy/698d68caba46a4833be114ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Pre-Open-Rupee-Push-Signals-New-FX-Strategy/698d68caba46a4833be114ed</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India executed a substantial dollar sale ahead of Thursday's market opening, a move that aggressively bolstered the Indian rupee and caught traders by surprise. The intervention, described as indiscriminate, saw the rupee surge from its previous close. This aggressive action deviates from the RBI's stated policy of merely curbing volatility, hinting at a potential preference for managing specific currency levels following recent trade deal optimism and underlying import pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indogulf Cropsciences Posts Robust Q3 Growth, Eyes Global Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Indogulf-Cropsciences-Posts-Robust-Q3-Growth-Eyes-Global-Markets/698d68a4ba46a4833be114dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Indogulf-Cropsciences-Posts-Robust-Q3-Growth-Eyes-Global-Markets/698d68a4ba46a4833be114dd</guid><description>Indogulf Cropsciences reported a strong Q3 FY26 with revenue jumping 17.0% YoY to INR 1,161 million and EBITDA up 16.4%. Despite challenging conditions, PBT surged 60.2%. Nine-month performance also showed robust growth with revenue up 19.3% and PAT up 31.1%. The company expanded into Venezuela and Taiwan and plans capacity upgrades, aiming for sustained product launches.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GIFT City Surges as India's ECB Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/GIFT-City-Surges-as-Indias-ECB-Hub/698d683dba46a4833be11440</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/GIFT-City-Surges-as-Indias-ECB-Hub/698d683dba46a4833be11440</guid><description>India's GIFT City has become the preferred channel for External Commercial Borrowings (ECBs), with over two-thirds of funds raised in the current financial year routed through its International Financial Services Centre (IFSC). Between April and December 2025, $18 billion out of a total $27.5 billion in ECBs were processed via GIFT-IFSC, a marked increase from previous periods. This surge is attributed to competitive financing costs, operational efficiencies, and enhanced regulatory and tax frameworks, positioning GIFT City as a strategic financial gateway. The Union Budget 2026 further cemented its appeal by extending tax holidays to 20 years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HUL: Volume Rises, but Revenue &amp; Profit Lag; Shares Dip 2%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/HUL-Volume-Rises-but-Revenue-and-Profit-Lag-Shares-Dip-2percent/698d673eba46a4833be11265</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/HUL-Volume-Rises-but-Revenue-and-Profit-Lag-Shares-Dip-2percent/698d673eba46a4833be11265</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever Ltd. reported a mixed December quarter. Underlying volume growth hit 4%, exceeding forecasts. However, standalone revenue registered a modest 2.6% increase to ₹15,805 crore, falling slightly short of market estimates. Net profit declined 13.7% year-on-year to ₹2,590 crore, impacted by portfolio transformation expenses, while EBITDA margins compressed. The market responded negatively, pushing HUL shares down 2%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalyani Forge Q3 FY26: Record EBITDA Margin Soars to 15.7% Despite Revenue Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kalyani-Forge-Q3-FY26-Record-EBITDA-Margin-Soars-to-157percent-Despite-Revenue-Dip/698d66c3ba46a4833be1122e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kalyani-Forge-Q3-FY26-Record-EBITDA-Margin-Soars-to-157percent-Despite-Revenue-Dip/698d66c3ba46a4833be1122e</guid><description>Kalyani Forge Limited reported a record EBITDA margin of 15.7% in Q3 FY26, a significant jump from 11.5% YoY, driven by strategic exits from low-margin businesses and enhanced cost discipline. Revenue saw a slight decrease to ₹58.22 Cr from ₹59.37 Cr. The company posted a net loss of ₹(0.12) Cr due to a non-cash deferred tax adjustment. Key growth drivers include the scaling of the Europe transmission program and the ramp-up of its xEV driveline business.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rupee Gains Mask IT Stock Plunge Amid Trade Deal Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Gains-Mask-IT-Stock-Plunge-Amid-Trade-Deal-Scrutiny/698d64dcba46a4833be105da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Gains-Mask-IT-Stock-Plunge-Amid-Trade-Deal-Scrutiny/698d64dcba46a4833be105da</guid><description>The Indian rupee strengthened by 38 paise to 90.40 against the US dollar on Thursday, supported by modest foreign fund inflows and suspected RBI intervention. However, domestic equity markets succumbed to selling pressure, with IT stocks leading the decline. The BSE Sensex fell 0.50% and the NSE Nifty dropped 0.47%, as markets digested fresh details of the India-US trade agreement, sparking renewed scrutiny and caution among participants. Rising crude oil prices also contributed to a subdued investor sentiment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sebi's Tech Gambit: India Markets Forge Sophistication Amid AI Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebis-Tech-Gambit-India-Markets-Forge-Sophistication-Amid-AI-Risks/698d646dba46a4833be105cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebis-Tech-Gambit-India-Markets-Forge-Sophistication-Amid-AI-Risks/698d646dba46a4833be105cd</guid><description>India's securities market is shifting from scale to sophistication, marked by a tenfold increase in market capitalization and a surge in investor participation. Sebi Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey highlighted the dual challenge: harnessing technology like AI for oversight and innovation, while managing emergent risks such as algorithmic feedback loops and data bias. Sebi is actively promoting data accessibility and regulatory technology adoption, positioning India for resilient market growth despite premium valuations and global economic shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Force Motors Surges 123% in PAT Growth on Strong Sales</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Force-Motors-Surges-123percent-in-PAT-Growth-on-Strong-Sales/698d6415ba46a4833be105ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Force-Motors-Surges-123percent-in-PAT-Growth-on-Strong-Sales/698d6415ba46a4833be105ad</guid><description>Force Motors Limited posted stellar Q3 FY26 results, with Profit After Tax (PAT) before exceptional items surging 123% year-over-year to ₹328 Cr, driven by a 14% increase in sales to ₹2,110 Cr. Profit Before Tax (PBT) before exceptional items also grew significantly by 62% YoY to ₹245 Cr, with margins improving to 12% for PBT and 15% for PAT. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, sales rose 13.8% to ₹6,451 Cr, and PAT before exceptional items jumped 110.4% to ₹779 Cr. The company highlighted strategic projects like Project Digiforce and Project Lakshya, alongside ESG progress.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HUL PAT Surges 121% on Demerger Gains; Revenue Up 6%, Margins Slip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-PAT-Surges-121percent-on-Demerger-Gains-Revenue-Up-6percent-Margins-Slip/698d60c5ba46a4833be10103</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-PAT-Surges-121percent-on-Demerger-Gains-Revenue-Up-6percent-Margins-Slip/698d60c5ba46a4833be10103</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever (HUL) posted a 121% year-on-year jump in net profit to ₹6,603 crores, largely driven by exceptional gains from its Ice Cream demerger. Revenue grew 6% YoY to ₹16,235 crores, supported by 5% underlying sales growth. However, EBITDA margins contracted by 70 basis points to 23.3%. The company highlighted progress in strategic initiatives, including the acquisition of OZiva and a focus on volume-led growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Paint Stocks: Morgan Stanley Downgrade Versus Divergent Performance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Paint-Stocks-Morgan-Stanley-Downgrade-Versus-Divergent-Performance/698d6071ba46a4833be0ffe7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Paint-Stocks-Morgan-Stanley-Downgrade-Versus-Divergent-Performance/698d6071ba46a4833be0ffe7</guid><description>Morgan Stanley has initiated a multi-year de-rating for India's paint sector, downgrading Asian Paints, Berger Paints, and Kansai Nerolac to 'underweight'. The brokerage cited growth volatility, weakening competitive moats, and elevated valuations. Despite this broad bearish outlook, operational metrics reveal a more complex picture: Berger Paints achieved its highest gross margins in 15 quarters due to input cost moderation, while Asian Paints projects stable volume growth. Analyst sentiment also shows a divergence, indicating the sector's de-rating thesis might not fully capture individual company strengths or recovery potential.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:09:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d6071ba46a4833be0ffe6_1770873227677.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's US Trade Deal: Coal Exports Rise Amid Energy Transition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-US-Trade-Deal-Coal-Exports-Rise-Amid-Energy-Transition/698d606dba46a4833be0ffdf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-US-Trade-Deal-Coal-Exports-Rise-Amid-Energy-Transition/698d606dba46a4833be0ffdf</guid><description>A new trade framework between the United States and India promises a significant increase in U.S. coal exports, with India committing to purchase $500 billion in American products over five years, including substantial energy items. This agreement, hailed by U.S. President Trump, aims to bolster trade ties and energy interdependence. However, the deal unfolds against a complex global energy backdrop, where India's increasing reliance on coal for power generation faces pressures from its own ambitious renewable energy targets and global decarbonization efforts. The long-term sustainability of escalating coal shipments remains a key question for investors and policymakers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:09:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>