<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:57:20 +0000</pubDate><item><title>IndusInd Bank Launches Next-Gen UPI Platform; Boosts Scalability for Millions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Launches-Next-Gen-UPI-Platform-Boosts-Scalability-for-Millions/699e9ae904a25a58c853e149</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Launches-Next-Gen-UPI-Platform-Boosts-Scalability-for-Millions/699e9ae904a25a58c853e149</guid><description>IndusInd Bank has gone live with its Next-Gen UPI Processing Platform (UPI 6.0), developed with Mindgate Solutions. This 6th-generation upgrade promises sub-second transaction speeds, near-zero technical glitches, and enhanced disaster recovery for millions of customers, aligning with the bank's 'Digital 2.0' strategy. It marks a significant step in modernizing its digital infrastructure to handle India's booming real-time payments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:47:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e9ae904a25a58c853e148_1772002374760.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCLTech Named IDC Canada AI Services Leader Amid $14.5Bn Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTech-Named-IDC-Canada-AI-Services-Leader-Amid-145Bn-Revenue/699e991204a25a58c853df4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTech-Named-IDC-Canada-AI-Services-Leader-Amid-145Bn-Revenue/699e991204a25a58c853df4a</guid><description>HCLTech has been recognized as a "Leader" in the IDC MarketScape: Canadian AI Services 2025 Vendor Assessment. The report highlighted the company's client-centricity and ability to translate AI investments into practical, production-ready solutions. This leadership position underscores HCLTech's effectiveness in aligning advanced AI capabilities with Canadian enterprises' strategic priorities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs Warns: Market Correction Tops US Economic Risk List</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Goldman-Sachs-Warns-Market-Correction-Tops-US-Economic-Risk-List/699e984304a25a58c853dd16</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Goldman-Sachs-Warns-Market-Correction-Tops-US-Economic-Risk-List/699e984304a25a58c853dd16</guid><description>Goldman Sachs has flagged a stock market correction as the most significant near-term risk to the U.S. economy in 2026. The firm projects a potential 10% equity price drop could shave 0.5 percentage points off GDP growth through reduced consumer spending, driven by a wealth effect impacting higher-income households. This warning emerges amidst forecasts for moderate economic expansion, powered by tax cuts and AI investment, but also signals underlying fragilities that could be amplified by market volatility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Auto Components Rebound: Earnings Shift Signals Value Opportunity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Components-Rebound-Earnings-Shift-Signals-Value-Opportunity/699e984204a25a58c853dcff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Components-Rebound-Earnings-Shift-Signals-Value-Opportunity/699e984204a25a58c853dcff</guid><description>Auto component manufacturers with international footprints are showing an earnings revision cycle reversal, moving from sharp downgrades to upward adjustments. Jefferies identifies Bharat Forge, Samvardhana Motherson International, and Sona BLW Precision Forgings as key beneficiaries. While overall automotive original equipment manufacturers (OEMs) display stable earnings trends, a divergence exists, with certain players like Ashok Leyland and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra seeing positive estimate revisions, contrasting with Maruti Suzuki India and Hyundai Motor India, which face downward adjustments. This shift suggests potential market re-evaluation of the sector's recovery prospects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indus Infra Trust Secures CRISIL AAA/Stable Rating for ₹3000 Cr Bank Facilities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indus-Infra-Trust-Secures-CRISIL-AAAStable-Rating-for-3000-Cr-Bank-Facilities/699e983304a25a58c853dce5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indus-Infra-Trust-Secures-CRISIL-AAAStable-Rating-for-3000-Cr-Bank-Facilities/699e983304a25a58c853dce5</guid><description>Indus Infra Trust has been assigned a 'CRISIL AAA/Stable' rating for its ₹3000 crore long-term bank facilities, marking the highest level of creditworthiness. This signifies a strong capacity to meet financial obligations and could facilitate easier access to future financing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HSBC Swings Past Charges, Eyes Higher Returns Despite Dividend Cut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HSBC-Swings-Past-Charges-Eyes-Higher-Returns-Despite-Dividend-Cut/699e97ae04a25a58c853dbb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HSBC-Swings-Past-Charges-Eyes-Higher-Returns-Despite-Dividend-Cut/699e97ae04a25a58c853dbb2</guid><description>HSBC Holdings disclosed a 7% pretax profit decline for the year, impacted by $4.9 billion in one-off charges, including a $2.1 billion write-off tied to its Bank of Communications stake amidst China's property downturn. Despite this, the bank elevated its return on tangible equity (ROTE) target to '17% or better' through 2028, reflecting confidence in its ongoing business overhaul and a strategic pivot towards enhanced shareholder value. The bank's London-listed stock has shown robust performance, rising 50% in 2025 and an additional 10% year-to-date. This strategic recalibration, however, is accompanied by a reduced final dividend of 45 cents per share and estimated $600 million in restructuring costs for the Hang Seng Bank integration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dharti Proteins: Patel Acquires 85% Stake Via NCLT Resolution Plan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Dharti-Proteins-Patel-Acquires-85percent-Stake-Via-NCLT-Resolution-Plan/699e972c04a25a58c853da88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Dharti-Proteins-Patel-Acquires-85percent-Stake-Via-NCLT-Resolution-Plan/699e972c04a25a58c853da88</guid><description>Dharti Proteins Limited has undergone a significant ownership overhaul, with Jatinbhai Ramanbhai Patel and Persons Acting in Concert (PACs) acquiring 85% of the company's voting capital. This acquisition, representing 4,25,000 equity shares, is a direct outcome of an approved Resolution Plan sanctioned by the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT). The move marks a complete shift in control following the company's corporate insolvency resolution process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India E2W Surge: Japanese Brands Lag, Locals Consolidate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-E2W-Surge-Japanese-Brands-Lag-Locals-Consolidate/699e96bd04a25a58c853d98f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-E2W-Surge-Japanese-Brands-Lag-Locals-Consolidate/699e96bd04a25a58c853d98f</guid><description>India's electric two-wheeler (E2W) market surged 11% in 2025 to 1.28 million units, with Indian manufacturers TVS Motor and Bajaj Auto leading sales. Meanwhile, Japanese giants Honda and Suzuki report subdued performance: Honda halted Activa e:/QC1 production due to low sales and high inventory, while Suzuki's premium-priced e-Access saw muted uptake despite incentives. Yamaha is entering via partnership with River Mobility, focusing on the premium segment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Clean Max IPO Slumps as Tariffs, High Valuation Dampen Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Clean-Max-IPO-Slumps-as-Tariffs-High-Valuation-Dampen-Demand/699e96b504a25a58c853d978</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Clean-Max-IPO-Slumps-as-Tariffs-High-Valuation-Dampen-Demand/699e96b504a25a58c853d978</guid><description>Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions' Rs 3,100 crore IPO is experiencing sluggish subscription, particularly in the retail segment, on its final day. This is occurring amidst new US preliminary duties on Indian solar imports, which have already sent listed peers like Waaree Energies, Premier Energies, and Vikram Solar plunging. The IPO's high valuation, with a post-IPO P/E ratio of 324.28x, stands in stark contrast to its competitors, raising further investor caution despite recent profitability and a growing operational capacity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Antariksh Industries Seeks Shareholder Approval for Wide Sector Diversification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Antariksh-Industries-Seeks-Shareholder-Approval-for-Wide-Sector-Diversification/699e93e004a25a58c853d60a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Antariksh-Industries-Seeks-Shareholder-Approval-for-Wide-Sector-Diversification/699e93e004a25a58c853d60a</guid><description>Antariksh Industries Limited is set to initiate a significant strategic shift by seeking shareholder approval to alter its Memorandum of Association (MOA). The proposed changes are designed to broaden the company's operational scope and explore new growth avenues across diverse sectors such as real estate, infrastructure, IT services, and power generation. Shareholders will vote on this crucial resolution through a postal ballot and remote e-voting process scheduled from February 26 to March 27, 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e93e004a25a58c853d609_1772000366277.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Omnitech IPO: Premium Valuation Amidst Leverage &amp; Concentration Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Omnitech-IPO-Premium-Valuation-Amidst-Leverage-and-Concentration-Risks/699e936904a25a58c853d56b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Omnitech-IPO-Premium-Valuation-Amidst-Leverage-and-Concentration-Risks/699e936904a25a58c853d56b</guid><description>Omnitech Engineering Ltd.'s Rs 583 crore IPO is priced at a P/E of approximately 50.5x annualized FY26 earnings, a premium that investors must scrutinize against substantial risks. The company's high debt-to-equity ratio of 1.60x and significant revenue reliance on its top five customers present notable financial and operational vulnerabilities. While the IPO aims to fuel expansion and debt reduction, a thorough risk assessment is crucial for potential investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:15:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e936904a25a58c853d56a_1772000993769.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Chip Deal Sparks Rally; China Trade Tensions Simmer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Chip-Deal-Sparks-Rally-China-Trade-Tensions-Simmer/699e90a804a25a58c853d209</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Chip-Deal-Sparks-Rally-China-Trade-Tensions-Simmer/699e90a804a25a58c853d209</guid><description>Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) and Meta Platforms inked a multiyear AI chip supply deal worth up to $60 billion, driving AMD shares up and boosting tech sector sentiment. This comes as China imposed export restrictions on 40 Japanese companies, citing national security, including firms like Mitsubishi and Subaru. Global markets saw mixed reactions, with Asian shares mostly rising, led by Japan's Nikkei 225 reaching a record high, supported by a weaker yen benefiting exporters and a positive Wall Street lead. U.S. consumer confidence saw a modest uptick in February.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:03:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SAMHI Hotels: Profit Surge Amidst Flat Revenue, New Marriott Deals Boost Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/SAMHI-Hotels-Profit-Surge-Amidst-Flat-Revenue-New-Marriott-Deals-Boost-Outlook/699e90a104a25a58c853d1ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/SAMHI-Hotels-Profit-Surge-Amidst-Flat-Revenue-New-Marriott-Deals-Boost-Outlook/699e90a104a25a58c853d1ef</guid><description>SAMHI Hotels' stock advanced following announcements of operating agreements with Marriott for two Navi Mumbai properties and approval for a second hotel in Bengaluru's Whitefield. The company reported a substantial year-on-year increase in net profit for Q3 FY26, driven by operational efficiencies, even as revenue remained largely flat. Analysts highlight discounted valuations and potential for narrowing the gap with peers, while also noting key risks. The expansion initiatives signal a strategic push for future revenue growth and market consolidation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:03:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e90a104a25a58c853d1ee_1771999816426.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TBZ Q3 Profit ₹12.5 Cr; Long-term Debt Rating Reaffirmed Stable</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/TBZ-Q3-Profit-125-Cr-Long-term-Debt-Rating-Reaffirmed-Stable/699e909c04a25a58c853d1d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/TBZ-Q3-Profit-125-Cr-Long-term-Debt-Rating-Reaffirmed-Stable/699e909c04a25a58c853d1d8</guid><description>Tribhovandas Bhimji Zaveri Limited (TBZ) has received a stable credit rating for its key long-term debt facilities. ICRA re-affirmed TBZ's '[ICRA] A- (Stable)' rating for its fund-based working capital and term loans, now assigned for an enhanced aggregate amount of ₹200 crore. This underscores the agency's positive view on the company's creditworthiness and its ability to service debt.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:03:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e909c04a25a58c853d1d7_1771999589183.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver's Wild Ride: Structural Strength Meets Leverage Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silvers-Wild-Ride-Structural-Strength-Meets-Leverage-Risk/699e909c04a25a58c853d1c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silvers-Wild-Ride-Structural-Strength-Meets-Leverage-Risk/699e909c04a25a58c853d1c2</guid><description>Silver has reached unprecedented nominal highs, propelled by robust industrial demand, supply constraints, and investor inflows. However, this ascent has been punctuated by extreme volatility, most notably a devastating single-day drop on January 30, 2026, underscoring the leveraged nature of its paper market. While long-term fundamentals suggest continued strength, participation demands disciplined allocation to navigate sharp, unpredictable swings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:03:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e909c04a25a58c853d1c1_1772000627628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Omnitech IPO: Precision Growth Meets Valuation Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Omnitech-IPO-Precision-Growth-Meets-Valuation-Hurdles/699e8f3604a25a58c853cfab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Omnitech-IPO-Precision-Growth-Meets-Valuation-Hurdles/699e8f3604a25a58c853cfab</guid><description>Omnitech Engineering launches its ₹583 crore IPO, banking on its high-precision component manufacturing and strong export base. Despite a 'Subscribe-Long Term' rating from Anand Rathi, the issue arrives with elevated valuations, significant leverage, a protracted working capital cycle, and geographical concentration risks in its manufacturing facilities, demanding careful investor due diligence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:57:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e8f3604a25a58c853cfaa_1771999464889.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SECL Taps Mine Waste for Critical Minerals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SECL-Taps-Mine-Waste-for-Critical-Minerals/699e8ec704a25a58c853cee5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SECL-Taps-Mine-Waste-for-Critical-Minerals/699e8ec704a25a58c853cee5</guid><description>South Eastern Coalfields Ltd. (SECL), a Coal India subsidiary, has identified seven mine dumps for potential rare earth element (REE) extraction, aligning with India's National Critical Mineral Mission. This strategic initiative aims to leverage waste streams for critical minerals vital for high-tech industries and national security. The move comes as global demand surges and China dominates the REE market. SECL's exploration process is underway, with assessments expected within a year to determine economic viability. The company's parent, Coal India, operates with a market cap of approximately ₹2.65 trillion and a P/E ratio around 8.9x, indicating a value-oriented investment profile. This diversification marks a significant step in India's bid for self-reliance in strategic resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Silver Surges Past Gold: Precious Metals Rally Tests ETF Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-Past-Gold-Precious-Metals-Rally-Tests-ETF-Strength/699e8e4504a25a58c853ce3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-Past-Gold-Precious-Metals-Rally-Tests-ETF-Strength/699e8e4504a25a58c853ce3b</guid><description>Precious metals markets exhibited firm gains as of February 25, 2026, with gold and silver futures on MCX and COMEX trading higher. Silver futures demonstrated particular strength, surging 2.55% on MCX and 2.11% on COMEX, outpacing gold's 0.49% rise. This momentum carried into Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs), where most silver ETFs posted notable gains, while gold ETFs traded in a tighter band. The broad-based nature of the rallies across exchanges and related ETFs suggests a cohesive market trend.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Coforge lands $158M UK contract; revenue to grow 5 years.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-lands-158M-UK-contract-revenue-to-grow-5-years/699e8d5604a25a58c853ccfa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-lands-158M-UK-contract-revenue-to-grow-5-years/699e8d5604a25a58c853ccfa</guid><description>Coforge has announced a substantial five-year contract worth $158 million with a UK-based client. The deal, set to commence in April 2026, is expected to drive significant revenue growth, including an expansion in ancillary services over the contract's duration, marking a key development for the IT services firm.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Veranda Learning ₹140 Cr Loan to Redeem NCDs; Promoters May Pledge Shares</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Veranda-Learning-140-Cr-Loan-to-Redeem-NCDs-Promoters-May-Pledge-Shares/699e898f04a25a58c853c8e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Veranda-Learning-140-Cr-Loan-to-Redeem-NCDs-Promoters-May-Pledge-Shares/699e898f04a25a58c853c8e5</guid><description>Veranda Learning Solutions Limited has secured a ₹140 crore term loan facility from City Union Bank. The funds are earmarked for redeeming outstanding Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs), continuing the company's strategic debt management. While the loan aims to improve the debt structure, promoters' proposal to pledge shares worth ₹50 crore is still pending execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:33:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e898f04a25a58c853c8e4_1772000506433.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Supreme Court Ruling Sparks $175 Billion Tariff Refund Frenzy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Supreme-Court-Ruling-Sparks-175-Billion-Tariff-Refund-Frenzy/699e895304a25a58c853c822</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Supreme-Court-Ruling-Sparks-175-Billion-Tariff-Refund-Frenzy/699e895304a25a58c853c822</guid><description>Global brands including L'Oreal and Dyson are initiating lawsuits to reclaim an estimated $175 billion in tariffs imposed under former President Trump's emergency trade powers. This follows a Supreme Court decision that found these tariffs unlawful, opening the door for over 1,400 companies to pursue refunds. The legal process is anticipated to be lengthy, potentially spanning years, leaving billions in collected duties in limbo and posing significant fiscal questions for the U.S. Treasury.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedanta Outperforms JSW Steel on Demerger Hopes &amp; Commodity Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Vedanta-Outperforms-JSW-Steel-on-Demerger-Hopes-and-Commodity-Rally/699e894f04a25a58c853c7c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Vedanta-Outperforms-JSW-Steel-on-Demerger-Hopes-and-Commodity-Rally/699e894f04a25a58c853c7c2</guid><description>Vedanta Ltd. shares surged over 5%, significantly outperforming JSW Steel Ltd.'s 2% rise, following distinct analyst ratings and commodity price outlooks. Citi initiated a pair trade favoring Vedanta ('Overweight') over JSW Steel ('Underweight'), citing Vedanta's demerger potential and attractive commodity price valuations against JSW Steel's limited upside as steel prices near import parity. BofA Securities further boosted Vedanta with a 'Buy' upgrade and a 75% price target increase, driven by a bullish stance on aluminum, supportive silver prices, and a nearly 6% dividend yield. Analyst consensus remains strongly positive for Vedanta, with 11 out of 15 analysts recommending 'Buy'.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:31:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e894f04a25a58c853c7c1_1771998016680.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SpiceJet Plummets on Block Deals Amidst Operational Chaos</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Plummets-on-Block-Deals-Amidst-Operational-Chaos/699e894204a25a58c853c79c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Plummets-on-Block-Deals-Amidst-Operational-Chaos/699e894204a25a58c853c79c</guid><description>SpiceJet's stock faced severe selling pressure, hitting a 10% lower circuit on large trading volumes driven by block deals. This downturn is amplified by a significant ₹262 crore net loss in Q3 FY26, mounting operational challenges such as a large portion of its fleet remaining grounded, and an ongoing dispute over unpaid navigation charges with Bangladesh. Despite differing reports, the airline confirms dialogues for resolution. These factors paint a grim picture for the carrier, contrasting with a cautiously optimistic sector outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:31:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e894204a25a58c853c79b_1771997871755.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TSMC Dominance Fuels Taiwan Stock Surge Amid AI Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TSMC-Dominance-Fuels-Taiwan-Stock-Surge-Amid-AI-Boom/699e887404a25a58c853c577</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TSMC-Dominance-Fuels-Taiwan-Stock-Surge-Amid-AI-Boom/699e887404a25a58c853c577</guid><description>Taiwan's equity market is attracting substantial foreign investment, with global funds pouring billions into semiconductor stocks, perceiving them as safe havens amidst AI disruption fears. Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (TSMC) represents a significant portion of the Taiex index, a trend expected to continue benefiting the market as long as AI remains integral to future technology. This influx has supported the Taiwanese dollar, although hedging needs remain low for equity investors. The concentration of TSMC's influence presents a unique dynamic for the broader market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bitcoin Eyes Double Bottom Amid Dollar Weakness; Risks Abound</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Eyes-Double-Bottom-Amid-Dollar-Weakness-Risks-Abound/699e884004a25a58c853c4dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Eyes-Double-Bottom-Amid-Dollar-Weakness-Risks-Abound/699e884004a25a58c853c4dd</guid><description>Bitcoin rallied to $65,400, buoyed by a weaker U.S. dollar and positive Asian equity markets, hinting at a potential "double bottom" chart pattern. However, this technical signal is overshadowed by thin conviction and significant downside risks, with analysts warning of a potential 25% drop if support fails. Geopolitical tensions and a historically inconsistent dollar-Bitcoin correlation add layers of uncertainty to the current recovery, underscoring a "crisis of confidence" despite the bounce.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ABB India: High Orders, High Valuation, Margin Recovery Crucial</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-India-High-Orders-High-Valuation-Margin-Recovery-Crucial/699e884004a25a58c853c4c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-India-High-Orders-High-Valuation-Margin-Recovery-Crucial/699e884004a25a58c853c4c6</guid><description>ABB India secured a 52% YoY order intake surge in Q3 FY25, boosted by data centers and infrastructure, securing future revenue. Despite this, profitability remains squeezed by rising material costs, forex volatility, and competition, leading to margin compression. Trading at a substantial 53.5x two-year forward earnings, the stock's valuation hinges critically on its ability to translate order execution into margin stabilization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:27:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e884004a25a58c853c4c5_1771997601774.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HUL Locks OZiva, Eyes Health Dominance Amidst Market Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HUL-Locks-OZiva-Eyes-Health-Dominance-Amidst-Market-Boom/699e883004a25a58c853c4a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HUL-Locks-OZiva-Eyes-Health-Dominance-Amidst-Market-Boom/699e883004a25a58c853c4a0</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever has finalized the ₹824 crore acquisition of the remaining 49% stake in OZiva, securing 100% ownership of the plant-based nutrition brand. This move aggressively expands HUL's footprint in India's burgeoning health and wellness sector, leveraging OZiva's clean-label and Ayurvedic product lines to capture significant market share. Valued at approximately ₹1,682 crore, the acquisition signals a strategic consolidation play in a high-growth segment where competitors are also increasing focus.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:27:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e883004a25a58c853c49f_1771997534881.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supreme Court Limits NCLT Power Over Benami Asset Attachments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Supreme-Court-Limits-NCLT-Power-Over-Benami-Asset-Attachments/699e882b04a25a58c853c489</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Supreme-Court-Limits-NCLT-Power-Over-Benami-Asset-Attachments/699e882b04a25a58c853c489</guid><description>The Supreme Court has definitively ruled that the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) and National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) cannot question the legality of property attachments made under the Prohibition of Benami Property Transactions Act, 1988. The apex court clarified that sovereign actions under the Benami Act take precedence over insolvency proceedings under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC), 2016, even when attached properties are linked to corporate debtors undergoing insolvency or liquidation. The judgment emphasized that IBC is for distributing the debtor's own estate, not assets suspected of being involved in benami transactions. Liquidators attempting to challenge these attachments through IBC tribunals were deemed to be abusing the legal process, leading to substantial costs being imposed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:27:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e882b04a25a58c853c488_1771997371244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC EV Charger Ruling: Housing Society Hurdles Threaten India's Green Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-EV-Charger-Ruling-Housing-Society-Hurdles-Threaten-Indias-Green-Push/699e87bc04a25a58c853c3c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-EV-Charger-Ruling-Housing-Society-Hurdles-Threaten-Indias-Green-Push/699e87bc04a25a58c853c3c0</guid><description>The Supreme Court has issued notices to the Union government and Uttar Pradesh officials, examining a plea alleging housing societies obstruct electric vehicle (EV) charger installations. This legal challenge underscores a critical gap between national EV adoption policies and on-ground implementation, potentially slowing the nation's green mobility transition. The intervention signals a move to enforce national guidelines against local administrative inertia, affecting both EV owners and the real estate sector's integration of charging infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:25:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e87bc04a25a58c853c3bf_1771997487979.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India EMS Sector: Motilal Oswal Bullish on Growth Catalysts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-EMS-Sector-Motilal-Oswal-Bullish-on-Growth-Catalysts/699e874004a25a58c853c2d9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-EMS-Sector-Motilal-Oswal-Bullish-on-Growth-Catalysts/699e874004a25a58c853c2d9</guid><description>India's electronics manufacturing services (EMS) sector is on an upward trajectory, with Motilal Oswal projecting a 42% profit growth by FY28. This surge is underpinned by the Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme and increased government budgetary allocation for local components, reaching ₹40,000 crore. Companies are actively shifting towards high-margin areas like defense, aerospace, and electric vehicles to bolster their market positions and profitability. The sector's revenue is anticipated to grow by 30% through FY28, fueled by robust domestic demand and expanding export opportunities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:23:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e874004a25a58c853c2d8_1771997367942.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vikram Solar Bags 378.75 MW Module Order from INGEL for Gujarat Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Vikram-Solar-Bags-37875-MW-Module-Order-from-INGEL-for-Gujarat-Project/699e856004a25a58c853c156</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Vikram-Solar-Bags-37875-MW-Module-Order-from-INGEL-for-Gujarat-Project/699e856004a25a58c853c156</guid><description>Vikram Solar has won a significant 378.75 MW order for advanced N-TOPCon solar modules from Indian Oil NTPC Green Energy Private Limited (INGEL). The modules will be deployed in Gujarat as part of a larger 600 MW initiative. This marks Vikram Solar's first major project with INGEL, with deliveries slated to begin in FY26, strengthening its presence in a key renewable energy hub.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tariff Promise Falters: US Consumers Bear Brunt, Legal Risks Mount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tariff-Promise-Falters-US-Consumers-Bear-Brunt-Legal-Risks-Mount/699e847704a25a58c853c04a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tariff-Promise-Falters-US-Consumers-Bear-Brunt-Legal-Risks-Mount/699e847704a25a58c853c04a</guid><description>The administration's push to replace income tax with tariffs is undermined by research showing US consumers and businesses bear nearly all the economic burden. This strategy faces significant headwinds from a Supreme Court ruling curtailing executive authority on tariffs, creating legal and regulatory uncertainty. Historically, such measures have not only failed to generate sufficient revenue but have also triggered market sell-offs and inflation concerns, contrasting sharply with the administration's optimistic economic claims.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:11:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e847704a25a58c853c049_1771996907455.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABB India's Valuation Under Fire Amidst Order Boom, Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-Indias-Valuation-Under-Fire-Amidst-Order-Boom-Margin-Squeeze/699e83fd04a25a58c853bfa1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-Indias-Valuation-Under-Fire-Amidst-Order-Boom-Margin-Squeeze/699e83fd04a25a58c853bfa1</guid><description>ABB India is experiencing a significant surge in order intake and boasts a substantial backlog, particularly in high-growth data center projects, signaling robust future revenue visibility. However, this top-line strength is overshadowed by ongoing margin compression driven by elevated material costs, currency headwinds, and intense competition. The company's premium valuation, trading at roughly 53-75 times forward earnings, is now critically dependent on its ability to translate order execution into improved profitability, a prospect met with mixed analyst sentiment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:09:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e83fd04a25a58c853bfa0_1771996468173.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashoka Buildcon Ratings Reaffirmed Stable; Removed From Rating Watch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ashoka-Buildcon-Ratings-Reaffirmed-Stable-Removed-From-Rating-Watch/699e83f004a25a58c853bf8a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ashoka-Buildcon-Ratings-Reaffirmed-Stable-Removed-From-Rating-Watch/699e83f004a25a58c853bf8a</guid><description>Ashoka Buildcon Limited's long-term and short-term debt ratings have been reaffirmed at 'ACUITE AA (Stable)' and 'ACUITE A1+' respectively. Critically, both ratings have been removed from 'Rating Watch', signaling improved stability and stronger creditworthiness for the infrastructure major following successful asset monetisation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:09:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e83f004a25a58c853bf89_1771996693144.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fine Organic Expands Aggressively Amid Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fine-Organic-Expands-Aggressively-Amid-Margin-Squeeze/699e82d604a25a58c853be39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fine-Organic-Expands-Aggressively-Amid-Margin-Squeeze/699e82d604a25a58c853be39</guid><description>Fine Organic Industries is undertaking significant capacity expansions, including new SEZ and US-based facilities, aiming to unlock future growth. However, recent financial results indicate margin compression and a moderation from peak profitability. The company's rich valuation, hovering around 35-38x P/E, prices in substantial future expansion, raising questions about execution timelines and near-term operational resilience against input cost volatility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:04:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e82d604a25a58c853be38_1771996033550.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Integration: India's IT Sector Faces Opportunity Amidst Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Integration-Indias-IT-Sector-Faces-Opportunity-Amidst-Sell-Off/699e822b04a25a58c853bd11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Integration-Indias-IT-Sector-Faces-Opportunity-Amidst-Sell-Off/699e822b04a25a58c853bd11</guid><description>Despite market fears of Artificial Intelligence disrupting traditional IT services, UBS maintains a constructive view, identifying AI integration complexities as a key demand driver for Indian IT firms. Following a significant sector sell-off, UBS suggests current valuations present an attractive entry point. The firm also maintains a positive outlook on Indian equities broadly, anticipating mild double-digit upside by year-end.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:01:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e822b04a25a58c853bd10_1771995817043.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Gains Fragile Amid Market Rally, Oil &amp; FII Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Gains-Fragile-Amid-Market-Rally-Oil-and-FII-Pressure/699e81a704a25a58c853bbd7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Gains-Fragile-Amid-Market-Rally-Oil-and-FII-Pressure/699e81a704a25a58c853bbd7</guid><description>The Indian Rupee advanced six paise to 90.89 against the US Dollar on February 25, 2026, supported by a weaker greenback and a strong domestic equity market rebound. However, escalating global crude oil prices and net foreign institutional investor outflows of ₹102.53 crore on February 24 limited sharper gains, highlighting currency sensitivity to external pressures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:59:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e81a704a25a58c853bbd6_1771996067841.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Correction Unlocks Value Amidst Sectoral Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Correction-Unlocks-Value-Amidst-Sectoral-Divergence/699e81a604a25a58c853bbc0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Correction-Unlocks-Value-Amidst-Sectoral-Divergence/699e81a604a25a58c853bbc0</guid><description>Market volatility is normalizing valuations, presenting pockets of opportunity across select sectors. While the metals sector shows strength driven by demand and positive commodity outlooks, and renewable energy continues to attract investment, investors must navigate a complex landscape. Companies like Vedanta are seeing analyst upgrades based on commodity prices and deleveraging, yet valuation concerns and ESG risks loom. The automotive sector faces moderate growth prospects amidst global trade uncertainties. High-growth IPOs like CleanMax Energy are priced at steep multiples, warranting caution, while Tata Technologies presents a divided analyst sentiment, balancing strong fundamentals with expensive valuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:59:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e81a604a25a58c853bbbf_1771995740245.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NTPC Surges to 52-Week High on Policy Tailwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Surges-to-52-Week-High-on-Policy-Tailwinds/699e81a204a25a58c853bba9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Surges-to-52-Week-High-on-Policy-Tailwinds/699e81a204a25a58c853bba9</guid><description>NTPC shares ascended to a new 52-week high, nearing ₹388.50, propelled by strong government policy initiatives including the SHANTI Nuclear Act and CERC's battery energy storage system (BESS) regulations. The company reported a 5.85% year-over-year increase in Q3 FY26 profit. While many analysts maintain buy ratings with targets around ₹440, a deeper review considers the company's thermal asset reliance amidst India's renewable push and potential valuation concerns, despite a P/E ratio favorable against sector averages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:59:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e81a204a25a58c853bba8_1771996009383.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nomura Spurs Lloyds Metals Rally Amidst Growth Ambitions, Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nomura-Spurs-Lloyds-Metals-Rally-Amidst-Growth-Ambitions-Risks-Loom/699e819804a25a58c853bb8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nomura-Spurs-Lloyds-Metals-Rally-Amidst-Growth-Ambitions-Risks-Loom/699e819804a25a58c853bb8f</guid><description>Nomura has initiated coverage on Lloyds Metals and Energy with a 'Buy' rating and a ₹1,600 target price, implying over 40% upside. The brokerage projects a surge in consolidated EBITDA to ₹10,900 crore by FY2028, driven by a strategic pivot to integrated steel production and cost advantages from the Surjagarh mine. However, significant risks persist, including geopolitical instability in the Democratic Republic of Congo, potential resurgence of Naxal activities, and execution challenges in scaling steel capacity, even as the Indian steel sector faces margin pressures despite healthy demand growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:59:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e819804a25a58c853bb8e_1771995751826.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>