<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:46:27 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Ad Market to Hit ₹2 Lakh Crore, Driven by Commerce &amp; AI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/India-Ad-Market-to-Hit-2-Lakh-Crore-Driven-by-Commerce-and-AI/6995dc43d25eafd9cdfda614</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/India-Ad-Market-to-Hit-2-Lakh-Crore-Driven-by-Commerce-and-AI/6995dc43d25eafd9cdfda614</guid><description>India's advertising market is projected to surge past ₹2 lakh crore in 2026, with a 9.7% growth rate, as forecasted by WPP Media. Digital channels will command 68.1% of revenue, led by a 24.2% expansion in commerce-led advertising, fueled by retail media and quick commerce. Artificial intelligence is increasingly orchestrating marketing, moving from assistance to active management. However, the focus is shifting from impressions to tangible outcomes, presenting a complex ecosystem for brands to navigate amidst evolving privacy regulations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:35:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995dc43d25eafd9cdfda613_1771429048015.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yatra Online Sees Profit Dip Despite 9% Revenue Jump in Q3</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Yatra-Online-Sees-Profit-Dip-Despite-9percent-Revenue-Jump-in-Q3/6995da4cd25eafd9cdfda531</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Yatra-Online-Sees-Profit-Dip-Despite-9percent-Revenue-Jump-in-Q3/6995da4cd25eafd9cdfda531</guid><description>Yatra Online Limited posted a 9% year-on-year rise in revenue to ₹256.8 crore for the third quarter of FY26. However, its profit after tax declined 17% to ₹8.3 crore, mainly due to a one-time charge of ₹3.8 crore related to new labour codes. Despite this, the company's adjusted EBITDA surged 41%, and the outlook for the full year and beyond remains strong, with continued growth expected in air ticketing and hotel bookings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:27:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995da4cd25eafd9cdfda530.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cochin Shipyard Lands Mega Order for Six LNG Ships from CMA CGM</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cochin-Shipyard-Lands-Mega-Order-for-Six-LNG-Ships-from-CMA-CGM/6995d78ad25eafd9cdfda3ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cochin-Shipyard-Lands-Mega-Order-for-Six-LNG-Ships-from-CMA-CGM/6995d78ad25eafd9cdfda3ae</guid><description>Cochin Shipyard Limited (CSL) has signed a major shipbuilding contract with France's CMA CGM for six LNG-fuelled 1,700 TEU feeder container vessels. The deal, classified as 'Mega' by CSL, is valued at over ₹2,000 Crore. Deliveries are expected to commence within 36 months.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:15:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995d78ad25eafd9cdfda3ad_1771427817983.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mindspace REIT's Top 'AAA' Rating Reaffirmed: Stable Outlook Secure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mindspace-REITs-Top-AAA-Rating-Reaffirmed-Stable-Outlook-Secure/6995d77dd25eafd9cdfda398</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mindspace-REITs-Top-AAA-Rating-Reaffirmed-Stable-Outlook-Secure/6995d77dd25eafd9cdfda398</guid><description>Mindspace Business Parks REIT has received a strong vote of confidence from CRISIL Ratings. The agency reaffirmed its highest 'Crisil AAA/Stable' rating for the REIT's Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) totalling ₹6,070 Crore and its corporate credit rating. Additionally, its Commercial Paper rating was reaffirmed at 'Crisil A1+'. These top-tier ratings signal robust creditworthiness and a stable financial outlook for the real estate investment trust, reassuring investors about the safety of its debt instruments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995d77dd25eafd9cdfda397.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sparc Electrex Revenue Crashes 93%, Faces Tax Freeze, Posts Huge Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sparc-Electrex-Revenue-Crashes-93percent-Faces-Tax-Freeze-Posts-Huge-Loss/6995d77ad25eafd9cdfda382</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sparc-Electrex-Revenue-Crashes-93percent-Faces-Tax-Freeze-Posts-Huge-Loss/6995d77ad25eafd9cdfda382</guid><description>Sparc Electrex Limited's financial health has dramatically worsened. The company reported a staggering 93.9% year-on-year drop in revenue for Q3 FY26, alongside a significant net loss of ₹0.97 Cr. Adding to its woes, the company's bank accounts have been provisionally attached by the Income Tax Department, raising serious concerns about its operational continuity and liquidity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:15:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995d77ad25eafd9cdfda381.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CMA CGM Bets on India: $360M LNG Vessel Order Signals Shift from Asia</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CMA-CGM-Bets-on-India-360M-LNG-Vessel-Order-Signals-Shift-from-Asia/6995d59cd25eafd9cdfda21a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CMA-CGM-Bets-on-India-360M-LNG-Vessel-Order-Signals-Shift-from-Asia/6995d59cd25eafd9cdfda21a</guid><description>Cochin Shipyard (CSL) has secured a substantial $360 million order from France's CMA CGM Group for six LNG-powered, 1700-TEU vessels. This deal signifies CMA CGM's strategic departure from sourcing ships primarily from China and Korea, indicating increased international confidence in India's advanced shipbuilding capacity. The order boosts CSL's order book to ₹23,000 crore. Delivery is slated to begin by February 2029. The move aligns with India's broader 'Maritime Vision 2047' and the development of new economic corridors like IMEC.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:07:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995d59cd25eafd9cdfda219_1771427356655.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zee Entertainment Pivots Content Strategy Amidst Digital Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Entertainment-Pivots-Content-Strategy-Amidst-Digital-Race/6995d59bd25eafd9cdfda203</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Entertainment-Pivots-Content-Strategy-Amidst-Digital-Race/6995d59bd25eafd9cdfda203</guid><description>Zee Entertainment Enterprises is aggressively retooling its content syndication strategy to capture value from its library across new digital frontiers. This includes adapting content for short-form mobile video, developing audio formats, and leveraging a new Multi-Channel Network (MCN) for broader distribution. The company is also enhancing its international reach through dubbing and regional partnerships. Despite these strategic moves, Zee Entertainment operates in a highly competitive Indian media landscape characterized by digital disruption and the dominance of larger players, alongside persistent concerns over its historical sales growth and past governance issues.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:07:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995d59bd25eafd9cdfda202_1771427359480.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Spectrum Ruling Hits RCom Creditors, Redefines Telco Financing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Spectrum-Ruling-Hits-RCom-Creditors-Redefines-Telco-Financing/6995d432d25eafd9cdfda10b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Spectrum-Ruling-Hits-RCom-Creditors-Redefines-Telco-Financing/6995d432d25eafd9cdfda10b</guid><description>The Supreme Court has ruled telecom spectrum is a public resource, not a corporate asset, severely curtailing lenders' recovery options in Reliance Communications' bankruptcy. This landmark decision upends traditional notions of spectrum as collateral, forcing a re-evaluation of financing models across the capital-intensive telecom sector. Companies like Vodafone Idea, already posting negative P/E ratios, face heightened scrutiny, while the government reinforces sovereign control over national resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:01:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995d432d25eafd9cdfda10a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ceigall India Expands Project Pipeline Amidst Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ceigall-India-Expands-Project-Pipeline-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/6995d0efd25eafd9cdfd9faf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ceigall-India-Expands-Project-Pipeline-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/6995d0efd25eafd9cdfd9faf</guid><description>Ceigall India Limited has established a new wholly-owned subsidiary to undertake a significant NH 139W highway project in Bihar under the Hybrid Annuity Model. Simultaneously, a key Haryana highway project achieved 90.03% physical progress, triggering milestone payments. While these developments bolster its substantial ₹13,268.10 crore order book and market cap exceeding ₹5,000 crore, the company's elevated P/E ratio of 45x warrants investor caution amidst a competitive infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:47:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995d0efd25eafd9cdfd9fae.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amwill Healthcare Data Breach: Account Data Compromised, Firm Investigates</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Amwill-Healthcare-Data-Breach-Account-Data-Compromised-Firm-Investigates/6995d0e8d25eafd9cdfd9f98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Amwill-Healthcare-Data-Breach-Account-Data-Compromised-Firm-Investigates/6995d0e8d25eafd9cdfd9f98</guid><description>Amwill Healthcare Limited has disclosed an IT security incident impacting account-related data from September 30, 2025. While the company states that critical compliance data remains secure and recovery actions are underway with cybersecurity experts, the breach raises concerns about operational integrity and data protection. Investors will be watching closely for further details on the scope and resolution of the incident.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:47:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995d0e8d25eafd9cdfd9f97.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICAI Lifts Digital Audit Bar with New ISAS Standards</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICAI-Lifts-Digital-Audit-Bar-with-New-ISAS-Standards/6995cffbd25eafd9cdfd9eb4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICAI-Lifts-Digital-Audit-Bar-with-New-ISAS-Standards/6995cffbd25eafd9cdfd9eb4</guid><description>The Institute of Chartered Accountants of India (ICAI) is set to release 11 Information Systems Audit Standards (ISAS) this month, designed to significantly enhance the reliability of digital financial reporting. These standards aim to create a direct link between robust system controls and financial statement integrity, crucial in an era of ERP-generated, algorithm-driven financial data. This initiative is expected to bolster stakeholder confidence by assuring the accuracy and transparency of digital disclosures within India's evolving economic ecosystem. The release marks the first time a professional accounting body has introduced such comprehensive digital audit standards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:43:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995cffbd25eafd9cdfd9eb3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lumax Auto Technologies Amalgamation Gets Green Light from NCLT</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lumax-Auto-Technologies-Amalgamation-Gets-Green-Light-from-NCLT/6995cf82d25eafd9cdfd9df7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lumax-Auto-Technologies-Amalgamation-Gets-Green-Light-from-NCLT/6995cf82d25eafd9cdfd9df7</guid><description>Lumax Auto Technologies Limited has received a significant boost as the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), New Delhi Bench, sanctioned the scheme for its amalgamation with Lumax Ancillary Limited on February 18, 2026. This move is expected to streamline operations and enhance efficiencies within the auto component manufacturer. Investors await the formal order for full details.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:41:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995cf82d25eafd9cdfd9df6_1771425799056.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pivots Oil Sourcing, Sacrificing Discounts for Geopolitics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Pivots-Oil-Sourcing-Sacrificing-Discounts-for-Geopolitics/6995cf3ad25eafd9cdfd9d4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Pivots-Oil-Sourcing-Sacrificing-Discounts-for-Geopolitics/6995cf3ad25eafd9cdfd9d4f</guid><description>India significantly reduced Russian crude oil imports in January 2026, marking the lowest volume since late 2022. Driven by US trade pressure and an interim agreement, New Delhi is increasingly sourcing from the Middle East, which now accounts for approximately 55% of its imports. This strategic shift, while navigating geopolitical demands, potentially sacrifices substantial cost savings from discounted Russian barrels, raising concerns about refinery margins and national energy economics. Meanwhile, China has emerged as Russia's primary seaborne crude buyer, absorbing volumes India is now eschewing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:39:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995cf3ad25eafd9cdfd9d4e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MTF Leverage Costs: Brokerage Hidden Risk Amplifies Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/MTF-Leverage-Costs-Brokerage-Hidden-Risk-Amplifies-Losses/6995ce8ed25eafd9cdfd9c88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/MTF-Leverage-Costs-Brokerage-Hidden-Risk-Amplifies-Losses/6995ce8ed25eafd9cdfd9c88</guid><description>Margin Trading Facility (MTF) participation is surging, but Nithin Kamath, Zerodha's co-founder, highlights a critical, often ignored, cost: brokerage fees. These transactional charges, especially on short-duration or low-gain trades, can compound rapidly, elevating the breakeven point and turning leveraged positions unprofitable. The cumulative effect of interest and brokerage on amplified positions represents a significant, underestimated risk multiplier for retail traders.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:37:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995ce8ed25eafd9cdfd9c87.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-France Trade Gap: Strategic Ambition vs. Economic Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-France-Trade-Gap-Strategic-Ambition-vs-Economic-Reality/6995ce44d25eafd9cdfd9bc8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-France-Trade-Gap-Strategic-Ambition-vs-Economic-Reality/6995ce44d25eafd9cdfd9bc8</guid><description>The India-France strategic partnership faces a stark economic disconnect, with bilateral trade of around $15 billion lagging behind deep defense and diplomatic trust. While political will is strong, execution in trade and investment requires a significant pivot. Analysts urge a shift from defense platforms to joint production in green energy, digital technologies, and engaging SMEs to truly embody the 'partnership of equals' envisioned by 2047. Failure to accelerate tangible economic outcomes risks undermining the alliance's broader strategic aims.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:35:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995ce44d25eafd9cdfd9bc7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Inc's SDG Push: Strategy Fuels Resilience and Financial Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Incs-SDG-Push-Strategy-Fuels-Resilience-and-Financial-Gains/6995ce1fd25eafd9cdfd9bb1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Incs-SDG-Push-Strategy-Fuels-Resilience-and-Financial-Gains/6995ce1fd25eafd9cdfd9bb1</guid><description>The Perpetual Capital Hurun India Impact 50 report ranks leading companies on UN Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs). Hindustan Unilever topped the list, followed by HCL Technologies and Grasim Industries. These 50 firms generated ₹48.5 lakh crore revenue and ₹4.95 lakh crore net profit, investing over ₹8,000 crore in CSR. Climate Action is the most prioritized goal. This integration signifies a strategic shift from compliance to measurable impact, enhancing long-term corporate resilience and shareholder value. However, sector-specific challenges and valuation concerns remain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:35:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995ce1fd25eafd9cdfd9bb0_1771425443350.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Overhauls ESG Ratings to Boost Investor Confidence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Overhauls-ESG-Ratings-to-Boost-Investor-Confidence/6995ce1bd25eafd9cdfd9b9a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Overhauls-ESG-Ratings-to-Boost-Investor-Confidence/6995ce1bd25eafd9cdfd9b9a</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has initiated a comprehensive review of its regulatory framework for Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) Rating Providers (ERPs). A newly formed working group, comprising diverse market stakeholders, will assess current rules to enhance transparency, reliability, and investor confidence. This move is critical for India's burgeoning sustainable finance sector, seeking to align domestic standards with global best practices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:35:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995ce1bd25eafd9cdfd9b99.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dr. Reddy's Buys Women's Health Brands for $32 Million</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Buys-Womens-Health-Brands-for-32-Million/6995cb4ad25eafd9cdfd9a72</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Buys-Womens-Health-Brands-for-32-Million/6995cb4ad25eafd9cdfd9a72</guid><description>Dr. Reddy's Laboratories has acquired the Indian trademarks Progynova® and Cyclo-Progynova®, along with related assets, from Mercury Pharma Group Limited for USD 32.15 million. This move significantly strengthens its gynecology business and marks a strategic entry into the Hormone Replacement Therapy (HRT) segment in India. The acquisition is expected to drive expansion in women's health, a growing market in the country.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995cb4ad25eafd9cdfd9a71.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Orient Tradelink Profit Jumps 5255%, But Financial Red Flags Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Orient-Tradelink-Profit-Jumps-5255percent-But-Financial-Red-Flags-Emerge/6995c9e0d25eafd9cdfd9922</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Orient-Tradelink-Profit-Jumps-5255percent-But-Financial-Red-Flags-Emerge/6995c9e0d25eafd9cdfd9922</guid><description>Orient Tradelink Limited announced a staggering 5255% year-on-year jump in Net Profit After Tax (PAT) for Q3 FY2026. However, the results reveal significant financial anomalies, including discrepancies in profit calculations and identical expense figures compared to the prior year. Coupled with a history of SEBI regulatory issues and low promoter holding, these findings raise serious investor concerns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c9e0d25eafd9cdfd9921.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Delays OTC Derivative UTI; Compliance Window Expands</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/RBI/RBI-Delays-OTC-Derivative-UTI-Compliance-Window-Expands/6995c9abd25eafd9cdfd98b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/RBI/RBI-Delays-OTC-Derivative-UTI-Compliance-Window-Expands/6995c9abd25eafd9cdfd98b7</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has postponed the implementation of its Unique Transaction Identifier (UTI) framework for over-the-counter (OTC) derivative transactions to January 1, 2027. This nine-month extension from the original April 1, 2026, deadline acknowledges industry feedback and the need for enhanced technical capabilities. The move provides market participants more time to integrate complex reporting requirements, aligning with global standards for enhanced transparency and risk mitigation in derivatives markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:16:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c9abd25eafd9cdfd98b6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sebi Eyes ESG Rating Overhaul to Boost India's Green Finance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sebi-Eyes-ESG-Rating-Overhaul-to-Boost-Indias-Green-Finance/6995c98cd25eafd9cdfd985b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sebi-Eyes-ESG-Rating-Overhaul-to-Boost-Indias-Green-Finance/6995c98cd25eafd9cdfd985b</guid><description>India's Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) has established a working group to overhaul the regulatory framework for ESG Rating Providers (ERPs). This initiative aims to bolster transparency, reliability, and investor confidence in ESG data. The panel will review global standards, seeking alignment to strengthen India's position in the rapidly growing sustainable finance market and ensure credibility for domestic issuers and investors navigating environmental, social, and governance factors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:15:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c98cd25eafd9cdfd985a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Infrastructure Boom Meets Deep-Rooted Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Infrastructure-Boom-Meets-Deep-Rooted-Challenges/6995c930d25eafd9cdfd97cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Infrastructure-Boom-Meets-Deep-Rooted-Challenges/6995c930d25eafd9cdfd97cc</guid><description>India is rapidly building its AI backbone with substantial investments in data centers and advanced chips, aiming for global leadership. However, widespread AI adoption faces critical challenges: significant infrastructure gaps in rural areas limit accessibility, existing data privacy laws lack AI-specific oversight, and the environmental footprint of AI infrastructure is a growing concern. Overcoming these barriers is crucial for realizing India's AI potential.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:14:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c930d25eafd9cdfd97cb.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kesar Petro Products Profit Skyrockets on Stronger Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kesar-Petro-Products-Profit-Skyrockets-on-Stronger-Margins/6995c8f1d25eafd9cdfd9771</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kesar-Petro-Products-Profit-Skyrockets-on-Stronger-Margins/6995c8f1d25eafd9cdfd9771</guid><description>Kesar Petroproducts Ltd. reported a robust Q3 FY26, with net profit surging 170.37% year-on-year to ₹2.92 crore, driven by a significant improvement in EBITDA margins to 15.31% from 7.07%. For the nine-month period, profit jumped 84.71% YoY to ₹14.74 crore, with margins more than doubling. The company's EBITDA and PAT for the nine months have already surpassed the full-year figures for FY25, signaling a strong operational turnaround.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:13:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c8f1d25eafd9cdfd9770.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dr. Reddy's Prepares $1B GLP-1 Play Amid Patent Expiry Frenzy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Prepares-1B-GLP-1-Play-Amid-Patent-Expiry-Frenzy/6995c87dd25eafd9cdfd9681</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Prepares-1B-GLP-1-Play-Amid-Patent-Expiry-Frenzy/6995c87dd25eafd9cdfd9681</guid><description>Dr. Reddy's Laboratories is poised to launch its oral semaglutide formulation, targeting the burgeoning diabetes and weight-loss market in India. Capitalizing on Novo Nordisk's patent expiry, the company plans a comprehensive 'full-stack' launch, integrating API production and a wider patient care ecosystem. This strategic move aims to leverage backward integration to navigate intense price competition and establish a strong foothold in a market analysts project could reach $1 billion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:11:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c87dd25eafd9cdfd9680.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Telecom's AI Ambition: Bridging Potential With Pragmatic Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Telecoms-AI-Ambition-Bridging-Potential-With-Pragmatic-Hurdles/6995c85dd25eafd9cdfd963b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Telecoms-AI-Ambition-Bridging-Potential-With-Pragmatic-Hurdles/6995c85dd25eafd9cdfd963b</guid><description>Artificial Intelligence is becoming indispensable for India's telecom sector, driving network optimization and customer experience. However, widespread adoption is hindered by substantial implementation costs, a shortage of skilled talent, complex data management, and evolving governance requirements. India's diverse market presents unique opportunities for AI-driven inclusion but demands careful, adaptive strategies to overcome these pragmatic hurdles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:10:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c85dd25eafd9cdfd963a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Funds' Outperformance Under Scrutiny Amidst Divergent Risk Profiles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Mid-Cap-Funds-Outperformance-Under-Scrutiny-Amidst-Divergent-Risk-Profiles/6995c825d25eafd9cdfd95e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Mid-Cap-Funds-Outperformance-Under-Scrutiny-Amidst-Divergent-Risk-Profiles/6995c825d25eafd9cdfd95e0</guid><description>Mid-cap equity funds have delivered impressive 5-year returns, outperforming benchmark indices with CAGRs often exceeding 23%. HDFC, Motilal Oswal, and Nippon India stand out. However, analysis reveals significant divergence in risk-adjusted performance, portfolio sector concentrations (technology vs. financials), and capital preservation capabilities. Investors must look beyond headline returns to assess the sustainability of this outperformance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:09:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c825d25eafd9cdfd95df.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashiana Ispat Faces Shareholder Move to Remove Director</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ashiana-Ispat-Faces-Shareholder-Move-to-Remove-Director/6995c70fd25eafd9cdfd9494</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ashiana-Ispat-Faces-Shareholder-Move-to-Remove-Director/6995c70fd25eafd9cdfd9494</guid><description>Shareholder Mr. Sandeep Garg, holding nearly 3.77% of Ashiana Ispat Limited, has formally served a special notice. This notice aims to move a resolution for the removal of Director Ms. Darshan at the company's forthcoming General Meeting. Ashiana Ispat has confirmed it will adhere to all regulatory requirements for processing this resolution, signaling a significant governance development for the real estate firm.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:05:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c70fd25eafd9cdfd9493.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHIT's Top 'AAA' Rating Holds Amid Portfolio Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NHITs-Top-AAA-Rating-Holds-Amid-Portfolio-Expansion/6995c6afd25eafd9cdfd93d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NHITs-Top-AAA-Rating-Holds-Amid-Portfolio-Expansion/6995c6afd25eafd9cdfd93d4</guid><description>National Highways Infra Trust (NHIT) has retained its highest 'AAA' credit rating from CARE Ratings, signaling strong financial health. The trust is also expanding its portfolio to 28 toll road assets. While revenues and profits surged in FY25, investors should note a rise in debt levels and a dip in interest coverage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:03:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995c6afd25eafd9cdfd93d3_1771423518955.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BIL Vyapar Enters Insolvency: NCLT Orders Corporate Resolution Process</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/BIL-Vyapar-Enters-Insolvency-NCLT-Orders-Corporate-Resolution-Process/6995c6abd25eafd9cdfd93be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/BIL-Vyapar-Enters-Insolvency-NCLT-Orders-Corporate-Resolution-Process/6995c6abd25eafd9cdfd93be</guid><description>BIL Vyapar Limited, formerly known as Binani Industries Limited, has been officially placed under the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) by an order from the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) dated January 13, 2026. Ms. Rachana Jhunjhunwala has been appointed as the Resolution Professional to manage the company's affairs and assets. This marks a critical turn for the once-diversified conglomerate, which has a history of financial challenges and significant asset sales.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:03:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c6abd25eafd9cdfd93bd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCLT Approves Lumax Auto Technologies' Merger with IAC International</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCLT-Approves-Lumax-Auto-Technologies-Merger-with-IAC-International/6995c61fd25eafd9cdfd930a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCLT-Approves-Lumax-Auto-Technologies-Merger-with-IAC-International/6995c61fd25eafd9cdfd930a</guid><description>The National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) has approved the amalgamation of IAC International Automotive India Private Limited with Lumax Auto Technologies Limited. The NCLT waived meetings for shareholders and creditors, recognizing IAC as a wholly-owned subsidiary. The effective date for this merger is set for October 1, 2025. This move streamlines Lumax Auto Technologies' corporate structure and is expected to unlock synergies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:01:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c61fd25eafd9cdfd9309.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Rallies Amid Sector Rotation: Tech Lagging as Banks, Metals Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Rallies-Amid-Sector-Rotation-Tech-Lagging-as-Banks-Metals-Surge/6995c5e6d25eafd9cdfd92d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Rallies-Amid-Sector-Rotation-Tech-Lagging-as-Banks-Metals-Surge/6995c5e6d25eafd9cdfd92d2</guid><description>Indian equity markets secured a third consecutive session of gains, propelled by late-hour buying in banking, metal, and FMCG sectors. The BSE Sensex closed 0.34% higher at 83,734.25 and the NSE Nifty rose 0.37% to 25,819.35. Institutional investors, FIIs and DIIs, were net buyers, injecting ₹995 crore and ₹187 crore respectively on Tuesday. However, the rally masked a significant divergence, with technology stocks like Infosys and Tech Mahindra underperforming, signaling a notable sector rotation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c5e6d25eafd9cdfd92d1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asgard Alcobev Sells Paper Unit for ₹11 Cr, Raises Tiny ₹0.24 Cr.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Asgard-Alcobev-Sells-Paper-Unit-for-11-Cr-Raises-Tiny-024-Cr/6995c3ccd25eafd9cdfd91e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Asgard-Alcobev-Sells-Paper-Unit-for-11-Cr-Raises-Tiny-024-Cr/6995c3ccd25eafd9cdfd91e0</guid><description>Asgard Alcobev Limited has completed the sale of its entire 99.96% stake in subsidiary Banganga Paper Mills Limited for ₹11.22 Crores. The company, formerly known as Banganga Paper Industries Limited, also raised ₹24.22 Lakhs through a preferential allotment of 16.70 Lakh equity shares at ₹1.45 per share to non-promoter public investors. This move signals a continued strategic pivot away from its legacy paper business.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:51:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995c3ccd25eafd9cdfd91df_1771422774949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Blends Exits Insolvency, Posts Profit But Faces Huge Negative Equity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Blue-Blends-Exits-Insolvency-Posts-Profit-But-Faces-Huge-Negative-Equity/6995c2e3d25eafd9cdfd90e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Blue-Blends-Exits-Insolvency-Posts-Profit-But-Faces-Huge-Negative-Equity/6995c2e3d25eafd9cdfd90e9</guid><description>Blue Blends (India) Limited has reported its financial results after exiting Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) on December 6, 2024. While the company has turned profitable in the last three quarters, showing revenue growth and positive net profit, its consolidated equity remains deeply negative at ₹(119.99) Crores. This highlights the ongoing financial restructuring challenges post-insolvency.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:47:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c2e3d25eafd9cdfd90e8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HUL to Invest ₹2,000 Crore in Premium Brands Manufacturing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-to-Invest-2000-Crore-in-Premium-Brands-Manufacturing/6995c2ddd25eafd9cdfd90d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-to-Invest-2000-Crore-in-Premium-Brands-Manufacturing/6995c2ddd25eafd9cdfd90d3</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever Limited (HUL) is set to invest up to ₹2,000 crore over the next two years to boost its manufacturing capacity. This significant investment will focus on fast-growing premium categories in Beauty &amp; Wellbeing and Home Care liquids. The expansion aligns with HUL's strategy of making 'fewer, bigger bets' and aims to enhance supply chain agility using advanced technology. A key aspect of this expansion is the target of operating facilities on 100% renewable energy, reinforcing HUL's commitment to sustainability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:47:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c2ddd25eafd9cdfd90d2.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Norway Eyes India's Green Economy: SWF Capital Flows Target Renewables</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Norway-Eyes-Indias-Green-Economy-SWF-Capital-Flows-Target-Renewables/6995c268d25eafd9cdfd9063</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Norway-Eyes-Indias-Green-Economy-SWF-Capital-Flows-Target-Renewables/6995c268d25eafd9cdfd9063</guid><description>India is actively seeking increased investment from Norway, particularly from its sovereign wealth funds and pension funds, in high-growth green sectors. Discussions between Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman and Norwegian officials highlighted opportunities in renewables, carbon capture, rare earths, and the blue economy, leveraging the India-EFTA TEPA. Norway's significant capital, channeled through entities like the Government Pension Fund Global and Norfund, is increasingly targeting India's long-term growth potential in sustainable industries and manufacturing, supported by India's reform momentum and predictable economic environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:45:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c268d25eafd9cdfd9062.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mother Dairy Eyes 30% Summer Surge Amidst Market Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mother-Dairy-Eyes-30percent-Summer-Surge-Amidst-Market-Pressures/6995c123d25eafd9cdfd8f21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mother-Dairy-Eyes-30percent-Summer-Surge-Amidst-Market-Pressures/6995c123d25eafd9cdfd8f21</guid><description>Mother Dairy anticipates a significant 30% growth across its ice cream, curd, and dairy beverage categories as summer temperatures climb. The company is enhancing production capacities and introducing approximately 30 new products to meet this demand. However, the Indian dairy market is increasingly competitive, with rivals like Amul, Havmor, and Kwality Walls launching aggressive innovation and expansion strategies, while also contending with rising input costs and evolving consumer preferences for healthier and premium options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:39:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c123d25eafd9cdfd8f20.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Google Maps AI Data Superhighway via India Cables</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Google-Maps-AI-Data-Superhighway-via-India-Cables/6995c0b0d25eafd9cdfd8eb3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Google-Maps-AI-Data-Superhighway-via-India-Cables/6995c0b0d25eafd9cdfd8eb3</guid><description>Alphabet Inc. is strategically fortifying its artificial intelligence infrastructure in India through the India-America Connect Initiative, unveiling plans for new undersea cable routes to accelerate AI-driven data flows and demand. The company is also deepening its collaboration with Google DeepMind for advanced AI development and expanding critical AI skilling programs. This aggressive push leverages India's burgeoning tech talent and rapid adoption, aiming to secure Alphabet's future dominance in global AI data conduits and services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:37:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995c0b0d25eafd9cdfd8eb2.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sanjivani Paranteral's Q3 Results Show Growth, But Big Math Question Arises</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sanjivani-Paranterals-Q3-Results-Show-Growth-But-Big-Math-Question-Arises/6995bdb0d25eafd9cdfd8d6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sanjivani-Paranterals-Q3-Results-Show-Growth-But-Big-Math-Question-Arises/6995bdb0d25eafd9cdfd8d6b</guid><description>Sanjivani Paranteral Limited posted a 20.2% year-on-year revenue growth for Q3 FY'26, reaching ₹20.9 Crores, and improved EBITDA margins. However, a significant mathematical discrepancy in its reported consolidated EBITDA figures of ₹14.1 Crores on a revenue of ₹22.1 Crores, leading to an stated margin of 18.5% (instead of an expected ~64%), has raised serious concerns for investors regarding the accuracy of financial reporting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:25:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995bdb0d25eafd9cdfd8d6a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBZ Jewellers Posts Strong Q3 Growth, Cuts FY26 Revenue Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/RBZ-Jewellers-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Cuts-FY26-Revenue-Outlook/6995bc6bd25eafd9cdfd8c58</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/RBZ-Jewellers-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Cuts-FY26-Revenue-Outlook/6995bc6bd25eafd9cdfd8c58</guid><description>RBZ Jewellers Limited reported a strong Q3 FY26, with revenue up 17% year-on-year to ₹226 Crores, driven by a significant 39% surge in its retail segment. EBITDA grew 36% and profit after tax rose 33%. However, the company revised its full-year revenue guidance downwards to ₹630-650 Crores, citing the delay in new store openings impacting Q4 sales. Despite this, plans for major store expansions in Surat and Rajkot are underway for FY27, signaling a continued push towards B2C transformation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:19:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995bc6bd25eafd9cdfd8c57.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Bank Deposit Insurance Premiums Shift: Profit Hits, Risk Incentives Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Bank-Deposit-Insurance-Premiums-Shift-Profit-Hits-Risk-Incentives-Loom/6995bbe1d25eafd9cdfd8b84</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Bank-Deposit-Insurance-Premiums-Shift-Profit-Hits-Risk-Incentives-Loom/6995bbe1d25eafd9cdfd8b84</guid><description>The Deposit Insurance and Credit Guarantee Corporation (DICGC) will implement a Risk-Based Premium (RBP) framework starting April 1, 2026, moving from a flat rate. ICRA estimates an annual profit impact of ₹2,000–12,000 crore on the banking system, potentially lowering return on assets by 1-4 basis points. However, stronger banks with better risk profiles and operational history will likely see premium discounts, fostering better risk management and potentially enhancing their profitability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:17:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995bbe1d25eafd9cdfd8b83_1771420797819.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>