<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:27:02 +0000</pubDate><item><title>PAN Card Urgency: Final 6 Days to Link Aadhaar! Avoid Deactivation by January 1st</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PAN-Card-Urgency-Final-6-Days-to-Link-Aadhaar-Avoid-Deactivation-by-January-1st/694cd849e10c98d07888fb30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PAN-Card-Urgency-Final-6-Days-to-Link-Aadhaar-Avoid-Deactivation-by-January-1st/694cd849e10c98d07888fb30</guid><description>Indian taxpayers who obtained Aadhaar on or before October 1, 2024, have until December 31, 2025, to link it with their Permanent Account Number (PAN). Failure to do so by this deadline will result in PAN deactivation from January 1, 2026, impacting financial transactions, tax filing, and investments. This specific deadline applies to a group of PAN holders who received their PAN using an Aadhaar Enrolment ID.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:12:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd849e10c98d07888fb2f_1766643864244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold to Skyrocket to $5200? Expert Reveals Shocking 2026 Forecast!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-to-Skyrocket-to-5200-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-2026-Forecast/694cd7efe10c98d07888fa91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-to-Skyrocket-to-5200-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-2026-Forecast/694cd7efe10c98d07888fa91</guid><description>Gold is projected to surge significantly in 2026, potentially reaching $5,200 per ounce, according to Anindya Banerjee, Senior VP at Kotak Securities. Central banks are actively diversifying their reserves away from the US dollar, a trend expected to intensify with ongoing de-dollarization efforts. This, combined with potential Federal Reserve rate cuts and broader currency debasement, creates a strongly bullish outlook for the precious metal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:12:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd7efe10c98d07888fa90_1766643765526.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Real Estate Gold Rush: Why Smart Investors Are Ditching Metros for Tier II &amp; III Cities!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Real-Estate-Gold-Rush-Why-Smart-Investors-Are-Ditching-Metros-for-Tier-II-and-III-Cities/694cd835e10c98d07888fae7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Real-Estate-Gold-Rush-Why-Smart-Investors-Are-Ditching-Metros-for-Tier-II-and-III-Cities/694cd835e10c98d07888fae7</guid><description>Real estate investment is surging in India's Tier II and III cities, driven by rising incomes, robust infrastructure, and evolving buyer preferences. Manoj Dhanotiya of Micro Mitti highlights that these cities are attracting significant urban population growth and organized employment, offering greater affordability and larger homes than metros. While challenges like market oversupply exist, these emerging locations present promising capital appreciation potential, making them attractive for diversified investment portfolios.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:12:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd835e10c98d07888fae6_1766643965518.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Toyota Sales Plummet: China's Subsidy Cut Triggers Major Global Slump! Is Your Investment Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Toyota-Sales-Plummet-Chinas-Subsidy-Cut-Triggers-Major-Global-Slump-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/694cd7a0e10c98d07888fa35</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Toyota-Sales-Plummet-Chinas-Subsidy-Cut-Triggers-Major-Global-Slump-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/694cd7a0e10c98d07888fa35</guid><description>Toyota Motor Corporation reported a significant 1.9% drop in global sales to 965,919 units and a 3.4% decrease in production to 934,001 units in November. The decline is largely attributed to a sharp 12% fall in sales in China, where the government has ended subsidies for electric and fuel-efficient vehicles, impacting sales of Toyota and Lexus brands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:12:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd7a0e10c98d07888fa34_1766643882299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Holds Steady on Christmas Day: Unchanged Rates Despite Global Buzz - What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Holds-Steady-on-Christmas-Day-Unchanged-Rates-Despite-Global-Buzz-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694cd532e10c98d07888f78f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Holds-Steady-on-Christmas-Day-Unchanged-Rates-Despite-Global-Buzz-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694cd532e10c98d07888f78f</guid><description>On December 25, 2025, gold prices in India remained unchanged. 24K gold held at ₹138,250 per 10 grams, and 22K gold stayed at ₹126,729 per 10 grams. Prices are influenced by global rates, US dollar, and import duties. The market saw consolidation after hitting record highs, with investors assessing upcoming US Federal Reserve actions and geopolitical events.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:02:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd532e10c98d07888f78e_1766643113488.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India IPO Boom Hits Record ₹1.75 Lakh Cr, But Investor Returns Plummet to 3-Year Low!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/India-IPO-Boom-Hits-Record-175-Lakh-Cr-But-Investor-Returns-Plummet-to-3-Year-Low/694cd558e10c98d07888f825</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/India-IPO-Boom-Hits-Record-175-Lakh-Cr-But-Investor-Returns-Plummet-to-3-Year-Low/694cd558e10c98d07888f825</guid><description>India's IPO market achieved a record ₹1.75 lakh crore in fundraising in 2025 from 101 companies. However, average listing gains have dropped to a three-year low of 9.9%, significantly down from previous years. This decline is attributed to richer IPO valuations, subdued demand, higher supply, and increased investor selectivity. The trend of Offer-for-Sale (OFS) also dominated IPO proceeds, indicating promoter stake monetization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:02:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd558e10c98d07888f824_1766643219768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Game-Changing Tax Overhaul Arrives April 1st! Discover the New Rules and Lower Rates!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Game-Changing-Tax-Overhaul-Arrives-April-1st-Discover-the-New-Rules-and-Lower-Rates/694cd534e10c98d07888f7ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Game-Changing-Tax-Overhaul-Arrives-April-1st-Discover-the-New-Rules-and-Lower-Rates/694cd534e10c98d07888f7ba</guid><description>India is set to implement a major tax overhaul starting April 1, 2025, with a new Income Tax Act replacing the old one. The government has already simplified the GST structure, compressing slabs and cutting rates on many goods and services to boost domestic demand amidst global economic challenges. Further reforms are planned for customs duties, aiming for greater transparency and simplification. These changes aim to stimulate consumption, support growth, and enhance ease of doing business.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:00:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd534e10c98d07888f7b9_1766643061603.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's $1 Trillion Export Dream Fades: Why Shipments Are Losing Momentum!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-1-Trillion-Export-Dream-Fades-Why-Shipments-Are-Losing-Momentum/694cd4a4e10c98d07888f6e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-1-Trillion-Export-Dream-Fades-Why-Shipments-Are-Losing-Momentum/694cd4a4e10c98d07888f6e9</guid><description>India is likely to miss its ambitious $1 trillion export target for FY26 due to a global economic slowdown and rising protectionism, according to the Global Trade Research Initiative (GTRI). Founder Ajay Shrivastava projects total exports to reach only around $850 billion, falling short by $150 billion. While services exports show growth, merchandise shipments are stagnant. Achieving the target hinges on major trade agreements and diversifying India's export basket to include more medium to high-tech products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:00:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd4a4e10c98d07888f6e8_1766642915726.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Luxury Housing EXPLODES Beyond Metros: $103 Billion Boom on the Horizon!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Luxury-Housing-EXPLODES-Beyond-Metros-103-Billion-Boom-on-the-Horizon/694cd38be10c98d07888f5b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Luxury-Housing-EXPLODES-Beyond-Metros-103-Billion-Boom-on-the-Horizon/694cd38be10c98d07888f5b3</guid><description>India's premium and luxury housing market is experiencing a significant expansion, shifting demand from major metros to Tier-2 and Tier-3 cities. Projections show this segment growing at a 35% CAGR, from $17 billion in 2024 to over $103 billion by 2030, driven by rising incomes, lifestyle upgrades, and a preference for enhanced living experiences in emerging urban centers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:55:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd38be10c98d07888f5b2_1766642639820.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New Tax Regime Shake-up: Is ELSS Losing Its Luster While PPF Stays Strong?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/New-Tax-Regime-Shake-up-Is-ELSS-Losing-Its-Luster-While-PPF-Stays-Strong/694cce3fe10c98d07888f175</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/New-Tax-Regime-Shake-up-Is-ELSS-Losing-Its-Luster-While-PPF-Stays-Strong/694cce3fe10c98d07888f175</guid><description>India's new optional tax regime, now the default, offers lower tax rates and fewer deductions. This shift has significantly reduced the appeal of Equity Linked Savings Schemes (ELSS). While investments like PPF remain attractive for debt savings, taxpayers are adapting their strategies. Experts advise focusing on goal-based investing rather than solely tax benefits, warning against potential underinvestment due to the reduced compulsion to save for tax purposes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:32:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cce3fe10c98d07888f174_1766641450399.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Symbiotec Pharmalab Launches Massive ₹2,180 Crore IPO: A Game Changer for Pharma Investors?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Symbiotec-Pharmalab-Launches-Massive-2180-Crore-IPO-A-Game-Changer-for-Pharma-Investors/694ccdfee10c98d07888f11d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Symbiotec-Pharmalab-Launches-Massive-2180-Crore-IPO-A-Game-Changer-for-Pharma-Investors/694ccdfee10c98d07888f11d</guid><description>Symbiotec Pharmalab Limited has announced an Initial Public Offering (IPO) worth ₹2,180 crore. The offering includes a ₹150 crore fresh issue to raise capital and a ₹2,030 crore offer for sale by existing shareholders. The company, a global leader in corticosteroid and steroidal-hormone APIs, was advised by Khaitan &amp; Co, while TT&amp;A and Hogan Lovells represented the book running lead managers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:32:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ccdfee10c98d07888f11c_1766641255283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai's New Airport Era Begins: Air India Express Launches Flights, Unlocking Massive Travel Potential!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbais-New-Airport-Era-Begins-Air-India-Express-Launches-Flights-Unlocking-Massive-Travel-Potential/694ccd9fe10c98d07888f063</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbais-New-Airport-Era-Begins-Air-India-Express-Launches-Flights-Unlocking-Massive-Travel-Potential/694ccd9fe10c98d07888f063</guid><description>Air India Express has officially inaugurated commercial operations at the new Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA), becoming one of the first airlines to launch services on its opening day. The Tata Group-owned carrier commenced direct flights to Bengaluru and Delhi, marking a significant step for Mumbai's second aviation gateway. This expansion aims to enhance capacity and ease congestion at the existing Mumbai airport, with further service ramp-ups planned.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:30:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ccd9fe10c98d07888f062_1766641117144.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Invesco India's Top Funds Surge: Discover Top 3 Equity Schemes Beating Benchmarks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Invesco-Indias-Top-Funds-Surge-Discover-Top-3-Equity-Schemes-Beating-Benchmarks/694ccd4be10c98d07888f002</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Invesco-Indias-Top-Funds-Surge-Discover-Top-3-Equity-Schemes-Beating-Benchmarks/694ccd4be10c98d07888f002</guid><description>Invesco India Mutual Fund, managing ₹1.5 trillion, focuses on quality businesses with strong fundamentals, ESG integration, and risk management. This analysis highlights its top 3 equity schemes: Invesco India Small Cap Fund (32.7% 5-yr CAGR vs 30.5% benchmark), Invesco India Focused Fund (23.2% 5-yr CAGR vs 21.2% benchmark), and Invesco India Mid Cap Fund (29.6% 5-yr CAGR vs 28.9% benchmark), all outperforming their respective indices and peers with strong risk-reward ratios.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:27:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ccd4be10c98d07888f001_1766641131360.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Deepak Fertilisers' Bold Move: Acquisition Set to Ignite Explosives Market Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Deepak-Fertilisers-Bold-Move-Acquisition-Set-to-Ignite-Explosives-Market-Growth/694ccd28e10c98d07888efb3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Deepak-Fertilisers-Bold-Move-Acquisition-Set-to-Ignite-Explosives-Market-Growth/694ccd28e10c98d07888efb3</guid><description>Deepak Fertilisers and Petrochemicals Corporation, via its subsidiary Deepak Mining Solutions, has agreed to acquire 100% equity in an unnamed explosives manufacturer. This strategic move aims to boost exports of value-added products and services, leveraging upcoming Technical Ammonium Nitrate (TAN) capacities. The deal value and acquired company name are confidential until the transaction closes, pending fulfillment of certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:27:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ccd28e10c98d07888efb2_1766641011996.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Talks Heat Up: Ambassador Kwatra Reveals Key Progress &amp; Stellar Space Partnership!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-US-Trade-Talks-Heat-Up-Ambassador-Kwatra-Reveals-Key-Progress-and-Stellar-Space-Partnership/694cc7bbe10c98d07888e6f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-US-Trade-Talks-Heat-Up-Ambassador-Kwatra-Reveals-Key-Progress-and-Stellar-Space-Partnership/694cc7bbe10c98d07888e6f0</guid><description>India's Ambassador to the US, Vinay Kwatra, confirmed continuous engagement with the United States Trade Representative (USTR) to forge a mutually beneficial and balanced trade arrangement. He highlighted significant progress in bilateral ties, particularly in space cooperation, citing the recent successful launch of an American commercial satellite by ISRO's LVM3 rocket as a major milestone. This event underscores the deepening partnership between India and the US in technology and exploration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:04:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cc7bbe10c98d07888e6ef_1766639692874.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Cinema Comeback: India's ₹13,500 Crore Box Office Surge! Big Stars Fade, Content Reigns Supreme. Uncover the Secrets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/2026-Cinema-Comeback-Indias-13500-Crore-Box-Office-Surge-Big-Stars-Fade-Content-Reigns-Supreme-Uncover-the-Secrets/694cc62ce10c98d07888e544</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/2026-Cinema-Comeback-Indias-13500-Crore-Box-Office-Surge-Big-Stars-Fade-Content-Reigns-Supreme-Uncover-the-Secrets/694cc62ce10c98d07888e544</guid><description>Indian cinemas are set for a strong 2026, following a robust 2025 projected to close with ₹13,000-13,500 crore in collections, a 10-14% year-on-year increase. While major star-led films saw mixed success, surprise hits and the booming performance of regional cinema underscore a shift. Experts highlight that audiences now prioritize strong narratives and unique concepts over just star power or scale. The industry looks towards original stories, well-made mid-budget films, and stricter adherence to anti-piracy measures and theatrical windows for continued growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:58:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cc62ce10c98d07888e543_1766639208270.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric's Shocking Comeback: Can Bhavish Aggarwal Reclaim Lost Ground From TVS &amp; Bajaj?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Ola-Electrics-Shocking-Comeback-Can-Bhavish-Aggarwal-Reclaim-Lost-Ground-From-TVS-and-Bajaj/694cc5bde10c98d07888e4c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Ola-Electrics-Shocking-Comeback-Can-Bhavish-Aggarwal-Reclaim-Lost-Ground-From-TVS-and-Bajaj/694cc5bde10c98d07888e4c5</guid><description>Once India's EV leader, Ola Electric faces a severe market share decline and valuation drop, now fifth in sales behind TVS Motors and Bajaj Auto. CEO Bhavish Aggarwal sold personal shares to repay loans amid regulatory scrutiny over service and consumer rights. The company is focused on cost-cutting and improving ownership experience while also expanding into battery storage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:54:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cc5bde10c98d07888e4c4_1766639381959.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lenskart Eyes Korea: $23 Million Investment in iiNeer Corp. to Revolutionize Optical Tech!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Lenskart-Eyes-Korea-23-Million-Investment-in-iiNeer-Corp-to-Revolutionize-Optical-Tech/694cc545e10c98d07888e428</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Lenskart-Eyes-Korea-23-Million-Investment-in-iiNeer-Corp-to-Revolutionize-Optical-Tech/694cc545e10c98d07888e428</guid><description>Lenskart Singapore is acquiring a 29.24% stake in South Korean startup iiNeer Corp. for approximately ₹186 million ($23 million). This strategic investment aims to bolster Lenskart's in-house optical hardware capabilities, including lens cutting and testing equipment, promising improved operational efficiencies and cost reductions. The deal is expected to conclude by January 31, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:53:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cc545e10c98d07888e427_1766638980974.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Forces Chase Oil Tanker Away From Venezuela! Is This A New Blockade Tactic?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Forces-Chase-Oil-Tanker-Away-From-Venezuela-Is-This-A-New-Blockade-Tactic/694cc3b4e10c98d07888e281</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Forces-Chase-Oil-Tanker-Away-From-Venezuela-Is-This-A-New-Blockade-Tactic/694cc3b4e10c98d07888e281</guid><description>US forces pursued a sanctioned oil tanker, Bella 1, which turned away from Venezuela towards the Atlantic Ocean. This incident highlights the US strategy under President Trump to pressure Venezuela's government by disrupting its oil exports through an ongoing blockade, a move aiming to squeeze the nation's finances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:44:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cc3b4e10c98d07888e280_1766638767290.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2025's Market Shockwave: Top 5 Nifty 500 Stocks CRASH, Wiping Out Investor Wealth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2025s-Market-Shockwave-Top-5-Nifty-500-Stocks-CRASH-Wiping-Out-Investor-Wealth/694cbdd7e10c98d07888d8e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2025s-Market-Shockwave-Top-5-Nifty-500-Stocks-CRASH-Wiping-Out-Investor-Wealth/694cbdd7e10c98d07888d8e0</guid><description>The Indian stock market experienced significant volatility in 2025. While benchmark indices reached new highs, the broader Nifty 500 index saw major losses. Aditya Birla Fashion and Retail, Tejas Networks, Ola Electric Mobility, SKF India, and Praj Industries were the top five losers, experiencing substantial wealth erosion due to various factors including corporate restructuring, network issues, promoter actions, and weak financial results.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:20:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cbdd7e10c98d07888d8df_1766637088121.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Religare Broking's 2026 Power Picks: 5 Stocks Set for a Massive Surge - Are You Invested?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Religare-Brokings-2026-Power-Picks-5-Stocks-Set-for-a-Massive-Surge-Are-You-Invested/694cbec8e10c98d07888dc6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Religare-Brokings-2026-Power-Picks-5-Stocks-Set-for-a-Massive-Surge-Are-You-Invested/694cbec8e10c98d07888dc6b</guid><description>Religare Broking has identified its top five stock picks for 2026, projecting significant upside potential of up to 24% for select counters over the next 12 months. The chosen companies are Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, Kotak Mahindra Bank, Lupin, ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company, and JK Lakshmi Cement. Religare has assigned 'Buy' ratings, citing robust outlooks driven by innovation, market positioning, and strategic growth plans following a period of market consolidation in 2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:20:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cbec8e10c98d07888dc6a_1766637405410.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Navi Mumbai Airport Takes Flight! India's Aviation Boom Ignites - Key Investor Insights!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Navi-Mumbai-Airport-Takes-Flight-Indias-Aviation-Boom-Ignites-Key-Investor-Insights/694cbd41e10c98d07888d7f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Navi-Mumbai-Airport-Takes-Flight-Indias-Aviation-Boom-Ignites-Key-Investor-Insights/694cbd41e10c98d07888d7f4</guid><description>Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA) has commenced commercial operations, marking a significant milestone for India's aviation sector. The first IndiGo flight arrived from Bengaluru and departed for Hyderabad. Developed by Adani Airports Holdings Limited, NMIA will initially handle 20 million passengers annually, significantly easing congestion for the Mumbai Metropolitan Region and supporting India's growing air travel demand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:19:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cbd41e10c98d07888d7f3_1766636935891.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mines Secretary's Clarion Call to Nalco: Boost Production NOW! Efficiency Drive Mandated Amid Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Mines-Secretarys-Clarion-Call-to-Nalco-Boost-Production-NOW-Efficiency-Drive-Mandated-Amid-Expansion/694cbd3ce10c98d07888d7c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Mines-Secretarys-Clarion-Call-to-Nalco-Boost-Production-NOW-Efficiency-Drive-Mandated-Amid-Expansion/694cbd3ce10c98d07888d7c5</guid><description>Mines Secretary Piyush Goyal reviewed National Aluminium Company Ltd (Nalco), urging it to meet production targets and boost operational efficiency. He stressed timely completion of expansion projects for Nalco's mines, refinery, and smelter complexes in Damanjodi and Angul, emphasizing increased capacity to meet rising domestic aluminium demand from sectors like EVs and infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:19:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cbd3ce10c98d07888d7c4_1766636951185.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Consolidate as IT Stocks Dip; Rupee Weakens Ahead of Holidays!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Consolidate-as-IT-Stocks-Dip-Rupee-Weakens-Ahead-of-Holidays/694cb7e1e10c98d07888d3b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Consolidate-as-IT-Stocks-Dip-Rupee-Weakens-Ahead-of-Holidays/694cb7e1e10c98d07888d3b3</guid><description>Indian equity markets, led by Nifty50, experienced another session of consolidation on Wednesday, struggling to maintain levels above 26,200. Weakness in IT stocks, impacted by a US H1B visa policy change, and a 13-paise depreciation in the Indian Rupee against the dollar marked the day. Investors also tracked positive US jobless claims data. Markets are closed on Thursday for Christmas.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:56:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cb7e1e10c98d07888d3b2_1766635720409.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Power Stocks Plummet: Top Firms Plunge Up to 55% Amidst Soaring Demand, Investors Warned!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indian-Power-Stocks-Plummet-Top-Firms-Plunge-Up-to-55percent-Amidst-Soaring-Demand-Investors-Warned/694cb660e10c98d07888d297</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indian-Power-Stocks-Plummet-Top-Firms-Plunge-Up-to-55percent-Amidst-Soaring-Demand-Investors-Warned/694cb660e10c98d07888d297</guid><description>Despite India's projected 20% surge in electricity demand by 2027 and ongoing grid modernization, four prominent power transmission stocks have seen sharp declines, falling as much as 55% from their 52-week highs. Companies like Transformers and Rectifiers (India), KEC International, Danish Power, and Torrent Power, crucial for the nation's expanding energy infrastructure, are under scrutiny. Investors are advised to exercise caution and conduct thorough due diligence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:50:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cb660e10c98d07888d296_1766635513507.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking Shift: Private Banks Lead Small Business Lending as PSBs Lose Ground to NBFCs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shocking-Shift-Private-Banks-Lead-Small-Business-Lending-as-PSBs-Lose-Ground-to-NBFCs/694cb59be10c98d07888d1cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shocking-Shift-Private-Banks-Lead-Small-Business-Lending-as-PSBs-Lose-Ground-to-NBFCs/694cb59be10c98d07888d1cb</guid><description>A report by SIDBI and CRIF High Mark reveals private banks now lead small business lending in India. Public sector banks (PSBs) have lost market share over the last two years, dropping to 37.8% by September 2025, with non-banking financial companies (NBFCs) steadily gaining ground, especially among sole proprietors. Overall credit exposure to small businesses reached ₹46 lakh crore, growing 16.2% year-on-year, driven by MSME support policies. Working capital loans remain dominant, while unsecured lending also shows strong momentum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:47:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cb59be10c98d07888d1ca_1766634974412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Auto Giant's Secret European Conquest: Motherson Buys Luxury Car's Lifeline!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Auto-Giants-Secret-European-Conquest-Motherson-Buys-Luxury-Cars-Lifeline/694cb557e10c98d07888d165</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Auto-Giants-Secret-European-Conquest-Motherson-Buys-Luxury-Cars-Lifeline/694cb557e10c98d07888d165</guid><description>Samvardhana Motherson International is acquiring Nexans Autoelectric, a German wiring harness maker crucial for BMW, Mercedes-Benz, and Porsche. This strategic move provides direct access to the high-end European automotive market. Analysts from Nomura and Motilal Oswal have reiterated Buy ratings, predicting significant earnings growth and seamless integration of this €749 million sales business.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:46:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cb557e10c98d07888d164_1766634908006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Novo Nordisk Eyes India's Rare Disease Market: New Centers &amp; Govt. Ties Fuel Ambitious Expansion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisk-Eyes-Indias-Rare-Disease-Market-New-Centers-and-Govt-Ties-Fuel-Ambitious-Expansion/694cb533e10c98d07888d11f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisk-Eyes-Indias-Rare-Disease-Market-New-Centers-and-Govt-Ties-Fuel-Ambitious-Expansion/694cb533e10c98d07888d11f</guid><description>Danish pharmaceutical giant Novo Nordisk is significantly expanding its presence in India's rare diseases sector, focusing on inherited blood disorders like thalassemia and sickle cell disease. The company plans to open five new specialized treatment centers by 2026, in addition to one already established, and is collaborating closely with Central and State governments to support affected families and patients. This strategic move aligns with India's national goals to reduce these conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:46:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cb533e10c98d07888d11e_1766634881210.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty 50 SHOCKER: These 5 Stocks MORE THAN DOUBLED Investor Wealth in 2025! Are You In?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-50-SHOCKER-These-5-Stocks-MORE-THAN-DOUBLED-Investor-Wealth-in-2025-Are-You-In/694ca4bfe10c98d07888c2e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-50-SHOCKER-These-5-Stocks-MORE-THAN-DOUBLED-Investor-Wealth-in-2025-Are-You-In/694ca4bfe10c98d07888c2e4</guid><description>In a volatile 2025, five Nifty 50 giants defied the market, delivering over 40% year-to-date returns. From automotive recovery to financial expansion, these stocks have rewarded shareholders significantly, showcasing pockets of strong growth amidst market uncertainties. Key drivers include robust revenue increases and profit surges, making them standouts for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 02:36:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ca4bfe10c98d07888c2e3_1766630659487.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Stock Market EXPLODES in 2025! Sensex, Nifty &amp; More Smash All-Time Highs – What You NEED to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Stock-Market-EXPLODES-in-2025-Sensex-Nifty-and-More-Smash-All-Time-Highs-What-You-NEED-to-Know/694c9a61e10c98d07888a155</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Stock-Market-EXPLODES-in-2025-Sensex-Nifty-and-More-Smash-All-Time-Highs-What-You-NEED-to-Know/694c9a61e10c98d07888a155</guid><description>In 2025, India's stock market witnessed historic milestones as key indices like the BSE Sensex and Nifty 50 surged to unprecedented all-time highs. The Sensex closed at a record 86,159.02, while the Nifty 50 reached 26,325.80. The Bank Nifty also broke the 60,000 mark, with midcap and broader indices like Nifty Midcap 100 and Nifty 500 joining the rally, signaling a robust year for Indian equities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:49:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9a61e10c98d07888a154_1766628003138.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Uncover India's Next Multibaggers: 3 Hidden Cable Stocks Set for Explosive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Uncover-Indias-Next-Multibaggers-3-Hidden-Cable-Stocks-Set-for-Explosive-Growth/694c9b33e10c98d07888a263</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Uncover-Indias-Next-Multibaggers-3-Hidden-Cable-Stocks-Set-for-Explosive-Growth/694c9b33e10c98d07888a263</guid><description>As India's infrastructure boom accelerates, demand for cables and wires surges across sectors like power, railways, and green energy. While large players like Polycab India Limited and KEI Industries Limited are well-known, this analysis highlights three small-cap cable manufacturers – Dynamic Cables Limited, Universal Cables Limited, and Paramount Communications Limited – that offer greater multibagger potential. The article explains how operating leverage, increasing capacity utilization, and absorption of fixed costs can drive significant earnings growth for these less-recognized companies, offering investors opportunities beyond the market leaders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:49:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9b33e10c98d07888a262_1766628313684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FIIs &amp; DIIs Pour Billions Into THIS AC Stock As Sector Tanks! Find Out Why!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FIIs-and-DIIs-Pour-Billions-Into-THIS-AC-Stock-As-Sector-Tanks-Find-Out-Why/694c9a45e10c98d07888a113</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FIIs-and-DIIs-Pour-Billions-Into-THIS-AC-Stock-As-Sector-Tanks-Find-Out-Why/694c9a45e10c98d07888a113</guid><description>Despite a 10.5% annual drop in the Nifty Consumer Durable index and significant FII selling worth ₹11,130 crore in Q2FY26, institutional investors are heavily backing Amber Enterprise India Limited. Both FIIs and DIIs increased their stakes, signaling confidence in the company's diversification into electronics manufacturing services, railway components, and solar/EV sectors, even as the company reported a Q2 loss. Amber Enterprise is a key AC component manufacturer and is expanding aggressively, particularly in PCB manufacturing facilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:49:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9a45e10c98d07888a112_1766628108519.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unseen Hero: The 'Tyre Skeleton' Stock Making Every 2nd Car Run Safely - Discover Rajratan's Hidden Empire!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Unseen-Hero-The-Tyre-Skeleton-Stock-Making-Every-2nd-Car-Run-Safely-Discover-Rajratans-Hidden-Empire/694c9a1be10c98d07888a0c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Unseen-Hero-The-Tyre-Skeleton-Stock-Making-Every-2nd-Car-Run-Safely-Discover-Rajratans-Hidden-Empire/694c9a1be10c98d07888a0c3</guid><description>Rajratan Global Wire Ltd is the dominant leader in India's essential bead wire market, the critical 'tyre skeleton' that ensures tyre safety. With over 50% domestic market share and a strategic international presence, particularly in Thailand, the company supplies major global tyre manufacturers, underpinning its vital role in the automotive sector. Its specialized product and long OEM approval cycles create a strong competitive moat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:49:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9a1be10c98d07888a0c2_1766627932891.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jaipur's Spice IPO Shatters Records: 918x Oversubscribed, Pulls in ₹25,300 Crore Bids!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Jaipurs-Spice-IPO-Shatters-Records-918x-Oversubscribed-Pulls-in-25300-Crore-Bids/694c991ae10c98d078889f5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Jaipurs-Spice-IPO-Shatters-Records-918x-Oversubscribed-Pulls-in-25300-Crore-Bids/694c991ae10c98d078889f5a</guid><description>Jaipur-based Shyam Dhani Industries' initial public offering (IPO) for its masala products was massively oversubscribed, hitting 918 times its target. The ₹38.5 crore IPO received bids worth approximately ₹25,300 crore, making it the fifth most subscribed SME IPO in India's history and the top performer for 2025. Funds will support working capital, loan repayment, marketing, and expansion, including a solar plant.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:43:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c991ae10c98d078889f59_1766627690511.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tired of Surprise Subscription Bills? NPCI's New Portal Makes Managing Autopay Effortless!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tired-of-Surprise-Subscription-Bills-NPCIs-New-Portal-Makes-Managing-Autopay-Effortless/694c9972e10c98d078889fe1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tired-of-Surprise-Subscription-Bills-NPCIs-New-Portal-Makes-Managing-Autopay-Effortless/694c9972e10c98d078889fe1</guid><description>The National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI) has launched a new central portal, upihelp.npci.org.in, simplifying the management of UPI autopay standing instructions. This initiative aims to enhance transparency and consumer control over recurring charges and subscriptions, curbing opaque billing practices. By December 31, 2025, all UPI network members must implement these changes, allowing users to view, manage, and even port mandates across different UPI apps with enhanced security features.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:43:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9972e10c98d078889fe0_1766627853673.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tired of Surprise Subscription Bills? NPCI's New Portal Makes Managing Autopay Effortless!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tired-of-Surprise-Subscription-Bills-NPCIs-New-Portal-Makes-Managing-Autopay-Effortless/694c9931e10c98d078889f85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tired-of-Surprise-Subscription-Bills-NPCIs-New-Portal-Makes-Managing-Autopay-Effortless/694c9931e10c98d078889f85</guid><description>The National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI) has launched a new central portal, upihelp.npci.org.in, simplifying the management of UPI autopay standing instructions. This initiative aims to enhance transparency and consumer control over recurring charges and subscriptions, curbing opaque billing practices. By December 31, 2025, all UPI network members must implement these changes, allowing users to view, manage, and even port mandates across different UPI apps with enhanced security features.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:43:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9931e10c98d078889f84_1766627724393.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Engineer Built Buffett's $174 Billion Cash Machine: The Secret to Berkshire's Success Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Engineer-Built-Buffetts-174-Billion-Cash-Machine-The-Secret-to-Berkshires-Success-Revealed/694c927de10c98d078889b20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Engineer-Built-Buffetts-174-Billion-Cash-Machine-The-Secret-to-Berkshires-Success-Revealed/694c927de10c98d078889b20</guid><description>Ajit Jain, an Indian engineer with no finance background, transformed Berkshire Hathaway's struggling reinsurance business under Warren Buffett. He masterfully managed the company's 'float' – premiums collected but not yet paid out – growing it to $174 billion. This capital pool, generating billions annually, fuels Buffett's investments and highlights Jain's pivotal role in Berkshire's vast empire.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:16:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c927de10c98d078889b1f_1766625997375.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Buffett Era Ends! Greg Abel Takes Over Berkshire's $1.1 Trillion Empire – 5 Key Changes Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Buffett-Era-Ends-Greg-Abel-Takes-Over-Berkshires-11-Trillion-Empire-5-Key-Changes-Ahead/694c9248e10c98d078889ad3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Buffett-Era-Ends-Greg-Abel-Takes-Over-Berkshires-11-Trillion-Empire-5-Key-Changes-Ahead/694c9248e10c98d078889ad3</guid><description>Greg Abel is set to succeed Warren Buffett as CEO of Berkshire Hathaway by the end of 2026. Abel, known for his strong financial background and success scaling Berkshire Hathaway Energy, is expected to bring a more active management style and tackle the challenge of deploying Berkshire's substantial $334 billion cash reserves. Investors anticipate a focus on operational rigor and potentially new sectors like technology and renewable energy, marking a significant shift from Buffett's era.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:16:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9248e10c98d078889ad2_1766626140114.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Doubles Duplicate Securities Limit to ₹10 Lakh: Faster Process for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Doubles-Duplicate-Securities-Limit-to-10-Lakh-Faster-Process-for-Investors/694c920de10c98d078889a7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Doubles-Duplicate-Securities-Limit-to-10-Lakh-Faster-Process-for-Investors/694c920de10c98d078889a7f</guid><description>SEBI has significantly eased the process for issuing duplicate securities by doubling the monetary threshold for simplified documentation to ₹10 lakh. Investors holding securities valued up to ₹10,000 can now submit a simple undertaking on plain paper, while those above ₹10 lakh will need additional documents like an FIR or police complaint. Notarization is waived for lower-value holdings. These measures aim to make the process faster, more efficient, and promote dematerialization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:15:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c920de10c98d078889a7e_1766625876676.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Supercharges Auto Sector! Govt Nearly Doubles EV Funds – Big Wins or Missed Opportunities Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Supercharges-Auto-Sector-Govt-Nearly-Doubles-EV-Funds-Big-Wins-or-Missed-Opportunities-Ahead/694c8d80e10c98d078889839</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Supercharges-Auto-Sector-Govt-Nearly-Doubles-EV-Funds-Big-Wins-or-Missed-Opportunities-Ahead/694c8d80e10c98d078889839</guid><description>India's government plans to nearly double funding for its auto and auto component Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme to ₹5,500 crore in FY27, reinforcing its commitment to electric vehicle (EV) manufacturing and advanced automotive tech. Despite the increased allocation, new EV makers like Ather Energy are unlikely to get their application window reopened, as the scheme's eligibility criteria continue to favour established players. The move aims to boost domestic production, attract investment, and create jobs in the rapidly growing EV market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:53:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8d80e10c98d078889838_1766624845857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>