<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:43:29 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Eicher Motors January Sales Jump 14%, YTD Growth Hits 25% on Strong Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Eicher-Motors-January-Sales-Jump-14percent-YTD-Growth-Hits-25percent-on-Strong-Demand/697ef37146be08bbe62fced4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Eicher-Motors-January-Sales-Jump-14percent-YTD-Growth-Hits-25percent-on-Strong-Demand/697ef37146be08bbe62fced4</guid><description>Eicher Motors posted a robust 14% YoY increase in January sales, selling 1,04,322 motorcycles. Year-to-date, the company achieved a significant 25% growth, surpassing 1 million units globally. Domestic sales climbed 16% in January, while exports saw a 30% YTD surge. Performance is driven by &lt;350cc models, with new product launches and innovative marketing collaborations bolstering the outlook.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Market Pauses: Circuit Breakers Stabilize Amid Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Pauses-Circuit-Breakers-Stabilize-Amid-Volatility/697ef33346be08bbe62fce21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Pauses-Circuit-Breakers-Stabilize-Amid-Volatility/697ef33346be08bbe62fce21</guid><description>Exchanges employ market-wide circuit breakers to manage extreme price swings, temporarily halting trading to allow for reassessment and prevent panic. Activated by significant declines in benchmark indices like the S&amp;P 500, these pauses aim to restore order and facilitate informed decision-making. This mechanism is particularly relevant in the current uncertain economic environment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Paisalo Digital: Debt Overhaul Fuels Stock Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digital-Debt-Overhaul-Fuels-Stock-Surge/697ef31246be08bbe62fcd87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digital-Debt-Overhaul-Fuels-Stock-Surge/697ef31246be08bbe62fcd87</guid><description>Paisalo Digital Limited has successfully completed the redemption of significant Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) and secured new capital at a reduced cost. This financial recalibration follows a Rs 188.5 crore capital raise at an 8.5% interest rate, aimed at expanding its "High Tech-High Touch" distribution model. The company's stock has responded positively, trading up from its 52-week low, reflecting investor confidence in its debt management and growth strategy.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MIC Electronics Wins Contracts, Eyes Infrastructure Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MIC-Electronics-Wins-Contracts-Eyes-Infrastructure-Boom/697ef2f946be08bbe62fcd1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MIC-Electronics-Wins-Contracts-Eyes-Infrastructure-Boom/697ef2f946be08bbe62fcd1f</guid><description>MIC Electronics Ltd has landed significant contract wins, including a Rs 114.10 crore project for Nava Raipur and orders under the Amrit Bharat Scheme. These drive a 668% surge in Q3 FY26 net sales to Rs 90.23 crore, though 9MFY26 net profit experienced a slight dip. The company, a small-cap with a market cap over Rs 1,000 crore, boasts exceptional historical shareholder returns and maintains a substantial promoter stake.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's UPI Shatters Records: January Transactions Top ₹28 Trillion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-UPI-Shatters-Records-January-Transactions-Top-28-Trillion/697ef27e46be08bbe62fcc14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-UPI-Shatters-Records-January-Transactions-Top-28-Trillion/697ef27e46be08bbe62fcc14</guid><description>UPI transactions reached a record ₹28.33 trillion and 21.7 billion in volume during January. National Payments Corporation of India data shows a 21% increase from December, highlighting robust growth in India's digital payment ecosystem. Daily transactions averaged 700 million.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Metals Plunge: Profit-Taking, Stronger Dollar Trigger Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metals-Plunge-Profit-Taking-Stronger-Dollar-Trigger-Sell-Off/697ef22e46be08bbe62fcb20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metals-Plunge-Profit-Taking-Stronger-Dollar-Trigger-Sell-Off/697ef22e46be08bbe62fcb20</guid><description>Gold, silver, and industrial metals are experiencing a significant market correction. This downturn follows a period of historic rallies and is driven by a confluence of economic factors including investor profit-taking, a strengthened U.S. dollar alongside rising real yields, leverage-induced forced selling, and concerns over global economic growth affecting base metals. The CME's increase in margin requirements has further amplified selling pressure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Defence Stocks Surge Ahead of Budget 2026 Amid Geopolitical Alerts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Stocks-Surge-Ahead-of-Budget-2026-Amid-Geopolitical-Alerts/697ef21a46be08bbe62fcae7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Stocks-Surge-Ahead-of-Budget-2026-Amid-Geopolitical-Alerts/697ef21a46be08bbe62fcae7</guid><description>Investor optimism fueled a significant surge in India's defence sector stocks on Sunday, February 1, 2026, propelling the Nifty India Defence index up by 1.6%. This ascent, occurring in an otherwise subdued market, is largely attributed to expectations of heightened government spending in the upcoming Union Budget 2026-27. Factors such as escalating global geopolitical tensions, a strategic push for force modernization, and the continuation of the indigenisation policy are reinforcing investor confidence in domestic defence manufacturers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Budget Eyes Biopharma Hub; Stocks Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Budget-Eyes-Biopharma-Hub-Stocks-Rise/697ef18d46be08bbe62fca24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Budget-Eyes-Biopharma-Hub-Stocks-Rise/697ef18d46be08bbe62fca24</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Union Budget 2026 announced a ₹10,000 crore "Biopharma Shakti" program over five years, aiming to establish India as a biopharmaceutical manufacturing hub. This strategic allocation spurred immediate gains across the sector, with Biocon Ltd. leading the surge. The move signals robust government backing for advanced pharmaceutical capabilities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Govt Staff Poised for 5% DA Hike on Stable CPI-IW</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Govt-Staff-Poised-for-5percent-DA-Hike-on-Stable-CPI-IW/697ef11846be08bbe62fc9af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Govt-Staff-Poised-for-5percent-DA-Hike-on-Stable-CPI-IW/697ef11846be08bbe62fc9af</guid><description>Millions of central government employees and pensioners are set to receive a substantial 5 percentage point Dearness Allowance (DA) hike. This anticipated adjustment, likely reaching 63%, follows the Labour Bureau's report of a stable Consumer Price Index for Industrial Workers (CPI-IW) at 148.2 points for December 2025. The move aims to protect real incomes against inflation, which showed moderating year-on-year trends.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:23:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef11846be08bbe62fc9ae_1769927003549.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE Eyes Diwali Listing Amid Budget Clarity Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-Eyes-Diwali-Listing-Amid-Budget-Clarity-Hopes/697eeec246be08bbe62fc53b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-Eyes-Diwali-Listing-Amid-Budget-Clarity-Hopes/697eeec246be08bbe62fc53b</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange (NSE) has signaled a potential listing by this year's Diwali Muhurat trading session, according to MD &amp; CEO Ashishkumar Chauhan. This comes as market participants gear up for the Union Budget, with industry leaders articulating key expectations for policy stability, fiscal prudence, and a streamlined investment process. Key proposals include rationalizing taxes for foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) and fostering an environment of 'liberalization' for entrepreneurs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eeec246be08bbe62fc53a_1769926806160.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Intellect Design: Profit Hit by Costs, But Deal Pipeline Strengthens</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Intellect-Design-Profit-Hit-by-Costs-But-Deal-Pipeline-Strengthens/697ef09f46be08bbe62fc904</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Intellect-Design-Profit-Hit-by-Costs-But-Deal-Pipeline-Strengthens/697ef09f46be08bbe62fc904</guid><description>Intellect Design Arena reported a sharp 61% year-on-year decline in net profit to ₹27.4 crore for Q3 FY26, despite a healthy 20% revenue increase to ₹732 crore. Profitability was significantly impacted by higher operational investments and a ₹30.84 crore one-time gratuity expense related to new labor codes. While margins contracted to 13.9%, the company highlighted a robust deal pipeline and increased average deal sizes, signaling underlying operational strength.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:21:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef09f46be08bbe62fc903_1769926890696.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Launches ISM 2.0, Pledges $54B to Boost Chip Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Launches-ISM-20-Pledges-54B-to-Boost-Chip-Sector/697eefae46be08bbe62fc7d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Launches-ISM-20-Pledges-54B-to-Boost-Chip-Sector/697eefae46be08bbe62fc7d6</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced the launch of India Semiconductor Mission (ISM) 2.0, aiming for full value-chain expansion and technological depth in the chip sector. Building on previous successes, the initiative includes a significant increase in funding for the Electronics Components Manufacturing Scheme (ECMS), now proposed at ₹40,000 crore. This move targets indigenous IP creation, specialized research centers, and advanced manufacturing capabilities to reduce import reliance and capitalize on a soaring global demand for semiconductors, projected to exceed $1 trillion by 2030.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:18:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eefae46be08bbe62fc7d5_1769926636968.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Growth, Aspirations, Inclusion Drive Fiscal Path</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Growth-Aspirations-Inclusion-Drive-Fiscal-Path/697eef3d46be08bbe62fc67e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Growth-Aspirations-Inclusion-Drive-Fiscal-Path/697eef3d46be08bbe62fc67e</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026, presented by Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, is anchored by three primary 'kartavyas' or guiding duties: fostering sustained economic growth with global resilience, fulfilling citizen aspirations through enhanced job opportunities and income stability, and ensuring inclusive development for all societal segments. Expert analysis highlights a strategic shift towards competitiveness-driven growth and emphasizes that successful outcomes will hinge on effective execution at the state and local levels, rather than fiscal expansion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:16:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eef3d46be08bbe62fc67d_1769926563040.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PVV Infra Plans ₹49 Cr Rights Issue Amid Revenue Drop, PAT Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PVV-Infra-Plans-49-Cr-Rights-Issue-Amid-Revenue-Drop-PAT-Surge/697eeecf46be08bbe62fc593</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PVV-Infra-Plans-49-Cr-Rights-Issue-Amid-Revenue-Drop-PAT-Surge/697eeecf46be08bbe62fc593</guid><description>PVV Infra Limited is launching a ₹49.33 crore rights issue to bolster working capital and fund general corporate needs. Despite a significant revenue decline from ₹87.92 Cr to ₹39.85 Cr in FY25, the company reported a PAT jump to ₹5.48 Cr from ₹3.09 Cr. However, operating cash flow turned negative at ₹25.08 Cr. Promoters have committed to subscribing their full entitlement.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:14:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eeecf46be08bbe62fc592_1769926497055.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE IPO Nod Triggers BSE Slump, IFCI Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NSE-IPO-Nod-Triggers-BSE-Slump-IFCI-Soars/697eee4b46be08bbe62fc456</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NSE-IPO-Nod-Triggers-BSE-Slump-IFCI-Soars/697eee4b46be08bbe62fc456</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has granted a No Objection Certificate (NOC) for the National Stock Exchange's (NSE) long-awaited Initial Public Offering (IPO). This development led to immediate, contrasting market reactions on February 1, 2026. Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) shares fell nearly 6%, while IFCI shares jumped approximately 12%. IFCI's gain is directly linked to its indirect ownership stake in NSE via its majority holding in Stock Holding Corporation of India (SHCIL). The NSE is expected to file its draft IPO papers within the next 4-5 months, with the offering structured as an Offer for Sale (OFS).</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:14:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eee4b46be08bbe62fc455_1769926393690.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Forms Rare Earth Corridors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Forms-Rare-Earth-Corridors/697eee4646be08bbe62fc443</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Forms-Rare-Earth-Corridors/697eee4646be08bbe62fc443</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced dedicated rare earth corridors across Odisha, Kerala, Andhra Pradesh, and Tamil Nadu as part of the Union Budget 2026-27. This strategic initiative aims to bolster India's domestic manufacturing capabilities and reduce reliance on imports for critical minerals, building upon prior efforts to stimulate local magnet production. The move acknowledges global supply chain volatilities and India's broader push for resource self-sufficiency.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:12:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eee4646be08bbe62fc442_1769926287465.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India FY27 Budget: Rs 12.2L Cr Capex Fuels Public Investment Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-FY27-Budget-Rs-122L-Cr-Capex-Fuels-Public-Investment-Drive/697eed7646be08bbe62fc2e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-FY27-Budget-Rs-122L-Cr-Capex-Fuels-Public-Investment-Drive/697eed7646be08bbe62fc2e7</guid><description>India's Union Budget for Fiscal Year 2027 has earmarked a record ₹12.2 lakh crore for capital expenditure, a significant escalation from the previous year's ₹11.21 lakh crore. This move signals a reinforced commitment to public investment as a primary driver of economic growth, particularly as private sector capital expenditure remains subdued due to policy uncertainties and demand concerns. The strategy aims to stimulate infrastructure development, job creation, and overall productivity, echoing recommendations from the Economic Survey.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:10:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eed7646be08bbe62fc2e6_1769926139199.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exchanges Hike Precious Metal Margins Post-Crash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Exchanges-Hike-Precious-Metal-Margins-Post-Crash/697eed5746be08bbe62fc28f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Exchanges-Hike-Precious-Metal-Margins-Post-Crash/697eed5746be08bbe62fc28f</guid><description>Following unprecedented price volatility and sharp declines in gold and silver on January 31, 2026, MCX and CME Group are implementing significant increases to margin requirements for precious metals futures. Effective February 1 and 2, 2026, respectively, these measures aim to mitigate risk but signal a shift towards tighter market controls, potentially affecting trading liquidity and accessibility for participants.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eed5746be08bbe62fc28e_1769926041330.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Growth Push Amid Global Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Growth-Push-Amid-Global-Uncertainty/697eecdb46be08bbe62fc1cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Growth-Push-Amid-Global-Uncertainty/697eecdb46be08bbe62fc1cf</guid><description>Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman presented the Union Budget 2026 against a backdrop of global economic volatility, driven by US trade policy shifts. The budget prioritizes sustaining India's robust GDP growth, projected to reach 7.4% in FY26, and fostering job creation through increased infrastructure spending. Key initiatives include potential tax relief, policy adjustments for exports, and manufacturing sector support, aiming to keep the economy in a 'Goldilocks' zone of high growth and low inflation, bolstered by record foreign exchange reserves.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:06:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eecdb46be08bbe62fc1ce_1769925921762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metal Stocks Plunge Amid Global Gloom, Budget Buzz</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Stocks-Plunge-Amid-Global-Gloom-Budget-Buzz/697eeb9946be08bbe62fc010</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Stocks-Plunge-Amid-Global-Gloom-Budget-Buzz/697eeb9946be08bbe62fc010</guid><description>The Indian metals sector experienced a significant downturn on February 1, 2026, with major players like Vedanta, Hindustan Zinc, Hindustan Copper, and National Aluminium Company (NALCO) hitting considerable losses. The Nifty Metal index saw a notable decline. This sell-off was fueled by escalating worries over global economic growth, heightened commodity price volatility, and cautious investor sentiment ahead of the Union Budget, which has prompted a defensive rotation in equities. Key commodity markets, particularly silver and gold, witnessed dramatic price corrections, exacerbating the pressure on metal counters.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eeb9946be08bbe62fc00f_1769925715637.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Plunge: Metal, Finance Stocks Tumble</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Plunge-Metal-Finance-Stocks-Tumble/697eeb8146be08bbe62fbf91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Plunge-Metal-Finance-Stocks-Tumble/697eeb8146be08bbe62fbf91</guid><description>Gold and silver prices plummeted Sunday, sparking a significant downturn across Indian metal and gold finance equities. Hindustan Zinc shares dropped 13.5%, while MCX saw a 15% decline. Gold financiers like Muthoot Finance fell nearly 8%, Manappuram Finance 6%, and IIFL Finance 5%. This broad market weakness underscores investor concern over commodity price volatility and its impact on company valuations and earnings prospects.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eeb8146be08bbe62fbf90_1769925600735.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Plunge: India's Fundamentals Unsettled by Capital Flight</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Plunge-Indias-Fundamentals-Unsettled-by-Capital-Flight/697ee5d846be08bbe62fb6a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Plunge-Indias-Fundamentals-Unsettled-by-Capital-Flight/697ee5d846be08bbe62fb6a1</guid><description>The Indian rupee has rapidly depreciated to 92 against the US dollar, a move economist Jahangir Aziz attributes not to poor economic performance but to a critical shortfall in capital inflows. Despite robust GDP growth of 6.6% in 2025, inflation averaging 1.7% in April-December 2025, and a current account deficit of 0.8% of GDP in H1 FY26, the currency weakness persists. This indicates a capital account deficit, impacting both FDI and FPI, with private equity firms notably opting out of reinvestment in India, suggesting a crisis of investor confidence rather than economic fundamentals.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:52:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee5d846be08bbe62fb6a0_1769925012610.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCX Precious Metals Tumble on Dollar Strength, Budget Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Precious-Metals-Tumble-on-Dollar-Strength-Budget-Fears/697ee65846be08bbe62fb9c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Precious-Metals-Tumble-on-Dollar-Strength-Budget-Fears/697ee65846be08bbe62fb9c0</guid><description>Multi Commodity Exchange (MCX) gold and silver futures opened sharply lower on February 1, continuing a steep decline initiated on Friday. At approximately 10:00 AM IST, MCX gold futures traded down 6.72% at Rs 1,40,000 per 10 grams, while silver futures plummeted 8.98% to Rs 2,65,701 per kilogram. This sharp correction follows significant single-day losses on January 30, attributed to profit-booking, a strengthening US dollar, and market reactions to a key US Federal Reserve nomination.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee65846be08bbe62fb9bf_1769924925184.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Surpasses ₹10 Trillion Market Cap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Surpasses-10-Trillion-Market-Cap/697ee74146be08bbe62fbbfe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Surpasses-10-Trillion-Market-Cap/697ee74146be08bbe62fbbfe</guid><description>State Bank of India has achieved a significant ₹10 trillion market capitalization, marking a new peak for the public sector lender. This valuation underscores the bank's robust performance year-to-date in 2026, where it has significantly outpaced the benchmark Sensex and its private sector peers like HDFC Bank and ICICI Bank. With strong credit growth forecasts and strategic initiatives in motion, SBI is positioned for continued expansion as it prepares to announce its third-quarter financial results.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:48:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee74146be08bbe62fbbfd_1769924801621.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Precious Metals Plunge: ETFs Hit by Budget Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Plunge-ETFs-Hit-by-Budget-Jitters/697ee7bc46be08bbe62fbd09</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Plunge-ETFs-Hit-by-Budget-Jitters/697ee7bc46be08bbe62fbd09</guid><description>Precious metals investors faced a brutal reversal on Sunday, February 1, 2026, as Gold and Silver Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) plummeted. Losses ranged up to 20%, reversing months of gains. The downturn was fueled by speculative profit-taking, apprehension over Union Budget 2026 implications, a strengthening US dollar, and increased margin requirements by CME Group. This correction hit ETFs across the board, prompting exchanges to impose circuit breakers and remind investors of direct redemption avenues via Asset Management Companies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee7bc46be08bbe62fbd08_1769924690387.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bullion Crash Sinks MCX Shares Amid Budget Session Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Bullion-Crash-Sinks-MCX-Shares-Amid-Budget-Session-Volatility/697ee75246be08bbe62fbc50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Bullion-Crash-Sinks-MCX-Shares-Amid-Budget-Session-Volatility/697ee75246be08bbe62fbc50</guid><description>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd (MCX) shares experienced a sharp 17% decline, their steepest in nearly five years, during a special Sunday trading session on February 1, 2026. The sell-off was triggered by an unprecedented crash in bullion prices, particularly silver, which significantly impacts the exchange's primary revenue driver. Despite robust Q3 FY26 financial results, the dramatic fall in gold and silver futures over preceding sessions and continued volatility prompted aggressive profit-taking.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:44:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee75246be08bbe62fbc4f_1769924577692.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Seals EU Trade Deal, Eyes Critical Minerals with Chile</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Seals-EU-Trade-Deal-Eyes-Critical-Minerals-with-Chile/697ee66646be08bbe62fba3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Seals-EU-Trade-Deal-Eyes-Critical-Minerals-with-Chile/697ee66646be08bbe62fba3b</guid><description>India has concluded a historic Free Trade Agreement with the European Union, marking its eighth major trade pact finalized in recent years. This strategic push includes ongoing negotiations with Chile and Peru, aimed at securing vital critical minerals crucial for advanced industries. These agreements signal India's intent to aggressively expand its global economic footprint and leverage its growing market power.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:42:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee66646be08bbe62fba3a_1769924459717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Fears Sink Broking Stocks in Special Session</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Budget-Fears-Sink-Broking-Stocks-in-Special-Session/697ee68146be08bbe62fbb28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Budget-Fears-Sink-Broking-Stocks-in-Special-Session/697ee68146be08bbe62fbb28</guid><description>Financial sector stocks, including BSE, Angel One, Nuvama Wealth Management, and IIFL Capital Services, experienced notable declines during a special trading session on Sunday, February 1, 2026. The sell-off is attributed to heightened investor nervousness ahead of the Union Budget 2026-27 announcement, with particular concern focused on potential changes to Securities Transaction Tax (STT) and Long-Term Capital Gains (LTCG) tax provisions. These fiscal adjustments could directly impact trading volumes and company earnings.

BSE Ltd. recorded the most significant loss, falling approximately 5.68% to ₹2,638. Angel One followed, dropping 4.8%, while Nuvama Wealth Management and IIFL Capital Services saw dips of over 3% and 2.9% respectively. The market's performance reflects a cautious stance as traders await clarity on potential tax policy shifts that could affect the stockbroking and financial services ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:40:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee68146be08bbe62fbb27_1769924365358.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta Shares Tumble on Global Metal Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Vedanta-Shares-Tumble-on-Global-Metal-Slump/697ee5e846be08bbe62fb6f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Vedanta-Shares-Tumble-on-Global-Metal-Slump/697ee5e846be08bbe62fb6f7</guid><description>Vedanta Ltd. experienced a significant stock price decline on Sunday, February 1, 2026, with shares falling up to 10% intraday. This slump was primarily driven by a severe overnight correction in global precious metal markets, particularly gold and silver, which triggered a broad sell-off across commodity-sensitive equities, including Vedanta's subsidiaries Hindustan Zinc and Hindustan Copper. Despite the market volatility, Vedanta's recent Q3 financial results showcased robust year-on-year growth in profit, revenue, and EBITDA.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:37:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee5e846be08bbe62fb6f6_1769924227355.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's January GST Roars, Bolstering Fiscal Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-January-GST-Roars-Bolstering-Fiscal-Outlook/697ee46c46be08bbe62fb1cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-January-GST-Roars-Bolstering-Fiscal-Outlook/697ee46c46be08bbe62fb1cb</guid><description>India's Goods and Services Tax (GST) revenue for January 2026 surged to ₹1.93 lakh crore, marking a 6.2% year-on-year increase. This performance, reflecting stable consumption and tax compliance, contributes significantly to the nation's fiscal health as the Union Budget 2026 approaches. Cumulative collections for April-January FY26 reached ₹18.43 lakh crore, an 8.3% rise, driven by both domestic transactions and a robust 10.1% jump in import-related GST. Net revenue after refunds also saw a healthy 7.6% growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:35:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee46c46be08bbe62fb1ca_1769924124086.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Education Overhaul: Budget 2026 Focus on Skills &amp; AI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Education-Overhaul-Budget-2026-Focus-on-Skills-and-AI/697ee48846be08bbe62fb250</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Education-Overhaul-Budget-2026-Focus-on-Skills-and-AI/697ee48846be08bbe62fb250</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Union Budget 2026-27 is set to detail increased allocations for India's education sector, aiming to bolster quality and relevance in line with the National Education Policy (NEP) 2020. Previous allocations saw a steady rise, reaching ₹1.28 lakh crore in FY26. Key priorities include enhancing skills, integrating Artificial Intelligence (AI) into learning, and improving teacher preparedness to address the persistent employability gap and prepare a future-ready workforce.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:33:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee48846be08bbe62fb24f_1769923989887.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metal Stocks Tumble as Gold, Silver Prices Crash Post-Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Stocks-Tumble-as-Gold-Silver-Prices-Crash-Post-Rally/697ee4bc46be08bbe62fb2e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Stocks-Tumble-as-Gold-Silver-Prices-Crash-Post-Rally/697ee4bc46be08bbe62fb2e3</guid><description>Budget Day saw a steep sell-off in Indian metal stocks as global gold and silver prices experienced a sharp correction after record rallies. MCX shares hit a 10% lower circuit, Hindustan Copper plunged 15%, Hindustan Zinc dropped 10%, and Hindalco also saw a 10% decline. This market turmoil follows extraordinary gains in precious metals during January, with analysts citing the unwinding of speculative positions as a primary driver for the sudden downturn.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:32:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee4bc46be08bbe62fb2e2_1769923858934.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BCCL's First Post-IPO Results Amidst Strong Market Debut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/BCCLs-First-Post-IPO-Results-Amidst-Strong-Market-Debut/697ee30646be08bbe62fafe5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/BCCLs-First-Post-IPO-Results-Amidst-Strong-Market-Debut/697ee30646be08bbe62fafe5</guid><description>Bharat Coking Coal Ltd. (BCCL) is set to announce its first quarterly financial results post-listing on February 3. The company's Initial Public Offering was a resounding success, oversubscribed 143.85 times and achieving a 96% listing premium. Investors now await Q3FY26 performance data amid mixed FY25 financials and a supportive sector outlook driven by India's push for coking coal self-sufficiency.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:29:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee30646be08bbe62fafe4_1769923775644.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Sales Surge 47% in January; XUV7XO Bookings Hit Record Rs 20,500 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Sales-Surge-47percent-in-January-XUV7XO-Bookings-Hit-Record-Rs-20500-Cr/697ee38046be08bbe62fb0ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Sales-Surge-47percent-in-January-XUV7XO-Bookings-Hit-Record-Rs-20500-Cr/697ee38046be08bbe62fb0ac</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra reported a stellar January 2026 sales performance, with total vehicle sales growing 24% YoY and Farm Equipment segment sales soaring 46% YoY. The company highlighted record bookings of 93,689 units for its XUV7XO and XEV 9S models, generating a massive Rs. 20,500 Crore in just four hours, signalling strong demand for its new offerings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee38046be08bbe62fb0ab_1769923523880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2026 Budget: Growth, Fiscal Discipline Under Global Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Budget-Growth-Fiscal-Discipline-Under-Global-Scrutiny/697ee30746be08bbe62faff1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Budget-Growth-Fiscal-Discipline-Under-Global-Scrutiny/697ee30746be08bbe62faff1</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has presented India's Union Budget for 2026-27, her ninth consecutive fiscal roadmap. The budget aims to balance sustained growth momentum with fiscal discipline, navigating a landscape marked by geopolitical tensions and volatile commodity prices. Key reforms are anticipated to shield the economy from global trade frictions, while addressing domestic imperatives like consumption, job creation, and capital expenditure. This presentation follows a traditional meeting with President Droupadi Murmu, continuing a procedural hallmark.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:24:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee30746be08bbe62faff0_1769923412065.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Market Cautious Amid Growth Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Market-Cautious-Amid-Growth-Outlook/697ee29046be08bbe62faf3c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Market-Cautious-Amid-Growth-Outlook/697ee29046be08bbe62faf3c</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman today presented the Union Budget for 2026-27, marking her ninth consecutive presentation. Indian equity markets opened with muted sentiment, reflecting investor caution. The Economic Survey projects strong GDP growth of 6.8-7.2% for FY27, positioning India as the fastest-growing major economy, driven by domestic demand despite persistent global headwinds.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:21:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee29046be08bbe62faf3b_1769923295741.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GST Collections Jump 6.2% to ₹1.93 Lakh Crore in January</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GST-Collections-Jump-62percent-to-193-Lakh-Crore-in-January/697ee21346be08bbe62fae85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GST-Collections-Jump-62percent-to-193-Lakh-Crore-in-January/697ee21346be08bbe62fae85</guid><description>Gross Goods and Services Tax (GST) collections for January reached over Rs 1.93 lakh crore, marking a 6.2% increase year-on-year. This growth was primarily fueled by higher revenues from imports, which rose 10.1%. Net GST revenues saw a 7.6% uplift, reaching approximately Rs 1.71 lakh crore. Domestic transaction collections grew a more modest 4.8%. The revised GST rates, effective September 2025, continue to influence overall collections.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:19:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ee21346be08bbe62fae84_1769923188442.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metal Stocks Tumble on Macro Re-pricing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Stocks-Tumble-on-Macro-Re-pricing/697edf4b46be08bbe62fad19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Stocks-Tumble-on-Macro-Re-pricing/697edf4b46be08bbe62fad19</guid><description>The Indian metal sector witnessed significant pressure, with the Nifty Metal index dropping 4.6% on Sunday, February 1, 2026, extending a two-day slide. This correction followed a strong January rally and was primarily driven by profit-booking and a macro re-pricing event sparked by President Trump's nomination of Kevin Warsh as the next US Federal Reserve Chair. Warsh's hawkish stance led to a stronger dollar and higher real yields, causing leveraged positions in commodities to unwind. Individual stocks like Hindustan Copper and Hindustan Zinc saw substantial declines.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:10:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697edf4b46be08bbe62fad18_1769922583833.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's January GST Collections Reach 8-Month High</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-January-GST-Collections-Reach-8-Month-High/697ededc46be08bbe62fac45</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-January-GST-Collections-Reach-8-Month-High/697ededc46be08bbe62fac45</guid><description>Gross Goods and Services Tax (GST) collections in January surged to ₹1.93 lakh crore, marking a significant 6.2% year-on-year increase and an eight-month high for the current fiscal year. Net revenues, after accounting for refunds, grew 7.6% to ₹1.71 lakh crore, indicating robust economic activity and strategic tax policy adjustments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:07:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ededc46be08bbe62fac44_1769922425406.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quadrant Televentures Issues Revised Insolvency Bid Invite Under IBC</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Quadrant-Televentures-Issues-Revised-Insolvency-Bid-Invite-Under-IBC/697edecb46be08bbe62fac11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Quadrant-Televentures-Issues-Revised-Insolvency-Bid-Invite-Under-IBC/697edecb46be08bbe62fac11</guid><description>Quadrant Televentures Limited has issued a revised Form G, re-inviting Expressions of Interest (EOI) for its Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP). The move follows an NCLT order and revised eligibility criteria set by the Committee of Creditors. With FY25 revenue at Rs 273.97 Cr, the company seeks resolution applicants to navigate its debt restructuring. Key dates for the process are now set, culminating in a Resolution Plan submission by April 17, 2026.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:05:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697edecb46be08bbe62fac10_1769922323576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>