<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:53 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Bluegod Entertainment to Raise ₹31.63 Cr Via Rights Issue; Signs Sports IP Term Sheet</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Bluegod-Entertainment-to-Raise-3163-Cr-Via-Rights-Issue-Signs-Sports-IP-Term-Sheet/69a2ddb0fa7d0695d1b031f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Bluegod-Entertainment-to-Raise-3163-Cr-Via-Rights-Issue-Signs-Sports-IP-Term-Sheet/69a2ddb0fa7d0695d1b031f2</guid><description>Bluegod Entertainment Limited will raise ₹31.63 crore through a Rights Issue at ₹3.00 per share. The company also executed a Term Sheet for the assignment of Intellectual Property rights related to Legends League Cricket, while deciding against acquiring a team in the league. This marks a strategic recalibration after a recent acquisition of LLC licensing rights.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:21:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ddb0fa7d0695d1b031f1_1772281370970.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>March Stock Picks: Seasonality vs. Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/March-Stock-Picks-Seasonality-vs-Volatility/69a2d97afa7d0695d1b0304e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/March-Stock-Picks-Seasonality-vs-Volatility/69a2d97afa7d0695d1b0304e</guid><description>Despite historical March seasonal strength, Pidilite Industries, Cummins India, and AIA Engineering face headwinds. Persistent inflation, geopolitical tensions, and company-specific challenges like export declines and margin pressures introduce significant volatility, questioning the reliability of past performance as a forward indicator for March 2026. Investors must scrutinize these factors beyond simple seasonal patterns.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2d97afa7d0695d1b0304d_1772280308200.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Hype vs. Enterprise Reality: India Poised to Outperform</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Hype-vs-Enterprise-Reality-India-Poised-to-Outperform/69a2d692fa7d0695d1b02e98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Hype-vs-Enterprise-Reality-India-Poised-to-Outperform/69a2d692fa7d0695d1b02e98</guid><description>Jefferies' global equity strategist Chris Wood suggests investors are overestimating AI's consumer profitability, likening its capital intensity to airlines. While consumer AI lacks clear monetization, enterprise adoption presents opportunities for Indian IT services firms, positioning them as AI integrators. Wood identifies U.S. private equity and credit markets as a bubble, heavily exposed to leveraged software buyouts. In contrast, India's market shows resilience, driven by strong domestic flows and extended consolidation, suggesting potential for relative outperformance during global tech or credit-induced corrections. Despite AI's disruptive potential for software and IT services, a nuanced view suggests enterprise AI utility and India's domestic demand may offer a more stable growth narrative.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:50:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2d692fa7d0695d1b02e97_1772279535895.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Teeters as Bearish Futures Signal Deep Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Teeters-as-Bearish-Futures-Signal-Deep-Concern/69a2d01afa7d0695d1b02b27</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Teeters-as-Bearish-Futures-Signal-Deep-Concern/69a2d01afa7d0695d1b02b27</guid><description>Bitcoin consolidated near $63,000-$68,000, grappling with a sharp decline in perpetual futures funding rates to -6%. This indicates aggressive bearish positioning, with traders paying a premium to short the asset. Over $500 million in crypto positions were liquidated in 24 hours, predominantly long. While this could fuel a short squeeze, the persistence of such negative sentiment, coupled with lower funding rates for Ethereum and weaker performance in Solana, raises questions about underlying market conviction.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2d01afa7d0695d1b02b26_1772277913521.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Airspace Curbs: Mideast Tensions Ground Carriers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Airspace-Curbs-Mideast-Tensions-Ground-Carriers/69a2cfbdfa7d0695d1b02a93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Airspace-Curbs-Mideast-Tensions-Ground-Carriers/69a2cfbdfa7d0695d1b02a93</guid><description>Indian carriers IndiGo, Air India, and SpiceJet have suspended flights to the Middle East amid escalating geopolitical tensions and dynamic airspace restrictions. These cancellations impose significant revenue losses and elevate operational costs due to rerouting and extended flight times. The situation strains the already fragile financial health of the Indian aviation sector, which is navigating substantial debt, volatile fuel prices, and currency risks. For carriers like SpiceJet, already facing financial headwinds, these disruptions compound existing challenges, while even market leader IndiGo faces profit margin pressures.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:21:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2cfbdfa7d0695d1b02a92_1772277788841.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Middle East Conflict Grounds Flights, Squeezing Airline Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Middle-East-Conflict-Grounds-Flights-Squeezing-Airline-Margins/69a2cfb8fa7d0695d1b02a7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Middle-East-Conflict-Grounds-Flights-Squeezing-Airline-Margins/69a2cfb8fa7d0695d1b02a7b</guid><description>Following strikes on Iran, airlines are suspending flights and rerouting operations, leading to increased fuel consumption and operational expenses. Major carriers like Lufthansa, Air France-KLM, and Wizz Air face immediate disruption, impacting their stock performance as oil prices surge. The sector, already navigating post-pandemic recovery, is now exposed to heightened geopolitical risk premiums and uncertain demand, prompting investor caution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:21:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2cfb8fa7d0695d1b02a7a_1772277846499.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OPEC+ Prepares Output Hike Amid Geopolitical Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/OPEC-Prepares-Output-Hike-Amid-Geopolitical-Fears/69a2cf53fa7d0695d1b029ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/OPEC-Prepares-Output-Hike-Amid-Geopolitical-Fears/69a2cf53fa7d0695d1b029ce</guid><description>OPEC+ is set to meet Sunday, with indications pointing towards a larger-than-planned oil output increase. This potential move comes as major Middle Eastern producers, Saudi Arabia and the UAE, have already ramped up exports. The proactive export surge is a strategic response to escalating geopolitical tensions stemming from the US-Israeli attack on Iran, aiming to buffer against potential supply disruptions and maintain market stability. While the group previously signaled a modest 137,000 bpd increase for April, sources suggest the actual hike could be more substantial.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:19:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2cf53fa7d0695d1b029cd_1772277666269.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bullion ETFs Face Cost Squeeze Amidst Volatility and Flows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Bullion-ETFs-Face-Cost-Squeeze-Amidst-Volatility-and-Flows/69a2ceb1fa7d0695d1b0292b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Bullion-ETFs-Face-Cost-Squeeze-Amidst-Volatility-and-Flows/69a2ceb1fa7d0695d1b0292b</guid><description>Indian gold and silver ETFs are experiencing heightened tracking errors and total expense ratios (TERs) as extreme market volatility and record investor inflows strain operational management. Fund managers hold more cash to manage redemptions, creating a drag on performance against underlying metal prices. This impacts investor returns despite significant year-over-year gains in precious metals, prompting scrutiny over tracking fidelity and prompting upcoming regulatory changes in valuation methodology.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ceb1fa7d0695d1b0292a_1772277558423.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DeFi Futures Surge on Iran Strikes, Proving 24/7 Risk Pricing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/DeFi-Futures-Surge-on-Iran-Strikes-Proving-247-Risk-Pricing/69a2c918fa7d0695d1b026a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/DeFi-Futures-Surge-on-Iran-Strikes-Proving-247-Risk-Pricing/69a2c918fa7d0695d1b026a9</guid><description>Following coordinated missile strikes on Iran by the U.S. and Israel on Saturday, February 28, 2026, oil-linked perpetual futures on the decentralized exchange Hyperliquid surged. Contracts saw gains exceeding 5%, with one trading around $71.26 and another above $86.00, handling nearly $4 million in volume and over $5 million in open interest. This rapid price discovery underscores decentralized finance's capability to price in geopolitical risk instantaneously, a stark contrast to the closure of traditional markets over the weekend. Gold and silver also advanced on safe-haven demand as heightened geopolitical tensions threatened prolonged uncertainty in the oil-rich Middle East and raised concerns over the critical Strait of Hormuz.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 10:53:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2c918fa7d0695d1b026a8_1772276172296.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fino Payments Bank CEO Arrest Sparks GST Overreach Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Payments-Bank-CEO-Arrest-Sparks-GST-Overreach-Fears/69a2c11cfa7d0695d1b0229c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Payments-Bank-CEO-Arrest-Sparks-GST-Overreach-Fears/69a2c11cfa7d0695d1b0229c</guid><description>Fino Payments Bank Managing Director and CEO Rishi Gupta was arrested under GST laws, prompting industry veteran Mohandas Pai to flag concerns over regulatory "overreach" and call for safeguards. While Fino states operations are unaffected and an interim CEO has been appointed, the incident intensifies scrutiny on GST enforcement powers impacting executive leadership in regulated financial entities. The Finance Minister has pledged to review the matter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 10:19:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2c11cfa7d0695d1b0229b_1772274113193.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godrej Wins Calcutta HC Case Against Harpic</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Godrej-Wins-Calcutta-HC-Case-Against-Harpic/69a2c117fa7d0695d1b02285</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Godrej-Wins-Calcutta-HC-Case-Against-Harpic/69a2c117fa7d0695d1b02285</guid><description>Calcutta High Court set aside an ad-interim injunction against Godrej Consumer Products' 'Spic' toilet cleaner bottle, siding with Godrej in a dispute with Reckitt Benckiser India. The bench questioned the prima facie case for trademark infringement based on bottle shape alone, particularly after design protection expiry. This ruling potentially impacts how brand owners defend packaging design in the competitive FMCG sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 10:19:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2c117fa7d0695d1b02284_1772274070417.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coforge Shareholders Greenlight SSPA Covenants for Encora Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-Shareholders-Greenlight-SSPA-Covenants-for-Encora-Acquisition/69a2bec8fa7d0695d1b020dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-Shareholders-Greenlight-SSPA-Covenants-for-Encora-Acquisition/69a2bec8fa7d0695d1b020dd</guid><description>Coforge Limited shareholders have overwhelmingly approved a special resolution granting special rights and covenants pursuant to the Share Purchase Agreement (SSPA) related to the company's significant acquisition of Encora. The postal ballot, concluded on February 27, 2026, saw over 99% of valid votes cast in favour, clearing a crucial hurdle for the $2.35 billion Encora deal. This approval empowers the company to proceed with the revised terms underpinning the acquisition, reinforcing strategic alignment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 10:09:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2bec8fa7d0695d1b020dc_1772273451799.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kalind Ltd. Approves ₹3100 Cr DBJ Acquisition, Boosts Capital to ₹10,000 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Kalind-Ltd-Approves-3100-Cr-DBJ-Acquisition-Boosts-Capital-to-10000-Cr/69a2b653fa7d0695d1b01d83</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Kalind-Ltd-Approves-3100-Cr-DBJ-Acquisition-Boosts-Capital-to-10000-Cr/69a2b653fa7d0695d1b01d83</guid><description>Kalind Limited's Board of Directors has greenlit a significant strategic move, approving the acquisition of DBJ Multi Services Private Limited for up to ₹3100 crore via a share swap. The company also plans a substantial increase in its authorized share capital to ₹10,000 crore, signaling a push for growth. These decisions, alongside appointments of new key personnel and auditors, are set to be presented to shareholders for approval at an Extraordinary General Meeting on March 27, 2026.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:33:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2b653fa7d0695d1b01d82_1772271289503.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kalind Limited Approves ₹310 Cr Acquisition, Boosts Financial Powers to ₹1000 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Kalind-Limited-Approves-310-Cr-Acquisition-Boosts-Financial-Powers-to-1000-Cr/69a2b383fa7d0695d1b01c05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Kalind-Limited-Approves-310-Cr-Acquisition-Boosts-Financial-Powers-to-1000-Cr/69a2b383fa7d0695d1b01c05</guid><description>Kalind Limited's board approved a significant ₹310 Crore acquisition of DBJ Multi Services Private Limited, funded by a preferential share issuance. The company also greenlit a substantial increase in financial limits across borrowing, mortgaging, and investments to ₹1000 Crore each, subject to shareholder approval. These moves signal strategic expansion and enhanced financial capacity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2b383fa7d0695d1b01c04_1772270567363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Jet Healthcare Breaks Ground on ₹1,000 Cr Vizag Plant; ₹2,300 Cr Future Potential</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Breaks-Ground-on-1000-Cr-Vizag-Plant-2300-Cr-Future-Potential/69a2b222fa7d0695d1b01b20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Breaks-Ground-on-1000-Cr-Vizag-Plant-2300-Cr-Future-Potential/69a2b222fa7d0695d1b01b20</guid><description>Blue Jet Healthcare commenced construction on its new ₹1,000 crore manufacturing facility in Vizag, Andhra Pradesh. The project has a long-term development potential of up to ₹2,300 crore and will focus on producing complex pharmaceutical intermediates and APIs. This expansion aims to bolster the company's position as a global supplier.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:15:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2b222fa7d0695d1b01b1f_1772270207094.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Market: Select Sectors Outperform Sluggish Economy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Market-Select-Sectors-Outperform-Sluggish-Economy/69a2acfbfa7d0695d1b0191d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Market-Select-Sectors-Outperform-Sluggish-Economy/69a2acfbfa7d0695d1b0191d</guid><description>Despite a perceived sluggish Indian market, Sohum Asset Managers' CIO is overweighting domestic themes including telecom, NBFCs, industrials, and cement, citing early recovery signs in commercial vehicles and steady credit growth. While underweight on banking, the strategy embraces IT giants and mid-caps, alongside infrastructure and defense plays, navigating a complex economic backdrop where targeted sectorial strength may diverge from broader index performance. Aggregate Nifty 50 earnings saw 7% growth in Q3 FY26, with Nifty 500 companies showing a more robust 19% year-on-year increase, highlighting a potential divergence in performance across market segments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:53:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2acfbfa7d0695d1b0191c_1772268913949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zenith Exports Fined By NSE, BSE For Compliance Lapses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Zenith-Exports-Fined-By-NSE-BSE-For-Compliance-Lapses/69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Zenith-Exports-Fined-By-NSE-BSE-For-Compliance-Lapses/69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017c9</guid><description>Zenith Exports Limited faces penalties from both NSE and BSE, totaling ₹7,90,600 (including GST), for non-compliance with SEBI's Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements (LODR) for the quarter ending December 2025. The company must pay the fine within 15 days or face potential trading restrictions, promoter shareholding freeze, or even suspension.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017c8_1772268444528.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goa Carbon Gets NGT Favourable Order for Goa Plant; Pollution Case Dismissed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Goa-Carbon-Gets-NGT-Favourable-Order-for-Goa-Plant-Pollution-Case-Dismissed/69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Goa-Carbon-Gets-NGT-Favourable-Order-for-Goa-Plant-Pollution-Case-Dismissed/69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017b3</guid><description>Goa Carbon Limited has received a favourable final order from the National Green Tribunal (NGT) dismissing a case alleging environmental pollution and health issues at its Goa plant. The tribunal found the applicant's medical reports insufficient and noted the company's compliance, removing a significant regulatory overhang. The company stated there will be no financial impact from this order.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017b2_1772268410861.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silicon Rental H1 FY26 Revenue ₹61.6 Cr; EBIDTA ₹20.2 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silicon-Rental-H1-FY26-Revenue-616-Cr-EBIDTA-202-Cr/69a2a2a1fa7d0695d1b013f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silicon-Rental-H1-FY26-Revenue-616-Cr-EBIDTA-202-Cr/69a2a2a1fa7d0695d1b013f9</guid><description>Silicon Rental Solutions Limited presented its H1 FY26 performance, showing ₹61.6 crore revenue and ₹20.2 crore EBIDTA. The company is pivoting to a full-stack tech rental model, expanding into AI and robotics, and launching a 'CoE-as-a-Service' for educational institutions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:09:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2a2a1fa7d0695d1b013f8_1772266285383.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MapmyIndia Data Reveals India Retail Shift to Tier 3-5 Cities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MapmyIndia-Data-Reveals-India-Retail-Shift-to-Tier-3-5-Cities/69a2a229fa7d0695d1b0136a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MapmyIndia-Data-Reveals-India-Retail-Shift-to-Tier-3-5-Cities/69a2a229fa7d0695d1b0136a</guid><description>A new report, co-powered by MapmyIndia's data, shows India's retail sector is decentralizing. Tier 3-5 cities are growing significantly faster than metros, driven by rising consumer spending and aspirations. MapmyIndia's location intelligence is crucial for retailers to navigate this evolving landscape.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:07:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2a229fa7d0695d1b01369_1772266329938.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRFC Tokyo Roadshow Targets Japanese Investors for Funding Diversification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IRFC-Tokyo-Roadshow-Targets-Japanese-Investors-for-Funding-Diversification/69a2a13dfa7d0695d1b0129f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IRFC-Tokyo-Roadshow-Targets-Japanese-Investors-for-Funding-Diversification/69a2a13dfa7d0695d1b0129f</guid><description>Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) held a two-day External Commercial Borrowing (ECB) roadshow in Tokyo, February 26-27, 2026. The initiative aimed to engage Japanese regional investors, diversify funding sources, and optimize borrowing costs, highlighting IRFC's credit profile and its crucial role in financing India's railway infrastructure expansion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:03:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2a13dfa7d0695d1b0129e_1772266119397.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fund Influx Meets Tobacco Tax Shock: Elitecon Valuation Questioned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Fund-Influx-Meets-Tobacco-Tax-Shock-Elitecon-Valuation-Questioned/69a29fd7fa7d0695d1b011a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Fund-Influx-Meets-Tobacco-Tax-Shock-Elitecon-Valuation-Questioned/69a29fd7fa7d0695d1b011a7</guid><description>Mauritius-based Minerva Ventures Fund has acquired an 8.58% stake in Elitecon International Limited via warrants and open market purchases. This investment enters a sector facing a harsh regulatory environment in 2026, with significant tax hikes set to increase costs and potentially compress margins. Elitecon's reported explosive growth contrasts sharply with its exceedingly high valuation multiples and recent stock volatility, prompting scrutiny over sustainability. Competitor valuations are notably lower, and analyst sentiment leans cautiously pessimistic due to sector-wide headwinds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:57:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29fd7fa7d0695d1b011a6_1772265744483.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Laxmipati Engineering Seeks ₹25 Cr RPT Approval; Vote March 2-31</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Laxmipati-Engineering-Seeks-25-Cr-RPT-Approval-Vote-March-2-31/69a29df0fa7d0695d1b01085</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Laxmipati-Engineering-Seeks-25-Cr-RPT-Approval-Vote-March-2-31/69a29df0fa7d0695d1b01085</guid><description>Laxmipati Engineering Works Limited is seeking shareholder approval for a material related party transaction (RPT) with Laxmipati Apparel Private Limited. The proposed job work and fabrication services deal is valued up to ₹25 Crore annually, representing 49.90% of the company's turnover. Shareholders will vote via postal ballot and remote e-voting from March 2 to March 31, 2026. The Board has recommended approval, citing it as an ordinary course of business.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:49:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29df0fa7d0695d1b01084_1772265203244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PE Firms Exit Vishal Mega Mart; Shares Slide Post Block Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PE-Firms-Exit-Vishal-Mega-Mart-Shares-Slide-Post-Block-Deal/69a29c8efa7d0695d1b00f7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PE-Firms-Exit-Vishal-Mega-Mart-Shares-Slide-Post-Block-Deal/69a29c8efa7d0695d1b00f7d</guid><description>Samayat Services LLP, backed by Kedaara Capital and Partners Group, divested nearly 14% of its stake in Vishal Mega Mart (VMM) for ₹7,635 crore. The sale reduced its holding to 40.13% from 54.09%. Prominent institutional investors, including the Singapore government, Monetary Authority of Singapore, and HDFC Mutual Fund, collectively acquired over 6.3% of VMM. The market reacted negatively, with VMM shares falling 7.59% to ₹117.85 on the NSE. This divestment follows a similar large stake sale in June last year.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:43:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29c8efa7d0695d1b00f7c_1772264739176.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Tumbles 3% as Geopolitical Shockwaves Hit Crypto</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Tumbles-3percent-as-Geopolitical-Shockwaves-Hit-Crypto/69a29677fa7d0695d1b00ca4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Tumbles-3percent-as-Geopolitical-Shockwaves-Hit-Crypto/69a29677fa7d0695d1b00ca4</guid><description>Bitcoin experienced a swift 3% decline, nearing $63,000, following U.S. and Israeli military actions against Iran. This sharp weekend sell-off demonstrates Bitcoin's function as a real-time barometer for geopolitical risk, reacting instantaneously due to its continuous trading cycle, unlike traditional markets. The move underscores increasing correlations between digital assets and global instability, impacting investor sentiment and liquidity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:17:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29677fa7d0695d1b00ca3_1772263203336.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Almondz Global Securities seeks EOGM nod for ₹13.26 cr preferential issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Almondz-Global-Securities-seeks-EOGM-nod-for-1326-cr-preferential-issue/69a29671fa7d0695d1b00c8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Almondz-Global-Securities-seeks-EOGM-nod-for-1326-cr-preferential-issue/69a29671fa7d0695d1b00c8d</guid><description>Almondz Global Securities Ltd. has called an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EOGM) on March 27, 2026, to seek shareholder approval for a preferential issue. The company plans to raise ₹13.26 crore by issuing 80 lakh convertible warrants at ₹16.58 each. Proceeds will bolster working capital, fund proprietary trading, and support general corporate needs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29671fa7d0695d1b00c8c_1772263125073.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ETFs vs. Mutual Funds: Indian Investor Behavior Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/ETFs-vs-Mutual-Funds-Indian-Investor-Behavior-Shifts/69a29539fa7d0695d1b00b6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/ETFs-vs-Mutual-Funds-Indian-Investor-Behavior-Shifts/69a29539fa7d0695d1b00b6e</guid><description>India's investment landscape sees a dichotomy: Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) attract with lower fees and transparency, while mutual funds, amplified by the ubiquitous Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) culture, foster crucial behavioral discipline. Recent data shows passive fund AUM nearing 17% of total industry assets, yet the psychological friction provided by mutual funds, especially during market volatility, offers a unique protective layer for retail investors. This structural advantage, combined with consistent inflows, suggests mutual funds, despite higher costs, may maintain relevance for wealth accumulation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:11:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29539fa7d0695d1b00b6d_1772262845200.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kopran Secures NSE Nod for Merger with Kopran Labs; NCLT Next</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Kopran-Secures-NSE-Nod-for-Merger-with-Kopran-Labs-NCLT-Next/69a2948ffa7d0695d1b00af2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Kopran-Secures-NSE-Nod-for-Merger-with-Kopran-Labs-NCLT-Next/69a2948ffa7d0695d1b00af2</guid><description>Kopran Limited has advanced its proposed merger with Kopran Laboratories Limited, receiving a "no objection" observation letter from the National Stock Exchange (NSE). This procedural milestone enables the company to proceed with submitting the amalgamation scheme to the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), paving the way for integration.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:09:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2948ffa7d0695d1b00af1_1772262861197.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Balkrishna Industries NCD Rating: CRISIL Assigns 'AA+/Stable' to ₹750 Cr Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balkrishna-Industries-NCD-Rating-CRISIL-Assigns-AAStable-to-750-Cr-Issue/69a291c0fa7d0695d1b00989</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balkrishna-Industries-NCD-Rating-CRISIL-Assigns-AAStable-to-750-Cr-Issue/69a291c0fa7d0695d1b00989</guid><description>Balkrishna Industries Limited (BIL) has secured a 'CRISIL AA+/Stable' credit rating for its proposed ₹750 crore Non-Convertible Debenture (NCD) issuance. This rating signifies a high degree of safety and very low credit risk, enhancing investor confidence in the company's ability to meet its financial obligations. The rating is crucial for the company's fundraising strategy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:57:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a291c0fa7d0695d1b00988_1772261998989.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Concord Control Systems bags Rs 53.73 Cr KAVACH order from Indian Railways</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Concord-Control-Systems-bags-Rs-5373-Cr-KAVACH-order-from-Indian-Railways/69a29059fa7d0695d1b00856</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Concord-Control-Systems-bags-Rs-5373-Cr-KAVACH-order-from-Indian-Railways/69a29059fa7d0695d1b00856</guid><description>Concord Control Systems Limited announced a significant Rs. 53.73 Crore order for KAVACH 4.0 equipment from Indian Railways, to be executed within 12 months. This win strengthens the company's position in critical railway safety systems and is expected to boost its order book and revenue trajectory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29059fa7d0695d1b00855_1772261592859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Balkrishna Industries Ratings Reaffirmed at Crisil AA+/A1+ by CRISIL</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Balkrishna-Industries-Ratings-Reaffirmed-at-Crisil-AAA1-by-CRISIL/69a28fdffa7d0695d1b007b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Balkrishna-Industries-Ratings-Reaffirmed-at-Crisil-AAA1-by-CRISIL/69a28fdffa7d0695d1b007b8</guid><description>CRISIL Ratings has reaffirmed Balkrishna Industries Limited's (BIL) long-term rating at 'Crisil AA+/Stable' for bank facilities and 'Crisil A1+' for short-term bank facilities and its Rs 500 Crore Commercial Paper. This reaffirmation indicates sustained financial stability and a low credit risk, assuring lenders and investors of the company's ability to meet its obligations. However, the company must avail proposed facilities within 180 days of the rating letter date, or a fresh revalidation will be required.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:49:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28fdffa7d0695d1b007b7_1772261487496.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UBS Pivots: US Equities Downgraded as EM &amp; Cyclicals Gain Traction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/UBS-Pivots-US-Equities-Downgraded-as-EM-and-Cyclicals-Gain-Traction/69a28fb9fa7d0695d1b00788</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/UBS-Pivots-US-Equities-Downgraded-as-EM-and-Cyclicals-Gain-Traction/69a28fb9fa7d0695d1b00788</guid><description>UBS has strategically shifted its stance on U.S. equities, downgrading the asset class to 'benchmark' due to elevated valuations, diminishing buyback support, and dollar-related risks. The firm reiterates a high-conviction overweight on emerging markets (EM), citing accelerating global growth, more attractive valuations, and improved operational leverage. This move signals a potential rotation favoring cyclical regions and sectors outside the U.S. as capital flows increasingly diversify.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:48:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28fb9fa7d0695d1b00787_1772261590146.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ramkrishna Forgings Subsidiaries Amalgamation Receives NCLT Approval</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ramkrishna-Forgings-Subsidiaries-Amalgamation-Receives-NCLT-Approval/69a28eeffa7d0695d1b006a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ramkrishna-Forgings-Subsidiaries-Amalgamation-Receives-NCLT-Approval/69a28eeffa7d0695d1b006a0</guid><description>The National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), Kolkata Bench, has approved the amalgamation of Ramkrishna Forgings Limited's subsidiaries, Mal Metalliks Private Limited and Multitech Auto Private Limited, with Ramkrishna Casting Solutions Limited (formerly JMT Auto Limited). This strategic move, effective from January 1, 2024, aims to enhance administrative control, reduce costs, and strengthen the company's financial structure for greater operational efficiency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:45:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28eeffa7d0695d1b0069f_1772261213208.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>d-Matrix Challenges GPU Giants in AI Inference Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/d-Matrix-Challenges-GPU-Giants-in-AI-Inference-Race/69a28da2fa7d0695d1b00535</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/d-Matrix-Challenges-GPU-Giants-in-AI-Inference-Race/69a28da2fa7d0695d1b00535</guid><description>Silicon Valley firm d-Matrix is emerging as a significant contender in the AI inference hardware market, directly challenging incumbent GPU manufacturers like Nvidia. By focusing on a specialized architecture built around SRAM and in-memory compute, d-Matrix claims its solutions offer substantial improvements in cost-effectiveness, power efficiency, and speed for running trained AI models at scale. With substantial funding and strategic backing, the company aims to democratize AI access by making inference operations economically viable for a broader range of enterprises, positioning itself as a critical enabler against market speculation and high operational costs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:39:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28da2fa7d0695d1b00534_1772261126823.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Bets on HPV Vaccine: Merck's China Woes vs. Domestic Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Bets-on-HPV-Vaccine-Mercks-China-Woes-vs-Domestic-Rise/69a28d16fa7d0695d1b0045d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Bets-on-HPV-Vaccine-Mercks-China-Woes-vs-Domestic-Rise/69a28d16fa7d0695d1b0045d</guid><description>India has initiated a nationwide Human Papillomavirus (HPV) Vaccination Programme targeting 1.15 crore girls annually. The program initially utilizes Merck's Gardasil vaccine but signals a strong push for domestic manufacturing, with Serum Institute of India's Cervavac poised to play a significant role. This initiative arrives as Merck faces declining Gardasil sales in China, creating a complex global market dynamic and highlighting India's growing pharmaceutical self-sufficiency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:37:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28d16fa7d0695d1b0045c_1772260758202.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BF Utilities Q3 Profit Jumps 22% Amid Auditor's Adverse Conclusion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Q3-Profit-Jumps-22percent-Amid-Auditors-Adverse-Conclusion/69a28d10fa7d0695d1b00446</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Q3-Profit-Jumps-22percent-Amid-Auditors-Adverse-Conclusion/69a28d10fa7d0695d1b00446</guid><description>BF Utilities reported a consolidated net profit of ₹102.76 crore for Q3 FY26, a 22.43% increase year-on-year, with revenue up 12.60%. However, the results are overshadowed by an adverse conclusion from statutory auditors regarding compliance with accounting standards. Significant concerns remain over a ₹500 crore arbitration liability, unresolved advances, and accounting non-compliance, casting a shadow over the reported financial performance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:37:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28d10fa7d0695d1b00445_1772260948553.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Precious Metals Rally: Tax Complexities Overshadow Stellar Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Rally-Tax-Complexities-Overshadow-Stellar-Gains/69a28c1ffa7d0695d1b0035d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Rally-Tax-Complexities-Overshadow-Stellar-Gains/69a28c1ffa7d0695d1b0035d</guid><description>Gold and silver have delivered exceptional returns in recent years, with significant appreciation in 2025 and early 2026. However, the surge is met by increasingly complex tax implications across various investment vehicles, including ETFs, funds of funds, Sovereign Gold Bonds, and physical assets. Recent budget changes have introduced new tax liabilities, particularly for secondary market SGB transactions, demanding a strategic re-evaluation of investment approaches.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:33:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28c1ffa7d0695d1b0035c_1772260727241.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indonesia Halts Tata, Mahindra Truck Deal Amidst Local Industry Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indonesia-Halts-Tata-Mahindra-Truck-Deal-Amidst-Local-Industry-Push/69a28baefa7d0695d1b002fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indonesia-Halts-Tata-Mahindra-Truck-Deal-Amidst-Local-Industry-Push/69a28baefa7d0695d1b002fc</guid><description>Indonesia has halted a significant order for 105,000 trucks from Indian manufacturers Tata Motors and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra. This decision follows strong pushback from local policymakers and industry associations concerned about undermining domestic industrialization and job creation. The pause is pending further government and legislative discussions, signaling a potential shift in procurement strategy to favor local production capacity, estimated at one million pickup trucks annually.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28baefa7d0695d1b002fb_1772260393068.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Caplin Point Unit Gets USFDA Nod for $26M Desmopressin Injection</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Caplin-Point-Unit-Gets-USFDA-Nod-for-26M-Desmopressin-Injection/69a28951fa7d0695d1b0019d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Caplin-Point-Unit-Gets-USFDA-Nod-for-26M-Desmopressin-Injection/69a28951fa7d0695d1b0019d</guid><description>Caplin Point Laboratories' subsidiary, Caplin Steriles, has secured final USFDA approval for its Desmopressin Acetate Injection USP. This generic drug, used for haemophilia and diabetes insipidus, targets a US market with $26 million in sales. The approval is a significant step for Caplin Steriles, opening access to the lucrative US market and expected to boost revenue for the parent company.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:21:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28951fa7d0695d1b0019c_1772259802464.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OpenAI Lands DoD Classified AI Deal as Anthropic Faces Ban</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/OpenAI-Lands-DoD-Classified-AI-Deal-as-Anthropic-Faces-Ban/69a288c4fa7d0695d1b00111</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/OpenAI-Lands-DoD-Classified-AI-Deal-as-Anthropic-Faces-Ban/69a288c4fa7d0695d1b00111</guid><description>OpenAI's agreement to deploy AI on US Department of Defense classified networks marks a significant expansion, occurring as President Trump orders a halt to Anthropic's government use, citing national security risks. This move sharpens the competitive edge in defense AI, with OpenAI securing a strategic partnership while grappling with stringent ethical safeguards. The landscape sees valuations soaring for private AI firms, fueling a global race for AI supremacy in military applications.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:18:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a288c4fa7d0695d1b00110_1772259806276.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>