<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:38:04 +0000</pubDate><item><title>DOMS Industries Surges 18% Revenue, Eyes Premium Bags with Italian JV</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/DOMS-Industries-Surges-18percent-Revenue-Eyes-Premium-Bags-with-Italian-JV/6984b629bf48f011a29e3fd7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/DOMS-Industries-Surges-18percent-Revenue-Eyes-Premium-Bags-with-Italian-JV/6984b629bf48f011a29e3fd7</guid><description>DOMS Industries posted an 18.2% YoY revenue growth to INR 592.2 crore in Q3 FY'26, with EBITDA up 17.7%. The company maintained a strong 17.5% EBITDA margin. A new 50-50 JV with Italy's Seven SpA targets the premium bag segment. Management projects continued steady growth, with FY'26 revenue at the upper end of guidance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:24:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Archean Chemical Profit Dips 50%, Eyes Semiconductor Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Archean-Chemical-Profit-Dips-50percent-Eyes-Semiconductor-Growth/6984b61bbf48f011a29e3f7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Archean-Chemical-Profit-Dips-50percent-Eyes-Semiconductor-Growth/6984b61bbf48f011a29e3f7f</guid><description>Archean Chemical Industries reported a sharp 49.8% YoY decline in Q3 FY26 net profit to ₹240 million, with EBITDA margins compressing significantly due to operational issues in its Bromine segment. Despite this near-term profit hit, the company is making substantial strategic investments in the high-growth semiconductor (SiC) and energy storage sectors, signalling a major pivot.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Commercial Syn Bags Surges on 120% PAT Growth, Expansion Plans</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Commercial-Syn-Bags-Surges-on-120percent-PAT-Growth-Expansion-Plans/6984b5a5bf48f011a29d80f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Commercial-Syn-Bags-Surges-on-120percent-PAT-Growth-Expansion-Plans/6984b5a5bf48f011a29d80f6</guid><description>Commercial Syn Bags reported a robust third quarter and nine months ending December 31, 2025. Revenue climbed 14.57% YoY to ₹28,644.91 Lakhs for the nine months, while Profit After Tax (PAT) surged 120.76% YoY to ₹1,997.94 Lakhs. Q3 saw PAT jump 70.64% YoY. The company is undertaking significant capacity expansions and faces a legal challenge regarding land acquisition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:22:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Arvind SmartSpaces Acquires Bengaluru Project for Rs 860 Cr Revenue Potential</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Arvind-SmartSpaces-Acquires-Bengaluru-Project-for-Rs-860-Cr-Revenue-Potential/6984b539bf48f011a29d7f60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Arvind-SmartSpaces-Acquires-Bengaluru-Project-for-Rs-860-Cr-Revenue-Potential/6984b539bf48f011a29d7f60</guid><description>Arvind SmartSpaces Limited has acquired a prime 4.7-acre residential high-rise project on Sarjapur Road, Bengaluru, with an estimated revenue potential of Rs. 860 crore. This marks the company's 10th high-rise development in the city, significantly boosting its development pipeline. The acquisition reinforces ASL's strategy to expand its vertical development portfolio in key markets like Bengaluru, Ahmedabad, and MMR, aiming to further leverage its strong brand resonance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pitti Engineering Sees Revenue Surge, Divests Standalone Profit Amid Subsidiary Merger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pitti-Engineering-Sees-Revenue-Surge-Divests-Standalone-Profit-Amid-Subsidiary-Merger/6984b535bf48f011a29d7f04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pitti-Engineering-Sees-Revenue-Surge-Divests-Standalone-Profit-Amid-Subsidiary-Merger/6984b535bf48f011a29d7f04</guid><description>Pitti Engineering announced mixed Q3 FY26 results, with standalone revenue growing 16.0% YoY to ₹42,154.20 Lakhs, but Profit After Tax (PAT) declining 10.5% YoY to ₹2,173.51 Lakhs. Consolidated revenue climbed 15.0% YoY to ₹47,742.15 Lakhs, with PAT up 7.3% YoY. The company's Board also approved the amalgamation of its two wholly-owned subsidiaries, Pitti Industries Private Limited and Dakshin Foundry Private Limited, with Pitti Engineering Limited, aiming to boost efficiency and growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jet Freight Logistics to Raise ₹73 Cr Via Warrants, Diluting Shareholder Equity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Jet-Freight-Logistics-to-Raise-73-Cr-Via-Warrants-Diluting-Shareholder-Equity/6984b4e3bf48f011a29d7d86</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Jet-Freight-Logistics-to-Raise-73-Cr-Via-Warrants-Diluting-Shareholder-Equity/6984b4e3bf48f011a29d7d86</guid><description>Jet Freight Logistics Limited will hold an Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on February 20, 2026, to approve a preferential issuance of up to 4,06,07,750 warrants. The issue, priced at ₹18 per warrant, aims to raise ₹73.09 crore. Proceeds will fund working capital (₹55 Cr), debt repayment (₹6 Cr), and general corporate purposes (₹12.09 Cr). Post-conversion, the total equity shares will surge, slightly increasing promoter holding from 50.92% to a projected 52.71%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Sets Rs 100 Umbrella Import Floor Amid China Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Sets-Rs-100-Umbrella-Import-Floor-Amid-China-Dominance/6984b4c2bf48f011a29d7cbe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Sets-Rs-100-Umbrella-Import-Floor-Amid-China-Dominance/6984b4c2bf48f011a29d7cbe</guid><description>India has established a minimum import price (MIP) of Rs 100 per umbrella, a significant policy shift from a 'free' to 'restricted' import category. This measure, coupled with recent duty increases announced in Budget 2026-27, aims to bolster domestic umbrella production. The policy addresses India's substantial dependence on China, which supplies approximately 95.8% of its umbrella imports, while potentially impacting consumer costs and navigating complex trade policy objectives.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>STT Hike on F&amp;O: Investor Protection or Liquidity Drain?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/STT-Hike-on-FandO-Investor-Protection-or-Liquidity-Drain/6984b498bf48f011a29d7bd2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/STT-Hike-on-FandO-Investor-Protection-or-Liquidity-Drain/6984b498bf48f011a29d7bd2</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 includes a significant increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) for futures and options trading, effective April 1, 2026. The government cites investor protection, aiming to curb excessive speculation and large retail losses, which reportedly exceeded ₹1.06 lakh crore in FY25. However, the tax hike is expected to increase trading costs, potentially dampen volumes, and may shift activity offshore, raising questions about its net impact on market efficiency and competitiveness. Immediate market reactions saw a sharp downturn.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jost's Engineering Profit Plummets 83% Amidst Key Subsidiary Sale Approval</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Josts-Engineering-Profit-Plummets-83percent-Amidst-Key-Subsidiary-Sale-Approval/6984b46cbf48f011a29d7a92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Josts-Engineering-Profit-Plummets-83percent-Amidst-Key-Subsidiary-Sale-Approval/6984b46cbf48f011a29d7a92</guid><description>Jost's Engineering reported a steep 83.4% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025, falling to ₹6.9 crore. This sharp drop was significantly influenced by exceptional items totalling ₹25.1 crore, primarily a provision for defined benefit obligations. Concurrently, the company's board approved the sale of its material wholly-owned subsidiary, JECL Engineering Limited, to Mr. Rahul Dhoot for ₹73 crore, a deal contingent on shareholder approval.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Commercial Syn Bags Posts Stellar 90% PAT Jump, Eyes Capacity Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Commercial-Syn-Bags-Posts-Stellar-90percent-PAT-Jump-Eyes-Capacity-Expansion/6984b43bbf48f011a29d79bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Commercial-Syn-Bags-Posts-Stellar-90percent-PAT-Jump-Eyes-Capacity-Expansion/6984b43bbf48f011a29d79bf</guid><description>Commercial Syn Bags Ltd. reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with standalone PAT surging 90.92% YoY to ₹624.81 Lakhs on a 15.68% revenue increase. Consolidated PAT rose 70.61%. The company is undertaking significant capacity expansions worth ₹53 Crores across its SEZ and Techtex units and a subsidiary, aiming for operational readiness by mid-2027. Legal challenges regarding land acquisition by NHAI are ongoing, with interim relief granted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Repco Home Finance Declares Dividend Amidst Mixed Q3 Results</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Repco-Home-Finance-Declares-Dividend-Amidst-Mixed-Q3-Results/6984b3d6bf48f011a29d7894</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Repco-Home-Finance-Declares-Dividend-Amidst-Mixed-Q3-Results/6984b3d6bf48f011a29d7894</guid><description>Repco Home Finance Limited (RHFL) declared a second interim dividend of ₹2 per share for FY26. However, the Q3 FY26 results reveal a stark divergence: standalone revenue grew marginally by 1.71%, but consolidated revenue plummeted 75.45% YoY. Standalone net profit saw a minor dip of 0.26%, while consolidated net profit jumped 37.15%. The significant decline in consolidated revenue is a key concern for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Outpaces Oversight: UN Panel Faces Bot-Created Digital Worlds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Outpaces-Oversight-UN-Panel-Faces-Bot-Created-Digital-Worlds/6984b3c9bf48f011a29d7828</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Outpaces-Oversight-UN-Panel-Faces-Bot-Created-Digital-Worlds/6984b3c9bf48f011a29d7828</guid><description>Global efforts to regulate artificial intelligence are struggling to keep pace with its rapid advancement. The United Nations has established an independent scientific panel to guide AI governance, even as AI systems autonomously create and inhabit digital platforms like Moltbook, designed solely for bot interaction. India is set to host the AI Impact Summit, highlighting the growing national and international focus on this transformative technology.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jost's Engineering Profit Plunges 70% Despite Revenue Surge; Sells Unit for ₹73 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Josts-Engineering-Profit-Plunges-70percent-Despite-Revenue-Surge-Sells-Unit-for-73-Cr/6984b37cbf48f011a29d7758</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Josts-Engineering-Profit-Plunges-70percent-Despite-Revenue-Surge-Sells-Unit-for-73-Cr/6984b37cbf48f011a29d7758</guid><description>Jost's Engineering reported a sharp 70.39% year-on-year decline in standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹122 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, even as revenue grew 31.73% to ₹6,186 Lakhs. Consolidated PAT also fell 72.12% to ₹116 Lakhs. The company announced the sale of its material wholly-owned subsidiary, JECL Engineering Limited, to Mr. Rahul Dhoot for ₹7,300 Lakhs (₹73 Crores), subject to shareholder approval. An exceptional expense of ₹261 Lakhs related to new Labour Codes further impacted profitability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Passive Home Loans Cost Borrowers Billions Annually</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Passive-Home-Loans-Cost-Borrowers-Billions-Annually/6984b372bf48f011a29d7711</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Passive-Home-Loans-Cost-Borrowers-Billions-Annually/6984b372bf48f011a29d7711</guid><description>Millions of homeowners are silently overpaying on their mortgages due to a lack of proactive interest rate and tenure management. This widespread inertia results in billions of dollars in unnecessary interest payments annually, while financial institutions miss opportunities for deeper customer engagement. A review of loan terms, strategic prepayments, and understanding macroeconomic influences are critical for financial optimization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>LIC Q3 Profit Jumps 17%: Valuation Gap Widens vs. Peers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Q3-Profit-Jumps-17percent-Valuation-Gap-Widens-vs-Peers/6984b34ebf48f011a29d7271</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Q3-Profit-Jumps-17percent-Valuation-Gap-Widens-vs-Peers/6984b34ebf48f011a29d7271</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) posted a 17% year-on-year increase in net profit to ₹12,958 crore for the third quarter ended December 2025. This performance was bolstered by a 17% rise in net premium income to ₹1.26 lakh crore. Despite robust growth and expanding margins, LIC's valuation continues to lag behind its private sector counterparts, which trade at significantly higher multiples.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BLS E-Services Declares 5% Dividend Amidst Mixed Q3 Results</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/BLS-E-Services-Declares-5percent-Dividend-Amidst-Mixed-Q3-Results/6984b2d6bf48f011a29d711e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/BLS-E-Services-Declares-5percent-Dividend-Amidst-Mixed-Q3-Results/6984b2d6bf48f011a29d711e</guid><description>BLS E-Services Limited announced its Q3 FY26 results, declaring a 5% interim dividend (₹0.50/share). Consolidated revenue surged by 120% YoY to ₹28,067.64 lakhs, driven by the acquisition of Aadifidelis Solutions. However, standalone net profit plummeted 60% to ₹405.57 lakhs. Unutilized IPO funds of ₹15,726.96 lakhs are parked in term deposits.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Gas Market Diverges: Local Supply Fuels IGX Volume Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Gas-Market-Diverges-Local-Supply-Fuels-IGX-Volume-Surge/6984b25ebf48f011a29d6f90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Gas-Market-Diverges-Local-Supply-Fuels-IGX-Volume-Surge/6984b25ebf48f011a29d6f90</guid><description>India's gas trading activity on the Indian Gas Exchange (IGX) surged 50% month-on-month in January 2026 to 8.4 million MMBtu, driven by rising city gas distribution demand and increased domestic HPHT gas availability. This surge occurred despite a 21% year-on-year drop in domestic prices to $10.6 per MMBtu, highlighting a significant divergence from firming global benchmarks like TTF, which rose 32%. The trend indicates growing reliance on India's indigenous production and exchange-based procurement for supply security and price stability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Chennai Housing Soars 55% Amidst Western Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Chennai-Housing-Soars-55percent-Amidst-Western-Slump/6984b210bf48f011a29d6e3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Chennai-Housing-Soars-55percent-Amidst-Western-Slump/6984b210bf48f011a29d6e3b</guid><description>India's residential property market in 2025 witnessed a dramatic regional divergence. Chennai recorded a 55% surge in sales, selling over 24,800 units, driven by stable end-user demand and strong fundamentals. This contrasts sharply with Mumbai and Pune, which experienced sales declines of 26.4% and 28.5% respectively, as Western markets faced headwinds. Policy interventions, including a repo rate cut to 5.25% and GST reduction on cement, are set to influence market dynamics into 2026. Despite an overall decline in national sales volumes, the value of transactions remained resilient, supported by a focus on premium segments and disciplined developer supply.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:06:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Suryo Foods Faces Distress: Rights Issue to Clear Debts Amidst Inactive Core Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Suryo-Foods-Faces-Distress-Rights-Issue-to-Clear-Debts-Amidst-Inactive-Core-Business/6984b1e5bf48f011a29d6d61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Suryo-Foods-Faces-Distress-Rights-Issue-to-Clear-Debts-Amidst-Inactive-Core-Business/6984b1e5bf48f011a29d6d61</guid><description>Suryo Foods &amp; Industries Limited is launching a rights issue of up to ₹5.94 crore at ₹20 per share. The capital will primarily fund outstanding trading and other liabilities, not growth. The company reported a steep year-on-year decline in total income to ₹63.13 lakhs in FY2025 from ₹178.71 lakhs in FY2024, with net profit plummeting to ₹24.87 lakhs from ₹113.14 lakhs. Critically, Suryo Foods has negative net worth of ₹(254.79) lakhs and no operational activity in its core shrimp business, relying instead on rental income. Management has provided no forward guidance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:06:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NASSCOM: AI Augments India IT Amid Enterprise Complexity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NASSCOM-AI-Augments-India-IT-Amid-Enterprise-Complexity/6984b198bf48f011a29d6c3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NASSCOM-AI-Augments-India-IT-Amid-Enterprise-Complexity/6984b198bf48f011a29d6c3b</guid><description>NASSCOM refutes fears of AI replacing India's IT sector, stating AI will augment services. The industry body highlights that complex global enterprise technology demands human expertise for meaningful AI value. Indian firms are proactively investing in AI platforms, talent, and partnerships to navigate this shift. Opportunities lie in modernizing legacy systems and building AI-ready data foundations, ensuring continued relevance in global AI strategies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:04:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Suzlon's Q3 Surge: Profitability Up, But EPS Plunge Raises Alarms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Suzlons-Q3-Surge-Profitability-Up-But-EPS-Plunge-Raises-Alarms/6984b16dbf48f011a29d6b51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Suzlons-Q3-Surge-Profitability-Up-But-EPS-Plunge-Raises-Alarms/6984b16dbf48f011a29d6b51</guid><description>Suzlon Group reported a strong Q3 FY26 with revenue up 42% to ₹4,228 crore and record 617 MW deliveries, alongside a 48% EBITDA jump. However, the company faces significant investor questions due to a sharp plunge into negative Earnings Per Share (EPS) despite robust pre-tax profits, a reduction in net cash reserves, and a SEBI show-cause notice. Coupled with a recent 'Sell' rating downgrade and headwinds in wind energy funding, Suzlon's ambitious 'Suzlon 2.0' strategy faces heightened scrutiny regarding execution risks and capital requirements amidst a competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:04:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jost's Engineering Profit Plunges 95%, Data Inconsistency Alarms Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Josts-Engineering-Profit-Plunges-95percent-Data-Inconsistency-Alarms-Investors/6984b0b4bf48f011a29d690b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Josts-Engineering-Profit-Plunges-95percent-Data-Inconsistency-Alarms-Investors/6984b0b4bf48f011a29d690b</guid><description>Jost's Engineering reported a sharp 95.6% year-on-year decline in standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹2.5 Crores for Q3 FY26, despite a 31.7% revenue increase to ₹618.6 Crores. Consolidated PAT fell 72.1% YoY to ₹11.6 Crores. A significant red flag emerged with the consolidated nine-month PAT turning negative at -₹6.9 Crores, while EPS remained positive at ₹2.15, indicating serious data reporting inconsistencies. The company also approved the sale of its material subsidiary, JECL Engineering, for ₹73 Crores.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MDL Posts Robust Q3 Growth, YTD Margins Narrow; Order Book Stands Strong</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MDL-Posts-Robust-Q3-Growth-YTD-Margins-Narrow-Order-Book-Stands-Strong/6984b09ebf48f011a29d6877</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MDL-Posts-Robust-Q3-Growth-YTD-Margins-Narrow-Order-Book-Stands-Strong/6984b09ebf48f011a29d6877</guid><description>Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders (MDL) announced a robust Q3 FY25-26, with revenue up 14.5% and PAT growing 9%. However, year-to-date performance reveals a concerning 400 bps margin compression to 19% and a 2.4% EBITDA decline. The company maintains a strong order book of ₹23,758 Cr, signalling significant future revenue visibility and strategic growth through key defence projects and international collaborations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharti Airtel Profit Dips 55% Amid Cost Surge, Capex Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtel-Profit-Dips-55percent-Amid-Cost-Surge-Capex-Hike/6984b013bf48f011a29d66b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtel-Profit-Dips-55percent-Amid-Cost-Surge-Capex-Hike/6984b013bf48f011a29d66b3</guid><description>Bharti Airtel's consolidated net profit plunged 55% year-on-year to Rs 6,630.5 crore for the December 2025 quarter, even as revenue rose 19.6% to Rs 53,982 crore. The steep decline in profitability was primarily due to a significant increase in network operating costs, statutory fees, and employee expenses, alongside a substantial 28% jump in capital expenditure. Despite these pressures, the company saw continued customer base expansion and a 5.7% rise in Average Revenue Per User (ARPU).</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ABFRL Posts 8% Revenue Growth Amidst Soft Demand, Remains Loss-Making</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ABFRL-Posts-8percent-Revenue-Growth-Amidst-Soft-Demand-Remains-Loss-Making/6984b002bf48f011a29d661a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ABFRL-Posts-8percent-Revenue-Growth-Amidst-Soft-Demand-Remains-Loss-Making/6984b002bf48f011a29d661a</guid><description>Aditya Birla Fashion and Retail (ABFRL) reported Q3 FY26 revenue growth of 8% YoY to ₹2,374 Cr, driven by strong performance in ethnic wear, TMRW, and luxury brands. EBITDA rose 13% to ₹370 Cr with a 70 bps margin improvement. However, the company posted a net loss of ₹137 Cr for the quarter, impacted by a soft demand environment and weaker consumer footfalls, despite proactive strategic shifts and store expansions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Avalon Technologies Q3 FY26 Earnings Call Recording Released Amidst Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Avalon-Technologies-Q3-FY26-Earnings-Call-Recording-Released-Amidst-Revenue-Surge/6984afafbf48f011a29d6510</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Avalon-Technologies-Q3-FY26-Earnings-Call-Recording-Released-Amidst-Revenue-Surge/6984afafbf48f011a29d6510</guid><description>Avalon Technologies Limited has made the audio recording of its Q3 FY26 earnings call, held on February 5, 2026, available to investors. This provides stakeholders access to management's discussions regarding the company's performance. Notably, the company reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue surging 48.7% year-on-year to ₹418 crore. However, profitability margins experienced pressure, with EBITDA and PAT margins compressing YoY, indicating operational challenges despite strong top-line growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Incredible Industries Q3 PAT Surges 29%, But Massive Tax Hit Dims Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Incredible-Industries-Q3-PAT-Surges-29percent-But-Massive-Tax-Hit-Dims-Outlook/6984af8abf48f011a29d6468</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Incredible-Industries-Q3-PAT-Surges-29percent-But-Massive-Tax-Hit-Dims-Outlook/6984af8abf48f011a29d6468</guid><description>Incredible Industries Limited posted a 29.3% year-on-year jump in Q3 FY26 Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹1.79 Cr, with revenue rising 16.7%. However, a staggering ₹94.58 Cr tax expense for the quarter significantly masked underlying profitability, despite a healthy Profit Before Tax (PBT) of ₹3.15 Cr. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, PAT plummeted 44.3% to ₹6.96 Cr on a 6.7% revenue increase, with margins collapsing from 23.75% to 12.40%. The company provided no balance sheet, cash flow details, or forward guidance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BLS E-Services Surges 120% Revenue Post-Acquisition, But Margins Compress</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/BLS-E-Services-Surges-120percent-Revenue-Post-Acquisition-But-Margins-Compress/6984af1fbf48f011a29d62de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/BLS-E-Services-Surges-120percent-Revenue-Post-Acquisition-But-Margins-Compress/6984af1fbf48f011a29d62de</guid><description>BLS E-Services Limited reported a massive 120.07% year-over-year revenue growth to ₹28,067.64 lakhs in Q3 FY26, largely fueled by the acquisition of Aadifidelis Solutions Private Limited. However, profitability faced headwinds with a 16.71% sequential decline in net profit and a significant compression in PAT margins to 5.42% from 10.98% a year ago. Basic EPS also saw a year-over-year dip. The company declared its first interim dividend of 5% for FY25-26.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Deep Industries Surges on Strong Q3 Results and Massive ONGC Contract</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Deep-Industries-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Results-and-Massive-ONGC-Contract/6984aef7bf48f011a29d6164</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Deep-Industries-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Results-and-Massive-ONGC-Contract/6984aef7bf48f011a29d6164</guid><description>Deep Industries reported robust Q3 FY26 results with a 43.1% YoY revenue jump to ₹221.5 Cr and a 49.8% surge in PAT to ₹71.3 Cr. The company also secured a landmark 15-year, ₹1,402 Cr contract from ONGC for field production boosting, alongside an ₹108 Cr GAIL contract. Management highlighted strong operational execution and a positive industry outlook driven by government policies and rising energy demand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Capital Infra Trust's PAT Plummets 86% Amid Margin Squeeze, Debt Ratios Deteriorate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Capital-Infra-Trusts-PAT-Plummets-86percent-Amid-Margin-Squeeze-Debt-Ratios-Deteriorate/6984aed3bf48f011a29d60d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Capital-Infra-Trusts-PAT-Plummets-86percent-Amid-Margin-Squeeze-Debt-Ratios-Deteriorate/6984aed3bf48f011a29d60d2</guid><description>Capital Infra Trust reported a steep 86.4% year-on-year drop in consolidated profit after tax to ₹107.58 million for Q3 FY26, driven by an 86.4% contraction in its EBITDA margin to 26.92%. Standalone PAT fell 52.3% due to a ₹496.11 million impairment loss. Debt servicing metrics saw a sharp decline, with the Debt Service Coverage Ratio falling to 0.23 and Interest Service Coverage Ratio to 1.03, raising concerns despite recent debt management actions and asset acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ABFRL Q3: Revenue Jumps 8% But Net Profit Turns Negative</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/ABFRL-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-8percent-But-Net-Profit-Turns-Negative/6984aea1bf48f011a29d5fda</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/ABFRL-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-8percent-But-Net-Profit-Turns-Negative/6984aea1bf48f011a29d5fda</guid><description>ABFRL's Q3 FY26 revenue climbed 8% YoY to ₹2374 Crore, driven by strong growth in ethnic wear (+20%), luxury (+16%), and digital brands. EBITDA rose 13% YoY to ₹370 Crore, improving margins to 15.6%. However, the company posted a net loss of ₹137 Crore for the quarter, despite a normalized PAT of ₹115 Crore after excluding one-off items. Retail footprint expanded with 50 new stores. Management aims for scale and efficiency.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Neerav Bairagi Launches Open Offer for JMG Corp at ₹5.30, Eyes 62.62% Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Neerav-Bairagi-Launches-Open-Offer-for-JMG-Corp-at-530-Eyes-6262percent-Stake/6984ae31bf48f011a29d5df9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Neerav-Bairagi-Launches-Open-Offer-for-JMG-Corp-at-530-Eyes-6262percent-Stake/6984ae31bf48f011a29d5df9</guid><description>Neerav Bairagi has launched an open offer to acquire up to 26% of JMG Corporation Limited at ₹5.30 per share, aiming to become the new promoter with a potential 62.62% stake. The offer follows a share purchase agreement at ₹4.20 per share. Mr. Bairagi plans to diversify JMG Corp's business into textile trading, alongside its existing green energy consulting services. The company's shares are currently under Graded Surveillance Measures (GSM) Stage 4, and historical financials show volatility.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Studds Accessories Posts Strong Q3 Profit Growth, Eyes Europe Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Studds-Accessories-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Growth-Eyes-Europe-Expansion/6984ae21bf48f011a29d5d77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Studds-Accessories-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Growth-Eyes-Europe-Expansion/6984ae21bf48f011a29d5d77</guid><description>Studds Accessories reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue up 9.4% YoY to INR 163 crore and PAT soaring 26.3% to INR 20.7 crore. Margins improved significantly due to favourable raw material costs and procurement efficiencies. The company is strategically expanding capacity and eyeing the European market via its Spain subsidiary, though a 1.5 million unit expansion is deferred by one quarter due to construction restrictions. Management targets an ASP over INR 800 for FY27.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SEBI Proposes Eased Commodity Norms, Tightens Pledge Rules</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/SEBI-Proposes-Eased-Commodity-Norms-Tightens-Pledge-Rules/6984ad61bf48f011a29d5bb0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/SEBI-Proposes-Eased-Commodity-Norms-Tightens-Pledge-Rules/6984ad61bf48f011a29d5bb0</guid><description>India's market regulator, the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi), is proposing significant changes. It plans to ease stress-testing and settlement guarantee fund norms for commodity derivatives clearing corporations. Simultaneously, Sebi is tightening rules on pledge invocation and withdrawing calendar spread margin benefits for single-stock derivatives on expiry day.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sebi Eases AIF Exit Norms, Streamlining Fund Wind-Ups</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Eases-AIF-Exit-Norms-Streamlining-Fund-Wind-Ups/6984ad48bf48f011a29d5b23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Eases-AIF-Exit-Norms-Streamlining-Fund-Wind-Ups/6984ad48bf48f011a29d5b23</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) has put forth proposals to simplify the winding-up processes for Alternative Investment Funds (AIFs). These changes aim to provide regulatory clarity and operational certainty, particularly for funds entangled in litigation or tax demands. A key proposal is the introduction of an 'inoperative AIF' status, which would significantly reduce compliance burdens for these entities while barring them from new schemes or management fees. The regulator's move acknowledges the operational challenges that have historically delayed asset distribution and prevented timely registration surrenders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mazagon Dock Profit Climbs 9%, Revenue Surges 14.6%, But Margins Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mazagon-Dock-Profit-Climbs-9percent-Revenue-Surges-146percent-But-Margins-Squeeze/6984ad32bf48f011a29d5a64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mazagon-Dock-Profit-Climbs-9percent-Revenue-Surges-146percent-But-Margins-Squeeze/6984ad32bf48f011a29d5a64</guid><description>Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders posted a 9% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹879.8 crore for Q3 FY26, fueled by a 14.6% jump in revenue to ₹3,601 crore. However, margins softened as expenses rose, leading to an 8.5% EBITDA growth. The company's shares closed 1.3% lower on the NSE.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Fiscal Divide: States Clash with Centre Over Tax Revenue Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Divide-States-Clash-with-Centre-Over-Tax-Revenue-Share/6984acdebf48f011a29d5987</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Divide-States-Clash-with-Centre-Over-Tax-Revenue-Share/6984acdebf48f011a29d5987</guid><description>Indian states are demanding a larger share of central taxes, citing shrinking fiscal space and the Centre's growing reliance on cesses and surcharges, which are not devolved. While the Centre maintains current devolution levels are unsustainable, this standoff highlights a structural imbalance in the nation's fiscal federalism. This dispute threatens states' ability to fund essential services and adapt policies to local needs, against a global trend of increasing sub-federal fiscal autonomy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SC prioritizes homebuyers, burdens NBCC with Supertech project takeover</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/SC-prioritizes-homebuyers-burdens-NBCC-with-Supertech-project-takeover/6984acbcbf48f011a29d5868</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/SC-prioritizes-homebuyers-burdens-NBCC-with-Supertech-project-takeover/6984acbcbf48f011a29d5868</guid><description>The Supreme Court has directed state-run NBCC (India) Limited to complete 16 stalled housing projects belonging to Supertech Limited, invoking its extraordinary powers under Article 142 of the Constitution. This landmark ruling unequivocally prioritizes the interests of thousands of homebuyers over those of financial and operational creditors, mandating the handover of fully furnished homes before any creditor claims are addressed. The apex court also prohibited tribunals and high courts from issuing orders that could impede NBCC's progress, aiming to expedite the resolution of these long-pending projects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NCC Ltd: Orders Surge Despite Profit Dip, Analysts See Upside</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Ltd-Orders-Surge-Despite-Profit-Dip-Analysts-See-Upside/6984ac5abf48f011a29d5707</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Ltd-Orders-Surge-Despite-Profit-Dip-Analysts-See-Upside/6984ac5abf48f011a29d5707</guid><description>NCC Ltd's third quarter saw net profit drop 36.6% to ₹122.5 crore on 9% lower revenue of ₹4,868.3 crore. Despite this, EBITDA margins improved to 9%, and the company secured ₹12,430 crore in new orders, bolstering a ₹7,957 crore order book. The board approved the amalgamation of NCC Infrastructure Holdings Ltd, effective February 28, 2026. The stock closed down 1.71% at ₹152.45.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DISA India Q3 Profit Surges 57.5% on Strong Sales, Order Book Robust</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DISA-India-Q3-Profit-Surges-575percent-on-Strong-Sales-Order-Book-Robust/6984ac40bf48f011a29d5672</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DISA-India-Q3-Profit-Surges-575percent-on-Strong-Sales-Order-Book-Robust/6984ac40bf48f011a29d5672</guid><description>DISA India Ltd. posted stellar Q3 FY26 results, with standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 57.5% year-on-year to ₹154.2 million on a 31.8% revenue jump to ₹1,286.2 million. Consolidated PAT also leaped 51.7% YoY. The company ended the quarter with a healthy order backlog of ₹2,958 million, providing strong revenue visibility for FY27.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>