<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:26:36 +0000</pubDate><item><title>WOG Technologies Eyes ₹375 Crore IPO: Environmental Engineering Giant Files DRHP for Market Debut!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/WOG-Technologies-Eyes-375-Crore-IPO-Environmental-Engineering-Giant-Files-DRHP-for-Market-Debut/695248564342f77179dc7586</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/WOG-Technologies-Eyes-375-Crore-IPO-Environmental-Engineering-Giant-Files-DRHP-for-Market-Debut/695248564342f77179dc7586</guid><description>WOG Technologies, a prominent environmental engineering and technology firm, has filed its draft red herring prospectus (DRHP) with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi). The company plans to raise ₹375 crore through a fresh issue of shares and an offer for sale of up to 4.32 million equity shares to meet working capital needs and acquire a stake in Bell Cooling Towers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:06:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Surges 14% to a 15-Year Peak: Is This PSU Stock India's Next Big Winner?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Copper-Surges-14percent-to-a-15-Year-Peak-Is-This-PSU-Stock-Indias-Next-Big-Winner/695247a44342f77179dc739b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Copper-Surges-14percent-to-a-15-Year-Peak-Is-This-PSU-Stock-Indias-Next-Big-Winner/695247a44342f77179dc739b</guid><description>Hindustan Copper shares dramatically climbed 14.79% on the NSE, reaching a 15-year high of ₹545.95. This surge is fueled by soaring silver prices, global copper supply disruptions in key regions like China, Indonesia, and Chile, and a weaker US dollar. The stock has doubled investor capital in 2025, significantly outperforming the Nifty Metal index.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:05:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695247a44342f77179dc739a_1767000227373.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock Trading Secrets: GTF's 'Human Scanner' Promises Real Market Understanding, Not Just Data!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Unlock-Trading-Secrets-GTFs-Human-Scanner-Promises-Real-Market-Understanding-Not-Just-Data/695247bb4342f77179dc7439</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Unlock-Trading-Secrets-GTFs-Human-Scanner-Promises-Real-Market-Understanding-Not-Just-Data/695247bb4342f77179dc7439</guid><description>GTF has launched GTF Eye, a novel 'human scanner' stock tool designed to enhance trader decision-making. Unlike traditional automated screeners that focus on raw data, GTF Eye utilizes human logic, price behavior analysis, and understanding of demand and supply zones. It aims to provide clarity and conviction, helping traders filter meaningful opportunities from market noise. The tool supports various trading styles and offers time-saving features for a more effective trading approach.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:05:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695247bb4342f77179dc7438_1767000349882.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Expert Predicts Double-Digit FY27 Earnings Growth: Key Sectors to Watch!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Expert-Predicts-Double-Digit-FY27-Earnings-Growth-Key-Sectors-to-Watch/695247004342f77179dc7183</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Expert-Predicts-Double-Digit-FY27-Earnings-Growth-Key-Sectors-to-Watch/695247004342f77179dc7183</guid><description>Market expert Manish Sonthalia of Emkay Investment Managers forecasts double-digit earnings growth of 12-13% for Indian equities in FY27, driven by favorable macroeconomics like low inflation and potential rate cuts. He identifies sectors like banks, capital goods, NBFCs, and healthcare as key growth drivers, while noting structural advantages for quick commerce players Zomato and Swiggy. Bottom-up stock picking is advised due to corrected valuations and sector-specific tailwinds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:05:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695247004342f77179dc7182_1766999989866.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Don't Make This Costly Mistake! Job Switch? Why Withdrawing EPF Could Ruin Your Retirement</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Dont-Make-This-Costly-Mistake-Job-Switch-Why-Withdrawing-EPF-Could-Ruin-Your-Retirement/695247884342f77179dc7334</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Dont-Make-This-Costly-Mistake-Job-Switch-Why-Withdrawing-EPF-Could-Ruin-Your-Retirement/695247884342f77179dc7334</guid><description>Switching jobs? Resist the urge to withdraw your EPF. Experts warn this seemingly small decision can severely impact your long-term financial security. EPF offers tax-free growth at ~8%, compounding power, and a crucial five-year tax-free withdrawal rule. Withdrawing early triggers taxes, erases the employer's contribution tax benefit, and resets the compounding clock, potentially costing you lakhs in retirement savings. Transferring your EPF to your new employer is the recommended path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:03:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695247884342f77179dc7333_1767000120181.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver SHOCKER: Tokenized Volumes EXPLODE 1200% as Price Hits Record Highs! 🚀</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-SHOCKER-Tokenized-Volumes-EXPLODE-1200percent-as-Price-Hits-Record-Highs/6952470a4342f77179dc71bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-SHOCKER-Tokenized-Volumes-EXPLODE-1200percent-as-Price-Hits-Record-Highs/6952470a4342f77179dc71bd</guid><description>Tokenized silver trading volumes have surged over 1200%, with holder numbers up 300%, mirroring the dramatic price increase of physical silver to record highs this month. This boom in digital silver markets, including the iShares Silver Trust (SLV), is driven by significant supply constraints, rising demand from industries like solar power, and unique market conditions such as double-digit premiums in Asia and backwardation in London, signaling strong near-term supply stress.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:02:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952470a4342f77179dc71bc_1767000058831.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Stocks SHOCKER! Manappuram, Muthoot Plummet 2% as Gold Prices See Dramatic Fall - What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Stocks-SHOCKER-Manappuram-Muthoot-Plummet-2percent-as-Gold-Prices-See-Dramatic-Fall-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/695246b34342f77179dc7051</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Stocks-SHOCKER-Manappuram-Muthoot-Plummet-2percent-as-Gold-Prices-See-Dramatic-Fall-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/695246b34342f77179dc7051</guid><description>Indian gold financier stocks, including Manappuram Finance, Muthoot Finance, and IIFL Finance, saw shares fall over 2% on December 29. This drop occurred as gold prices corrected sharply from recent highs, impacting the value of collateral for these companies. The stocks had previously surged alongside the yellow metal's rally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:01:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695246b34342f77179dc7050_1766999823065.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Insurer Merger Hangs in Balance: Finance Ministry Divided, Key Deal Faces Uncertain Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/PSU-Insurer-Merger-Hangs-in-Balance-Finance-Ministry-Divided-Key-Deal-Faces-Uncertain-Future/695245f54342f77179dc6ea7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/PSU-Insurer-Merger-Hangs-in-Balance-Finance-Ministry-Divided-Key-Deal-Faces-Uncertain-Future/695245f54342f77179dc6ea7</guid><description>The proposed merger of state-owned general insurers National Insurance Company, Oriental Insurance Company, and United India Insurance Company is stalled. Disagreements within India's Finance Ministry over valuation, capital requirements, and the effectiveness of consolidation are causing uncertainty. The process remains in a preliminary assessment stage with no formal execution plan or timeline in place.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:01:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695245f54342f77179dc6ea6_1766999846409.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>REITs vs. Rental Flats in 2026: Which Real Estate Investment is Your Golden Ticket?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/REITs-vs-Rental-Flats-in-2026-Which-Real-Estate-Investment-is-Your-Golden-Ticket/695245744342f77179dc6dc4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/REITs-vs-Rental-Flats-in-2026-Which-Real-Estate-Investment-is-Your-Golden-Ticket/695245744342f77179dc6dc4</guid><description>Choosing between a rental flat and a Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT) for 2026? Rental flats offer control and leverage but demand significant effort and face income uncertainties. REITs provide easier entry, liquidity, and diversified risk with professional management, though they introduce market volatility. The best choice hinges on your investment goals: predictable income with minimal hassle (REITs) or concentrated wealth building with active management (rental flat).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:01:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695245744342f77179dc6dc3_1766999701746.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Smokers' Shops Skyrocket as India's Digital Payment Boom Creates Unlikely Billion-Dollar Winners!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Smokers-Shops-Skyrocket-as-Indias-Digital-Payment-Boom-Creates-Unlikely-Billion-Dollar-Winners/695245644342f77179dc6d5e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Smokers-Shops-Skyrocket-as-Indias-Digital-Payment-Boom-Creates-Unlikely-Billion-Dollar-Winners/695245644342f77179dc6d5e</guid><description>India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) is revolutionizing small purchases, leading to an unexpected surge in transaction volumes at cigarette and tobacco shops. These outlets saw their share of UPI transactions jump over fourfold between November 2023 and November 2025, while average transaction values dropped, indicating UPI is becoming the go-to for daily micro-purchases previously dominated by cash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 09:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bengaluru Home Prices SKYROCKET 15%! India's Silicon Valley Sees Premium Housing Boom - What Buyers REALLY Want Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bengaluru-Home-Prices-SKYROCKET-15percent-Indias-Silicon-Valley-Sees-Premium-Housing-Boom-What-Buyers-REALLY-Want-Now/695243d04342f77179dc69ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bengaluru-Home-Prices-SKYROCKET-15percent-Indias-Silicon-Valley-Sees-Premium-Housing-Boom-What-Buyers-REALLY-Want-Now/695243d04342f77179dc69ed</guid><description>Bengaluru's property market is showing remarkable resilience, with average home prices surging 15% year-on-year in Q3 2025, despite a slight 5% dip in sales volumes. New housing supply also saw a 5% annual increase. Industry experts highlight a significant shift towards 'premiumisation,' where buyers prioritize comfort, liveability, and measurable home performance over sheer scale. This trend is reshaping luxury housing, with a focus on deeper value alignment and robust engineering, expected to continue into 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:55:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695243d04342f77179dc69ec_1766999137399.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2025 IPO Surge: Record Funds Raised, But Many New Stocks Fail to Shine Long-Term</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-2025-IPO-Surge-Record-Funds-Raised-But-Many-New-Stocks-Fail-to-Shine-Long-Term/6952437d4342f77179dc6907</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-2025-IPO-Surge-Record-Funds-Raised-But-Many-New-Stocks-Fail-to-Shine-Long-Term/6952437d4342f77179dc6907</guid><description>2025 saw record fundraising in India's IPO market, but post-listing performance has been a mixed bag. While many stocks debuted strongly, a significant portion later fell below their issue prices. Smaller IPOs struggled most, while larger ones showed resilience. Experts now advise investors to focus on fundamentals over listing-day hype.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:51:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952437d4342f77179dc6906_1766999043457.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2026 Growth Surge Unlocked? RBI Rate Cuts &amp; Reforms Fuel Optimism, But Watch Out for China!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Growth-Surge-Unlocked-RBI-Rate-Cuts-and-Reforms-Fuel-Optimism-But-Watch-Out-for-China/6952430b4342f77179dc67e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Growth-Surge-Unlocked-RBI-Rate-Cuts-and-Reforms-Fuel-Optimism-But-Watch-Out-for-China/6952430b4342f77179dc67e8</guid><description>Invesco forecasts India to lead global growth in 2026, remaining the fastest-growing large economy. This optimism is driven by anticipated Reserve Bank of India rate cuts and ongoing domestic economic reforms. Despite geopolitical challenges, the report expresses cautious optimism, noting stabilization and improved US-India relations. However, it suggests Chinese stocks may outperform Indian equities in Emerging Markets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:49:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952430b4342f77179dc67e7_1766998888226.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jindal Steel's Bold Move: Doubling Capacity to Fuel India's Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Steels-Bold-Move-Doubling-Capacity-to-Fuel-Indias-Growth/695240a84342f77179dc63a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Steels-Bold-Move-Doubling-Capacity-to-Fuel-Indias-Growth/695240a84342f77179dc63a6</guid><description>Jindal Steel Limited is set to significantly boost its structural steel production, doubling capacity at its Raigarh facility to 2.4 MTPA by mid-2028. This strategic expansion aims to meet India's rising infrastructure and energy demands, reduce import reliance, and introduce India's largest specialized steel sections for critical projects. The company's stock shows strong investor interest, trading well above its 52-week low.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:37:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695240a84342f77179dc63a5_1766999013030.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dixon Technologies in Freefall: Stock Hits 16-Month Low, Investors Reel from 35% Wipeout!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Dixon-Technologies-in-Freefall-Stock-Hits-16-Month-Low-Investors-Reel-from-35percent-Wipeout/695240954342f77179dc6329</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Dixon-Technologies-in-Freefall-Stock-Hits-16-Month-Low-Investors-Reel-from-35percent-Wipeout/695240954342f77179dc6329</guid><description>Dixon Technologies' stock plummeted to a 16-month low of ₹11,915, marking a sharp 35% decline from its September peak. The consumer electronics manufacturer's shares fell further on Monday, hitting their lowest point since August 2024 amidst broader market weakness.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:33:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695240954342f77179dc6328_1766998281714.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metal Mania: Hindustan Copper &amp; Zinc Surge on Copper, Silver Boom – What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Mania-Hindustan-Copper-and-Zinc-Surge-on-Copper-Silver-Boom-Whats-Next/695240054342f77179dc61f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Mania-Hindustan-Copper-and-Zinc-Surge-on-Copper-Silver-Boom-Whats-Next/695240054342f77179dc61f3</guid><description>Hindustan Copper and Hindustan Zinc have surged significantly in December, driven by booming copper and silver prices. Hindustan Copper climbed up to 67% to a 15-year high, while Hindustan Zinc rose 35.3%. Analysts remain optimistic due to favorable commodity momentum, though some advise waiting for price corrections as stocks appear overbought.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:32:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695240054342f77179dc61f2_1766998895607.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PL Capital Sees Solar Surge: HUGE Buy Ratings for Premier, Waaree Energies Amidst Massive Growth Forecast!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/PL-Capital-Sees-Solar-Surge-HUGE-Buy-Ratings-for-Premier-Waaree-Energies-Amidst-Massive-Growth-Forecast/69523fe44342f77179dc61b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/PL-Capital-Sees-Solar-Surge-HUGE-Buy-Ratings-for-Premier-Waaree-Energies-Amidst-Massive-Growth-Forecast/69523fe44342f77179dc61b3</guid><description>Brokerage firm PL Capital is highly optimistic about India's solar equipment manufacturing sector, forecasting a near tripling of installed solar capacity by 2030. It has initiated coverage on Premier Energies and Waaree Energies with 'Buy' ratings, and Vikram Solar with an 'Accumulate' stance. PL Capital highlights significant capacity expansions, backward integration efforts, and export potential, particularly to the US, as key drivers for these companies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:32:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69523fe44342f77179dc61b2_1766998738258.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Arfin India STUNS Market: Bags Massive ₹321 Crore Repeat Order! What This Means for Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Arfin-India-STUNS-Market-Bags-Massive-321-Crore-Repeat-Order-What-This-Means-for-Investors/69523f744342f77179dc6053</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Arfin-India-STUNS-Market-Bags-Massive-321-Crore-Repeat-Order-What-This-Means-for-Investors/69523f744342f77179dc6053</guid><description>Arfin India Limited has secured a significant repeat order worth ₹321 crore from Diamond Power Infrastructure Limited. The order is for 11,000 metric tonnes of aluminium sector conductors, expected to be executed between January and November 2026. This substantial contract reinforces Arfin India's strong customer relationship and market position. The company recently reported a substantial 126.85% quarter-on-quarter increase in net profit for Q2 FY26, showing positive financial momentum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:32:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69523f744342f77179dc6052_1766998118935.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coforge AI Deal: Smart Move or Overpriced? Expert Reveals Which Indian IT Giants Truly Hold the Edge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-AI-Deal-Smart-Move-or-Overpriced-Expert-Reveals-Which-Indian-IT-Giants-Truly-Hold-the-Edge/69523ef34342f77179dc5f50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-AI-Deal-Smart-Move-or-Overpriced-Expert-Reveals-Which-Indian-IT-Giants-Truly-Hold-the-Edge/69523ef34342f77179dc5f50</guid><description>Coforge has acquired US-based Encora for $2.35 billion, aiming for a combined revenue of $2.5 billion with a strong AI focus. However, Wedbush Securities analyst Moshe Katri views the deal as 'decent' but favors the AI strategies of larger Indian IT firms like Tata Consultancy Services and Infosys. He believes these tier-1 companies are structurally better positioned to leverage Generative AI due to their evolving business models and focus on integration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:32:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69523ef34342f77179dc5f4f_1766998403535.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Prices EXPLODE 160% in 2025! Motilal Oswal Uncovers Shocking Supply Crunch, Predicts Further Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Prices-EXPLODE-160percent-in-2025-Motilal-Oswal-Uncovers-Shocking-Supply-Crunch-Predicts-Further-Gains/69523edd4342f77179dc5ee3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Prices-EXPLODE-160percent-in-2025-Motilal-Oswal-Uncovers-Shocking-Supply-Crunch-Predicts-Further-Gains/69523edd4342f77179dc5ee3</guid><description>Silver prices surged over 160% in 2025, reaching $75 per ounce on COMEX and ₹2.3 lakh per kilogram domestically. Motilal Oswal Financial Services Ltd.'s report, 'Silver Unchained!!!', attributes this historic rally to prolonged physical supply deficits, declining exchange inventories, and sustained industrial/investment demand, signaling a significant structural shift in the global silver market. The firm advises a 'buy-on-dips' strategy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69523edd4342f77179dc5ee2_1766998235769.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal's Bold Move: Coforge Buy Signal Flashed with ₹2500 Target After Mega Acquisition!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Motilal-Oswals-Bold-Move-Coforge-Buy-Signal-Flashed-with-2500-Target-After-Mega-Acquisition/69523e744342f77179dc5dc4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Motilal-Oswals-Bold-Move-Coforge-Buy-Signal-Flashed-with-2500-Target-After-Mega-Acquisition/69523e744342f77179dc5dc4</guid><description>Motilal Oswal has issued a 'Buy' recommendation for Coforge, setting a target price of ₹2,500, implying a 49% potential upside. The research report highlights the acquisition of US-based Encora, an engineering and AI services firm with approximately $500 million in revenue. This strategic move is expected to significantly boost Coforge's revenue base and be accretive to earnings from day one, positioning the company for strong growth in the IT services sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:28:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69523e744342f77179dc5dc3_1766997804165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Savings Meltdown: Debt Culture Surges, Reshaping Fortunes and Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Savings-Meltdown-Debt-Culture-Surges-Reshaping-Fortunes-and-Future/69523e1a4342f77179dc5d06</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Savings-Meltdown-Debt-Culture-Surges-Reshaping-Fortunes-and-Future/69523e1a4342f77179dc5d06</guid><description>India is undergoing a dramatic financial transformation. Household savings have fallen sharply, while debt levels have surged, driven by an aspirational culture that favors credit (EMIs, BNPL) over traditional saving. This shift is reshaping social dynamics, increasing financial fragility for many, and creating a divide between the financially literate and those left behind. The nation's future prosperity hinges on navigating this transition with better financial education and regulation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:28:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69523e1a4342f77179dc5d05_1766997973169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric's Scooter Sales CRASH! Can New Inverter Business Be the Lifeline?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-Scooter-Sales-CRASH-Can-New-Inverter-Business-Be-the-Lifeline/69523d6e4342f77179dc5b97</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-Scooter-Sales-CRASH-Can-New-Inverter-Business-Be-the-Lifeline/69523d6e4342f77179dc5b97</guid><description>Ola Electric's electric scooter sales are declining sharply across major Indian markets like Maharashtra, Uttar Pradesh, Tamil Nadu, and Karnataka. Despite expanding its retail store network significantly, the company has failed to post year-on-year growth since February. With sales falling over 50% year-to-date and competitors gaining ground, Ola Electric is now banking on its new home inverter business, Ola Shakti, to boost revenue and offset weakening demand in its core EV segment. However, experts question the cross-selling strategy's success amid existing servicing issues and consumer dissatisfaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:27:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69523d6e4342f77179dc5b96_1766997418660.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cancer Insurance Shock: Is Your Mediclaim Your REAL Lifeline Against Skyrocketing Medical Bills?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Cancer-Insurance-Shock-Is-Your-Mediclaim-Your-REAL-Lifeline-Against-Skyrocketing-Medical-Bills/69523e0e4342f77179dc5ccf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Cancer-Insurance-Shock-Is-Your-Mediclaim-Your-REAL-Lifeline-Against-Skyrocketing-Medical-Bills/69523e0e4342f77179dc5ccf</guid><description>A recent analysis by insurance expert Kapil Mehta highlights that standard Mediclaim is superior to critical illness plans for cancer coverage. Cancer treatment costs can exceed ₹30 lakh, and traditional critical illness policies often lapse after one claim. Mediclaim, being annually renewable for life, provides continuous coverage, making it a more robust financial safeguard against the disease's high expenses and potential recurrence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:27:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69523e0e4342f77179dc5cce_1766999493698.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Silver Export Shock: Is THIS the Real Driver of Record Prices?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Chinas-Silver-Export-Shock-Is-THIS-the-Real-Driver-of-Record-Prices/69523cb54342f77179dc59f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Chinas-Silver-Export-Shock-Is-THIS-the-Real-Driver-of-Record-Prices/69523cb54342f77179dc59f9</guid><description>China is set to restrict silver exports starting in 2026, requiring licenses that favor large state-sanctioned firms. With China supplying nearly 65% of global silver, this move is expected to exacerbate existing supply shortages and increase price volatility. Silver prices have already surged over 160% this year. The restrictions will impact industries reliant on silver, including electronics and renewable energy, a concern highlighted by Elon Musk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:23:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69523cb54342f77179dc59f8_1766997304863.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tech Funding Dips But Stays World's 3rd Strongest! What This Means for Your Investments.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Tech-Funding-Dips-But-Stays-Worlds-3rd-Strongest-What-This-Means-for-Your-Investments/69523b974342f77179dc57ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Tech-Funding-Dips-But-Stays-Worlds-3rd-Strongest-What-This-Means-for-Your-Investments/69523b974342f77179dc57ea</guid><description>Indian tech startups secured over $10.5 billion (₹94,000 crore) in 2025, marking a 17% decrease from the previous year. Despite the slowdown, India remains the world's third-largest funded startup ecosystem, trailing only the United States and the United Kingdom. Early-stage funding showed resilience, growing 7% year-on-year, while late-stage and seed-stage funding saw declines. Enterprise applications, retail, and fintech were the leading sectors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:19:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69523b974342f77179dc57e9_1766997067635.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ravelcare Stock Skyrockets 13% as Investment Giants Buy Stakes Post-IPO Success!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ravelcare-Stock-Skyrockets-13percent-as-Investment-Giants-Buy-Stakes-Post-IPO-Success/6952382a4342f77179dc53c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ravelcare-Stock-Skyrockets-13percent-as-Investment-Giants-Buy-Stakes-Post-IPO-Success/6952382a4342f77179dc53c7</guid><description>Ravelcare shares surged 12.6% on the BSE, hitting an intra-day high of ₹158.6. This jump followed significant bulk deals where NAV Capital VCC and Navbharat Investment Opportunities Fund acquired substantial stakes. The digital-first beauty and personal care brand recently debuted on the BSE SME platform at a 55% premium, with IPO funds allocated for marketing and a new manufacturing facility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:00:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952382a4342f77179dc53c6_1766996096458.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Small-Cap Stocks Poised for 2026 Comeback? Invesco's Big Prediction Sparks Investor Buzz!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Small-Cap-Stocks-Poised-for-2026-Comeback-Invescos-Big-Prediction-Sparks-Investor-Buzz/695237cc4342f77179dc52c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Small-Cap-Stocks-Poised-for-2026-Comeback-Invescos-Big-Prediction-Sparks-Investor-Buzz/695237cc4342f77179dc52c2</guid><description>Taher Badshah, Chief Investment Officer at Invesco Mutual Fund, forecasts a gradual recovery for small-cap stocks starting in the second half of 2026. He anticipates increased sector and asset-class rotation, favoring consumption-linked, defensive themes, defence, and hospitality. Precious metals remain a focus, while flexibility and portfolio rebalancing are key for investors navigating potential market shifts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:59:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695237cc4342f77179dc52c1_1766996008005.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Bank Crashes Below 59,000! Top Banks Reel – Is a Big Fall Coming?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nifty-Bank-Crashes-Below-59000-Top-Banks-Reel-Is-a-Big-Fall-Coming/6952378c4342f77179dc527c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nifty-Bank-Crashes-Below-59000-Top-Banks-Reel-Is-a-Big-Fall-Coming/6952378c4342f77179dc527c</guid><description>The Nifty Bank index has fallen for the fourth consecutive trading session, dipping below 59,000. Heavyweights like IndusInd Bank, ICICI Bank, and HDFC Bank are leading the decline. Investors are closely watching key technical levels for potential upside or further downside movement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:55:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952378c4342f77179dc527b_1766996033045.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 4 Lakh Crore IPO Frenzy Coming! India's Stock Market Set for Structural Revolution in 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rs-4-Lakh-Crore-IPO-Frenzy-Coming-Indias-Stock-Market-Set-for-Structural-Revolution-in-2026/695236cf4342f77179dc5093</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rs-4-Lakh-Crore-IPO-Frenzy-Coming-Indias-Stock-Market-Set-for-Structural-Revolution-in-2026/695236cf4342f77179dc5093</guid><description>India's primary markets are poised for a massive expansion, with Pantomath Capital forecasting nearly Rs 4 lakh crore in capital formation through IPOs by 2026. The report highlights a significant structural shift, moving beyond cyclical waves to a sustained period of broad-based capital mobilization. This boom is driven by quality capital deployment, focusing on expansion and capacity creation, and supported by leading sectors like financial services and manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:55:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695236cf4342f77179dc5092_1766995760931.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys Shocker: Automation Triggers Major Fresher Hiring Cut! India's IT Talent Future Questioned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Shocker-Automation-Triggers-Major-Fresher-Hiring-Cut-Indias-IT-Talent-Future-Questioned/695236bf4342f77179dc5044</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Shocker-Automation-Triggers-Major-Fresher-Hiring-Cut-Indias-IT-Talent-Future-Questioned/695236bf4342f77179dc5044</guid><description>Infosys, India's second-largest IT services provider, is set to hire fewer fresh graduates in the coming years due to increased productivity from automation. This marks the first time a major IT outsourcer explicitly forecasts a decline in entry-level jobs, raising concerns for millions of engineering students. While current fiscal hiring remains on track, future strategies diverge from peers like Cognizant and TCS, who plan to increase or selectively hire AI-native talent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:54:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695236bf4342f77179dc5043_1766995802708.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rare Earth Secret: Why World's 3rd Biggest Reserves Mean Nothing Without Production!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Rare-Earth-Secret-Why-Worlds-3rd-Biggest-Reserves-Mean-Nothing-Without-Production/695236504342f77179dc4f2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Rare-Earth-Secret-Why-Worlds-3rd-Biggest-Reserves-Mean-Nothing-Without-Production/695236504342f77179dc4f2a</guid><description>India holds the world's third-largest rare earth reserves, estimated at 6.9 million tonnes, but ranks seventh globally in production. A new report highlights major bottlenecks in mining and processing, complicated by thorium presence and strict regulations. While China dominates global refining, India's limited capacity means its vast reserves offer little economic or strategic advantage currently.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:52:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695236504342f77179dc4f29_1766995621371.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Midday Market Mayhem: Stocks Surge &amp; Plunge on Orders, Fraud Alerts, and Commodity Waves!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Midday-Market-Mayhem-Stocks-Surge-and-Plunge-on-Orders-Fraud-Alerts-and-Commodity-Waves/695236e34342f77179dc50ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Midday-Market-Mayhem-Stocks-Surge-and-Plunge-on-Orders-Fraud-Alerts-and-Commodity-Waves/695236e34342f77179dc50ea</guid><description>Indian stock markets faced pressure today, with Nifty 50 near 25,974 and BSE Sensex below 84,800. Despite the broader decline, several stocks saw significant movement. Hindustan Copper and Hindustan Zinc surged on strong metal prices. Vedanta rose after winning a critical mineral auction bid. Conversely, Punjab National Bank dropped over 3% due to a large loan fraud disclosure, while railway stocks like IRFC and RVNL pulled back after a strong rally. Sigachi Industries declined amid an investigation into a fire incident, and Timex Group India shares fell sharply due to a promoter offer for sale at a discount.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:50:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695236e34342f77179dc50e9_1766995951120.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Green Hydrogen Boom: 3 Giants Set to Dominate? Watch These Stocks Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Hydrogen-Boom-3-Giants-Set-to-Dominate-Watch-These-Stocks-Now/695235504342f77179dc4d75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Hydrogen-Boom-3-Giants-Set-to-Dominate-Watch-These-Stocks-Now/695235504342f77179dc4d75</guid><description>India is pushing aggressively into green hydrogen with its National Green Hydrogen Mission, aiming for global leadership by 2030 with over Rs 8,000 billion investment and 125 GW renewable capacity. Key players like NTPC Ltd, Reliance Industries, and Bharat Petroleum Corporation are making significant strides. NTPC has operational projects and is developing hydrogen hubs, Reliance plans massive production and integrated manufacturing, while BPCL partners for renewable and green hydrogen ventures. Investors should watch these diversified giants as they venture into this burgeoning sector, considering government support and technological advancements.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:50:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695235504342f77179dc4d74_1766995656603.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Automobile Boom Ahead! Nuvama Predicts Double-Digit Growth for Indian Car Makers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Automobile-Boom-Ahead-Nuvama-Predicts-Double-Digit-Growth-for-Indian-Car-Makers/695233da4342f77179dc4aa3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Automobile-Boom-Ahead-Nuvama-Predicts-Double-Digit-Growth-for-Indian-Car-Makers/695233da4342f77179dc4aa3</guid><description>Nuvama Institutional Equities forecasts robust double-digit sales growth for India's automobile sector by December 2025. Key drivers include improved affordability from GST cuts, new product launches, lower interest rates, and easier finance availability. The report anticipates significant year-on-year volume increases across two-wheelers (22%), passenger vehicles (21%), and commercial vehicles (17%), with companies like TVS Motor, Eicher's Royal Enfield, Hero MotoCorp, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, and Maruti Suzuki expected to lead.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:47:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695233da4342f77179dc4aa2_1766994970152.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Industrial Output Set for Strong November Rebound: Union Bank Forecasts 4% IIP Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Industrial-Output-Set-for-Strong-November-Rebound-Union-Bank-Forecasts-4percent-IIP-Growth/6952347a4342f77179dc4bbd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Industrial-Output-Set-for-Strong-November-Rebound-Union-Bank-Forecasts-4percent-IIP-Growth/6952347a4342f77179dc4bbd</guid><description>Union Bank of India forecasts India's Index of Industrial Production (IIP) to surge to 4.0% year-on-year in November 2025, a significant recovery from October's 0.4%. This rebound is driven by post-festive season normalization, increased manufacturing output, and healthy consumption trends. The report also notes positive contributions from automobile production and digital payment growth, though electricity demand saw a dip.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:47:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952347a4342f77179dc4bbc_1766995163642.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Penny Stock Surprise: SEPC Limited Lands Massive Rs 230 Crore Mining Deal with MOIL – Will This Be a Multibagger?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Penny-Stock-Surprise-SEPC-Limited-Lands-Massive-Rs-230-Crore-Mining-Deal-with-MOIL-Will-This-Be-a-Multibagger/695230744342f77179dc4557</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Penny-Stock-Surprise-SEPC-Limited-Lands-Massive-Rs-230-Crore-Mining-Deal-with-MOIL-Will-This-Be-a-Multibagger/695230744342f77179dc4557</guid><description>SEPC Limited has secured a significant ₹230 crore turnkey mining infrastructure order from Government of India enterprise MOIL Limited. The contract, awarded through a competitive global tender where SEPC was the lowest bidder (L1), involves designing, constructing, and commissioning a vertical shaft at the Chikla Mine in Maharashtra. This major win is expected to enhance SEPC's revenue visibility and operational performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:31:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695230744342f77179dc4556_1766994239032.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mishra Dhatu Nigam EXPLODES 15% on Massive Volume Surge! Is This India's Next Defence Powerhouse Stock?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mishra-Dhatu-Nigam-EXPLODES-15percent-on-Massive-Volume-Surge-Is-This-Indias-Next-Defence-Powerhouse-Stock/69522ff64342f77179dc448f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mishra-Dhatu-Nigam-EXPLODES-15percent-on-Massive-Volume-Surge-Is-This-Indias-Next-Defence-Powerhouse-Stock/69522ff64342f77179dc448f</guid><description>Mishra Dhatu Nigam (Midhani) shares surged 15% to ₹363 on heavy volumes, reaching a 5-month high. This rally is fueled by a strong ₹1,869 crore order book, primarily from aerospace and defence, robust revenue guidance for FY26, and a 'Buy' rating from ICICI Securities with a ₹460 target price. The company's key role in manufacturing special metals for critical sectors drives investor optimism.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:27:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69522ff64342f77179dc448e_1766994063772.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Hits Rough Seas: 5% Plunge as Silver Price Takes a Sharp Dive!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Zinc-Hits-Rough-Seas-5percent-Plunge-as-Silver-Price-Takes-a-Sharp-Dive/69522dd04342f77179dc3eba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Zinc-Hits-Rough-Seas-5percent-Plunge-as-Silver-Price-Takes-a-Sharp-Dive/69522dd04342f77179dc3eba</guid><description>Hindustan Zinc shares fell over 5% intraday on December 29 following an 8% decline in silver prices from their all-time high. As India's largest silver producer, the company's stock is highly sensitive to bullion market movements. Despite the intraday fall, the stock has shown strong gains over the past month and year-to-date.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69522dd04342f77179dc3eb9_1766993466042.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC Life's Big Margin Comeback? CEO Vibha Padalkar Unveils FY27 Strategy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/HDFC-Lifes-Big-Margin-Comeback-CEO-Vibha-Padalkar-Unveils-FY27-Strategy/69522e694342f77179dc40b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/HDFC-Lifes-Big-Margin-Comeback-CEO-Vibha-Padalkar-Unveils-FY27-Strategy/69522e694342f77179dc40b8</guid><description>HDFC Life Insurance CEO Vibha Padalkar anticipates Value of New Business (VNB) margins will normalize by FY27. The company is strategically recalibrating post-GST changes, enhancing its product mix with protection and ULIPs, and investing in technology and distribution. Despite short-term pressures from input tax credit withdrawal, HDFC Life plans to absorb these over the next 2-3 quarters, aiming for sustained profitability and market share growth, as retail protection business shows sharp gains.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:22:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69522e694342f77179dc40b7_1766993702389.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>