<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 21:15:57 +0000</pubDate><item><title>EVs: From Green Cars to Political Battlegrounds? How the Toyota Prius Sparked a Polarizing Debate!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/EVs-From-Green-Cars-to-Political-Battlegrounds-How-the-Toyota-Prius-Sparked-a-Polarizing-Debate/6956c7514342f77179f8ade4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/EVs-From-Green-Cars-to-Political-Battlegrounds-How-the-Toyota-Prius-Sparked-a-Polarizing-Debate/6956c7514342f77179f8ade4</guid><description>Electric vehicles (EVs) are no longer just cars; they've become deeply political. This polarization, fueled by government mandates and environmental debates, traces its roots back 25 years to the marketing of the humble Toyota Prius. Experts note this partisan divide hinders objective discussion about EV adoption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:03:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956c7514342f77179f8ade3_1767294867964.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MIB Seals Arugn Tech's Planetcast Media Buyout: Is This India's Next Media Giant?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/MIB-Seals-Arugn-Techs-Planetcast-Media-Buyout-Is-This-Indias-Next-Media-Giant/6956c6f54342f77179f8ad06</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/MIB-Seals-Arugn-Techs-Planetcast-Media-Buyout-Is-This-Indias-Next-Media-Giant/6956c6f54342f77179f8ad06</guid><description>India's Ministry of Information and Broadcasting (MIB) has approved Arugn Technologies' proposal to buy Apollo Global-backed AION Capital's stake in teleport operator Planetcast Media. Arugn Technologies, a special purpose vehicle of Planetcast promoters, raised ₹600 crore via non-convertible debentures for the acquisition, which will shift the liability to Planetcast's balance sheet post-merger. This marks a significant ownership change for the MIB-licensed broadcast services provider.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:00:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956c6f54342f77179f8ad05_1767294844714.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Box Office Reality Bites: Streamers Slash Film Payments on Flops!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Box-Office-Reality-Bites-Streamers-Slash-Film-Payments-on-Flops/6956c6934342f77179f8abbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Box-Office-Reality-Bites-Streamers-Slash-Film-Payments-on-Flops/6956c6934342f77179f8abbb</guid><description>Streaming platforms are now tying film payments to box office performance, slashing guaranteed prices for underperforming movies. Platforms like Netflix have reduced base payments by up to 50% for films like "Akhanda 2: Thaandavam" after theatrical disappointment. This shift prioritizes profitability and risk-sharing, moving away from previously inflated payments. Distributors see this as a fairer system, but it pressures producers to ensure theatrical success before digital release.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:00:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956c6934342f77179f8abba_1767294784235.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Realty Funding Revolution: New Rules, Higher Developer Equity, and Investor Confidence Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Realty-Funding-Revolution-New-Rules-Higher-Developer-Equity-and-Investor-Confidence-Surge/6956c67a4342f77179f8ab4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Realty-Funding-Revolution-New-Rules-Higher-Developer-Equity-and-Investor-Confidence-Surge/6956c67a4342f77179f8ab4a</guid><description>India's real estate sector is experiencing a fundamental shift in funding. Capital is now dispensed in more structured, conditional, and disciplined ways, driven by regulatory tightening like RERA and GST, alongside a greater demand for developer equity (now 25-30%). Funding is increasingly project-specific and released based on construction milestones. This evolution favors large developers and promotes consolidation, with institutional capital seeking platform-level partnerships focused on governance and execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:59:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956c67a4342f77179f8ab49_1767294657322.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Irdai Set to Unleash Major Investment Shake-Up for Insurers: Get Ready for Big Changes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Irdai-Set-to-Unleash-Major-Investment-Shake-Up-for-Insurers-Get-Ready-for-Big-Changes/6956c6994342f77179f8abee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Irdai-Set-to-Unleash-Major-Investment-Shake-Up-for-Insurers-Get-Ready-for-Big-Changes/6956c6994342f77179f8abee</guid><description>India's insurance regulator, Irdai, now has greater control over investment rules for insurers, following amendments to the Insurance Act. Key investment provisions are consolidated into a single section, with operational details shifting to regulations. This change grants insurers more flexibility, including for repo and securities lending transactions, and opens up investments in private limited companies. The move aims to allow Irdai to adapt regulations faster to market changes. Insurers manage ₹74.4 lakh crore in assets, with a significant portion in sovereign debt, which the RBI notes could be too conservative for meeting policyholder return expectations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:58:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956c6994342f77179f8abed_1767294726801.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHB's Stern Warning: Housing Finance Firms Urged to Accelerate PMAY 2.0 Loans Amidst Slow Disbursal Pace</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NHBs-Stern-Warning-Housing-Finance-Firms-Urged-to-Accelerate-PMAY-20-Loans-Amidst-Slow-Disbursal-Pace/6956c5a34342f77179f8a34d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NHBs-Stern-Warning-Housing-Finance-Firms-Urged-to-Accelerate-PMAY-20-Loans-Amidst-Slow-Disbursal-Pace/6956c5a34342f77179f8a34d</guid><description>The National Housing Bank (NHB) has expressed concern over the slow pace of loan disbursements under the PMAY 2.0 interest subsidy scheme. During a review with leading housing finance companies (HFCs), NHB officials urged them to step up participation. HFCs cited concerns over higher repayment risk and lower ticket sizes associated with the scheme, preferring larger loans. NHB aims to expand credit access to smaller borrowers, highlighting the need for HFCs to recalibrate risk assessment and increase focus on the program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:58:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956c5a34342f77179f8a34c_1767294632335.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Borrowing Costs Jump! Indian Banks Hike Lending Rates to 8.7% - What It Means For Your Loans!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Borrowing-Costs-Jump-Indian-Banks-Hike-Lending-Rates-to-87percent-What-It-Means-For-Your-Loans/6956c5644342f77179f86243</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Borrowing-Costs-Jump-Indian-Banks-Hike-Lending-Rates-to-87percent-What-It-Means-For-Your-Loans/6956c5644342f77179f86243</guid><description>Average lending rates on fresh rupee loans in India rose 10 basis points to 8.71% by November-end. State-run banks led the increase, raising rates by 16 basis points to 8.05%, while private and foreign banks saw mixed changes. This trend is driven by rising 10-year sovereign bond yields and slower deposit growth, making it harder for banks to pass on RBI rate cuts to borrowers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:58:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956c5644342f77179f86242_1767294388838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NFRA's New Toolkit: Are Auditors Ready to Catch Every Financial Statement Error?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/NFRAs-New-Toolkit-Are-Auditors-Ready-to-Catch-Every-Financial-Statement-Error/6956be7f4342f77179f75780</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/NFRAs-New-Toolkit-Are-Auditors-Ready-to-Catch-Every-Financial-Statement-Error/6956be7f4342f77179f75780</guid><description>India's National Financial Reporting Authority (NFRA) has launched a new toolkit designed to help small and medium accounting firms detect errors in company financial statements. This initiative aims to enhance overall audit quality across the nation, providing a practical guide for auditors to improve their assessment processes. NFRA plans to release similar resources for other key audit areas.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:27:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956be7f4342f77179f7577f_1767292613112.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BYD Smashes 2025 Sales Goal, Likely Overtakes Tesla: Is This the New EV King?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/BYD-Smashes-2025-Sales-Goal-Likely-Overtakes-Tesla-Is-This-the-New-EV-King/6956bc094342f77179f74b2b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/BYD-Smashes-2025-Sales-Goal-Likely-Overtakes-Tesla-Is-This-the-New-EV-King/6956bc094342f77179f74b2b</guid><description>BYD Co. met its revised 2025 sales target, delivering 4.6 million vehicles and is poised to become the world's largest electric vehicle maker, surpassing Tesla Inc. Despite this achievement, the company faces mounting pressures in China's auto market, including reduced government incentives and intense competition. Strong overseas sales growth offers a positive outlook, though BYD also contends with declining profits and industry consolidation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:18:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956bc094342f77179f74b2a_1767291981281.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Reveals: ₹2000 Notes Almost Entirely Returned! What it Means for Your Money</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Reveals-2000-Notes-Almost-Entirely-Returned-What-it-Means-for-Your-Money/6956ba394342f77179f746aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Reveals-2000-Notes-Almost-Entirely-Returned-What-it-Means-for-Your-Money/6956ba394342f77179f746aa</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has announced that 98.41% of the ₹2000 banknotes withdrawn from circulation since May 19, 2023, have been returned. The total value in circulation has dropped significantly from ₹3.56 lakh crore to just ₹5,669 crore. While direct bank branch exchanges ended in October 2023, individuals can still deposit these notes at RBI Issue Offices or via India Post. The ₹2000 banknotes remain legal tender.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:05:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956ba394342f77179f746a9_1767291521217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Stern Warning: Crypto &amp; Stablecoins Risk Financial Stability; Favors CBDCs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Stern-Warning-Crypto-and-Stablecoins-Risk-Financial-Stability-Favors-CBDCs/6956b9bb4342f77179f7452f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Stern-Warning-Crypto-and-Stablecoins-Risk-Financial-Stability-Favors-CBDCs/6956b9bb4342f77179f7452f</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has strongly reiterated its cautious stance on crypto assets and stablecoins. The central bank emphasized that central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) should be prioritized as they offer efficiency, programmability, and instant settlement with the credibility and safety of central bank money, serving as the ultimate anchor of trust and the primary settlement asset in the monetary system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:05:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956b9bb4342f77179f7452e_1767291398424.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Britannia Industries Faces ₹109 Crore GST Demand: What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannia-Industries-Faces-109-Crore-GST-Demand-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6956b1da4342f77179f72f3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannia-Industries-Faces-109-Crore-GST-Demand-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6956b1da4342f77179f72f3f</guid><description>Britannia Industries has received a Goods and Services Tax (GST) order demanding ₹108.50 crore in tax, plus an equivalent penalty and interest, for alleged incorrect input tax credit claims spanning six financial years (FY19-FY24). The company stated the order is appealable and expects no significant financial or operational impact, planning to exercise its legal remedies. Its shares closed down 0.53% on BSE.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:33:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956b1da4342f77179f72f3e_1767289377092.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tax Transformation: A Decade of Trust Building Fueling Investor Confidence and Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Transformation-A-Decade-of-Trust-Building-Fueling-Investor-Confidence-and-Growth/6956afdb4342f77179f7286e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Transformation-A-Decade-of-Trust-Building-Fueling-Investor-Confidence-and-Growth/6956afdb4342f77179f7286e</guid><description>Over the past decade, India's Union Budget speeches have detailed a significant shift in tax administration, moving from suspicion and heavy enforcement to treating taxpayers as partners in nation-building. Key reforms aimed at tax predictability, fairness, and simplification have been introduced, including lower corporate tax rates and faceless assessments. This evolution is critical for fostering investor confidence and sustaining India's economic momentum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:23:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956afdb4342f77179f7286d_1767288975285.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Rings in 2026: Maruti Hits Record High, GST Stabilizes, Sin Taxes Hike! 📈</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Rings-in-2026-Maruti-Hits-Record-High-GST-Stabilizes-Sin-Taxes-Hike/6956aad54342f77179f716af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Rings-in-2026-Maruti-Hits-Record-High-GST-Stabilizes-Sin-Taxes-Hike/6956aad54342f77179f716af</guid><description>India's 2026 debut saw mixed market signals. The Nifty edged up slightly while the Sensex dipped, but broader indices and auto stocks, led by Maruti Suzuki's 42-year wholesale high, soared. GST collections in December showed stabilization post rate cuts. The government also recalibrated sin taxes with higher duties on cigarettes and a new cess on pan masala. Household borrowing remains manageable at 41.3% of GDP, though experts caution against reckless lending. The rupee weakened against the dollar amid foreign fund outflows.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:02:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956aad54342f77179f716ae_1767287578931.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eases Director KYC Rules &amp; Govt Firm Closures: Big Relief for Businesses!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eases-Director-KYC-Rules-and-Govt-Firm-Closures-Big-Relief-for-Businesses/6956a88b4342f77179f70d93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eases-Director-KYC-Rules-and-Govt-Firm-Closures-Big-Relief-for-Businesses/6956a88b4342f77179f70d93</guid><description>India's corporate affairs ministry has significantly eased compliance for company directors by extending KYC filing to once every three years, effective March 31. Additionally, rules for voluntarily closing sick government companies have been simplified through a centralized system (C-PACE). These changes aim to reduce the regulatory burden and streamline business operations across the country.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:53:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956a88b4342f77179f70d92_1767287109553.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises' Mega Deal: Data Centre JV Seals Rs 366 Crore Acquisition!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Adani-Enterprises-Mega-Deal-Data-Centre-JV-Seals-Rs-366-Crore-Acquisition/6956a3c54342f77179f6f9eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Adani-Enterprises-Mega-Deal-Data-Centre-JV-Seals-Rs-366-Crore-Acquisition/6956a3c54342f77179f6f9eb</guid><description>AdaniConneX, the data centre joint venture of Adani Enterprises, has successfully acquired 100% of Girdhari Build Estate for Rs 366.65 crore. This strategic move bolsters Adani's digital infrastructure capabilities across India. In a separate development, Adani Green Energy has operationalized 307.4 MW of new renewable power projects in Gujarat, expanding its total renewable capacity to 17,237.2 MW.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:31:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956a3c54342f77179f6f9ea_1767285899850.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Office Space Boom: Flex Offices Become The Secret Weapon For Global Giants!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Office-Space-Boom-Flex-Offices-Become-The-Secret-Weapon-For-Global-Giants/6956a2234342f77179f6f2aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Office-Space-Boom-Flex-Offices-Become-The-Secret-Weapon-For-Global-Giants/6956a2234342f77179f6f2aa</guid><description>Flexible workspace operators are aggressively partnering with Global Capability Centers (GCCs) to fuel their expansion in India. Experts predict flex spaces will capture a significant portion, 65-80 million sq. ft., of the massive 160-200 million sq. ft. office space demand from GCCs by 2030, signaling a strategic shift towards agile, Opex-led operational models.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:24:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956a2234342f77179f6f2a9_1767285465080.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KFC &amp; Pizza Hut India Giants Sapphire Foods, Devyani International Forge Mega Merger!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/KFC-and-Pizza-Hut-India-Giants-Sapphire-Foods-Devyani-International-Forge-Mega-Merger/6956a1d74342f77179f6f114</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/KFC-and-Pizza-Hut-India-Giants-Sapphire-Foods-Devyani-International-Forge-Mega-Merger/6956a1d74342f77179f6f114</guid><description>Sapphire Foods and Devyani International, major operators of KFC and Pizza Hut in India, are set to merge. This consolidation aims to create a dominant quick-service restaurant (QSR) player, though it requires extensive regulatory approvals expected to take 12-15 months. The merged entity will focus on expansion and growth across its brands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:23:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956a1d74342f77179f6f113_1767285318732.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor Sales EXPLODE 50% in December! EV Growth Soars - Is This India's Next Auto King?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Sales-EXPLODE-50percent-in-December-EV-Growth-Soars-Is-This-Indias-Next-Auto-King/6956a1724342f77179f6eefc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Sales-EXPLODE-50percent-in-December-EV-Growth-Soars-Is-This-Indias-Next-Auto-King/6956a1724342f77179f6eefc</guid><description>TVS Motor Company reported a massive 50% surge in total sales for December 2025, reaching 4,81,389 units compared to 3,21,687 units in December 2024. Two-wheeler sales climbed 48%, domestic sales rose 54%, and electric vehicle sales jumped an impressive 77% to 35,605 units. International business also saw strong growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:22:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956a1724342f77179f6eefb_1767285549047.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki Hints at Small Car Price Hike: Is Your Next Car More Expensive?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Hints-at-Small-Car-Price-Hike-Is-Your-Next-Car-More-Expensive/6956a1c44342f77179f6f08d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Hints-at-Small-Car-Price-Hike-Is-Your-Next-Car-More-Expensive/6956a1c44342f77179f6f08d</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki India is contemplating revising prices for its small cars, reversing reductions made last year. The decision comes as the company manages a backlog of over 1.5 months in bookings for its mini-segment vehicles and will be announced soon.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:22:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956a1c44342f77179f6f08c_1767285439307.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp's December Sales EXPLODE 40% Past Expectations! Domestic Demand &amp; Exports Soar!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorps-December-Sales-EXPLODE-40percent-Past-Expectations-Domestic-Demand-and-Exports-Soar/69569cc74342f77179f6dbbf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorps-December-Sales-EXPLODE-40percent-Past-Expectations-Domestic-Demand-and-Exports-Soar/69569cc74342f77179f6dbbf</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp reported a robust December with total sales of 4.56 lakh units, a 40% year-on-year increase and surpassing CNBC-TV18's poll estimate of 4.10 lakh units. Domestic sales surged 42.5% to 4.19 lakh units, leading the growth, while exports also saw a healthy 21% rise to 37,236 units. This strong performance, driven by both home and overseas markets, signals improving demand conditions and reinforces Hero MotoCorp's leading position in the two-wheeler sector. The company's shares closed up 1.14% at ₹5,837.00.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69569cc74342f77179f6dbbe_1767283994365.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹2000 Note Return! RBI Confirms 98.41% Back - Is Your Money Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Massive-2000-Note-Return-RBI-Confirms-9841percent-Back-Is-Your-Money-Safe/69569cbe4342f77179f6db36</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Massive-2000-Note-Return-RBI-Confirms-9841percent-Back-Is-Your-Money-Safe/69569cbe4342f77179f6db36</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) announced that 98.41% of the ₹2000 banknotes, initially valued at ₹3.56 lakh crore, have been returned. The remaining circulation is now just ₹5,669 crore as of December 31, 2025. The facility to deposit or exchange these notes at bank branches closed on October 7, 2023, but individuals can still send them to RBI Issue Offices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:00:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69569cbe4342f77179f6db35_1767283982820.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Steel Prices Hit 5-Year Low in 2025 Amid Global Turmoil: Tata Steel CEO Warns!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Steel-Prices-Hit-5-Year-Low-in-2025-Amid-Global-Turmoil-Tata-Steel-CEO-Warns/69569c0d4342f77179f6d863</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Steel-Prices-Hit-5-Year-Low-in-2025-Amid-Global-Turmoil-Tata-Steel-CEO-Warns/69569c0d4342f77179f6d863</guid><description>Tata Steel CEO and Managing Director T V Narendran announced that Indian steel prices reached a five-year low in 2025, despite robust domestic demand. He attributed this to global trade disruptions, protectionist policies, and increased Chinese steel exports flooding international markets. While Tata Steel's Indian operations remained stable, its European business faced pressure. Narendran remains optimistic about India's growing economy but emphasizes preparedness for global challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:59:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69569c0d4342f77179f6d862_1767283825446.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Auto's Big Comeback: 2026 Demand Surges on GST &amp; Premium Cars! Are Your Investments Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Autos-Big-Comeback-2026-Demand-Surges-on-GST-and-Premium-Cars-Are-Your-Investments-Ready/69569c994342f77179f6daab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Autos-Big-Comeback-2026-Demand-Surges-on-GST-and-Premium-Cars-Are-Your-Investments-Ready/69569c994342f77179f6daab</guid><description>India's automobile sector is poised for growth in 2026, recovering from a slow 2025 thanks to government GST cuts on cars, two-wheelers, and commercial vehicles. Key drivers for the upcoming year include a trend towards premiumisation, potential boosts from the 8th Pay Commission's increased disposable income, and higher infrastructure spending. While demand is expected to remain strong, investors should watch for risks like a weakening rupee and rising raw material costs impacting automaker margins.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:59:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69569c994342f77179f6daaa_1767283992186.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking Sales Reveal: Pernod Ricard India DETHRONES Diageo to Become India's ALCOHOLIC BEVERAGE KING!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shocking-Sales-Reveal-Pernod-Ricard-India-DETHRONES-Diageo-to-Become-Indias-ALCOHOLIC-BEVERAGE-KING/69569b094342f77179f6d37b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shocking-Sales-Reveal-Pernod-Ricard-India-DETHRONES-Diageo-to-Become-Indias-ALCOHOLIC-BEVERAGE-KING/69569b094342f77179f6d37b</guid><description>Pernod Ricard India has solidified its position as India's largest alcoholic beverage maker by value in FY25, recording sales of ₹27,445.80 crore. This figure places it ahead of Diageo India (United Spirits Ltd), which reported consolidated revenue from operations at ₹27,276 crore for the same period. The combined income of these two giants exceeded ₹55,000 crore, highlighting their dominance in the Indian market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:55:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69569b094342f77179f6d37a_1767283643434.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Punjab &amp; Sind Bank Posts Strong Q3 Growth: Total Business Surges to ₹2.49 Lakh Crore!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Punjab-and-Sind-Bank-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Total-Business-Surges-to-249-Lakh-Crore/695695284342f77179f6bb17</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Punjab-and-Sind-Bank-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Total-Business-Surges-to-249-Lakh-Crore/695695284342f77179f6bb17</guid><description>Punjab &amp; Sind Bank reported robust performance for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. Total business increased by 11.84% year-on-year to ₹2.49 lakh crore. Deposits grew 9.27% to ₹1.39 lakh crore, while gross advances saw a significant 15.25% jump to ₹1.10 lakh crore. CASA deposits also rose, maintaining a healthy CASA ratio of 31.02%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:28:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695695284342f77179f6bb16_1767282049887.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹2 Lakh Crore Fertilizer Subsidy Goes Fully Digital: Efficiency &amp; Transparency Boost for Indian Farming!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/2-Lakh-Crore-Fertilizer-Subsidy-Goes-Fully-Digital-Efficiency-and-Transparency-Boost-for-Indian-Farming/695695184342f77179f6baa8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/2-Lakh-Crore-Fertilizer-Subsidy-Goes-Fully-Digital-Efficiency-and-Transparency-Boost-for-Indian-Farming/695695184342f77179f6baa8</guid><description>Union Fertilizers Minister Jagat Prakash Nadda launched a new integrated e-bill system to digitally process fertilizer subsidies worth approximately ₹2 lakh crore. This significant move transitions from manual, paper-based methods to a fully digital workflow, eliminating physical bill movement. The system aims to enhance transparency, efficiency, and accountability in financial operations, providing real-time oversight and accelerating payment timelines for fertilizer companies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:28:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695695184342f77179f6baa7_1767282016717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Export Boom? Bharat Forge Chief Baba Kalyani's Bold Budget 2026 Demand!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Export-Boom-Bharat-Forge-Chief-Baba-Kalyanis-Bold-Budget-2026-Demand/695694664342f77179f6b780</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Export-Boom-Bharat-Forge-Chief-Baba-Kalyanis-Bold-Budget-2026-Demand/695694664342f77179f6b780</guid><description>Bharat Forge Chairman Baba Kalyani is urging the government for significant reforms in the Union Budget 2026 to boost India's private defence manufacturing sector. He highlighted the critical need for more flexible export credit, arguing that current systems hinder exports to emerging markets where competitors offer better financing. Kalyani also called for dedicated research and development (R&amp;D) funding for private defence firms to drive innovation and competitiveness, aiming to strengthen India's position as a global defence exporter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:28:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695694664342f77179f6b77f_1767282142844.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹567 Crore Health Tech Order Lands: RailTel Corporation Poised for Huge Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Massive-567-Crore-Health-Tech-Order-Lands-RailTel-Corporation-Poised-for-Huge-Growth/695694c64342f77179f6b8cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Massive-567-Crore-Health-Tech-Order-Lands-RailTel-Corporation-Poised-for-Huge-Growth/695694c64342f77179f6b8cb</guid><description>RailTel Corporation of India has secured a significant Letter of Acceptance from the Assam Health Infrastructure Development &amp; Management Society for a Hospital Management Information System (HMIS) project. The order, valued at ₹567 crore, includes procurement, implementation, and maintenance, with execution planned until January 31, 2032. This major win comes as the company reported a 4.7% rise in its Q2 net profit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:28:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695694c64342f77179f6b8ca_1767281937036.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 8-9% Growth Secret? Baba Kalyani Reveals Critical Infrastructure &amp; Logistics Gaps!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-8-9percent-Growth-Secret-Baba-Kalyani-Reveals-Critical-Infrastructure-and-Logistics-Gaps/6956945b4342f77179f6b713</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-8-9percent-Growth-Secret-Baba-Kalyani-Reveals-Critical-Infrastructure-and-Logistics-Gaps/6956945b4342f77179f6b713</guid><description>Bharat Forge Chairman Baba Kalyani emphasizes that while India's investment climate is improving, achieving sustained 8-9% economic growth requires a significant focus on infrastructure and logistics. He highlights that India's logistics costs, at 16-17% of GDP, are double China's, a gap that must be closed to boost competitiveness and capitalize on global supply chain diversification opportunities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956945b4342f77179f6b712_1767281836228.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yajur Fibres IPO Launches Jan 7: Rs 120 Cr Raise Amidst Record SME Buzz! Don't Miss Out!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Yajur-Fibres-IPO-Launches-Jan-7-Rs-120-Cr-Raise-Amidst-Record-SME-Buzz-Dont-Miss-Out/695693514342f77179f6b2a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Yajur-Fibres-IPO-Launches-Jan-7-Rs-120-Cr-Raise-Amidst-Record-SME-Buzz-Dont-Miss-Out/695693514342f77179f6b2a2</guid><description>Yajur Fibres is launching its Initial Public Offering (IPO) on January 7, aiming to raise Rs 120.4 crore. With a price band of Rs 168-174 per share, the subscription will remain open until January 9. This is noted as the largest SME IPO in over three months, with funds earmarked for expansion, setting up a new greenfield unit, and working capital needs. Shares are set to list on the BSE SME platform on January 14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:23:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695693514342f77179f6b2a1_1767281597090.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PM Modi Greenlights India's First Underwater Rail Tunnel: Assam Gears Up for ₹20,000 Crore Mega Project!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/PM-Modi-Greenlights-Indias-First-Underwater-Rail-Tunnel-Assam-Gears-Up-for-20000-Crore-Mega-Project/695693494342f77179f6b25f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/PM-Modi-Greenlights-Indias-First-Underwater-Rail-Tunnel-Assam-Gears-Up-for-20000-Crore-Mega-Project/695693494342f77179f6b25f</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi has approved the inclusion of a railway component in the ambitious Gohpur-Numaligarh twin-tube underwater tunnel project in Assam. This strategic addition, proposed by the Prime Minister himself, increases the project's estimated cost from ₹12,000 Crore to ₹20,000 Crore. The tunnel, designed to be over 32 meters below the Brahmaputra riverbed, is crucial for national defence and security due to its proximity to the Arunachal Pradesh border. The Finance Ministry has cleared the project, with the Union Cabinet's approval imminent and the Public Investment Board having already approved it on December 19. Construction is expected to take five years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:21:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695693494342f77179f6b25e_1767281570719.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yes Bank's Crucial Q3 Results Date Revealed! Board Meeting Set for January 17, 2026 - What Investors Must Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Banks-Crucial-Q3-Results-Date-Revealed-Board-Meeting-Set-for-January-17-2026-What-Investors-Must-Know/69568e554342f77179f69c04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Banks-Crucial-Q3-Results-Date-Revealed-Board-Meeting-Set-for-January-17-2026-What-Investors-Must-Know/69568e554342f77179f69c04</guid><description>Yes Bank has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on Saturday, January 17, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ending December 31, 2025. This announcement details the schedule for the bank's upcoming earnings report, which is crucial for investors monitoring its financial performance for the fiscal year 2025-26. The trading window for company insiders will also be closed until two days after the results are published.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:56:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568e554342f77179f69c03_1767280437683.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Hints at Major Breakout! Can 26,200 Conquer Amidst ITC's Tax Shock?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Hints-at-Major-Breakout-Can-26200-Conquer-Amidst-ITCs-Tax-Shock/69568d274342f77179f696b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Hints-at-Major-Breakout-Can-26200-Conquer-Amidst-ITCs-Tax-Shock/69568d274342f77179f696b7</guid><description>The Nifty 50 index ended near flat, closing up just 16 points at 26,146, extending its winning streak. However, charts suggest a potential breakout above 26,200. Gains were capped by a sharp 9% fall in ITC due to increased excise duty on tobacco and health cess on pan masala. Auto, Realty, and Metal stocks led sectoral gains, while FMCG, Pharma, and Healthcare saw pressure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:55:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568d274342f77179f696b6_1767279980628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyderabad EV Hub Ignites! Olectra Greentech Unveils Massive Production Capacity – A Game Changer for Electric Mobility?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyderabad-EV-Hub-Ignites-Olectra-Greentech-Unveils-Massive-Production-Capacity-A-Game-Changer-for-Electric-Mobility/69568d3c4342f77179f69738</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyderabad-EV-Hub-Ignites-Olectra-Greentech-Unveils-Massive-Production-Capacity-A-Game-Changer-for-Electric-Mobility/69568d3c4342f77179f69738</guid><description>Olectra Greentech Limited has officially commenced commercial operations for Phase I of its new electric vehicle manufacturing facility in Hyderabad. The plant's initial phase brings an annual production capacity of 2,500 electric buses, representing half of the facility's total planned capacity. This significant expansion is expected to bolster the company's manufacturing capabilities and support its growing order book in the booming electric bus segment, reinforcing its commitment to sustainable public transport solutions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:55:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568d3c4342f77179f69737_1767280274383.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KPI Green Energy Bags Crucial Grid Nod for 32.40 MW Projects! What This Means for Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Bags-Crucial-Grid-Nod-for-3240-MW-Projects-What-This-Means-for-Investors/69568b564342f77179f68ebc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Bags-Crucial-Grid-Nod-for-3240-MW-Projects-What-This-Means-for-Investors/69568b564342f77179f68ebc</guid><description>KPI Green Energy announced it has received grid connection approval for 32.40 megawatts of solar and hybrid power projects. These projects are developed for clients under its Captive Power Plant (CPP) business segment. This energization approval is a regulatory green light from grid operators, signifying the final step before connection to the main electricity grid, paving the way for power generation and revenue realization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:49:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568b564342f77179f68ebb_1767279505531.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India's Production Climbs But Offtake Dips in December: What Investors Need to Know</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-Indias-Production-Climbs-But-Offtake-Dips-in-December-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/69568ac94342f77179f68bc2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-Indias-Production-Climbs-But-Offtake-Dips-in-December-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/69568ac94342f77179f68bc2</guid><description>Coal India reported a 4.6% year-on-year increase in production to 75.7 million tonnes (MT) in December. However, offtake fell by 5.2% to 64.9 MT during the same period. For the April-December period of FY26, cumulative production decreased by 2.6% to 529.2 MT, while offtake slipped by 2.2% to 544.7 MT compared to the previous fiscal year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:47:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568ac94342f77179f68bc1_1767279390818.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 2000 Notes Mystery Solved: RBI Reveals Jaw-Dropping 98.41% Returned!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rs-2000-Notes-Mystery-Solved-RBI-Reveals-Jaw-Dropping-9841percent-Returned/69568a774342f77179f689ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rs-2000-Notes-Mystery-Solved-RBI-Reveals-Jaw-Dropping-9841percent-Returned/69568a774342f77179f689ed</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India announced that a significant 98.41% of the withdrawn Rs 2000 banknotes have been returned. As of December 31, 2025, only ₹5,669 crore worth of these high-value notes remain outside circulation, down from ₹3.56 lakh crore when withdrawal began on May 19, 2023. The Rs 2000 banknotes continue to be legal tender.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:46:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568a774342f77179f689ec_1767279299967.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Honda Cars India Roars Back: December Sales Surge 3.6% Amidst Strong Demand!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Honda-Cars-India-Roars-Back-December-Sales-Surge-36percent-Amidst-Strong-Demand/69568a4d4342f77179f688f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Honda-Cars-India-Roars-Back-December-Sales-Surge-36percent-Amidst-Strong-Demand/69568a4d4342f77179f688f7</guid><description>Honda Cars India reported a 3.6% rise in domestic sales for December 2025, reaching 5,807 units compared to 5,603 in December 2024. While exports saw a decline to 2,352 units, the company experienced robust demand across its popular models like the Honda Amaze, City, and Elevate. Honda Cars India attributes this positive momentum to factors including the GST 2.0 implementation and anticipates unlocking new opportunities with multiple product launches planned for 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:46:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568a4d4342f77179f688f6_1767279250419.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking! India's Steel Prices Hit 5-Year Low in 2025 Amidst Global Trade Chaos: Tata Steel CEO Reveals Alarming Trends!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Shocking-Indias-Steel-Prices-Hit-5-Year-Low-in-2025-Amidst-Global-Trade-Chaos-Tata-Steel-CEO-Reveals-Alarming-Trends/69568a084342f77179f68774</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Shocking-Indias-Steel-Prices-Hit-5-Year-Low-in-2025-Amidst-Global-Trade-Chaos-Tata-Steel-CEO-Reveals-Alarming-Trends/69568a084342f77179f68774</guid><description>Tata Steel CEO T V Narendran revealed that Indian steel prices hit a five-year low in 2025, despite robust domestic demand. He cited global trade disruptions, protectionist policies, and a surge in Chinese steel exports as key challenges impacting international markets. While Tata Steel's European business faced pressure, its domestic operations remained stable. Narendran also touched upon the company's expansion plans and expressed optimism about India's strong economic growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:44:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568a084342f77179f68773_1767279190520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>