<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:55 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Indoco Remedies' EBITDA Surges 163% Amidst International Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indoco-Remedies-EBITDA-Surges-163percent-Amidst-International-Growth/6989d78eb81b2b81dcffba94</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indoco-Remedies-EBITDA-Surges-163percent-Amidst-International-Growth/6989d78eb81b2b81dcffba94</guid><description>Indoco Remedies reported robust Q3 FY26 results with consolidated EBITDA surging 162.5% YoY to INR 31.5 crore, boosting margins to 7.3%. This was powered by strong international formulation growth (+26.2%), API (+24%), and OTC businesses, offsetting flat domestic sales. However, INR 29 crore in one-off costs and INR 900 crore debt remain key watchpoints. Management projects over 20% growth in Europe and debt reduction to ~INR 775-800 crore by March 2027.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bluspring Q3 Revenue Up 10%, Navigates ₹29.8 Cr Labour Code Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bluspring-Q3-Revenue-Up-10percent-Navigates-298-Cr-Labour-Code-Costs/6989d712b81b2b81dcffb8dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bluspring-Q3-Revenue-Up-10percent-Navigates-298-Cr-Labour-Code-Costs/6989d712b81b2b81dcffb8dd</guid><description>Bluspring Enterprises reported a 10% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹844 crore in Q3 FY26, primarily driven by its Facility and Food Services segment. Despite a 12% EBITDA increase, an exceptional charge of ₹29.8 crore related to new Labour Codes impacted profitability, though adjusted PAT still rose 54% YoY. The Foundit platform saw a 27% revenue decline. The company aims to achieve 4% EBITDA margins in Q4 FY26.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GIC Re Posts Lower GWP But Boosts Profitability in Q3 FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-Posts-Lower-GWP-But-Boosts-Profitability-in-Q3-FY26/6989d6c1b81b2b81dcffb754</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-Posts-Lower-GWP-But-Boosts-Profitability-in-Q3-FY26/6989d6c1b81b2b81dcffb754</guid><description>General Insurance Corporation of India (GIC Re) has reported its Q3 FY2026 results for the nine-month period ending December 2025. While Gross Written Premium (GWP) stood at ₹32,976 Cr, a decrease compared to the full fiscal year FY23-24, the company showcased operational improvements. The combined ratio reduced to 106.9% and underwriting losses narrowed to ₹1,847 Cr. Profit After Tax (PAT) saw a slight dip to ₹6,138 Cr. The insurer highlighted a robust solvency ratio of 387% and a growing Net Worth. The outlook remains positive, focusing on leveraging its international brand, geographical diversification, and growth in specialized insurance lines.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra Lifespace Restructures Bengaluru Project, Forges JV with Mitsui Fudosan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mahindra-Lifespace-Restructures-Bengaluru-Project-Forges-JV-with-Mitsui-Fudosan/6989d699b81b2b81dcffb64d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mahindra-Lifespace-Restructures-Bengaluru-Project-Forges-JV-with-Mitsui-Fudosan/6989d699b81b2b81dcffb64d</guid><description>Mahindra Lifespace Developers (MLDL) approved a major restructuring for its Bengaluru residential project, 'Alembic Undertaking'. The undertaking will be slump-sold to its subsidiary, Mahindra Blossom Developers (MBLDL), for up to ₹100 crore. Subsequently, MLDL will form a joint venture with Japan's Mitsui Fudosan (Asia) in MBLDL, where Mitsui will hold 49%. The JV will raise ₹230.30 crore via a rights issue, with MLDL contributing ₹117.45 crore, enhancing project execution and operational flexibility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Artemis Medicare Plans Major Expansion, Seeks INR 700 Cr Funding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Artemis-Medicare-Plans-Major-Expansion-Seeks-INR-700-Cr-Funding/6989d65ab81b2b81dcffb518</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Artemis-Medicare-Plans-Major-Expansion-Seeks-INR-700-Cr-Funding/6989d65ab81b2b81dcffb518</guid><description>Artemis Medicare Services reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 17.2% YoY to INR 272 crores and PAT growing 7.9% to INR 22 crores. For the nine months, revenue reached INR 802 crores. The company unveiled ambitious expansion plans, aiming to triple bed capacity by 2029, including new hospitals in Raipur and South Delhi. To fund this growth, a INR 700 crore capital raise via QIP or preferential allotment is planned.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Linde India's Q3 PAT Surges 68% Amidst Looming SEBI Regulatory Storm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Linde-Indias-Q3-PAT-Surges-68percent-Amidst-Looming-SEBI-Regulatory-Storm/6989d623b81b2b81dcffb410</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Linde-Indias-Q3-PAT-Surges-68percent-Amidst-Looming-SEBI-Regulatory-Storm/6989d623b81b2b81dcffb410</guid><description>Linde India announced strong standalone Q3 FY25 results with revenue up 15.7% YoY to ₹7,010.34 million and PAT soaring 68.1% YoY to ₹1,915.90 million. A ₹900 million liability reversal boosted the nine-month standalone PAT growth to 41.1%. However, consolidated PAT growth was a more moderate 13.0% for Q3. The company also appointed Mr. Ajay Kumar Sah as Interim CFO. Critically, Linde India is embroiled in SEBI investigations concerning related party transactions, with appeals pending in the Supreme Court, creating significant uncertainty noted by auditors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Cotex Q3 Revenue Slumps 56%, PAT Growth Hides Data Anomalies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Gujarat-Cotex-Q3-Revenue-Slumps-56percent-PAT-Growth-Hides-Data-Anomalies/6989d5abb81b2b81dcffb249</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Gujarat-Cotex-Q3-Revenue-Slumps-56percent-PAT-Growth-Hides-Data-Anomalies/6989d5abb81b2b81dcffb249</guid><description>Gujarat Cotex Limited posted a 9.4% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹762.55 Cr in Q3 FY26. However, revenue plummeted 56.1% quarter-on-quarter from Q2 FY26. While Profit After Tax (PAT) rose 15.5% YoY to ₹36.52 Cr for the quarter, the identical PAT figures for Q3 and the nine-month period, coupled with auditor observations of PBT discrepancies, cast a shadow over data transparency and demand a closer look from investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lloyds Metals Surges Past ₹11,000 Cr Revenue, Eyes Copper Diversification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Lloyds-Metals-Surges-Past-11000-Cr-Revenue-Eyes-Copper-Diversification/6989d54ab81b2b81dcffb0eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Lloyds-Metals-Surges-Past-11000-Cr-Revenue-Eyes-Copper-Diversification/6989d54ab81b2b81dcffb0eb</guid><description>Lloyds Metals and Energy Limited has achieved a significant milestone, crossing INR 11,000 crores in consolidated revenue. The company reported robust standalone Q3 FY26 results with revenues up 129% YoY to INR 3,875 Cr and PAT up 128% YoY to INR 889 Cr, maintaining strong EBITDA margins around 34%. Key growth drivers include expansion in pellet and steel capacities, and a strategic diversification into copper mining in the Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC). A substantial INR 14,000 crore capex is planned over the next two years, funded by debt and internal accruals, pushing consolidated net debt towards INR 10,600 Cr by FY28. An MoU with Tata Steel signals potential collaborations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Richfield Financial Slashes Share Issue Size After BSE Observations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Richfield-Financial-Slashes-Share-Issue-Size-After-BSE-Observations/6989d532b81b2b81dcffb003</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Richfield-Financial-Slashes-Share-Issue-Size-After-BSE-Observations/6989d532b81b2b81dcffb003</guid><description>Richfield Financial Services Limited has revised its preferential equity share issue, cutting the size by ₹1.4 crore to ₹8.605 crore and reducing the number of shares from 40 lakh to 34.42 lakh. These changes follow observations from BSE Limited and aim for SEBI compliance. The number of proposed allottees has also decreased significantly from 139 to 112.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sterlite Tech Eyes ₹498 Cr Promoter Warrant Issue, Seeks EGM Nod</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sterlite-Tech-Eyes-498-Cr-Promoter-Warrant-Issue-Seeks-EGM-Nod/6989d50bb81b2b81dcffaeb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sterlite-Tech-Eyes-498-Cr-Promoter-Warrant-Issue-Seeks-EGM-Nod/6989d50bb81b2b81dcffaeb2</guid><description>Sterlite Technologies Limited (STL) has called an Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on March 4, 2026, seeking shareholder approval for a significant preferential issuance of up to 4,53,00,000 warrants to its promoter, Twin Star Overseas Limited. The issue, priced at ₹110 per warrant, aggregates ₹498.30 crore. The company plans to deploy approximately 75% of the funds towards repaying financial facilities and the remainder for general corporate purposes, including strategic initiatives and working capital. This move is expected to increase the promoter's shareholding from 44.44% to 49.16% post-conversion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Credo Brands Plunges 62% in Profit; Revenue Dips in Q3 FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Credo-Brands-Plunges-62percent-in-Profit-Revenue-Dips-in-Q3-FY26/6989d4e4b81b2b81dcffad82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Credo-Brands-Plunges-62percent-in-Profit-Revenue-Dips-in-Q3-FY26/6989d4e4b81b2b81dcffad82</guid><description>Credo Brands Marketing Limited reported a stark 61.7% year-on-year decline in Net Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹70.19 million for the third quarter of FY26. Revenue from operations slipped 6.03% to ₹1,461.34 million. Profitability margins compressed significantly, with PAT margin falling from 11.7% to 4.7%. For the nine-month period, PAT dropped 41.0% to ₹321.94 million on a 7.56% revenue decrease. An exceptional item of ₹13.97 million related to employee benefits due to new Labour Codes was recognized. The filing lacked balance sheet, cash flow data, and management outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Eicher Motors: Margin Squeeze Looms Despite Strong Volume Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Margin-Squeeze-Looms-Despite-Strong-Volume-Outlook/6989d4c3b81b2b81dcffacb1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Margin-Squeeze-Looms-Despite-Strong-Volume-Outlook/6989d4c3b81b2b81dcffacb1</guid><description>Eicher Motors Ltd. is poised to announce solid third-quarter financial results for FY26, propelled by substantial volume increases in both its Royal Enfield and commercial vehicle divisions. Consolidated profit is projected to climb 18% year-on-year, with revenue up 22%. However, a concerning trend emerges as standalone realisations and margins are expected to contract due to a reduced contribution from exports and a less favorable product mix, a factor investors will scrutinize closely against the backdrop of a buoyant auto sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Exchange Flags STT Hike Impact Amidst Govt Speculation Crackdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Exchange-Flags-STT-Hike-Impact-Amidst-Govt-Speculation-Crackdown/6989d400b81b2b81dcffaa49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Exchange-Flags-STT-Hike-Impact-Amidst-Govt-Speculation-Crackdown/6989d400b81b2b81dcffaa49</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange (NSE) has formally urged the government to reconsider the recent increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on equity futures. NSE officials highlighted concerns that the elevated tax burden, enacted to curb excessive speculation, could disproportionately affect investors using derivatives for essential hedging and long-term risk management. The exchange emphasized that such measures risk diminishing market liquidity and depth over time, potentially impacting the efficient functioning of capital markets. This pushback comes as the government defends the hike as a necessary step to deter retail investor losses in the high-risk derivatives segment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Sparks Data Sovereignty Shift: IBM Bets on Sovereign Core</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Sparks-Data-Sovereignty-Shift-IBM-Bets-on-Sovereign-Core/6989d3ceb81b2b81dcffa98e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Sparks-Data-Sovereignty-Shift-IBM-Bets-on-Sovereign-Core/6989d3ceb81b2b81dcffa98e</guid><description>Artificial intelligence is fundamentally altering data sovereignty, pushing beyond mere residency to require control over platforms, models, and outcomes. IBM is responding with its new AI-ready Sovereign Core software, aiming to embed sovereignty into enterprise operations. This move comes as regulatory pressures mount and the market for sovereign cloud solutions is projected for significant growth. IBM's strategy aims to offer a flexible, hybrid approach distinct from hyperscaler offerings, positioning itself in a critical emerging sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Cotex Q3 PAT Skyrockets 199%, Revenue Up 9.4% on Margin Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gujarat-Cotex-Q3-PAT-Skyrockets-199percent-Revenue-Up-94percent-on-Margin-Boost/6989d2f2b81b2b81dcffa735</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gujarat-Cotex-Q3-PAT-Skyrockets-199percent-Revenue-Up-94percent-on-Margin-Boost/6989d2f2b81b2b81dcffa735</guid><description>Gujarat Cotex Limited posted stellar Q3 FY26 results, with Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 198.94% year-on-year to ₹36.52 Cr. Revenue increased by 9.39% YoY to ₹762.55 Cr. For the nine-month period, revenue grew substantially by 52.66% YoY to ₹2946.71 Cr, and PAT rose 45.41% YoY to ₹45.95 Cr. The company also witnessed a significant improvement in PBT margins, expanding to 4.20% from 1.75% in the prior-year period.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fractal Analytics IPO Opens: AI Firm Seeks ₹2,834 Cr, GMP Signals Modest Gain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Opens-AI-Firm-Seeks-2834-Cr-GMP-Signals-Modest-Gain/6989d2c3b81b2b81dcffa5c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Opens-AI-Firm-Seeks-2834-Cr-GMP-Signals-Modest-Gain/6989d2c3b81b2b81dcffa5c6</guid><description>Fractal Analytics' ₹2,833.90 crore initial public offering (IPO) opened Monday, seeking investors for its AI and analytics solutions. Priced between ₹857 and ₹900 per share, the offering aims to tap into the expanding global Data, Analytics, and AI market. Grey market sentiment suggests a modest 1.9% gain on listing day, but the company's focus on AI transformation and GenAI is eyed for long-term growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apollo Micro Systems Hits Record Revenue on Defence Boom &amp; Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Apollo-Micro-Systems-Hits-Record-Revenue-on-Defence-Boom-and-Acquisition/6989d29db81b2b81dcffa4d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Apollo-Micro-Systems-Hits-Record-Revenue-on-Defence-Boom-and-Acquisition/6989d29db81b2b81dcffa4d6</guid><description>Apollo Micro Systems Limited announced its highest-ever quarterly and nine-month revenue for the period ending December 31, 2025. Consolidated revenue surged 70% YoY to ₹2522 million in Q3 FY26, while nine-month revenue grew 53% YoY to ₹6111 million. The company completed the acquisition of IDL Explosives Ltd and forecasts a 45-50% revenue CAGR over the next three years. Despite rising debt, key financial metrics and a credit rating upgrade reflect positive momentum in the defence sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Patanjali Foods: Court Halts Land Move Amidst Sector Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Patanjali-Foods-Court-Halts-Land-Move-Amidst-Sector-Headwinds/6989d264b81b2b81dcffa3fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Patanjali-Foods-Court-Halts-Land-Move-Amidst-Sector-Headwinds/6989d264b81b2b81dcffa3fa</guid><description>The Supreme Court mandated status quo on Patanjali Foods' Telangana oil palm factory land dispute, halting the state government's re-allocation. This legal intervention follows earlier High Court rulings against the company, highlighting potential execution and compliance challenges. The development occurs against a backdrop of global edible oil market volatility and India's significant import dependence, while Patanjali Foods seeks to diversify its revenue streams beyond its core edible oil business. The stock has seen a year-long decline, juxtaposing strong analyst buy ratings with cautious 'Sell' calls from other research firms focusing on valuation and operational risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AWL Agri Revenue Climbs 10%, Food Business Fuels Growth; Guidance Reaffirmed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/AWL-Agri-Revenue-Climbs-10percent-Food-Business-Fuels-Growth-Guidance-Reaffirmed/6989d199b81b2b81dcffa1b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/AWL-Agri-Revenue-Climbs-10percent-Food-Business-Fuels-Growth-Guidance-Reaffirmed/6989d199b81b2b81dcffa1b4</guid><description>AWL Agri Business Limited posted a 10% year-on-year revenue increase in Q3 FY'26, powered by a robust 13% growth in its Fortune oils and Food segment and a significant 32% surge from the Kohinoor brand. The company also reported healthy performance from its G.D. Foods acquisition. Management reaffirmed its EBITDA per ton guidance, signaling confidence in navigating market volatilities while investing for future margin expansion in the food business.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:22:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989d199b81b2b81dcffa1b3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fractal AI IPO Opens: Grey Market Premium Tumbles Amid Valuation Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-AI-IPO-Opens-Grey-Market-Premium-Tumbles-Amid-Valuation-Fears/6989d14db81b2b81dcffa03c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-AI-IPO-Opens-Grey-Market-Premium-Tumbles-Amid-Valuation-Fears/6989d14db81b2b81dcffa03c</guid><description>Fractal Analytics' AI-focused IPO opened for subscription on February 9, with an ambitious price band of ₹857-900 per share. However, the Grey Market Premium (GMP) has sharply declined from its peak, now standing at a modest 2%. Brokerage houses are divided, with some flagging rich valuations and potential client insourcing risks, while others recommend a 'Subscribe-Long Term' rating based on the company's AI sector presence and future growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:21:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989d14db81b2b81dcffa03b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ceinsys Tech Surges on Strong Q3 Results, Eyes US Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ceinsys-Tech-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Results-Eyes-US-Expansion/6989d120b81b2b81dcff9f26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ceinsys-Tech-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Results-Eyes-US-Expansion/6989d120b81b2b81dcff9f26</guid><description>Ceinsys Tech posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue jumping 52.05% YoY to ₹169.94 Cr and PAT surging 118.25% to ₹38.87 Cr. The company also greenlit a ₹40 Cr equity infusion into its US subsidiary, Technology Associates Inc., to fuel growth, and re-appointed Dr. Abhay Kimmatkar as MD for three years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Castrol India Hits Record Revenue; FY25 PAT Climbs Amid Q4 Profit Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Castrol-India-Hits-Record-Revenue-FY25-PAT-Climbs-Amid-Q4-Profit-Dip/6989d0ffb81b2b81dcff9e73</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Castrol-India-Hits-Record-Revenue-FY25-PAT-Climbs-Amid-Q4-Profit-Dip/6989d0ffb81b2b81dcff9e73</guid><description>Castrol India reported its highest-ever revenue for FY2025, surging 7% YoY to INR 5,722 crores, driven by robust volume growth and a strong industrial segment. While full-year PAT rose to INR 950 crores, Q4 PAT declined year-on-year due to one-time Labour Code changes. Management addressed margin concerns, attributing them to a strategic shift and investments, while maintaining a positive outlook on India's evolving mobility and industrial sectors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sky Gold &amp; Diamonds Surges 77% YoY on Robust Q3 Performance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sky-Gold-and-Diamonds-Surges-77percent-YoY-on-Robust-Q3-Performance/6989d0cbb81b2b81dcff9cdd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sky-Gold-and-Diamonds-Surges-77percent-YoY-on-Robust-Q3-Performance/6989d0cbb81b2b81dcff9cdd</guid><description>Sky Gold and Diamonds Limited posted a strong Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue jumping 77.12% YoY to ₹1,767.68 Cr and PAT soaring 120.38% YoY to ₹80.53 Cr. EBITDA also saw a significant 101.53% YoY rise to ₹129.83 Cr, with margins improving. Management highlighted execution-led growth, sustained demand, and international expansion, including a new Dubai office, as key drivers. The company also launched India's first 24-carat diamond jewellery collection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:19:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989d0cbb81b2b81dcff9cdc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emami Q3 Revenue Surges 11%, Profit Jumps 15% on Strong Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Emami-Q3-Revenue-Surges-11percent-Profit-Jumps-15percent-on-Strong-Demand/6989d0a2b81b2b81dcff9c1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Emami-Q3-Revenue-Surges-11percent-Profit-Jumps-15percent-on-Strong-Demand/6989d0a2b81b2b81dcff9c1c</guid><description>Emami Limited delivered a strong Q3 FY26, with consolidated net sales climbing 11% year-on-year to ₹1,152 crore, driven by robust domestic volume growth of 9%. Profit After Tax (PAT) surged 15% to ₹319 crore, supported by margin expansion. The company declared a 600% interim dividend, signalling confidence, and remains optimistic about future consumption momentum, with a renewed focus on rural markets and new age opportunities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dreamfolks Revenue Halved, Swings to Net Loss Amidst Acquisition Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Dreamfolks-Revenue-Halved-Swings-to-Net-Loss-Amidst-Acquisition-Drive/6989d082b81b2b81dcff9b44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Dreamfolks-Revenue-Halved-Swings-to-Net-Loss-Amidst-Acquisition-Drive/6989d082b81b2b81dcff9b44</guid><description>Dreamfolks Services Limited reported a dismal Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue down 84.4% YoY to ₹534.50 Cr and a net loss of ₹78.63 Cr, a stark reversal from profit. Nine-month performance also saw significant drops in revenue and profit. The company announced strategic acquisitions in UAE (ETT Solutions) and Ten 11 Hospitality LLP, but provided no forward guidance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:18:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989d082b81b2b81dcff9b43.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Genus Power Q3 Revenue Dips; Order Book Shines, NIPL Acquisition Eyed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Genus-Power-Q3-Revenue-Dips-Order-Book-Shines-NIPL-Acquisition-Eyed/6989cfc2b81b2b81dcff98b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Genus-Power-Q3-Revenue-Dips-Order-Book-Shines-NIPL-Acquisition-Eyed/6989cfc2b81b2b81dcff98b7</guid><description>Genus Power Infrastructures reported a mixed Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue down 2.32% YoY to ₹1,122.36 Cr and PAT down 4.57% to ₹136.45 Cr. However, nine-month consolidated PAT surged 27.54% to ₹397.14 Cr. The company boasts a robust ₹27,217 Cr order book, signaling strong future revenue visibility. Strategic expansion is underway with the acquisition of an additional 86.49% stake in Newlectric Innovation Private Limited. A demerger focused the business on its core metering operations. The Directorate of Enforcement conducted a search, with the company cooperating and expecting no material impact.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NTPC Commissions 14.43 MW Solar Power Capacity in Gujarat</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Commissions-1443-MW-Solar-Power-Capacity-in-Gujarat/6989cf93b81b2b81dcff97a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Commissions-1443-MW-Solar-Power-Capacity-in-Gujarat/6989cf93b81b2b81dcff97a1</guid><description>NTPC Green Energy Limited (NGEL) has announced the commercial operation of a 14.43 MW solar power capacity at its Khavda-I Solar PV Project in Gujarat. This commissioning, effective February 10, 2026, part of the CPSU scheme Phase-II Tranche-III, pushes the NTPC group's total installed capacity to 87,804 MW and NGEL's commercial capacity to 8,813.25 MW. The development reinforces NTPC's commitment to renewable energy expansion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:14:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989cf93b81b2b81dcff97a0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GSFC Posts Strong Q3 Profit Growth, Revenue Edges Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/GSFC-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Growth-Revenue-Edges-Up/6989cf44b81b2b81dcff963e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/GSFC-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Growth-Revenue-Edges-Up/6989cf44b81b2b81dcff963e</guid><description>Gujarat State Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals (GSFC) announced robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated net profit rising 18.2% YoY to ₹158.15 Cr on a 4.5% revenue increase. Standalone net profit saw a significant 31.5% jump. For the nine months, consolidated revenue grew 10.5% and net profit 19.5%. Fertilizer Products remain the primary revenue and profit driver. Notably, no future guidance was provided by the management.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FCS Software Turns Red: Standalone PBT Plunges 700% Despite Revenue Slip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/FCS-Software-Turns-Red-Standalone-PBT-Plunges-700percent-Despite-Revenue-Slip/6989cf1db81b2b81dcff954a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/FCS-Software-Turns-Red-Standalone-PBT-Plunges-700percent-Despite-Revenue-Slip/6989cf1db81b2b81dcff954a</guid><description>FCS Software Solutions reported a stark financial reversal for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. Standalone revenue dipped YoY to ₹778.07 Lakhs, while PBT collapsed to a loss of ₹(235.08) Lakhs from a profit of ₹66.38 Lakhs. The company posted a net loss of ₹240.52 Lakhs, a significant downturn from profit last year. On a consolidated basis, revenue surged 60.6% to ₹1,718.82 Lakhs, yet profitability also reversed into a net loss of ₹172.21 Lakhs from a profit of ₹125.78 Lakhs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:12:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989cf1db81b2b81dcff9549.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vascon Engineers: Order Book Surges, But PAT Dives Amid Real Estate Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vascon-Engineers-Order-Book-Surges-But-PAT-Dives-Amid-Real-Estate-Woes/6989cee6b81b2b81dcff93d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vascon-Engineers-Order-Book-Surges-But-PAT-Dives-Amid-Real-Estate-Woes/6989cee6b81b2b81dcff93d7</guid><description>Vascon Engineers' 9M FY26 results show a robust ₹2,825 Cr order book, offering strong revenue visibility. Consolidated EBITDA jumped 22.3% YoY to ₹70.73 Cr with margins improving to 10%. However, PAT plunged 53.5% YoY to ₹43.18 Cr due to a prior-year exceptional gain. Q3 FY26 revenue declined 15.4% YoY. The company aims to secure ₹1,500–2,000 Cr in new EPC orders for FY26.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Isgec Heavy Engineering Surges Q3 PAT 248% on Strong Orders, Approves ₹240Cr Capex</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Isgec-Heavy-Engineering-Surges-Q3-PAT-248percent-on-Strong-Orders-Approves-240Cr-Capex/6989cecab81b2b81dcff92f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Isgec-Heavy-Engineering-Surges-Q3-PAT-248percent-on-Strong-Orders-Approves-240Cr-Capex/6989cecab81b2b81dcff92f6</guid><description>Isgec Heavy Engineering Ltd. posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 247.99% year-on-year to ₹8,444 lakhs. Standalone PAT also grew 28.15% YoY. The company's Board approved a significant capital expenditure of approximately ₹240.6 crore for capacity expansion, including a new Machining Shop and expansion of the Machine Building Division. While Manufacturing and Industrial Projects segments showed growth, Sugar and Ethanol segments saw revenue declines. An exceptional item impacted standalone and consolidated results due to revised employee benefit provisions. The sale of a subsidiary, 'Bioeq Energy Holdings One', failed due to buyer default.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Genus Power Surges on Robust 9M Growth, Huge Order Book; ED Probe Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Genus-Power-Surges-on-Robust-9M-Growth-Huge-Order-Book-ED-Probe-Looms/6989cea6b81b2b81dcff91fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Genus-Power-Surges-on-Robust-9M-Growth-Huge-Order-Book-ED-Probe-Looms/6989cea6b81b2b81dcff91fb</guid><description>Genus Power Infrastructures reported a stellar nine-month performance ended December 31, 2025, with standalone revenue up 36.43% YoY and net profit soaring 42.30% to ₹424.27 Cr. The company boasts a significant executable order book of ₹27,217 Cr. Strategic moves include acquiring Newlectric Innovation Private Limited and demerging its investment division to focus on the core metering business. Despite a Directorate of Enforcement search, management remains confident of no material impact.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:10:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989cea6b81b2b81dcff91fa.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Neuland Labs Profit Halved as Sales Slump, Costs Sap Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Neuland-Labs-Profit-Halved-as-Sales-Slump-Costs-Sap-Margins/6989ce12b81b2b81dcff8fb5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Neuland-Labs-Profit-Halved-as-Sales-Slump-Costs-Sap-Margins/6989ce12b81b2b81dcff8fb5</guid><description>Neuland Laboratories Ltd. reported a stark 60% plunge in net profit for the third quarter, falling to ₹40.6 crore. Revenue slid 10.5% year-on-year to ₹439.7 crore, with EBITDA also declining and margins contracting significantly. The company approved capital expenditure for a new R&amp;D center in Hyderabad.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:07:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Navin Fluorine's Stellar Q3 Ignites Margin Debate Amidst Valuation Premium</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Navin-Fluorines-Stellar-Q3-Ignites-Margin-Debate-Amidst-Valuation-Premium/6989cdfeb81b2b81dcff8f36</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Navin-Fluorines-Stellar-Q3-Ignites-Margin-Debate-Amidst-Valuation-Premium/6989cdfeb81b2b81dcff8f36</guid><description>Navin Fluorine International Ltd. posted exceptional Q3 FY26 results, with net profit leaping to ₹185.4 crore and EBITDA more than doubling. Revenue climbed 47.2% to ₹892.3 crore, and EBITDA margins expanded significantly to 34.4%. However, an ₹18.84 crore provision for employee benefits due to new labor codes and a P/E ratio of ~74x invite scrutiny on margin sustainability and valuation amidst a mixed sector outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:07:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989cdfeb81b2b81dcff8f35.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Religare Broking Bets on New MD Amid High Valuation &amp; Profitability Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Broking-Bets-on-New-MD-Amid-High-Valuation-and-Profitability-Woes/6989cdc5b81b2b81dcff8e16</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Broking-Bets-on-New-MD-Amid-High-Valuation-and-Profitability-Woes/6989cdc5b81b2b81dcff8e16</guid><description>Religare Broking has appointed Vijay Kumar Goel as its new Managing Director, signaling an aggressive focus on scaling its core broking business and expanding wealth product distribution. Goel brings over three decades of experience from firms like Motilal Oswal and Aditya Birla Group. However, the appointment comes as Religare faces a significant valuation premium, with a P/E ratio of approximately 57-58, far exceeding the industry average, coupled with recent reports of net losses and low profitability metrics. The company must navigate intense competition from dominant digital players like Groww and Zerodha to justify its market standing and growth ambitions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:06:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GRSE Seals Naval Pact, Eyes Growth Amid Strong Earnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/GRSE-Seals-Naval-Pact-Eyes-Growth-Amid-Strong-Earnings/6989cd3ab81b2b81dcff8c83</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/GRSE-Seals-Naval-Pact-Eyes-Growth-Amid-Strong-Earnings/6989cd3ab81b2b81dcff8c83</guid><description>Kolkata-based Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers (GRSE) has formalized a strategic alliance with Hindustan Shipyard Ltd. (HSL) through a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to form a consortium for large-scale national shipbuilding programs. This collaboration coincides with GRSE's robust financial performance, showcasing a 73.9% year-on-year surge in net profit to ₹170.7 crore for the quarter ending December 2025, driven by strong order book execution. The partnership aims to bolster India's maritime infrastructure and technological self-reliance, aligning with a positive outlook for the Indian defense sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:04:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989cd3ab81b2b81dcff8c82_1770639413932.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axis Max Life Leads Insurers; Sector Momentum Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Axis-Max-Life-Leads-Insurers-Sector-Momentum-Shifts/6989cce5b81b2b81dcff8b4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Axis-Max-Life-Leads-Insurers-Sector-Momentum-Shifts/6989cce5b81b2b81dcff8b4f</guid><description>January life insurance data reveals Axis Max Life as the strongest performer, posting significant gains in new business premium and Annualised Premium Equivalent (APE). This contrasts with a notable slowdown for SBI Life and a contraction for HDFC Life, while ICICI Prudential Life and Canara HSBC Life showed moderate growth. The results indicate a dynamic shift in market leadership and competitive positioning within the Indian life insurance sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:02:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dharti Proteins Plans Massive Capital Cut, Promoters Lose All Shares</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Dharti-Proteins-Plans-Massive-Capital-Cut-Promoters-Lose-All-Shares/6989ccc2b81b2b81dcff8a51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Dharti-Proteins-Plans-Massive-Capital-Cut-Promoters-Lose-All-Shares/6989ccc2b81b2b81dcff8a51</guid><description>Dharti Proteins Limited (formerly Devika Proteins) will drastically cut its paid-up share capital as per an NCLT-approved Resolution Plan. The plan, scheduled for Board consideration on Feb 13, 2026, will see existing promoter holdings completely extinguished. New shares will be issued to a successful resolution applicant, public shareholders, and a financial creditor, reshaping the company's ownership structure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Conart Engineers Posts Massive 196% Profit Jump, Auditor Flags Labor Code Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Conart-Engineers-Posts-Massive-196percent-Profit-Jump-Auditor-Flags-Labor-Code-Issue/6989cc4bb81b2b81dcff88df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Conart-Engineers-Posts-Massive-196percent-Profit-Jump-Auditor-Flags-Labor-Code-Issue/6989cc4bb81b2b81dcff88df</guid><description>Conart Engineers Limited reported a stellar third quarter ended December 31, 2025, with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring by 195.80% year-on-year to ₹60.75 Lakh. Total income grew 10.28% YoY to ₹1,567.54 Lakh. For the nine months, PAT rose 83.36% YoY to ₹261.84 Lakh on a 34.54% revenue increase. However, the auditor's report noted a non-provision of retirement benefits as per the New Labour Code, to be addressed by March 31, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989cc4bb81b2b81dcff88de.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NFIL Q3 Results: Revenue Soars 47%, Profit Surges 122% on Margin Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/NFIL-Q3-Results-Revenue-Soars-47percent-Profit-Surges-122percent-on-Margin-Expansion/6989cbf3b81b2b81dcff8780</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/NFIL-Q3-Results-Revenue-Soars-47percent-Profit-Surges-122percent-on-Margin-Expansion/6989cbf3b81b2b81dcff8780</guid><description>Navin Fluorine International (NFIL) delivered a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue jumping 47% YoY to ₹892.4 Cr and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 122% YoY to ₹185.4 Cr. Operating EBITDA more than doubled, rising 109% YoY to ₹307.6 Cr, propelling EBITDA margins to a healthy 34.5% (up 1017 bps YoY). This robust performance was driven by broad-based growth across Specialty Chemicals (+60% YoY), HPP (+35% YoY), and CDMO (+61% YoY). The company is investing over ₹400 Cr in significant capex projects, including HFC capacity expansion and advanced materials, funded by internal accruals, signalling strong confidence in future growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>