<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:40:49 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Coal India's Gevra Mine Surges Amidst Global Coal Decline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-Indias-Gevra-Mine-Surges-Amidst-Global-Coal-Decline/699a9c5881427192210209b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-Indias-Gevra-Mine-Surges-Amidst-Global-Coal-Decline/699a9c5881427192210209b8</guid><description>Coal India's Gevra mine is poised to become the world's largest coal producer, targeting 63 million tonnes annually by FY2026-27, surpassing the US-based Black Thunder Mine. This expansion occurs as global coal trade faces a predicted two-year decline through 2026. Despite Gevra's growing output, Coal India reported a 16% dip in net profit for Q3 FY25 and maintains a 'Neutral' analyst consensus. The company is simultaneously pursuing diversification into solar, gasification, and critical minerals, alongside plans for an IPO of its subsidiary SECL.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:04:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a9c5881427192210209b7_1771740374382.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pernod Ricard India IPO Off Table Amid Global Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pernod-Ricard-India-IPO-Off-Table-Amid-Global-Slump/699a9c5781427192210209a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pernod-Ricard-India-IPO-Off-Table-Amid-Global-Slump/699a9c5781427192210209a1</guid><description>Pernod Ricard's India operations are a bright spot, delivering 4% net sales growth driven by premiumization trends, contributing 12-13% to global revenue. This contrasts sharply with a global sales decline of 5.9% organically in the first half of FY26, dragged by the Americas and China. Despite a deleveraging target to reduce its net debt-to-EBITDA ratio below 3x by FY2029, the company has ruled out an initial public offering of its Indian business, emphasizing its strategic importance as a growth engine.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:04:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a9c5781427192210209a0_1771740378022.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor: CEO Bullish, But High P/E Spurs Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-CEO-Bullish-But-High-PE-Spurs-Valuation-Scrutiny/699a9be181427192210208ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-CEO-Bullish-But-High-PE-Spurs-Valuation-Scrutiny/699a9be181427192210208ec</guid><description>TVS Motor CEO KN Radhakrishnan projects an optimistic long-term growth trajectory for the Indian two-wheeler sector, expecting an 8-9% CAGR fueled by favorable policies and enhanced personal mobility needs. While analysts maintain positive ratings and raise price targets, the company's significantly higher price-to-earnings multiple compared to peers like Hero MotoCorp and Bajaj Auto warrants cautious assessment of its premium valuation. Recent Q4 expectations of over 15% growth and continued momentum into FY27 are noted, but sustainability risks remain under scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:02:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a9be181427192210208eb_1771740301835.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Coal Faces Demand Paradox: Record Output Meets Uncertain Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Coal-Faces-Demand-Paradox-Record-Output-Meets-Uncertain-Future/699a9b698142719221020816</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Coal-Faces-Demand-Paradox-Record-Output-Meets-Uncertain-Future/699a9b698142719221020816</guid><description>India's coal sector is navigating conflicting signals. A strong recovery in power demand during December and January, driven by a harsh winter and economic uptick, offers a short-term reprieve after a period of demand slowdown. However, this comes after the industry hit a record one-billion-tonne production milestone, creating an environment of strategic uncertainty. Industry leaders will convene at the "Coalosseum" conference to address these complex dynamics, balancing immediate demand boosts against evolving global energy landscapes and the sector's substantial production capacity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:00:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a9b698142719221020815_1771740159034.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India GDP Cools; Capex Slump, Exports Drag Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Cools-Capex-Slump-Exports-Drag-Growth/699a9b6781427192210207ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Cools-Capex-Slump-Exports-Drag-Growth/699a9b6781427192210207ff</guid><description>India's economic growth is projected to ease to 7.2% year-on-year in Q3 FY2025-26, down from 8.2% in Q2, according to ICRA. This deceleration stems from a significant 23.4% contraction in government capital expenditure and slower expansion in services and agriculture. While the industrial sector shows resilience with an 8.3% growth projection, it's insufficient to offset broader slowdowns. Weak merchandise exports and moderating services exports also contribute to the headwinds, though robust domestic demand, buoyed by GST rationalization, is expected to maintain growth above the 7% mark.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:00:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a9b6781427192210207fe_1771740136785.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Bank Faces ₹50.38 Cr GST Demand On Appeal; Contests Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Bank-Faces-5038-Cr-GST-Demand-On-Appeal-Contests-Order/699a981f81427192210206e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Bank-Faces-5038-Cr-GST-Demand-On-Appeal-Contests-Order/699a981f81427192210206e6</guid><description>ICICI Bank has received an Order in Appeal from the Maharashtra GST Department, confirming a tax demand of ₹50.38 crore, plus penalty and interest. The bank, which had disclosed the original order previously, intends to contest this appellate decision through a further appeal, adding to ongoing tax-related litigation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:46:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a981f81427192210206e5_1771739302522.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sector Divide: Infra, Banks Gain as Tech, Telecom Value Erodes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sector-Divide-Infra-Banks-Gain-as-Tech-Telecom-Value-Erodes/699a96bf814271922102063f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sector-Divide-Infra-Banks-Gain-as-Tech-Telecom-Value-Erodes/699a96bf814271922102063f</guid><description>India's largest corporations displayed a stark performance split last week. Larsen &amp; Toubro and State Bank of India led valuation gains, adding significant market capitalisation. In contrast, IT bellwethers Infosys and Tata Consultancy Services, alongside telecom major Bharti Airtel, experienced substantial erosion in their market value, signaling distinct sector-specific pressures impacting large-cap equities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:40:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a96bf814271922102063e_1771738927251.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Navigates USFDA Scrutiny Amidst API Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Navigates-USFDA-Scrutiny-Amidst-API-Expansion/699a958d814271922102057b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Navigates-USFDA-Scrutiny-Amidst-API-Expansion/699a958d814271922102057b</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma reported Q3 FY26 revenue of ₹8,646 crore, a 8.4% year-on-year increase, with EBITDA margins holding at 20.5%. The company is significantly ramping up Penicillin-G production and expects its China plant to achieve EBITDA breakeven this quarter. However, recent USFDA observations at its Unit VII facility in Telangana, citing contamination and data integrity issues, have raised regulatory concerns, leading to a stock price correction. Despite these challenges, Aurobindo maintains its FY26 EBITDA margin targets of 20-21% and sees continued growth driven by complex generics and strong European market performance.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:35:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a958d814271922102057a_1771738637193.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UP Policy Fuels ₹5,500 Cr Brew Investment Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/UP-Policy-Fuels-5500-Cr-Brew-Investment-Surge/699a951381427192210204a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/UP-Policy-Fuels-5500-Cr-Brew-Investment-Surge/699a951381427192210204a0</guid><description>The Brewers' Association of India (BAI) projects a ₹5,500 crore investment in Uttar Pradesh's brewing sector over three years, spurred by the state's 2026-27 excise policy. This policy maintains beer taxes while increasing duties on spirits, aiming to encourage lower-alcohol consumption. Investments will span new breweries and ancillary facilities like aluminum can and glass production plants, boosting supply chain capabilities and creating local jobs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:33:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a9513814271922102049f_1771738561060.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OMC Power, Honda Forge EV Battery Repurposing Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/OMC-Power-Honda-Forge-EV-Battery-Repurposing-Deal/699a94d5814271922102043d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/OMC-Power-Honda-Forge-EV-Battery-Repurposing-Deal/699a94d5814271922102043d</guid><description>OMC Power is launching an initiative to repurpose used electric vehicle (EV) batteries in India through a strategic partnership with Honda Motor Co., Ltd. This venture leverages Honda's EV batteries, extending their lifecycle for stationary energy storage solutions, including UPS systems and hybrid solar installations. The collaboration addresses India's burgeoning demand for reliable energy storage and tackles the environmental challenge of EV battery waste, positioning OMC Power as an early mover in a rapidly expanding market.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:32:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a94d5814271922102043c_1771738459259.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor: Growth Fuels Premium Valuation, Peers Lag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Growth-Fuels-Premium-Valuation-Peers-Lag/699a94998142719221020404</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Growth-Fuels-Premium-Valuation-Peers-Lag/699a94998142719221020404</guid><description>The Indian two-wheeler industry is on track for a robust 7-9% growth in fiscal year 2027, driven by GST benefits, infrastructure development, and strong demand for personal mobility. TVS Motor Company, a key player, benefits from these trends, boasting strong revenue and profit growth. However, its current market valuation, reflected in a high Price-to-Earnings ratio, significantly outpaces competitors like Bajaj Auto and Hero MotoCorp, raising questions about sustainability despite positive industry tailwinds. Analyst sentiment is mixed, with a 'Moderate Buy' consensus but a wide dispersion in price targets, suggesting caution amidst high expectations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a94998142719221020403_1771738420542.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quadrant Televentures Extends EOI Deadline Amid Ongoing Insolvency Process</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quadrant-Televentures-Extends-EOI-Deadline-Amid-Ongoing-Insolvency-Process/699a8958814271922102018f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quadrant-Televentures-Extends-EOI-Deadline-Amid-Ongoing-Insolvency-Process/699a8958814271922102018f</guid><description>Quadrant Televentures Limited, currently under Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), has extended key deadlines for submitting Expression of Interest (EOI). The National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) initiated CIRP on September 2, 2025. The extended EOI deadline is now March 2, 2026, with subsequent steps in the resolution process also rescheduled. This procedural update signals ongoing efforts to find a resolution applicant for the financially distressed company.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:43:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a8958814271922102018e_1771735552787.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cyber Scammers Exploit Tax Refund Anxiety Amidst Rising Fraud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Cyber-Scammers-Exploit-Tax-Refund-Anxiety-Amidst-Rising-Fraud/699a7e96814271922101ff38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Cyber-Scammers-Exploit-Tax-Refund-Anxiety-Amidst-Rising-Fraud/699a7e96814271922101ff38</guid><description>Sophisticated scams are preying on taxpayer anxiety regarding income tax refunds. Fraudsters deploy fake messages and websites to steal sensitive information, leading to significant financial losses. Despite improved refund processing times by the Income Tax Department, the evolving tactics of cybercriminals necessitate heightened vigilance from citizens and continuous adaptation of government cybersecurity measures.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 03:57:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a7e96814271922101ff37_1771732757620.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Fraud: Rs 590 Cr Lost, Controls Scrutinized</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Rs-590-Cr-Lost-Controls-Scrutinized/699a778a814271922101fd95</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Rs-590-Cr-Lost-Controls-Scrutinized/699a778a814271922101fd95</guid><description>IDFC First Bank disclosed a significant internal breach involving unauthorized and fraudulent activities totaling Rs 590 crore, linked to Haryana government accounts at its Chandigarh branch. The incident, discovered starting February 18, 2026, has led to the suspension of four employees and the initiation of a forensic audit. This development casts a shadow over the bank's internal control mechanisms and operational integrity, prompting closer examination by investors and regulators.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a778a814271922101fd94_1771730950086.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Luxury Asset Correction: India's Growth Contrasts Global Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Luxury-Products/Luxury-Asset-Correction-Indias-Growth-Contrasts-Global-Slump/699a7712814271922101fd34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Luxury-Products/Luxury-Asset-Correction-Indias-Growth-Contrasts-Global-Slump/699a7712814271922101fd34</guid><description>The global luxury asset market, including prestige watches, rare whiskies, and fine wines, is experiencing a post-pandemic slowdown with prices falling 10-20% from peaks due to market normalization and reduced demand in key Western markets. Concurrently, India is witnessing significant growth in Swiss watch exports, rising over 35.5% in the first ten months of 2025, indicating a local expansion amidst a global correction. This divergence highlights a market bifurcation favoring assets with enduring cultural or technical value over those inflated by hype. Major luxury conglomerates like LVMH and Richemont reported revenue declines in 2025, reflecting the broader global trend, though both demonstrated resilience in profitability and cash flow. Swiss watch exports overall saw a 1.7% decrease in value for 2025, contrasting sharply with India's specific market surge.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 03:25:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a7712814271922101fd33_1771730891509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Drone Firms: Valuation vs. Reality Amidst Defence Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Drone-Firms-Valuation-vs-Reality-Amidst-Defence-Boom/699a6725814271922101f9b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Drone-Firms-Valuation-vs-Reality-Amidst-Defence-Boom/699a6725814271922101f9b2</guid><description>India's burgeoning drone sector sees Paras Defence and Space Technologies and Zen Technologies report strong Q3 FY26 results driven by defence orders. Paras Defence's revenue grew 24% and profit 21%, while Zen Technologies saw revenue up 16.8% and profit 38%. However, differing valuations, operational efficiencies, and mixed analyst outlooks create a complex investment narrative, especially as the broader defence sector faces valuation scrutiny post-Budget.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:17:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a6725814271922101f9b1_1771726841359.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Nuclear Boom: Investors bet on shaky giants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Nuclear-Boom-Investors-bet-on-shaky-giants/699a6721814271922101f99b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Nuclear-Boom-Investors-bet-on-shaky-giants/699a6721814271922101f99b</guid><description>India's SHANTI Act ends a 60-year state monopoly on atomic energy, paving the way for a projected ₹2 lakh crore industry aimed at achieving 100 GW by 2047. Prominent investors Mukul Agrawal and Ashish Kacholia are positioning themselves, backing companies from infrastructure giants like HCC to specialized component makers like Walchandnagar Industries, though many beneficiaries grapple with significant financial headwinds and valuation concerns.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a6721814271922101f99a_1771726832760.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Ethanol Glut: Policy Gap Fuels Farmer Distress</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Ethanol-Glut-Policy-Gap-Fuels-Farmer-Distress/699a4a13814271922101f48c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Ethanol-Glut-Policy-Gap-Fuels-Farmer-Distress/699a4a13814271922101f48c</guid><description>India's ethanol sector is crippled by a massive supply surplus, with installed capacity vastly exceeding demand for the E20 petrol blending mandate. This policy-driven imbalance strains the entire value chain, impacting farmers and leading to underutilization of distilleries. As the industry awaits clarity on higher blending targets, the complex technical challenges of integrating ethanol into diesel, India's dominant fuel, loom large. Companies like IOC and BPCL face pressure to absorb excess supply while navigating uncertain policy shifts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:13:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a4a13814271922101f48b_1771719387196.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>