<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:36:26 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Glycols Shareholders to Vote on Major Company Restructuring</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Glycols-Shareholders-to-Vote-on-Major-Company-Restructuring/69982876057e346edab3ea37</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Glycols-Shareholders-to-Vote-on-Major-Company-Restructuring/69982876057e346edab3ea37</guid><description>India Glycols Limited has called a crucial meeting for its equity shareholders, convened by the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), Allahabad Bench. Shareholders will vote on a significant Scheme of Arrangement involving the company and its subsidiaries, Ennature Biopharma Limited and IGL Spirits Limited. The meeting is scheduled for March 24, 2026, via video conference, with e-voting facilities available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:25:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69982876057e346edab3ea36_1771579666277.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Embassy Developments Hearing Adjourned Amidst Deepening Financial Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-Developments-Hearing-Adjourned-Amidst-Deepening-Financial-Crisis/69982875057e346edab3ea21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-Developments-Hearing-Adjourned-Amidst-Deepening-Financial-Crisis/69982875057e346edab3ea21</guid><description>Embassy Developments Limited's critical hearing at the National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) regarding insolvency proceedings has been postponed for the third time, now to February 27, 2026. The stay on the National Company Law Tribunal's (NCLT) order admitting Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) remains in effect, but the company faces significant financial distress with widening losses and a battered stock price.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:25:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69982875057e346edab3ea20.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Triton Valves Posts Strong Q3, Eyes Expansion with Bonus Share Plan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triton-Valves-Posts-Strong-Q3-Eyes-Expansion-with-Bonus-Share-Plan/6998286f057e346edab3ea02</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triton-Valves-Posts-Strong-Q3-Eyes-Expansion-with-Bonus-Share-Plan/6998286f057e346edab3ea02</guid><description>Triton Valves Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 25.57% year-on-year to ₹152.75 Cr. The company saw significant profit growth, with consolidated PAT rising 146.73% to ₹2.64 Cr. Key highlights include improved margins and a proposal for a 3-for-1 bonus share issue. The merger of TritonValves Climatech is expected to complete by March 2026, aiming to streamline operations and boost profitability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:25:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998286f057e346edab3ea01_1771579653292.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>N R Agarwal Secures Key Approvals For Massive New Dahej Plant</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/N-R-Agarwal-Secures-Key-Approvals-For-Massive-New-Dahej-Plant/69982838057e346edab3e991</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/N-R-Agarwal-Secures-Key-Approvals-For-Massive-New-Dahej-Plant/69982838057e346edab3e991</guid><description>N R Agarwal Industries Ltd has received vital approvals from Gujarat Industrial Development Corporation (GIDC) for water and effluent disposal at its new Unit VI Multilayer Board Plant in Dahej, Gujarat. This marks a significant step towards the ₹1,200 crore expansion project's infrastructure readiness. The approvals allow for 4,000 KLPD of water and 2,000 KLPD of effluent disposal, clearing a key hurdle for the large-scale facility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:24:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69982838057e346edab3e990_1771579545049.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's PMI surges, but export orders signal potential headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-PMI-surges-but-export-orders-signal-potential-headwinds/69982736057e346edab3e786</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-PMI-surges-but-export-orders-signal-potential-headwinds/69982736057e346edab3e786</guid><description>India's private sector activity accelerated to a composite PMI of 59.3 in February, marking a three-month high, driven primarily by strong manufacturing output. This uplift follows a significant reduction in U.S. tariffs and anticipates benefits from the India-EU trade deal. However, growth in manufacturing export orders has decelerated, while domestic services demand moderated, even as the trade deficit widened to $34.68 billion in January. Businesses remain optimistic, increasing hiring and output.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:19:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69982736057e346edab3e785_1771579360067.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sobhagya Mercantile to Raise ₹178 Cr for Road Projects via Warrants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sobhagya-Mercantile-to-Raise-178-Cr-for-Road-Projects-via-Warrants/69982712057e346edab3e76f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sobhagya-Mercantile-to-Raise-178-Cr-for-Road-Projects-via-Warrants/69982712057e346edab3e76f</guid><description>Sobhagya Mercantile Limited is set to raise approximately ₹178.71 Crores through a preferential issue of convertible warrants. The funds will primarily be invested in promoter group Special Purpose Vehicles (SPVs) undertaking Hybrid Annuity Model (HAM) road projects, with a smaller portion for general corporate purposes. This move signals a strategic pivot towards a diversified infrastructure enterprise focused on stable, long-term cash flows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:19:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69982712057e346edab3e76e_1771579309012.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Seals Trade Pacts: US Deal Operational in April, Exports Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Seals-Trade-Pacts-US-Deal-Operational-in-April-Exports-Surge/69982710057e346edab3e759</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Seals-Trade-Pacts-US-Deal-Operational-in-April-Exports-Surge/69982710057e346edab3e759</guid><description>India is poised to operationalize key trade agreements, with the interim pact with the United States expected to take effect in April 2026. This move, alongside imminent FTAs with the United Kingdom and Oman, signals a significant push for global market access. The US deal reduces reciprocal tariffs from 50% to 18%, unlocking the $30 trillion US market for Indian farmers, fishermen, and MSMEs. Concurrently, India joins the US-led Pax Silica initiative, focusing on securing technology supply chains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:19:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69982710057e346edab3e758_1771579303863.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Glycols Plans Demerger Amidst Legal Storms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Glycols-Plans-Demerger-Amidst-Legal-Storms/6998270d057e346edab3e73f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Glycols-Plans-Demerger-Amidst-Legal-Storms/6998270d057e346edab3e73f</guid><description>India Glycols Limited is moving forward with a significant corporate restructuring, planning to demerge its Bio Pharma undertaking into Ennature Bio Pharma Limited and its Spirits &amp; Biofuel undertaking into IGL Spirits Limited. This move, approved by the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), will see a meeting of unsecured creditors on March 24, 2026, to rubber-stamp the scheme. However, the company is also navigating a complex web of ongoing legal and tax proceedings, including civil disputes, tax appeals, and customs duty demands, which present considerable risks for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:19:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998270d057e346edab3e73e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Threat Meets India's Growth Engine: Disruption or Digital Leap?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Threat-Meets-Indias-Growth-Engine-Disruption-or-Digital-Leap/6998270c057e346edab3e729</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Threat-Meets-Indias-Growth-Engine-Disruption-or-Digital-Leap/6998270c057e346edab3e729</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) projects artificial intelligence could disrupt 40% of global jobs, with India's workforce facing a 26% exposure, particularly in entry-level roles. However, India's dynamic economy, bolstered by rapid digital infrastructure development and structural reforms, is poised for significant AI-driven GDP growth, potentially adding over $550 billion by 2035. The nation's proactive stance in AI talent acquisition and educational reform underscores a strategic effort to harness this technological wave, though challenges in skill readiness and inclusive implementation persist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:19:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998270c057e346edab3e728_1771579298484.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Biocon Biologics Eyes FY27 Growth Amid Biosimilar Race, GLP-1 Disruption</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biocon-Biologics-Eyes-FY27-Growth-Amid-Biosimilar-Race-GLP-1-Disruption/699823c6057e346edab3e5d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biocon-Biologics-Eyes-FY27-Growth-Amid-Biosimilar-Race-GLP-1-Disruption/699823c6057e346edab3e5d8</guid><description>Bengaluru-based Biocon Biologics anticipates a robust fiscal year 2027, fueled by upcoming launches of biosimilars Aspart, Aflibercept, and Denosumab, alongside continued insulin demand. Management forecasts Q3 margins within the 24-26% range, reiterating confidence in financial performance. However, the company navigates a complex market characterized by aggressive competitor activity, lengthy biosimilar market penetration timelines, and significant disruption from the burgeoning GLP-1 drug class, all while trading at a premium valuation. Its stock currently holds a market capitalization of approximately ₹61,951 crore, with a P/E ratio around 97.70x, indicating high investor expectations for future growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:05:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699823c6057e346edab3e5d7_1771578473632.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Defence Sector: Indigenous Push Fuels Growth Amidst Execution Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Defence-Sector-Indigenous-Push-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Execution-Scrutiny/699821e8057e346edab3e4db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Defence-Sector-Indigenous-Push-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Execution-Scrutiny/699821e8057e346edab3e4db</guid><description>India's defense sector is experiencing a surge driven by a ₹3.6 lakh crore procurement approval, heavily favoring indigenous manufacturing and HAL, BEL, and BDL. While HAL reports robust Q3 performance and a substantial order book, BEL and BDL trade at higher valuations. Despite a strong sector-wide rally fueled by government impetus and geopolitical undertones, concerns over execution timelines and the sustainability of high multiples loom large, particularly for BDL with its weaker growth metrics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:57:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699821e8057e346edab3e4da_1771577987580.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Banks Hit New Highs Amidst Earnings Boom, But Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Hit-New-Highs-Amidst-Earnings-Boom-But-Risks-Loom/69981d12057e346edab3e2da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Hit-New-Highs-Amidst-Earnings-Boom-But-Risks-Loom/69981d12057e346edab3e2da</guid><description>Public sector banks (PSUs) have reached an all-time high on the Nifty PSU Bank index, propelled by robust Q3FY26 net profits, a 17.5% year-on-year earnings growth surpassing private peers. Strong credit expansion, improved asset quality, and favorable regulatory shifts are key drivers. However, concerns are emerging regarding potential margin compression, intensifying deposit competition, and the sustainability of further valuations. Analysts caution that while the sector has re-rated significantly, future gains may be more selective, with private banks anticipated to show higher credit growth in the medium term.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:36:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69981d12057e346edab3e2d9_1771576722007.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Pact Finalized: Deal Set for April Launch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Finalized-Deal-Set-for-April-Launch/69981cc2057e346edab3e2c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Finalized-Deal-Set-for-April-Launch/69981cc2057e346edab3e2c2</guid><description>Officials from India and the United States will convene for a three-day meeting starting February 23 to finalize the legal text of their interim trade agreement. The pact, expected to be signed in March, aims to operationalize in April, introducing duty concessions on various goods. Notably, the US will reduce reciprocal tariffs on Indian products from 25% to 18%, while also eliminating punitive tariffs on Indian crude oil purchases.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:35:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69981cc2057e346edab3e2c1_1771576701686.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dee Development Engineers: $40M Order Fuels Rally Amid Premium Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dee-Development-Engineers-40M-Order-Fuels-Rally-Amid-Premium-Valuation/69981cb9057e346edab3e2a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dee-Development-Engineers-40M-Order-Fuels-Rally-Amid-Premium-Valuation/69981cb9057e346edab3e2a8</guid><description>Dee Development Engineers surged over 10% Friday following a $40 million order win for HRSG piping from a US-based power sector OEM. This significant contract follows a strong December 2025 quarter where the company posted a net profit turnaround and a 77% revenue jump. The stock's year-to-date gain of 9% significantly outpaces the Nifty 50's decline. Dee Development Engineers' order book now totals ₹1,319.91 crore, reflecting robust activity in its Piping segment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:35:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69981cb9057e346edab3e2a7_1771576722801.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Data-Driven Tax Probe Targets Restaurant Software</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Data-Driven-Tax-Probe-Targets-Restaurant-Software/69981be6057e346edab3e1d9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Data-Driven-Tax-Probe-Targets-Restaurant-Software/69981be6057e346edab3e1d9</guid><description>India's Income Tax Department is using advanced data analytics to expose a multi-crore tax evasion racket, primarily within the restaurant industry. Anomalies detected through inconsistencies in raw material purchases, delivery platform data, and GST filings have pinpointed software-enabled suppression mechanisms. While the 'biryani angle' is merely a spotlight, the investigation signals heightened regulatory scrutiny on financial transparency and technology's role in compliance across the sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:31:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69981be6057e346edab3e1d8_1771576469002.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NARCL Anchors BLA Power Debt Sale; Swiss Challenge Launched</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NARCL-Anchors-BLA-Power-Debt-Sale-Swiss-Challenge-Launched/69981ada057e346edab3e0dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NARCL-Anchors-BLA-Power-Debt-Sale-Swiss-Challenge-Launched/69981ada057e346edab3e0dc</guid><description>National Asset Reconstruction Company Ltd (NARCL) has lodged an anchor bid of ₹285 crore for BLA Power's ₹738.18 crore stressed debt, initiating a Swiss Challenge auction set for March 9. This bid, implying a 38.6% recovery rate, highlights ongoing efforts to resolve NPAs in India's power sector. Indian Bank leads the lender consortium, with BOB Capital Markets advising. The process reflects the complexities of distressed asset resolution amid evolving energy market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:27:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69981ada057e346edab3e0db.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Sovereignty Push Amidst Global Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Sovereignty-Push-Amidst-Global-Race/69981a6b057e346edab3e071</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Sovereignty-Push-Amidst-Global-Race/69981a6b057e346edab3e071</guid><description>Prime Minister Modi's high-level meeting with AI and deeptech startup leaders underscores India's intensified drive for AI sovereignty. The agenda focuses on leveraging domestic innovation to address local needs and build global capabilities, moving beyond a service-provider role. This strategic push aims to position India as a creator of foundational AI technology, attracting significant investment and talent, yet faces considerable hurdles in compute power, talent retention, and global competition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:25:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69981a6b057e346edab3e070_1771576094737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FPIs Flock to India, Shun IT Amid AI Disruption Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/FPIs-Flock-to-India-Shun-IT-Amid-AI-Disruption-Fears/699818ff057e346edab3df88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/FPIs-Flock-to-India-Shun-IT-Amid-AI-Disruption-Fears/699818ff057e346edab3df88</guid><description>Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) returned to Indian equities in the first half of February, injecting ₹19,675 crore. Inflows centered on capital goods (₹8,032 Cr), financial services (₹6,175 Cr), and oil &amp; gas (₹4,678 Cr), supported by robust economic growth forecasts and a new US-India trade deal. In stark contrast, the Information Technology (IT) sector faced aggressive selling, with FPIs divesting ₹10,956 crore, pushing the Nifty IT index down approximately 15% year-to-date amid escalating artificial intelligence (AI) disruption concerns. This marks a significant sectoral divergence within the Indian market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:19:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699818ff057e346edab3df87_1771575724037.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anchor Investors Back Clean Max IPO Amidst Market Chill</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Anchor-Investors-Back-Clean-Max-IPO-Amidst-Market-Chill/699815b3057e346edab3de48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Anchor-Investors-Back-Clean-Max-IPO-Amidst-Market-Chill/699815b3057e346edab3de48</guid><description>Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions Ltd. is preparing for its Initial Public Offering (IPO) with significant backing from sovereign wealth funds Temasek Holdings and Abu Dhabi Investment Authority (ADIA) acting as cornerstone investors. The company aims to raise approximately ₹31 billion ($341 million) at ₹1,053 per share. This move occurs within a subdued Indian IPO market in early 2026, marked by cautious investor sentiment and recent underperformance in renewable energy stocks. The participation of these anchor investors, alongside domestic entities like HDFC Asset Management Co. Ltd and SBI Life Insurance Co., signals strong conviction. However, the premium valuation faces scrutiny as the broader market navigates a period of cooling listing gains and increased selectivity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:05:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699815b3057e346edab3de47.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>8th Pay Commission: Fiscal Strain Looms Amid Modest Real Wage Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8th-Pay-Commission-Fiscal-Strain-Looms-Amid-Modest-Real-Wage-Gains/6998153a057e346edab3dd9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8th-Pay-Commission-Fiscal-Strain-Looms-Amid-Modest-Real-Wage-Gains/6998153a057e346edab3dd9e</guid><description>The 8th Pay Commission's progress signals potential salary increases for over a crore government employees and pensioners. However, robust fiscal deficit targets and rising inflation are expected to temper the real purchasing power gains, making it a 'muted stimulus' compared to past commissions. This situation presents a delicate balance between employee compensation and national fiscal health, with early estimates projecting an annual burden of over ₹3.7 lakh crore.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998153a057e346edab3dd9d_1771574710909.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Torrent Pharma: Growth Juggernaut Meets Regulatory Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Torrent-Pharma-Growth-Juggernaut-Meets-Regulatory-Headwinds/699814d3057e346edab3dcc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Torrent-Pharma-Growth-Juggernaut-Meets-Regulatory-Headwinds/699814d3057e346edab3dcc3</guid><description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals reported a robust Q3FY26 with 17.6% revenue growth, driven by strong domestic and Brazilian operations. The company also finalized its acquisition of a controlling stake in JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals, aiming for merger completion within months. Despite operational strengths and strategic expansion, Torrent's high P/E ratio and ongoing regulatory scrutiny over the JB merger present significant valuation and integration challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:01:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699814d3057e346edab3dcc2_1771574633480.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPFO UPI/ATM Withdrawals: Convenience Over Core Reforms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/EPFO-UPIATM-Withdrawals-Convenience-Over-Core-Reforms/699814c1057e346edab3dca7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/EPFO-UPIATM-Withdrawals-Convenience-Over-Core-Reforms/699814c1057e346edab3dca7</guid><description>The Employees' Provident Fund Organisation (EPFO) is piloting UPI and ATM withdrawal facilities, aiming for an April 2026 rollout to expedite fund access. While this promises near-instantaneous payouts for approved partial withdrawals, experts caution that the move does not resolve long-standing data discrepancies or eligibility hurdles, potentially creating a false sense of liquidity without fundamentally enhancing the retirement corpus. The integration faces significant technical challenges, particularly linking UPI IDs with Aadhaar-based authentication systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:01:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699814c1057e346edab3dca6_1771574637710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Olyv Secures ₹207 Cr Series C for Fintech Lending Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Olyv-Secures-207-Cr-Series-C-for-Fintech-Lending-Expansion/69981476057e346edab3dbdc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Olyv-Secures-207-Cr-Series-C-for-Fintech-Lending-Expansion/69981476057e346edab3dbdc</guid><description>Bengaluru-based Olyv has secured ₹207 crore in a Series C funding round, co-led by The Fundamentum Partnership – Fund II and SMBC Asia Rising Fund. This capital injection will fuel Olyv's expansion in digital financial services, particularly personal loans up to ₹5 lakh. The company leverages partnerships with RBI-registered lenders for a fully online process. Legal advisories from Khaitan &amp; Co and SAMVĀD: Partners facilitated the transaction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:59:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69981476057e346edab3dbdb_1771574493697.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Balances Oil, US Tech Push Amid Geopolitical Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Balances-Oil-US-Tech-Push-Amid-Geopolitical-Squeeze/69981461057e346edab3db9d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Balances-Oil-US-Tech-Push-Amid-Geopolitical-Squeeze/69981461057e346edab3db9d</guid><description>U.S. Ambassador Gor urged global oil buyers, including India, to cease Russian purchases, coinciding with swift progress on an interim trade deal. India has officially joined the U.S.-led Pax Silica initiative, signaling alignment on critical AI supply chains. While India's energy strategy prioritizes diversification and cost-efficiency, geopolitical pressures and trade dynamics present a complex balancing act. The global AI market is projected for substantial growth, with U.S. tech exports forming a core part of its strategy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:59:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69981461057e346edab3db9c_1771574520724.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auto Sector Inventory Fixes Fuel Demand Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Sector-Inventory-Fixes-Fuel-Demand-Surge/69981394057e346edab3da4e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Sector-Inventory-Fixes-Fuel-Demand-Surge/69981394057e346edab3da4e</guid><description>India's automotive sector experienced a strong start to 2026, with both two-wheeler (2W) and passenger vehicle (PV) segments posting significant year-on-year volume growth in January. This demand surge is underpinned by sustained consumer momentum, favorable GST adjustments, wedding season purchases, and new model introductions. Notably, dealer inventory levels have drastically reduced to 32-34 days from approximately 60 days in late 2025, indicating a marked improvement in operational efficiency and supply chain responsiveness, allowing the industry to better capitalize on sales opportunities. ICRA projects continued steady momentum for the remainder of FY2026, with wholesale volumes anticipated to grow 6-9% for 2W and 5-7% for PVs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:56:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69981394057e346edab3da4d_1771574385287.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Equity Debate: North-South Divide Impacts Tech Giants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Equity-Debate-North-South-Divide-Impacts-Tech-Giants/69981362057e346edab3d9fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Equity-Debate-North-South-Divide-Impacts-Tech-Giants/69981362057e346edab3d9fd</guid><description>The India AI Impact Summit 2026 spotlighted AI's potential to either widen or bridge global inequalities, driven by disparities in capital and compute infrastructure concentrated in the Global North. Panelists underscored that control and equitable benefit distribution are paramount. For major IT players like Salesforce and Tata Consultancy Services, this translates into navigating intense competition, investing in AI capabilities, and addressing structural challenges in data access and talent development to ensure inclusive growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:55:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69981362057e346edab3d9fc_1771574225307.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SpiceJet Market Share Climbs, But Stock Hits 52-Week Lows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Market-Share-Climbs-But-Stock-Hits-52-Week-Lows/6998135e057e346edab3d9e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Market-Share-Climbs-But-Stock-Hits-52-Week-Lows/6998135e057e346edab3d9e6</guid><description>SpiceJet significantly boosted its domestic market share to 4.3% by December 2025, driven by expanded capacity and fleet induction. This operational rebound, however, stands in stark contrast to its plummeting stock price, which hit a 52-week low around ₹16.68 in late February 2026. Despite adding capacity, the airline faces severe financial headwinds, including negative equity and a 'Strong Sell' analyst rating, suggesting a widening gap between operational gains and investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:55:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998135e057e346edab3d9e5_1771574240824.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Promoter Stake Buys Signal Concern Amid IndiQube's Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Promoter-Stake-Buys-Signal-Concern-Amid-IndiQubes-Losses/6998122e057e346edab3d909</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Promoter-Stake-Buys-Signal-Concern-Amid-IndiQubes-Losses/6998122e057e346edab3d909</guid><description>IndiQube Spaces Limited announced its promoter group may acquire shares via open market transactions. This move coincides with the company reporting strong revenue growth in Q3 FY26 to ₹395 crore, yet continued net losses, evidenced by a trailing twelve-month P/E ratio of -33.16. The company's market capitalization stands around ₹3,830 crore, with shares trading near their 52-week low. This action occurs against a backdrop of Indian startups experiencing founder ownership dilution post-IPO, raising questions about strategic motivations beyond simple confidence.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:50:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998122e057e346edab3d908_1771573938831.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US-India Trade Deal: Tariffs Ease, But Strategic Hurdles Remain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-India-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Ease-But-Strategic-Hurdles-Remain/69980f3f057e346edab3d6fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-India-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Ease-But-Strategic-Hurdles-Remain/69980f3f057e346edab3d6fb</guid><description>The United States has lowered tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, a move signaling a de-escalation in trade tensions. However, this reduction masks persistent strategic disagreements, particularly concerning India's oil imports from Russia and access to its agricultural and dairy sectors. While diplomatic engagement continues with upcoming visits and ongoing negotiations, the core challenges suggest a complex path forward for bilateral trade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:37:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69980f3f057e346edab3d6fa.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Climb as Geopolitics Trump Dollar Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Climb-as-Geopolitics-Trump-Dollar-Fears/69980edb057e346edab3d630</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Climb-as-Geopolitics-Trump-Dollar-Fears/69980edb057e346edab3d630</guid><description>Precious metals gold and silver futures advanced on Friday, extending recent gains driven by escalating geopolitical uncertainty and sustained safe-haven demand. Despite a firmer US dollar and a Federal Reserve signaling caution on interest rate cuts, prices found support from robust central bank buying and strong investor inflows into gold ETFs. Analysts maintain a constructive outlook, projecting continued strength through 2026, albeit with potential volatility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:35:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69980edb057e346edab3d62f_1771573326804.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Senco Gold Revenue Soars 50%, But Volume Declines Hint at Price Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Senco-Gold-Revenue-Soars-50percent-But-Volume-Declines-Hint-at-Price-Pressures/69980ecc057e346edab3d5cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Senco-Gold-Revenue-Soars-50percent-But-Volume-Declines-Hint-at-Price-Pressures/69980ecc057e346edab3d5cb</guid><description>Senco Gold achieved a striking 50% year-on-year revenue growth to INR 30.7 billion, significantly outperforming peers. This surge was propelled by strong festive demand and a higher contribution from old-gold exchanges, which now form 43% of sales. However, this top-line success masks a 3% sequential and 10% year-to-date decline in gold volumes, a direct consequence of soaring gold prices. Analysts remain divided, with a 'Buy' consensus target of ₹503.17 contrasting with a 'Neutral' view and a lower target of ₹375 from Motilal Oswal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:35:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69980ecc057e346edab3d5ca.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Siemens Energy India: Valuation Strain Amidst Energy Transition Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Siemens-Energy-India-Valuation-Strain-Amidst-Energy-Transition-Boom/69980eb7057e346edab3d57b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Siemens-Energy-India-Valuation-Strain-Amidst-Energy-Transition-Boom/69980eb7057e346edab3d57b</guid><description>Siemens Energy India reported robust Q3 FY26 results, exceeding expectations with a 35% year-over-year profit increase driven by expanded EBITDA margins. The company is undertaking significant capacity expansion for power transformers, signaling confidence in sustained domestic and global demand from energy transition initiatives. However, the stock currently trades at a stretched P/E ratio of over 80x TTM earnings, significantly higher than peers, following a substantial recent rally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:35:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69980eb7057e346edab3d57a_1771573099531.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alkem Labs' Medtech Gamble: Margin Hope vs. Raw Material Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alkem-Labs-Medtech-Gamble-Margin-Hope-vs-Raw-Material-Risk/69980e62057e346edab3d407</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alkem-Labs-Medtech-Gamble-Margin-Hope-vs-Raw-Material-Risk/69980e62057e346edab3d407</guid><description>Alkem Laboratories is strategically acquiring a majority stake in Occlutech, a European Medtech firm specializing in cardiovascular devices, aiming to inject growth and higher margins into its portfolio. This move comes as Alkem's core pharmaceutical business grapples with increased raw material costs due to India's Minimum Import Price (MIP) policy and lingering weakness in certain domestic therapies. While Occlutech shows a path to profitability, its historical losses and integration challenges present a significant risk, juxtaposed against analysts' divided outlook and revised earnings estimates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:33:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69980e62057e346edab3d406_1771573002695.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Inox Wind: Bullish Broker Clash With Weaker Analyst Forecasts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Inox-Wind-Bullish-Broker-Clash-With-Weaker-Analyst-Forecasts/69980e5a057e346edab3d3eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Inox-Wind-Bullish-Broker-Clash-With-Weaker-Analyst-Forecasts/69980e5a057e346edab3d3eb</guid><description>Inox Wind reported a Q3 FY26 revenue of ₹1,238 crore, missing analyst expectations, primarily due to weaker project execution (252 MW vs. target). Despite this, EBITDA margins remained robust at approximately 25%. Motilal Oswal reiterated a 'Buy' rating with a ₹150 target price, citing order book stability. However, recent analyst revisions have led to lowered earnings per share and revenue forecasts, creating a divergence between bullish broker calls and a more cautious analyst consensus.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:33:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69980e5a057e346edab3d3ea.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mrs Bector Foods: High Valuation Casts Shadow on Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Mrs-Bector-Foods-High-Valuation-Casts-Shadow-on-Growth/69980e4e057e346edab3d3d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Mrs-Bector-Foods-High-Valuation-Casts-Shadow-on-Growth/69980e4e057e346edab3d3d2</guid><description>Mrs. Bector Foods reported an 8.4% year-over-year revenue increase for 3QFY26, driven by its bakery segment. Despite a brokerage upgrade to 'BUY' with a target price of ₹270, the company's current valuation appears stretched. Analysts project growth, but the stock trades at a significant premium to industry peers, highlighting execution risks in a maturing packaged foods market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:33:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69980e4e057e346edab3d3d1_1771572975344.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IGL's Strong Q3 Driven by Cost Efficiency, Valuation Cues</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IGLs-Strong-Q3-Driven-by-Cost-Efficiency-Valuation-Cues/69980e46057e346edab3d3bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IGLs-Strong-Q3-Driven-by-Cost-Efficiency-Valuation-Cues/69980e46057e346edab3d3bb</guid><description>Indraprastha Gas Limited (IGL) delivered a strong third quarter for fiscal year 2026, exceeding earnings expectations. Adjusted EBITDA climbed 38% year-over-year to ₹5 billion, driven by a 5% beat in EBITDA per scm, aided by a ₹0.9/scm decrease in gas costs. Volumes rose 3% YoY to 9.42 mmscmd. Motilal Oswal reiterated a 'Buy' rating, citing an attractive valuation at 15x Dec'27E P/E plus JV value, forecasting a 3% dividend yield and 9% EPS growth through FY28.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:33:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69980e46057e346edab3d3ba_1771572927093.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Petronet LNG: Earnings Beat Meets Tariff Cut Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Petronet-LNG-Earnings-Beat-Meets-Tariff-Cut-Concerns/69980e42057e346edab3d382</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Petronet-LNG-Earnings-Beat-Meets-Tariff-Cut-Concerns/69980e42057e346edab3d382</guid><description>Petronet LNG (PLNG) reported a robust third quarter for fiscal year 2026, with EBITDA exceeding projections by 7% and total volumes surpassing estimates. Despite these positive operational metrics, the company's outlook is tempered by assumptions of a significant tariff cut in FY28 and a conservatively valued petrochemical project. This creates a valuation paradox as the market digests near-term operational strength against future regulatory and project execution uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:33:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69980e42057e346edab3d381_1771572940954.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold for Indian families: Stability vs. Growth debate intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Gold-for-Indian-families-Stability-vs-Growth-debate-intensifies/69980e3f057e346edab3d36a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Gold-for-Indian-families-Stability-vs-Growth-debate-intensifies/69980e3f057e346edab3d36a</guid><description>Indian families often prioritize gold for its emotional security, but this cultural inclination can hinder wealth creation for long-term goals like education or weddings. While gold offers stability during crises and has a strong emotional value, it lacks income generation and can be outperformed by growth assets. Financial experts increasingly advocate for gold's role as a diversifier (5-15% of a portfolio) rather than a primary growth engine, emphasizing equities for substantial wealth accumulation. Digital gold options like Sovereign Gold Bonds (SGBs) and ETFs mitigate the high costs associated with physical gold, making them more financially viable alternatives for investment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:33:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69980e3f057e346edab3d369_1771572908820.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Legal Lag: Economic Drag from Judicial Overload</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Legal-Lag-Economic-Drag-from-Judicial-Overload/69980dfa057e346edab3d2c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Legal-Lag-Economic-Drag-from-Judicial-Overload/69980dfa057e346edab3d2c4</guid><description>India's judicial system grapples with a staggering backlog exceeding 50 million pending cases, exacerbated by legislative enactments that fail to account for their enforcement capacity. This systemic issue, rooted in the absence of comprehensive Judicial Impact Assessments (JIA), translates into prolonged dispute resolution times, estimated at over four years for commercial matters. The resulting legal inefficiency acts as a substantial economic drag, deterring foreign investment and undermining contract enforcement, despite repeated judicial calls for reform.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:32:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69980dfa057e346edab3d2c3_1771572859498.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FTA Push: AI Crucial for Navigating Trade Complexity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-FTA-Push-AI-Crucial-for-Navigating-Trade-Complexity/69980dbb057e346edab3d22b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-FTA-Push-AI-Crucial-for-Navigating-Trade-Complexity/69980dbb057e346edab3d22b</guid><description>India's strategic acceleration into global markets via new Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) with the EU and GCC presents significant operational challenges. While agreements unlock market access for sectors like textiles and engineering, businesses must overcome complex origin rules and documentation demands. AI-powered trade automation platforms, such as EY Global Trade Automation (EY GTA), are emerging as essential tools to transform compliance from a burden into a strategic driver, enabling proactive risk management and maximizing the benefits of these expanded trade corridors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 07:31:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69980dbb057e346edab3d22a_1771572795294.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>