<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:44:09 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Shree Ram Twistex IPO Soars; Bets on Green Energy for Cost Control</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Shree-Ram-Twistex-IPO-Soars-Bets-on-Green-Energy-for-Cost-Control/699fa2d2cd95b9dc08f95975</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Shree-Ram-Twistex-IPO-Soars-Bets-on-Green-Energy-for-Cost-Control/699fa2d2cd95b9dc08f95975</guid><description>Shree Ram Twistex Ltd's initial public offering concluded with a staggering 43.66 times subscription, attracting immense investor interest. The ₹110.24 crore issue, set to list on March 2, 2026, will channel proceeds into establishing 6.1 MW solar and 4.2 MW wind power plants for captive use, alongside loan repayment and working capital enhancement, marking a significant operational and financial restructuring.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fa2d2cd95b9dc08f95974_1772069713527.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sedemac IPO: Promoter Exit, Valuation Scrutiny Amid EV Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Sedemac-IPO-Promoter-Exit-Valuation-Scrutiny-Amid-EV-Shift/699fa1e3cd95b9dc08f95864</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Sedemac-IPO-Promoter-Exit-Valuation-Scrutiny-Amid-EV-Shift/699fa1e3cd95b9dc08f95864</guid><description>Sedemac Mechatronics is launching a Rs 1,087-crore IPO on March 4, structured entirely as an Offer for Sale (OFS). This means existing promoters and investors are selling stakes, with no new capital infusion for company growth. The IPO, priced at Rs 1,287-1,352 per share, values the manufacturer of control-intensive products for automotive and gensets at Rs 5,970.6 crore. Investors face scrutiny over the valuation given the company's reliance on internal combustion engine (ICE) technology amidst the sector's pivot to electrification. Sedemac leads the Indian genset controller market with over 75 percent share and also produces integrated starter generator ECUs for two- and three-wheelers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:29:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fa1e3cd95b9dc08f95863_1772069531920.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Big Bull Conviction: Damani &amp; Jhunjhunwala Estate Bet On Deep Value</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Big-Bull-Conviction-Damani-and-Jhunjhunwala-Estate-Bet-On-Deep-Value/699f9a51cd95b9dc08f9534c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Big-Bull-Conviction-Damani-and-Jhunjhunwala-Estate-Bet-On-Deep-Value/699f9a51cd95b9dc08f9534c</guid><description>While Indian markets reach new highs, Radhakishan Damani and the estate of the late Rakesh Jhunjhunwala demonstrate unwavering conviction in Concord Biotech and BF Utilities, stocks that have fallen over 55% and 80% from their peaks, respectively. This resilience highlights a strategic focus on intrinsic value and capital efficiency, defying typical market sentiment. Concord Biotech showcases robust operational metrics despite margin pressures, while BF Utilities navigates significant leverage and contingent liabilities. Their continued holdings signal a deep-seated belief in the long-term prospects of these entities, far beyond short-term stock fluctuations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:56:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f9a51cd95b9dc08f9534b_1772067892015.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ford India's GBS: From Cost Hub to AI &amp; EV Innovation Engine</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ford-Indias-GBS-From-Cost-Hub-to-AI-and-EV-Innovation-Engine/699f9a26cd95b9dc08f95309</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ford-Indias-GBS-From-Cost-Hub-to-AI-and-EV-Innovation-Engine/699f9a26cd95b9dc08f95309</guid><description>Ford's Global Business Solutions (GBS) center in India has dramatically transformed from a traditional back-office to its largest global hub outside the U.S., spearheading AI, vehicle software, and enterprise-wide transformation. With over 12,000 employees, the Chennai facility is pivotal to Ford's electrification strategy, developing core intelligence for new EV platforms. Senior leaders trained in India are now ascending to top roles in U.S. headquarters, underscoring the center's growing strategic importance and talent export capabilities. This evolution positions Ford India as a key innovation engine, directly influencing the automaker's future product development and technological advancement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:56:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f9a26cd95b9dc08f95308_1772067637671.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia's AI Revenue Surge Faces Evolving Competitive Threats</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidias-AI-Revenue-Surge-Faces-Evolving-Competitive-Threats/699f9a16cd95b9dc08f952bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidias-AI-Revenue-Surge-Faces-Evolving-Competitive-Threats/699f9a16cd95b9dc08f952bd</guid><description>Nvidia anticipates first-quarter revenue around $78 billion, fueled by sustained AI demand from major tech firms. Despite this strong outlook, the company faces intensifying competition from AMD and custom silicon efforts by cloud providers. Concerns also persist around the uncertain trajectory of China sales due to export controls and potential pressure on its historically high profit margins. While analysts remain largely optimistic, the market is increasingly scrutinizing the sustainability of Nvidia's dominance and its premium valuation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:55:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f9a16cd95b9dc08f952bc_1772067697675.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Retail Arena: Regional Chains Mimic Trent, But Can They Scale?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Retail-Arena-Regional-Chains-Mimic-Trent-But-Can-They-Scale/699f99f2cd95b9dc08f95286</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Retail-Arena-Regional-Chains-Mimic-Trent-But-Can-They-Scale/699f99f2cd95b9dc08f95286</guid><description>India's consumption shift to Tier-2 and Tier-3 cities is fueling growth for regional retailers like Cantabil Retail India and Sai Silks (Kalamandir). These companies are mirroring Trent's successful value-fashion model, expanding store networks and improving margins. Cantabil reported strong Q3 FY26 results with 19% revenue growth, while Sai Silks navigated a revenue dip but showed nine-month growth. However, the critical question remains whether these agile regional players can achieve the immense scale and market dominance of national giants like Trent, given their financial structures and competitive pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:55:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f99f2cd95b9dc08f95285_1772067657684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AgriStack: Digital Backbone for Rural Economic Revolution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-AgriStack-Digital-Backbone-for-Rural-Economic-Revolution/699f99eecd95b9dc08f9526f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-AgriStack-Digital-Backbone-for-Rural-Economic-Revolution/699f99eecd95b9dc08f9526f</guid><description>India's AgriStack initiative is constructing a comprehensive Digital Public Infrastructure (DPI) for agriculture, moving beyond farmer services to fundamentally restructure the rural economy. This initiative aims to enhance productivity, streamline access to credit and subsidies, and foster a data-driven ecosystem. It's projected to unlock significant economic value and attract substantial private sector investment, though challenges in data governance and farmer adoption persist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:55:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f99eecd95b9dc08f9526e_1772067710650.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's EV Battery Boom: Profit Plunge for Key Chemical Suppliers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Indias-EV-Battery-Boom-Profit-Plunge-for-Key-Chemical-Suppliers/699f99e9cd95b9dc08f95258</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Indias-EV-Battery-Boom-Profit-Plunge-for-Key-Chemical-Suppliers/699f99e9cd95b9dc08f95258</guid><description>India's push into electric mobility and battery production is creating a multi-billion dollar opportunity, with demand for lithium-ion batteries set to surge. Specialty chemical companies like PCBL, Neogen Chemicals, and Balaji Amines are positioning themselves to capitalize on this shift by developing critical battery components. However, recent financial results reveal a stark contrast: declining net profits and contracting margins across the board, despite strategic advancements and market tailwinds. This divergence signals potential execution challenges and questions the sustainability of current valuations for these key players.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:55:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f99e9cd95b9dc08f95257_1772067536150.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Water Stocks: Execution is King Amidst Sector Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Water-Stocks-Execution-is-King-Amidst-Sector-Boom/699f99e8cd95b9dc08f95241</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Water-Stocks-Execution-is-King-Amidst-Sector-Boom/699f99e8cd95b9dc08f95241</guid><description>India's urban water sector is transitioning from project announcements to tangible execution, with robust demand fueled by government initiatives and water scarcity. However, the critical factor for investors is not just order inflows, but a company's ability to convert these into steady revenues and profits through disciplined execution and working capital management. This challenging phase is creating a divergence in stock performance, rewarding those that demonstrate superior operational conversion over thematic plays.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:55:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f99e8cd95b9dc08f95240_1772067485483.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Stake Sale: Unlocking Value Amidst Disinvestment Delays</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Stake-Sale-Unlocking-Value-Amidst-Disinvestment-Delays/699f9990cd95b9dc08f9516b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Stake-Sale-Unlocking-Value-Amidst-Disinvestment-Delays/699f9990cd95b9dc08f9516b</guid><description>Despite a slow disinvestment program, State Bank of India (SBI) offers a substantial opportunity for stake reduction. With projected profits exceeding ₹75,000 crore for FY26, a 5% stake sale could yield upwards of ₹55,000 crore, bolstering fiscal space. This move would also enhance market liquidity and corporate governance, even as the broader government disinvestment program grapples with consistent target misses. Current market conditions are deemed favourable, with a buoyant primary market and robust investor appetite for quality assets, making SBI an attractive candidate for unlocking value.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:53:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f9990cd95b9dc08f9516a_1772067318032.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Smart Factories: Beyond Tech, Towards Discipline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Smart-Factories-Beyond-Tech-Towards-Discipline/699f998ccd95b9dc08f95154</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Smart-Factories-Beyond-Tech-Towards-Discipline/699f998ccd95b9dc08f95154</guid><description>India's manufacturing sector is rapidly adopting AI and smart factory technologies, moving beyond traditional perceptions of shop-floor work. While this digital transformation promises enhanced productivity and global competitiveness, the core catalyst for sustained growth lies in cultivating robust organizational discipline, fostering systems thinking among leadership, and crucially, addressing the significant capital, digital, and skill constraints faced by Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs). Policy initiatives like PLI schemes are driving investment, yet the target of increasing manufacturing's GDP share to 25% will depend on integrating these technological advancements with fundamental operational excellence and deep managerial depth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:53:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f998ccd95b9dc08f95153_1772067422990.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Solar Duty: India Exports Face 126% Tax, Stocks Tumble</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/US-Solar-Duty-India-Exports-Face-126percent-Tax-Stocks-Tumble/699f941fcd95b9dc08f94efc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/US-Solar-Duty-India-Exports-Face-126percent-Tax-Stocks-Tumble/699f941fcd95b9dc08f94efc</guid><description>The U.S. Department of Commerce levied a preliminary countervailing duty of 125.87% on Indian solar cells and modules, citing government subsidies. This move has triggered sharp declines in the shares of major Indian solar manufacturers like Waaree Energies, Premier Energies, and Vikram Solar, as it threatens to significantly limit exports to the crucial U.S. market. Companies that had already begun diversifying supply chains and reducing shipments are now better positioned to navigate the ensuing market volatility.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:30:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f941fcd95b9dc08f94efb_1772065938636.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Premium Pivot Squeezes Chinese Smartphone Brands</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Premium-Pivot-Squeezes-Chinese-Smartphone-Brands/699f935ccd95b9dc08f94e5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Premium-Pivot-Squeezes-Chinese-Smartphone-Brands/699f935ccd95b9dc08f94e5f</guid><description>Chinese electronics firms in India logged their first revenue contraction in FY25, down 4.5%, as consumer preference shifted decisively to premium smartphones. While Apple and Samsung capitalized on this trend, major Chinese players like Xiaomi, Oppo, and Realme faced shrinking entry-to-mid-level markets. Rising component costs, particularly memory chips, coupled with a depreciating rupee, are expected to further pressure Chinese brands, driving up device prices and dampening demand in their traditional strongholds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:27:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f935ccd95b9dc08f94e5e_1772065958290.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Slaps 126% Tariff on Indian Solar After Adani Probe Dodge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/US-Slaps-126percent-Tariff-on-Indian-Solar-After-Adani-Probe-Dodge/699f91b6cd95b9dc08f94d55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/US-Slaps-126percent-Tariff-on-Indian-Solar-After-Adani-Probe-Dodge/699f91b6cd95b9dc08f94d55</guid><description>The U.S. Department of Commerce imposed a preliminary 126% tariff on Indian solar products, citing Adani Group companies' failure to cooperate with a subsidy investigation and triggering the 'Adverse Facts Available' penalty. This action follows a significant nine-fold increase in Indian solar exports to the U.S. to $792.6 million in 2024. The punitive duties threaten to cripple Indian solar exports, potentially flooding the domestic market with excess modules and intensifying price competition amid already substantial manufacturing overcapacity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:20:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f91b6cd95b9dc08f94d54_1772065520768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gushwork Secures $9M Seed for AI Search Lead Gen</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Gushwork-Secures-9M-Seed-for-AI-Search-Lead-Gen/699f90dacd95b9dc08f94ca1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Gushwork-Secures-9M-Seed-for-AI-Search-Lead-Gen/699f90dacd95b9dc08f94ca1</guid><description>Gushwork has closed a $9 million seed funding round, valuing the startup at $33 million post-money. The company leverages AI agents to help businesses capture customers from emerging AI search platforms, generating significant inbound leads. With $1.5 million in annualized recurring revenue and rapid month-over-month growth, Gushwork is positioned to capitalize on the disruptive shift in online discovery, driven by tools like ChatGPT and Google's AI Overviews.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:16:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f90dacd95b9dc08f94ca0_1772065045051.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>XTGlobal Secures USD 796,900 TxDOT AI Work Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/XTGlobal-Secures-USD-796900-TxDOT-AI-Work-Order/699f8ee4cd95b9dc08f94bb8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/XTGlobal-Secures-USD-796900-TxDOT-AI-Work-Order/699f8ee4cd95b9dc08f94bb8</guid><description>XTGlobal Infotech's US subsidiary has clinched a USD 796,900 work order from the Texas Department of Transportation (TxDOT) for AI Enablement in Engineering Services. The six-month contract, running from March to September 2026, marks an expansion into the US public sector and highlights the company's focus on AI-driven solutions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:08:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f8ee4cd95b9dc08f94bb7_1772064609614.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>