<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 18:35:21 +0000</pubDate><item><title>IRB InvIT Fund Wins ₹273 Cr Award, Boosts Growth Amidst Profit Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRB-InvIT-Fund-Wins-273-Cr-Award-Boosts-Growth-Amidst-Profit-Plunge/69a1df9ffa7d0695d1af9a9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRB-InvIT-Fund-Wins-273-Cr-Award-Boosts-Growth-Amidst-Profit-Plunge/69a1df9ffa7d0695d1af9a9b</guid><description>IRB InvIT Fund's Kaithal Tollway Ltd secured a unanimous arbitral award of ₹273.54 crore, plus interest, and a 136.77-day concession extension from NHAI for construction delays. This financial boost supports IRB Infrastructure Developers' ambitious plan to grow its asset base to ₹1.40 lakh crore. However, this comes as IRB Infra reported a 96.5% year-on-year drop in net profit for Q3 FY26 to ₹210.79 crore, despite a 600 basis point expansion in operating margins. The company's high leverage remains a key concern for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 18:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1df9ffa7d0695d1af9a9a_1772216543358.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo's JOLCO Deal: Tax Shields Fuel Cheaper Jet Financing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-JOLCO-Deal-Tax-Shields-Fuel-Cheaper-Jet-Financing/69a1d8a9fa7d0695d1af9713</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-JOLCO-Deal-Tax-Shields-Fuel-Cheaper-Jet-Financing/69a1d8a9fa7d0695d1af9713</guid><description>IndiGo has secured a significant financing advantage by becoming the first Indian airline to utilize Japanese JOLCO (Japanese Operating Lease with Call Option) for two Airbus A320 family aircraft. This transaction, facilitated through GIFT City, leverages Japanese investors' preference for tax shields to achieve lower lease rates than traditional debt. The deal is underpinned by India's recent alignment with the Cape Town Convention, which significantly de-risks aircraft repossession and boosts investor confidence in the Indian aviation sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:47:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1d8a9fa7d0695d1af9712_1772214742780.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys, HCL Tech Pivot to AI as Market Weighs Disruption Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-HCL-Tech-Pivot-to-AI-as-Market-Weighs-Disruption-Risks/69a1d835fa7d0695d1af9664</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-HCL-Tech-Pivot-to-AI-as-Market-Weighs-Disruption-Risks/69a1d835fa7d0695d1af9664</guid><description>Infosys and HCL Tech are aggressively pursuing AI strategies, exemplified by Infosys Topaz and partnerships with AI leaders, aiming to capture a substantial share of the burgeoning AI services market. Despite revised growth guidance and recent financial performance showing modest improvements, investor sentiment remains cautious. The market grapples with AI's potential to disrupt traditional IT service models, creating valuation pressures and highlighting execution risks for Indian IT giants as they compete with global players like Accenture.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1d835fa7d0695d1af9663_1772214465283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gabriel India Completes Jinos JV; Expands into Fasteners Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Gabriel-India-Completes-Jinos-JV-Expands-into-Fasteners-Business/69a1d425fa7d0695d1af8c75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Gabriel-India-Completes-Jinos-JV-Expands-into-Fasteners-Business/69a1d425fa7d0695d1af8c75</guid><description>Gabriel India Limited has successfully completed its joint venture with South Korea's Jinos Co., Ltd., making Jinhap Gabriel Auto India Private Limited (JGAIPL) a subsidiary. Effective February 27, 2026, Gabriel India holds a 51% stake in JGAIPL, which will focus on manufacturing automotive and industrial fasteners. This move marks Gabriel India's strategic entry into the fasteners segment, leveraging Jinos' expertise to cater to OEMs and the industrial sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:28:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1d425fa7d0695d1af8c74_1772213539877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto Rebounds Stalled: Macro Fears Hit Bitcoin, Tech Stocks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Crypto-Rebounds-Stalled-Macro-Fears-Hit-Bitcoin-Tech-Stocks/69a1d376fa7d0695d1af883b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Crypto-Rebounds-Stalled-Macro-Fears-Hit-Bitcoin-Tech-Stocks/69a1d376fa7d0695d1af883b</guid><description>Bitcoin tumbled below $66,000 Friday, erasing earlier gains as escalating macroeconomic risks prompted an investor flight from risk assets. The downturn extended to crypto-related equities, including MicroStrategy and Coinbase, as well as miners increasingly tied to AI infrastructure. Major equity indexes also declined, driven by a hotter-than-expected Producer Price Index and persistent credit market stress, which are diminishing hopes for Federal Reserve rate cuts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:25:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1d376fa7d0695d1af883a_1772214182829.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gabriel India JV with SK On advances; 51% equity allotted, new date set</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gabriel-India-JV-with-SK-On-advances-51percent-equity-allotted-new-date-set/69a1d190fa7d0695d1af75c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gabriel-India-JV-with-SK-On-advances-51percent-equity-allotted-new-date-set/69a1d190fa7d0695d1af75c2</guid><description>Gabriel India announced it has met the initial conditions for its joint venture with SK Enmove Co., Ltd. Equity shares have been issued to SK On Co., Ltd. (51%) and Gabriel India (49%) in the JV company, with a new First Tranche Long Stop Date of February 27, 2026. This marks significant progress in the company's strategic move into the EV battery components sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1d190fa7d0695d1af75c1_1772214523009.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India's FY27: Trust Gamble Amid Fleet Surge and Geopolitical Crosswinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-Indias-FY27-Trust-Gamble-Amid-Fleet-Surge-and-Geopolitical-Crosswinds/69a1cdd5fa7d0695d1af0304</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-Indias-FY27-Trust-Gamble-Amid-Fleet-Surge-and-Geopolitical-Crosswinds/69a1cdd5fa7d0695d1af0304</guid><description>Air India aims to accelerate growth and capture premium market share in FY27, designated as a 'conversion year.' This strategy relies on a substantially upgraded fleet and expanded global partnerships with Singapore Airlines and Lufthansa Group. However, rebuilding customer confidence following FY26 operational disruptions and a tragic incident remains paramount. The airline must also navigate persistent geopolitical tensions impacting international routes and fierce competition, all while integrating its diverse fleet and operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:01:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1cdd5fa7d0695d1af0303_1772212333339.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ethereum Pivots L1 Scaling: Gas Fees Reworked for Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Ethereum-Pivots-L1-Scaling-Gas-Fees-Reworked-for-Future/69a1cd08fa7d0695d1aef54e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Ethereum-Pivots-L1-Scaling-Gas-Fees-Reworked-for-Future/69a1cd08fa7d0695d1aef54e</guid><description>Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin has outlined a strategic pivot towards enhancing the base layer's scalability, moving beyond a singular reliance on Layer 2 solutions. The proposal introduces a significant recalibration of transaction fees, differentiating costs between computation and long-term data storage. This aims to bolster network throughput and efficiency, while mitigating the risk of escalating node operating expenses and ensuring sustained decentralization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:57:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1cd08fa7d0695d1aef54d_1772212869285.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Expands HRA Metro List, Bolstering Old Tax Regime Choice</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Expands-HRA-Metro-List-Bolstering-Old-Tax-Regime-Choice/69a1cc8ffa7d0695d1aeecc5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Expands-HRA-Metro-List-Bolstering-Old-Tax-Regime-Choice/69a1cc8ffa7d0695d1aeecc5</guid><description>The Income Tax Department's proposed draft rules are set to boost the old tax regime's appeal by expanding the definition of 'metro cities' for House Rent Allowance (HRA) exemption. Hyderabad, Pune, Ahmedabad, and Bengaluru are now slated for the higher 50% HRA ceiling, previously exclusive to Mumbai, Delhi, Kolkata, and Chennai. This change offers tangible tax savings for salaried individuals renting in these urban hubs. Concurrently, the regulations introduce stricter disclosure requirements for HRA claims, including specifying the relationship with the landlord, aiming to enhance transparency and curb tax evasion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:55:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1cc8ffa7d0695d1aeecc4_1772212720557.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Thermax Acquires 51% Stake in Exactspace for ₹30.48 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Thermax-Acquires-51percent-Stake-in-Exactspace-for-3048-Cr/69a1c920fa7d0695d1ae1a7e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Thermax-Acquires-51percent-Stake-in-Exactspace-for-3048-Cr/69a1c920fa7d0695d1ae1a7e</guid><description>Thermax Limited is acquiring an additional 35.83% stake in Exactspace Technologies Private Limited for ₹30.48 crore, taking its total ownership to 51% and making Exactspace a subsidiary. This move aims to bolster Thermax's end-to-end asset support and service offerings with Exactspace's AI-based predictive maintenance and analytics solutions, signalling a push into digitally enhanced industrial services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:41:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c920fa7d0695d1ae1a7d_1772211513110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABB India Shareholders Approve Robotics Business Sale to Subsidiary</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-India-Shareholders-Approve-Robotics-Business-Sale-to-Subsidiary/69a1c8affa7d0695d1adfb6c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-India-Shareholders-Approve-Robotics-Business-Sale-to-Subsidiary/69a1c8affa7d0695d1adfb6c</guid><description>ABB India Limited shareholders have given a strong go-ahead for the sale of its Robotics Business to its subsidiary, ABB Robotics India Private Limited, through a postal ballot. The resolution passed with an overwhelming 94% of votes in favour, endorsing the ₹1,568.2 crore slump sale. This strategic move aligns ABB India with ABB Group's global divestment plans for its robotics sector, aiming to streamline operations and sharpen focus on core businesses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:39:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c8affa7d0695d1adfb6b_1772214382449.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rain Industries Q4 FY25 Profit Turns Around to ₹51 Cr; Revenue Surges 17%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Rain-Industries-Q4-FY25-Profit-Turns-Around-to-51-Cr-Revenue-Surges-17percent/69a1c7edfa7d0695d1adc950</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Rain-Industries-Q4-FY25-Profit-Turns-Around-to-51-Cr-Revenue-Surges-17percent/69a1c7edfa7d0695d1adc950</guid><description>Rain Industries reported a strong Q4 FY2025, marking a significant turnaround with a net profit of ₹510 million against a loss last year. Revenue from operations grew 17% year-on-year to ₹43.01 billion, driven by resilient performance in its carbon segment and growth in cement. The company's full-year results also showed a substantial recovery, with consolidated adjusted EBITDA up 52% to ₹22.75 billion, underscoring a successful operational rebound.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:35:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c7edfa7d0695d1adc94f_1772211951115.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Barclays' Blockchain Push: Chasing Peers Amid Tech Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Barclays-Blockchain-Push-Chasing-Peers-Amid-Tech-Race/69a1c6ccfa7d0695d1ad8d4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Barclays-Blockchain-Push-Chasing-Peers-Amid-Tech-Race/69a1c6ccfa7d0695d1ad8d4c</guid><description>Barclays is investigating the development of a proprietary blockchain platform for payments and other core banking functions. This strategic move places the London-based financial giant in direct competition with established players like JPMorgan Chase and HSBC, who are already integrating decentralized ledger technology into their services. The initiative aims to enhance transparency, efficiency, and settlement speed by reducing intermediaries, potentially incorporating stablecoins and tokenization. Barclays' exploration reflects a broader industry trend as financial institutions seek to modernize through advanced digital solutions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:31:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c6ccfa7d0695d1ad8d4b_1772214141708.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NTPC Pays Rs 2,666 Cr Dividend Amidst Energy Transition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Pays-Rs-2666-Cr-Dividend-Amidst-Energy-Transition/69a1c5e1fa7d0695d1ad6adb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Pays-Rs-2666-Cr-Dividend-Amidst-Energy-Transition/69a1c5e1fa7d0695d1ad6adb</guid><description>NTPC Ltd. has paid its second interim dividend for FY26, amounting to Rs 2,666.58 crore. This marks the 33rd consecutive year of dividend payouts, highlighting the state-owned power giant's sustained profitability. The company operates over 87 GW of installed capacity with significant expansion plans underway, crucial for meeting India's escalating energy demand.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:27:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c5e1fa7d0695d1ad6ada_1772210815027.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Triton Valves Eyes ₹550 Cr+ Sales in FY26, Proposes 3:1 Bonus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triton-Valves-Eyes-550-Cr-Sales-in-FY26-Proposes-31-Bonus/69a1c5dbfa7d0695d1ad6289</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triton-Valves-Eyes-550-Cr-Sales-in-FY26-Proposes-31-Bonus/69a1c5dbfa7d0695d1ad6289</guid><description>Triton Valves projects FY26 sales to exceed ₹550 crore, driven by strong YoY growth and a focus on high-margin EV components and TPMS. The company plans a 3:1 bonus share issue and is undertaking a strategic merger of its climate control vertical. Key risks include current losses in climate control and competitive pressure from Chinese dumping.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:27:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c5dbfa7d0695d1ad6288_1772213310409.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Altius InvIT 9M FY26 Revenue Surges 34% to ₹181Bn; EBITDA Jumps 37%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Altius-InvIT-9M-FY26-Revenue-Surges-34percent-to-181Bn-EBITDA-Jumps-37percent/69a1c5d7fa7d0695d1ad6261</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Altius-InvIT-9M-FY26-Revenue-Surges-34percent-to-181Bn-EBITDA-Jumps-37percent/69a1c5d7fa7d0695d1ad6261</guid><description>Altius InvIT, India's largest independent telecom infrastructure platform, has reported a strong performance for the first nine months of FY26. Revenue climbed 34% year-on-year to INR 181 billion, while EBITDA surged 37% to INR 74 billion. The company continues its robust growth trajectory, supported by India's increasing data consumption and 5G rollout, while maintaining a commitment to distributions to unitholders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:27:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c5d7fa7d0695d1ad6260_1772214208696.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's REIT Lending Boost: Cautious Liberalization with Strong Safeguards</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBIs-REIT-Lending-Boost-Cautious-Liberalization-with-Strong-Safeguards/69a1c5b6fa7d0695d1ad590f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBIs-REIT-Lending-Boost-Cautious-Liberalization-with-Strong-Safeguards/69a1c5b6fa7d0695d1ad590f</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has introduced draft norms permitting banks to lend directly to listed Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs), aiming to reduce capital costs and facilitate expansion. This liberalization, expected to be effective by July 2026, is balanced by robust safeguards including a 49% exposure cap, amortised repayment schedules, and restrictions on financing land acquisition. The move seeks to foster a more mature Indian REIT market, currently a small fraction of the global industry, by prioritizing stability and transparency amidst real estate's inherent cyclicality. Major REITs like Embassy Office Parks REIT and Mindspace Business Parks REIT are positioned to potentially benefit, provided they meet the new eligibility criteria.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:26:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c5b6fa7d0695d1ad590e_1772210383445.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-EU FTA: Rules Over Tariffs Sparking New Market Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-EU-FTA-Rules-Over-Tariffs-Sparking-New-Market-Risks/69a1c525fa7d0695d1ad4537</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-EU-FTA-Rules-Over-Tariffs-Sparking-New-Market-Risks/69a1c525fa7d0695d1ad4537</guid><description>The India-EU Free Trade Agreement (FTA) marks a strategic pivot, prioritizing deep regulatory alignment over mere tariff reductions. Key areas like digital trade, intellectual property (IP), and sustainability commitments, including the EU's Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (CBAM), introduce significant compliance hurdles and potential competitive shifts for Indian industries. While praised for opening markets, the focus on rules-based integration presents a complex new terrain for businesses, with analysts noting potential challenges alongside expected trade growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:24:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c525fa7d0695d1ad4536_1772211087174.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New India Assurance ₹672 Cr Tax Demand Deleted by NFAC.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/New-India-Assurance-672-Cr-Tax-Demand-Deleted-by-NFAC/69a1c470fa7d0695d1acf9a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/New-India-Assurance-672-Cr-Tax-Demand-Deleted-by-NFAC/69a1c470fa7d0695d1acf9a9</guid><description>The New India Assurance Company Ltd. has received a significant boost with the National Faceless Appeal Centre (NFAC), Delhi, deleting a tax demand of ₹672.36 crore for Assessment Year 2022-23. This favourable order removes a substantial financial liability, strengthening the company's financial standing and reducing a key overhang. The insurer plans to focus on continued growth in its core business operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:21:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c470fa7d0695d1acf9a8_1772210055273.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Angst Rocks Indian IT: Stocks Tumble, Valuations Tested</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Angst-Rocks-Indian-IT-Stocks-Tumble-Valuations-Tested/69a1c229fa7d0695d1acbc23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Angst-Rocks-Indian-IT-Stocks-Tumble-Valuations-Tested/69a1c229fa7d0695d1acbc23</guid><description>Veteran investors acknowledge AI anxiety but see opportunity in Indian IT's strategic adaptation. Despite India's strong AI adoption and governance efforts, the Nifty IT index has seen a significant downturn, trading near yearly lows with a "Strong Sell" technical signal. Global AI leaders' valuations far exceed Indian IT firms, highlighting competitive pressures and the need for companies to embrace AI or face obsolescence, while investors caution against blind capital deployment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:11:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c229fa7d0695d1acbc22_1772208988879.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Norway Fund Exits AGEL on Vague Allegations; Indian Funds Pile In</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Norway-Fund-Exits-AGEL-on-Vague-Allegations-Indian-Funds-Pile-In/69a1c13bfa7d0695d1abfbf6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Norway-Fund-Exits-AGEL-on-Vague-Allegations-Indian-Funds-Pile-In/69a1c13bfa7d0695d1abfbf6</guid><description>Norway's $1.2 trillion sovereign wealth fund divested Adani Green Energy Ltd. (AGEL) citing "gross corruption or other serious financial crime," without specific elaboration. This decision starkly contrasts with robust accumulation of AGEL shares by Indian mutual funds since 2025, totaling over $500 million, amidst India's expanding renewable energy market. The Norwegian fund's own significant fossil fuel investments and AGEL's stretched valuation metrics add layers of complexity to the divestment narrative.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:07:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c13bfa7d0695d1abfbf5_1772208756797.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India FDI Surges: Strength Amidst Shifting Global Flows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-FDI-Surges-Strength-Amidst-Shifting-Global-Flows/69a1c03cfa7d0695d1abfac2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-FDI-Surges-Strength-Amidst-Shifting-Global-Flows/69a1c03cfa7d0695d1abfac2</guid><description>Foreign direct investment into India demonstrated robust growth, with equity inflows reaching $47.87 billion in April-December 2025-26, an 18% increase year-on-year. This surge, propelled by significant capital from Singapore and a near doubling of US investment, highlights India's appeal amid global economic flux. However, a 23% quarter-on-quarter dip in equity inflows and concentrated investment in specific states and sectors warrant a closer examination of sustainability and potential imbalances.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:03:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1c03cfa7d0695d1abfac1_1772208463423.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IMFA Acquires Tata Plant: Dominance Boost Amid Market Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IMFA-Acquires-Tata-Plant-Dominance-Boost-Amid-Market-Headwinds/69a1bffcfa7d0695d1abfa7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IMFA-Acquires-Tata-Plant-Dominance-Boost-Amid-Market-Headwinds/69a1bffcfa7d0695d1abfa7a</guid><description>Indian Metals &amp; Ferro Alloys (IMFA) has successfully acquired Tata Steel's ferrochrome plant in Odisha for ₹707.26 crore, funded entirely by internal accruals. Completed on February 27, 2026, this strategic move significantly expands IMFA's production capacity to over 0.5 million tonnes, solidifying its position as India's largest ferrochrome producer. The acquisition leverages synergies with captive mines and addresses growing domestic demand, though sector-specific pressures persist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:02:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1bffcfa7d0695d1abfa79_1772208448799.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta declared preferred bidder for Odisha bauxite block</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Vedanta-declared-preferred-bidder-for-Odisha-bauxite-block/69a1bf52fa7d0695d1abf985</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Vedanta-declared-preferred-bidder-for-Odisha-bauxite-block/69a1bf52fa7d0695d1abf985</guid><description>Vedanta Limited has been declared the preferred bidder for the Karnapodikonda bauxite block in Odisha, a key development for its Aluminium business. The G2 explored block, spanning over 532 hectares, is crucial for the company's backward integration strategy, enhancing raw material security for its aluminium production. This win is a step towards securing resources for Vedanta's growing aluminium operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:59:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1bf52fa7d0695d1abf984_1772208079227.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rain Industries FY25 Turns Profitable; Consolidated Revenue ₹17,084 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Rain-Industries-FY25-Turns-Profitable-Consolidated-Revenue-17084-Cr/69a1bf47fa7d0695d1abf969</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Rain-Industries-FY25-Turns-Profitable-Consolidated-Revenue-17084-Cr/69a1bf47fa7d0695d1abf969</guid><description>Rain Industries has achieved a significant turnaround, reporting a consolidated net profit of ₹1,358.94 million (₹135.89 crore) for the fiscal year ended December 31, 2025, a stark contrast to the prior year's loss. Consolidated revenue grew 9.37% to ₹170,842.23 million (₹17,084.22 crore). However, standalone performance declined, and the company faces ongoing geopolitical risks and high debt levels.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:59:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1bf47fa7d0695d1abf968_1772208661138.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia Slumps as PPI Data Fuels Inflation Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Slumps-as-PPI-Data-Fuels-Inflation-Fears/69a1bb41fa7d0695d1abf71e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Slumps-as-PPI-Data-Fuels-Inflation-Fears/69a1bb41fa7d0695d1abf71e</guid><description>Nvidia's stock faced renewed selling pressure as robust January Producer Price Index (PPI) data intensified inflation worries, overshadowing strong company fundamentals. A significant surge in core PPI, far exceeding forecasts, amplified fears of stubbornly entrenched inflation and its implications for Federal Reserve policy. This macro backdrop, coupled with evolving sentiment around Nvidia's substantial AI-related capital expenditures and strategic investments, contributed to a broader tech sector downturn and a volatile end to February for major market indices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:41:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1bb41fa7d0695d1abf71d_1772207239171.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lumax Auto Tech: NCLT Sanctions Lumax Ancillary Merger; Final Order Awaited</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Lumax-Auto-Tech-NCLT-Sanctions-Lumax-Ancillary-Merger-Final-Order-Awaited/69a1ba97fa7d0695d1abf66c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Lumax-Auto-Tech-NCLT-Sanctions-Lumax-Ancillary-Merger-Final-Order-Awaited/69a1ba97fa7d0695d1abf66c</guid><description>Lumax Auto Technologies Limited has received a significant boost as the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), New Delhi Bench, sanctioned its amalgamation scheme with subsidiary Lumax Ancillary Limited on February 18, 2026. This move is poised to streamline operations and enhance efficiencies within the auto component manufacturer. While the NCLT has sanctioned the scheme, investors await the formal order for full details.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:39:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1ba97fa7d0695d1abf66b_1772206878161.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Promoter Sells Major Stake in VMML; Bulk Deals Signal Sector Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Promoter-Sells-Major-Stake-in-VMML-Bulk-Deals-Signal-Sector-Shifts/69a1ba24fa7d0695d1abf5e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Promoter-Sells-Major-Stake-in-VMML-Bulk-Deals-Signal-Sector-Shifts/69a1ba24fa7d0695d1abf5e1</guid><description>Vishal Mega Mart's promoter entity, Samayat Services LLP, divested 13.96% of its stake for over ₹7,600 crore on February 27th, a move that saw institutional investors like HDFC MF and the Government of Singapore acquire substantial holdings. Despite this, VMML shares closed down 7.65%. In parallel, block deals involving IRCTC and Jubilant Foodworks highlighted varied market sentiment across retail, travel, and QSR sectors. IRCTC shares plunged 4.27%, while Jubilant Foodworks saw a modest gain, reflecting distinct sector-specific pressures and opportunities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:37:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1ba24fa7d0695d1abf5e0_1772206957077.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fino Payments Bank MD Arrested Under GST Act; CFO Takes Interim Charge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Payments-Bank-MD-Arrested-Under-GST-Act-CFO-Takes-Interim-Charge/69a1b8b8fa7d0695d1abf4aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Payments-Bank-MD-Arrested-Under-GST-Act-CFO-Takes-Interim-Charge/69a1b8b8fa7d0695d1abf4aa</guid><description>Fino Payments Bank's Managing Director &amp; CEO, Rishi Gupta, was arrested on February 27, 2026, under the provisions of the CGST and SGST Act. The bank stated the investigation relates to business partners and not its direct GST compliance. Chief Financial Officer Ketan Merchant has been appointed interim head to manage daily operations. The bank assures no immediate impact.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b8b8fa7d0695d1abf4a9_1772206383623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market Divergence: Value Emerging Amidst Broad Sell-off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Market-Divergence-Value-Emerging-Amidst-Broad-Sell-off/69a1b858fa7d0695d1abf41a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Market-Divergence-Value-Emerging-Amidst-Broad-Sell-off/69a1b858fa7d0695d1abf41a</guid><description>Headline Indian indices like the Sensex and Nifty are near all-time highs, masking a severe downturn in the broader market. A Monarch AIF report highlights that approximately 80% of listed companies above ₹1,000 crore market capitalization are in a bear market. This divergence, lasting 18 months, has seen a narrow band of stocks prop up index performance while the majority face declines. However, this correction presents a favorable risk-reward scenario for stock pickers, with many growing companies trading at attractive forward P/E ratios below 20x, supported by strong earnings, potential lower rates, and reform momentum.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b858fa7d0695d1abf419_1772206455817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Elpro International Buys Fintech Firm Mynd Solutions for ₹11.37 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Elpro-International-Buys-Fintech-Firm-Mynd-Solutions-for-1137-Cr/69a1b408fa7d0695d1abf1f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Elpro-International-Buys-Fintech-Firm-Mynd-Solutions-for-1137-Cr/69a1b408fa7d0695d1abf1f9</guid><description>Elpro International Ltd. announced on February 27, 2026, its acquisition of equity shares in Mynd Solutions Private Limited for ₹11.37 Crores. Mynd Solutions, an RBI-licensed fintech entity operating the "Mlxchange" platform, reported a total turnover of ₹104.70 Crores in FY25. This strategic move aims to bolster Elpro International's footprint in the rapidly growing financial technology sector, aligning with its diversification strategy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:11:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b408fa7d0695d1abf1f8_1772205379218.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Credit Boom Diverges: Gold Loans Surge Amid Export Slowdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Credit-Boom-Diverges-Gold-Loans-Surge-Amid-Export-Slowdown/69a1b2c4fa7d0695d1abf08e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Credit-Boom-Diverges-Gold-Loans-Surge-Amid-Export-Slowdown/69a1b2c4fa7d0695d1abf08e</guid><description>Indian credit markets show a pronounced split in January 2026. Gold-backed lending exploded by 128% year-on-year, indicating elevated household demand for liquidity. Concurrently, overall non-food credit accelerated to 14%, with retail loans up 15% and corporate borrowing improving. Conversely, export credit plummeted 17.2%, a direct consequence of global trade uncertainties and past US tariff adjustments. The renewable energy sector also saw substantial 62% growth, largely driven by regulatory mandates. This dual trend underscores a robust domestic economy grappling with external trade pressures and highlights a growing reliance on gold as an accessible credit source.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:05:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b2c4fa7d0695d1abf08d_1772205075448.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Nears $4T GDP Amid Data Overhaul and Growth Revisions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Nears-4T-GDP-Amid-Data-Overhaul-and-Growth-Revisions/69a1b22efa7d0695d1abefe7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Nears-4T-GDP-Amid-Data-Overhaul-and-Growth-Revisions/69a1b22efa7d0695d1abefe7</guid><description>India is projected to surpass the $4 trillion GDP mark by fiscal year 2026-27, supported by a revised series of National Accounts Estimates. The new methodology enhances data accuracy, especially for manufacturing, while a recalibrated GDP base leads to an increased fiscal deficit ratio. This data overhaul aims to address previous concerns regarding statistical reliability, positioning India's economic narrative on a more robust foundation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:03:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b22efa7d0695d1abefe6_1772204721933.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OpenAI Lands $110B War Chest for AI Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAI-Lands-110B-War-Chest-for-AI-Dominance/69a1b0d6fa7d0695d1abee3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAI-Lands-110B-War-Chest-for-AI-Dominance/69a1b0d6fa7d0695d1abee3a</guid><description>OpenAI has finalized a colossal $110 billion funding round, bringing its pre-money valuation to $730 billion. Major investors Amazon, Nvidia, and SoftBank injected $50 billion, $30 billion, and $30 billion, respectively. This infusion fuels OpenAI's ambitious expansion, highlighted by a new strategic partnership with Amazon Web Services (AWS) focused on enterprise AI agent deployment through the 'OpenAI Frontier' platform. Despite this deepening relationship with AWS, OpenAI reaffirmed its exclusive stateless API commitment with Microsoft Azure, underscoring a complex multi-cloud strategy amidst escalating global AI competition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:57:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b0d6fa7d0695d1abee39_1772204388236.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goyal's $54M Temple Raise: Deep Tech Gamble in Crowded Wearables</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Goyals-54M-Temple-Raise-Deep-Tech-Gamble-in-Crowded-Wearables/69a1b0d1fa7d0695d1abee22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Goyals-54M-Temple-Raise-Deep-Tech-Gamble-in-Crowded-Wearables/69a1b0d1fa7d0695d1abee22</guid><description>Deepinder Goyal, fresh from leading Zomato, has injected $54 million into his new venture, Temple, at a $190 million valuation. This early-stage funding, primarily from Zomato's early backers and employees, signals strong conviction in Goyal's vision for a high-performance wearable tracking cerebral blood flow for elite athletes. Temple enters a saturated market against giants like Whoop and Oura, but Goyal's track record in ambitious, long-term projects, including longevity research and aerospace, underpins this bold pivot into deep-tech hardware.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:57:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b0d1fa7d0695d1abee21_1772204355761.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Elitecon Int. ED Resigns; Sunbridge Agro Deal Reversal Under Review</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Elitecon-Int-ED-Resigns-Sunbridge-Agro-Deal-Reversal-Under-Review/69a1b046fa7d0695d1abed7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Elitecon-Int-ED-Resigns-Sunbridge-Agro-Deal-Reversal-Under-Review/69a1b046fa7d0695d1abed7d</guid><description>Elitecon International accepted Executive Director Dayanand Ray's resignation. The company is also reviewing the reversal of its Sunbridge Agro Private Limited acquisition due to significant funding issues and unreleased pledged shares, appointing legal advisors to explore a resolution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:55:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b046fa7d0695d1abed7c_1772204212720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CBDC Pilot: India Rewrites Welfare Distribution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/CBDC-Pilot-India-Rewrites-Welfare-Distribution/69a1ac12fa7d0695d1abeaf2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/CBDC-Pilot-India-Rewrites-Welfare-Distribution/69a1ac12fa7d0695d1abeaf2</guid><description>India has initiated a Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) pilot in Puducherry, enabling the digital rupee (e₹) for food subsidy transfers under the Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Anna Yojana. Beneficiaries now receive programmable e₹ tokens directly into CBDC wallets, enhancing transparency, efficiency, and ensuring targeted utilization of funds. This initiative builds upon previous digital governance reforms and aims to address operational challenges, with potential for national expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:37:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1ac12fa7d0695d1abeaf1_1772203406364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki Bets on Existing Network for EVs, Skips Dedicated Channels</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Bets-on-Existing-Network-for-EVs-Skips-Dedicated-Channels/69a1aba1fa7d0695d1abea61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Bets-on-Existing-Network-for-EVs-Skips-Dedicated-Channels/69a1aba1fa7d0695d1abea61</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki India Limited (MSIL) will not create a dedicated retail network for electric vehicles (EVs), opting instead to integrate them within its existing multi-powertrain portfolio and leverage its premium Nexa network. The company's first EV, the e Vitara, is priced from ₹17.49 lakh, with a Battery-as-a-Service option available. Production will be measured, initially below 2,000 units monthly, with a new dedicated EV production line planned for July 2026. This contrasts with Tata Motors' dedicated EV strategy, as MSIL prioritizes customer experience across all powertrains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:35:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1aba1fa7d0695d1abea60_1772203033372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Shatters SaaS Playbook, Valuations Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Shatters-SaaS-Playbook-Valuations-Plunge/69a1ab9ffa7d0695d1abea4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Shatters-SaaS-Playbook-Valuations-Plunge/69a1ab9ffa7d0695d1abea4a</guid><description>The traditional SaaS model, built on per-seat pricing and feature expansion, is collapsing under the weight of AI-driven automation. AI agents are abstracting human workflows, shifting value from 'systems of record' to 'systems of agency.' This seismic shift has triggered a market correction, with software valuations plummeting. Companies must now pivot to outcome-based pricing, redefine competitive moats, and redesign go-to-market strategies to survive and thrive.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:35:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1ab9ffa7d0695d1abea49_1772203040614.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai Court Seals EOW Closure, Weakens ED Probe in MSCB Case</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Mumbai-Court-Seals-EOW-Closure-Weakens-ED-Probe-in-MSCB-Case/69a1a704fa7d0695d1abe727</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Mumbai-Court-Seals-EOW-Closure-Weakens-ED-Probe-in-MSCB-Case/69a1a704fa7d0695d1abe727</guid><description>A Mumbai special court has accepted the Economic Offences Wing (EOW) closure report in the ₹25,000-crore Maharashtra State Cooperative Bank (MSCB) case, effectively clearing Maharashtra Deputy Chief Minister Sunetra Pawar, the late Ajit Pawar, and over 70 others. The decision signifies a legal reprieve, significantly complicating the Enforcement Directorate's (ED) parallel money-laundering probe which hinges on the EOW's findings. The EOW concluded no criminal offense was committed, highlighting substantial loan recoveries and no financial loss to the bank.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:15:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a704fa7d0695d1abe726_1772201964330.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>