<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:19 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Netweb Technologies' AI Rally Faces Scrutiny Over Valuation, Execution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Netweb-Technologies-AI-Rally-Faces-Scrutiny-Over-Valuation-Execution/699693efd25eafd9cd00384e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Netweb-Technologies-AI-Rally-Faces-Scrutiny-Over-Valuation-Execution/699693efd25eafd9cd00384e</guid><description>Netweb Technologies India Ltd. experienced a significant stock rally, exceeding 16% over recent sessions, following the launch of its 'Make in India' AI supercomputing systems powered by NVIDIA's Grace Blackwell architecture. The company aims to bolster India's sovereign compute capabilities. However, the stock's substantial year-to-date gains and a high Price-to-Earnings ratio, nearing 100-130, prompt an examination of the sustainability of this growth trajectory amidst intense market competition and operational scaling challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:39:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699693efd25eafd9cd00384d_1771476102966.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Inflation Surge Tempered by CPI Basket Restructuring</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Inflation-Surge-Tempered-by-CPI-Basket-Restructuring/699693ced25eafd9cd003813</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Inflation-Surge-Tempered-by-CPI-Basket-Restructuring/699693ced25eafd9cd003813</guid><description>India's consumer inflation is projected to climb to 4.3% in fiscal year 2027, a notable increase from FY26's 2.5%. This rise, driven by normalizing food prices due to a low base effect, will be significantly tempered by a revised Consumer Price Index (CPI) basket where food holds less weight. Core inflation is anticipated to remain moderate, suggesting the Reserve Bank of India will likely maintain its repo rate pause to facilitate policy transmission.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699693ced25eafd9cd003812_1771476005370.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Rally Masks AI Threat to IT Sector's Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Rally-Masks-AI-Threat-to-IT-Sectors-Future/699690b8d25eafd9cd0036d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Rally-Masks-AI-Threat-to-IT-Sectors-Future/699690b8d25eafd9cd0036d2</guid><description>Indian equities witnessed substantial foreign institutional investor (FII) inflows in February 2026, buoyed by broad-based earnings growth and supportive fiscal and monetary stimuli. However, the burgeoning impact of Artificial Intelligence presents a significant disruptive force, particularly threatening the IT services sector's future revenue streams and employment stability amidst ongoing geopolitical uncertainties. This dynamic creates a market narrative where positive domestic momentum clashes with fundamental technological shifts, demanding investor vigilance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:25:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699690b8d25eafd9cd0036d1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Launches India's First Affordable Eye Biosimilar</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Launches-Indias-First-Affordable-Eye-Biosimilar/6996902ad25eafd9cd00365e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Launches-Indias-First-Affordable-Eye-Biosimilar/6996902ad25eafd9cd00365e</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences has launched ANYRA™, India's first indigenously developed biosimilar of Aflibercept 2 mg. This move is set to significantly enhance ophthalmic care by making treatments for conditions like wet age-related macular degeneration (wet AMD), diabetic retinopathy (DR), and diabetic macular edema (DME) more affordable and accessible to Indian patients. The company aims to leverage innovation for patient-centric outcomes, addressing a critical need for cost-effective retinal therapies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996902ad25eafd9cd00365d_1771475094114.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alcohol Sector: Premiumization Fuels Margins Amidst Growth Deceleration</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Alcohol-Sector-Premiumization-Fuels-Margins-Amidst-Growth-Deceleration/69968ec2d25eafd9cd003543</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Alcohol-Sector-Premiumization-Fuels-Margins-Amidst-Growth-Deceleration/69968ec2d25eafd9cd003543</guid><description>The Indian alcoholic beverages sector demonstrated robust margin expansion and sustained premiumization trends in Q3-FY26, even as overall sales growth decelerated. EBITDA surged 21% year-on-year, significantly outpacing the 8% sales growth. Spirits companies like Radico Khaitan and United Spirits continued to gain volume traction over beer majors such as United Breweries, which faced headwinds from extended monsoons and regulatory shifts. Gross margins expanded by up to 350 basis points across the sector, driven by price hikes and favorable product mix.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:17:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69968ec2d25eafd9cd003542.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Rise: IT Gains Mask Mid/Small-Cap Valuation Chasm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Rise-IT-Gains-Mask-MidSmall-Cap-Valuation-Chasm/69968e4ed25eafd9cd003466</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Rise-IT-Gains-Mask-MidSmall-Cap-Valuation-Chasm/69968e4ed25eafd9cd003466</guid><description>Benchmark Indian stock indices opened higher, propelled by a recovery in IT stocks. However, the market's true narrative lies in the stark valuation divergence between large-caps, which offer comfort, and mid and small-caps, which trade at significant premiums. This imbalance, coupled with emerging AI disruption risks in the IT sector, signals a complex environment demanding selective investment strategies. Positive outlooks persist for financials, autos, capital goods, pharmaceuticals, and hotels, buoyed by government policy and resilient domestic demand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:15:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69968e4ed25eafd9cd003465_1771474643404.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCX, NSE Ease Gold, Silver Futures Margins; Risk Remains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-NSE-Ease-Gold-Silver-Futures-Margins-Risk-Remains/69968e4cd25eafd9cd00344f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-NSE-Ease-Gold-Silver-Futures-Margins-Risk-Remains/69968e4cd25eafd9cd00344f</guid><description>The Multi Commodity Exchange (MCX) and National Stock Exchange (NSE) have reversed earlier decisions, withdrawing additional margins imposed on gold and silver futures contracts effective February 19, 2026. This move lowers the capital required for traders, potentially boosting liquidity and retail participation. However, the underlying leverage inherent in futures trading, coupled with ongoing global macroeconomic uncertainties and geopolitical tensions, means substantial risks remain for market participants. Despite reduced entry costs, disciplined risk management is paramount as price swings can rapidly amplify losses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:15:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69968e4cd25eafd9cd00344e_1771474648756.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Dips as Fed Policy Fears Override Easing Tensions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Dips-as-Fed-Policy-Fears-Override-Easing-Tensions/69968dd6d25eafd9cd0033cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Dips-as-Fed-Policy-Fears-Override-Easing-Tensions/69968dd6d25eafd9cd0033cd</guid><description>Gold prices experienced marginal fluctuations, trading around Rs 1,56,019 per 10g on MCX. Despite easing geopolitical tensions, a strengthening US dollar and evolving Federal Reserve monetary policy expectations, driven by mixed economic data, are creating headwinds. Investors are closely watching Fed minutes for further rate path signals, while analysts anticipate short-term consolidation with specific support and resistance levels.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:13:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69968dd6d25eafd9cd0033cc_1771474517737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Hub Bid Faces Digital Sovereignty Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Hub-Bid-Faces-Digital-Sovereignty-Concerns/69968c7ad25eafd9cd0032c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Hub-Bid-Faces-Digital-Sovereignty-Concerns/69968c7ad25eafd9cd0032c4</guid><description>India is aggressively positioning itself as a global AI and data hub, incentivizing infrastructure development with a 20-year tax holiday for data centers and attracting major tech investments, including Google's $15 billion AI initiative. However, concerns persist regarding foreign companies dominating the upstream AI data layer, potentially compromising digital sovereignty. While organizational AI adoption is high, per-capita usage lags, and the sector faces infrastructure funding gaps and environmental scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:07:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69968c7ad25eafd9cd0032c3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Market Rallies Amidst Valuation Gap &amp; Fed Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Market-Rallies-Amidst-Valuation-Gap-and-Fed-Caution/69968b80d25eafd9cd003221</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Market-Rallies-Amidst-Valuation-Gap-and-Fed-Caution/69968b80d25eafd9cd003221</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks continued their advance for a third consecutive session, propelled by a revival in mid and small-cap stocks and strong domestic sector performance. While the Nifty50 and BSE Sensex traded higher, market sentiment is shaped by a widening valuation premium in smaller caps compared to large-caps, and a cautious stance from the U.S. Federal Reserve regarding interest rate policy. Tech giants like Nvidia and Amazon reported robust earnings, yet a nuanced global economic outlook necessitates careful stock selection across promising sectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:03:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69968b80d25eafd9cd003220.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE Launches Cement Index: Concentration Risks Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NSE-Launches-Cement-Index-Concentration-Risks-Emerge/699687cad25eafd9cd003010</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NSE-Launches-Cement-Index-Concentration-Risks-Emerge/699687cad25eafd9cd003010</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange of India has launched the Nifty Cement Index, tracking the cement and cement products sector. While intended as a benchmark for fund portfolios and new investment products, the index's construction reveals significant concentration. The top four constituents collectively hold nearly 60% of the index's weight, primarily comprising UltraTech Cement and Grasim Industries, highlighting the dominance of a few players in the Indian cement market. This structure implies that passive tracking vehicles may offer limited diversification benefits and be highly sensitive to the performance of these sector giants, necessitating a deeper analysis beyond mere sector inclusion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:47:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699687cad25eafd9cd00300f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dividend Surge Signals Profitability, Investor Payouts Accelerate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dividend-Surge-Signals-Profitability-Investor-Payouts-Accelerate/699687c2d25eafd9cd002ff6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dividend-Surge-Signals-Profitability-Investor-Payouts-Accelerate/699687c2d25eafd9cd002ff6</guid><description>An extensive list of over two dozen Indian companies, including Alkem Laboratories and IRCTC, are set to trade ex-dividend on February 20, 2026. These payouts, led by Alkem's ₹43 per share, indicate robust corporate profitability and a strategic focus on returning capital to investors amidst a dynamic market environment. The broad participation across sectors suggests a generalized strength in corporate earnings, prompting a closer look at underlying financial health and future growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:47:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699687c2d25eafd9cd002ff5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Market: AI Ambitions Clash with Safety Gaps</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/India-Market-AI-Ambitions-Clash-with-Safety-Gaps/699687c1d25eafd9cd002fdf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/India-Market-AI-Ambitions-Clash-with-Safety-Gaps/699687c1d25eafd9cd002fdf</guid><description>India's market faces a complex dynamic. Ambitious AI development and regulatory actions against cyber fraud signal progress. However, recent fatal industrial accidents highlight systemic safety failures, raising concerns over operational risks and regulatory enforcement. These contrasting factors create a mixed outlook for sector investments, potentially dampening investor confidence despite strong demographic and technological ambitions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:47:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699687c1d25eafd9cd002fde.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aluminium Rally Cools: Vedanta Stands as Kotak's Top Pick</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aluminium-Rally-Cools-Vedanta-Stands-as-Kotaks-Top-Pick/69968745d25eafd9cd002f07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aluminium-Rally-Cools-Vedanta-Stands-as-Kotaks-Top-Pick/69968745d25eafd9cd002f07</guid><description>Aluminium prices have retreated 7% from recent highs to approximately $3,030 per tonne, driven by shifting US Federal Reserve expectations and a stronger dollar. Kotak Institutional Equities notes this moderation, but maintains that structurally robust demand, lagging capacity, and supply disruptions underpin a persistent market deficit. The brokerage designates Vedanta Limited as its top 'Buy' in the sector, projecting a 32% upside to ₹890 based on sustained favourable conditions and Vedanta's operational performance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:45:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69968745d25eafd9cd002f06.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eicher Motors: Hunter 350 Momentum Meets Valuation Skepticism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Hunter-350-Momentum-Meets-Valuation-Skepticism/69968743d25eafd9cd002eef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Hunter-350-Momentum-Meets-Valuation-Skepticism/69968743d25eafd9cd002eef</guid><description>Eicher Motors reported a robust 23% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹6,114 crore for Q3 FY26, with net profit climbing 21.3% to ₹1,420 crore. Despite exceeding estimates, the company's premium valuation is under scrutiny, as highlighted by mixed analyst sentiment. Goldman Sachs reiterated a 'Buy' with an elevated target price, contrasting with broader consensus and cautionary views on future margin expansion. The successful Hunter 350 model continues to drive volume growth, supported by planned capacity expansions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:45:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69968743d25eafd9cd002eee.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IPO Surge Sparks Market Revival; Selectivity Dominates Investor Sentiment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Surge-Sparks-Market-Revival-Selectivity-Dominates-Investor-Sentiment/699686cad25eafd9cd002e53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Surge-Sparks-Market-Revival-Selectivity-Dominates-Investor-Sentiment/699686cad25eafd9cd002e53</guid><description>Following a quiet spell, India's primary market is set to see significant activity with four mainboard IPOs raising over ₹3,700 crore. While Gaudium IVF shows strong fundamentals and a promising grey market premium (GMP), the large Clean Max Enviro IPO and others present a more mixed picture. This indicates a discerning investor base, prioritizing robust business models and valuation discipline over sheer deal volume amid a heavy IPO pipeline.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:43:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699686cad25eafd9cd002e52_1771472779734.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Dips as Fed Division Dampens Rate Cut Hopes Amid Thin Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Dips-as-Fed-Division-Dampens-Rate-Cut-Hopes-Amid-Thin-Markets/69968567d25eafd9cd002d2f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Dips-as-Fed-Division-Dampens-Rate-Cut-Hopes-Amid-Thin-Markets/69968567d25eafd9cd002d2f</guid><description>Gold and silver prices retreated as Federal Reserve meeting minutes revealed a stark policy division, with some officials signaling potential rate hikes if inflation persists. Thin trading volumes, exacerbated by Lunar New Year holidays in Asia, coupled with evolving geopolitical sentiment, contributed to market caution. Analysts highlight uncertainty in the Fed's rate trajectory and the need for clearer inflation signals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:37:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69968567d25eafd9cd002d2e_1771472374068.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>INOXGFL Buys Wind World India Assets to Boost Green Energy Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/INOXGFL-Buys-Wind-World-India-Assets-to-Boost-Green-Energy-Business/699684ebd25eafd9cd002cc6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/INOXGFL-Buys-Wind-World-India-Assets-to-Boost-Green-Energy-Business/699684ebd25eafd9cd002cc6</guid><description>The INOXGFL Group, through its subsidiaries Inox Clean Energy and Inox Green Energy Services, has successfully acquired the Independent Power Producer (IPP) and Operations &amp; Maintenance (O&amp;M) businesses of Wind World India. This strategic move, approved by the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), is set to significantly enhance the group's renewable energy platform, bolstering its installed capacity and recurring revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:35:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699684ebd25eafd9cd002cc5_1771472215143.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Equities Rally: Nifty Surges, Stocks Eye Gains Amid Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Rally-Nifty-Surges-Stocks-Eye-Gains-Amid-Caution/69968389d25eafd9cd002bf9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Rally-Nifty-Surges-Stocks-Eye-Gains-Amid-Caution/69968389d25eafd9cd002bf9</guid><description>The Indian market demonstrated bullish momentum, with the Nifty confirming a breakout above its short-term consolidation and Bank Nifty hitting fresh all-time highs. Analysts have identified Sona BLW Precision Forgings, PFC, and NLC India as potential buys, citing technical patterns and recent performance. However, a closer examination reveals elevated valuations for Sona BLW, significant debt concerns for PFC, and past performance headwinds for NLC India, suggesting a complex risk-reward dynamic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:29:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69968389d25eafd9cd002bf8_1771471939310.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ACME Solar Signs 190 MW Hybrid Power Deal with SECI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ACME-Solar-Signs-190-MW-Hybrid-Power-Deal-with-SECI/699680d3d25eafd9cd002a7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ACME-Solar-Signs-190-MW-Hybrid-Power-Deal-with-SECI/699680d3d25eafd9cd002a7b</guid><description>ACME Solar Holdings, via its subsidiary, has signed a 25-year Power Purchase Agreement (PPA) with SECI for a 190 MW wind-solar hybrid project featuring battery storage. This deal boosts ACME's PPA-signed portfolio to 5,820 MW, reinforcing its strong position in India's renewable energy market and securing future revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:17:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699680d3d25eafd9cd002a7a_1771471166976.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel: Analyst Target Fuels Rally, But CBAM Clouds Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Analyst-Target-Fuels-Rally-But-CBAM-Clouds-Outlook/69968042d25eafd9cd0029b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Analyst-Target-Fuels-Rally-But-CBAM-Clouds-Outlook/69968042d25eafd9cd0029b8</guid><description>Tata Steel shares are gaining momentum, driven by analyst upgrades and a projected 15% upside to ₹240, citing robust Indian demand and progress in its EU business. Despite a strong yearly gain and bullish sentiment, the company faces increased scrutiny regarding its valuation, with a P/E ratio hovering around 27-38x. Emerging risks, including the EU's Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (CBAM) and intense competition, necessitate a deeper look beyond the immediate optimism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69968042d25eafd9cd0029b7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cement Sector: JPMorgan Flags Pricing Discipline vs. Market Share Clash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Sector-JPMorgan-Flags-Pricing-Discipline-vs-Market-Share-Clash/69968040d25eafd9cd0029a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Sector-JPMorgan-Flags-Pricing-Discipline-vs-Market-Share-Clash/69968040d25eafd9cd0029a1</guid><description>JPMorgan analysts predict capped utilization in India's cement sector over the next three years, stemming from substantial upcoming capacity additions. While companies target cost reductions and market share gains, the market's expectation for EBITDA per tonne expansion relies heavily on price increases, not just efficiency. This creates a dilemma: aggressive market share strategies could undermine the pricing discipline required for sustained profit growth. UltraTech Cement is rated 'Overweight' with a ₹15,000 target, citing scale and pricing power, while Dalmia Bharat is upgraded to 'Neutral' with a ₹2,215 target.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:15:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69968040d25eafd9cd0029a0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Q3 Earnings Split: Large Caps Lift Nifty Amidst Small Cap Struggles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Indias-Q3-Earnings-Split-Large-Caps-Lift-Nifty-Amidst-Small-Cap-Struggles/69968040d25eafd9cd00298a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Indias-Q3-Earnings-Split-Large-Caps-Lift-Nifty-Amidst-Small-Cap-Struggles/69968040d25eafd9cd00298a</guid><description>Q3 FY26 earnings revealed a stark divergence: largecap companies delivered resilient performance and boosted the Nifty50, which surpassed EPS expectations. Conversely, smallcaps struggled with a high miss rate, signaling increasing performance disparities across market capitalizations. While Nifty50 EPS grew 13.4% year-on-year, the market navigates elevated valuations against a backdrop of modest future earnings growth projections and mixed sectoral outlooks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:15:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69968040d25eafd9cd002989.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Disruption Threatens IT Sector's FMCG Valuation Narrative</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Disruption-Threatens-IT-Sectors-FMCG-Valuation-Narrative/69967f45d25eafd9cd002881</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Disruption-Threatens-IT-Sectors-FMCG-Valuation-Narrative/69967f45d25eafd9cd002881</guid><description>The long-held comparison of IT stocks to stable FMCG companies is being tested by Artificial Intelligence. AI's disruptive force is automating traditional IT services, leading to commoditization, pricing pressure, and potential revenue deflation. This shift necessitates a strategic pivot towards AI-native business models, with analysts warning that firms failing to adapt risk obsolescence and may no longer warrant defensive-tier valuations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:11:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69967f45d25eafd9cd002880_1771470788085.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FY27 MF Tax Maze: Complexity &amp; Strategy Rule Investor Choices</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/FY27-MF-Tax-Maze-Complexity-and-Strategy-Rule-Investor-Choices/69967ed4d25eafd9cd002807</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/FY27-MF-Tax-Maze-Complexity-and-Strategy-Rule-Investor-Choices/69967ed4d25eafd9cd002807</guid><description>As fiscal year 2026-27 approaches, India's mutual fund taxation landscape continues to be defined by intricate rules rather than straightforward tax benefits. The shift in debt fund taxation, effective since April 2023, has permanently altered investment dynamics, pushing risk-averse investors towards higher-risk assets or fixed deposits and demanding strategic portfolio recalibration. Investors must navigate evolving equity and hybrid fund rules alongside precedents set by REITs and InvITs, where complexity now dictates post-tax returns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:09:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69967ed4d25eafd9cd002806_1771470686916.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IPO Surge Cools: Growth Stocks Face Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/IPO-Surge-Cools-Growth-Stocks-Face-Valuation-Scrutiny/69967e5dd25eafd9cd002791</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/IPO-Surge-Cools-Growth-Stocks-Face-Valuation-Scrutiny/69967e5dd25eafd9cd002791</guid><description>Recent Indian IPOs, particularly in technology and electric vehicles, have rewarded investors with substantial listing gains. Aditya Infotech and Ather Energy exemplify this trend, with significant jumps from issue prices. However, market analysis reveals a divergence, as capital prioritizes growth visibility over established brands. While some smaller tech and EV offerings are thriving, scrutiny is mounting over the sustainability of their high valuations, contrasting with the more subdued performance of larger, well-known entities' offerings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:07:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69967e5dd25eafd9cd002790_1771470553398.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCS, Tata Group Forge AI Pact with OpenAI for India Innovation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Tata-Group-Forge-AI-Pact-with-OpenAI-for-India-Innovation/69967cf7d25eafd9cd0026e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Tata-Group-Forge-AI-Pact-with-OpenAI-for-India-Innovation/69967cf7d25eafd9cd0026e9</guid><description>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) and the Tata Group have announced a foundational strategic partnership with OpenAI. This collaboration aims to drive AI innovation across enterprises and consumer sectors, with a significant focus on India. Key initiatives include providing Enterprise ChatGPT access to thousands of Tata employees, developing industry-specific AI solutions, building AI infrastructure in India starting with 100MW capacity, and a social impact program to train one million Indian youth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:01:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69967cf7d25eafd9cd0026e8_1771470173014.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bandhan Fund Bets on Unpopular Small Caps Amidst Market Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Bandhan-Fund-Bets-on-Unpopular-Small-Caps-Amidst-Market-Jitters/69967937d25eafd9cd002580</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Bandhan-Fund-Bets-on-Unpopular-Small-Caps-Amidst-Market-Jitters/69967937d25eafd9cd002580</guid><description>The Bandhan Small Cap Fund, managed by Manish Gunwani, has significantly outperformed its peers by adopting a deep-value investment strategy. The fund focuses on identifying undervalued, often unpopular, stocks, particularly within the internet and textile sectors. Recent portfolio additions include companies like Paytm, Info Edge India Ltd., and IndiaMart InterMesh Ltd., reflecting a belief that regulatory headwinds and temporary losses present accumulation opportunities. This approach has led to strong returns, even as the broader Nifty Smallcap 100 index shows year-to-date weakness, signaling a potential market rotation towards undervalued assets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:45:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69967937d25eafd9cd00257f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Growth Narrative: Trade Gains Face Domestic Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Narrative-Trade-Gains-Face-Domestic-Headwinds/699678bed25eafd9cd0024ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Narrative-Trade-Gains-Face-Domestic-Headwinds/699678bed25eafd9cd0024ce</guid><description>India's economy is projected for robust growth, underscored by strong forecasts from major institutions like Goldman Sachs and Moody's, and solid credit ratings from agencies like S&amp;P and Fitch. Recent international trade agreements are seen as beneficial. However, persistent domestic issues, including rising household debt, struggles within the MSME sector, and productivity gaps, present significant headwinds. While the government touts reforms, historical context and ongoing structural challenges suggest a complex path to sustained, inclusive growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:43:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699678bed25eafd9cd0024cd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dixon Tech Slumps on Downgrade, But Component Shift Offers Counterpoint</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Tech-Slumps-on-Downgrade-But-Component-Shift-Offers-Counterpoint/699678b9d25eafd9cd0024b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Tech-Slumps-on-Downgrade-But-Component-Shift-Offers-Counterpoint/699678b9d25eafd9cd0024b7</guid><description>CLSA's downgrade of Dixon Technologies (India) Ltd. due to memory market pressures and potential smartphone demand weakness has hit the stock. However, the company's strategic pivot towards higher-margin component manufacturing, bolstered by government incentives, and its valuation appearing historically cheap relative to peers, suggests a potentially resilient outlook. This analysis contrasts the bearish sentiment with Dixon's evolving operational strategy and market positioning.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:43:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699678b9d25eafd9cd0024b6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCC Loses NHAI Bids for 2 Years; Financials Sag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Loses-NHAI-Bids-for-2-Years-Financials-Sag/699677d4d25eafd9cd002390</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Loses-NHAI-Bids-for-2-Years-Financials-Sag/699677d4d25eafd9cd002390</guid><description>NCC Limited shares are under pressure after the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) barred the company and its subsidiary from future tenders for two years, effective February 17, 2026. This regulatory action follows a challenging financial quarter, which saw net profit drop 36.6% and revenue decline 8.9%. While NCC stated its existing order book and ongoing projects remain unaffected, the debarment raises concerns about its future revenue pipeline from the NHAI, a key client. The company is reviewing the order and plans legal recourse.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:39:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699677d4d25eafd9cd00238f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Secures Niche Pediatric Drug Approval Amidst Sector Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Secures-Niche-Pediatric-Drug-Approval-Amidst-Sector-Shifts/699677cbd25eafd9cd002379</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Secures-Niche-Pediatric-Drug-Approval-Amidst-Sector-Shifts/699677cbd25eafd9cd002379</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences received final USFDA approval for Bosentan tablets for oral suspension, targeting pediatric Pulmonary Arterial Hypertension (PAH). This niche indication, with estimated annual US sales of $9.3 million, enters a competitive generic space. The company is also focusing on its domestic PEPAIR respiratory device launch. Analysts maintain a 'Neutral' consensus with an average price target of ₹999, indicating a modest upside. The broader Indian pharmaceutical sector faces challenges in the US market due to price erosion, while European and domestic markets show stronger growth. Zydus's P/E ratio of ~18.5x is below industry averages, suggesting potential value, but past quality control concerns warrant scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:39:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699677cbd25eafd9cd002378.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pharma Rally: Nuvama Sees 27% Upside, But Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-Rally-Nuvama-Sees-27percent-Upside-But-Risks-Loom/699676e5d25eafd9cd002297</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-Rally-Nuvama-Sees-27percent-Upside-But-Risks-Loom/699676e5d25eafd9cd002297</guid><description>Nuvama Securities analysts initiated 'Buy' calls on four Indian pharmaceutical companies, forecasting potential gains of 15-27% driven by domestic strength and product pipelines. However, a deeper look reveals moderating US market growth, heightened regulatory scrutiny, and premium valuations for some players, suggesting a complex outlook. The sector faces a structural shift towards quality and innovation amidst ongoing pricing pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:35:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699676e5d25eafd9cd002296_1771468634263.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Struggling Jauss Polymers Faces Takeover Bid at Deep Discount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Struggling-Jauss-Polymers-Faces-Takeover-Bid-at-Deep-Discount/699676d7d25eafd9cd00227d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Struggling-Jauss-Polymers-Faces-Takeover-Bid-at-Deep-Discount/699676d7d25eafd9cd00227d</guid><description>Jauss Polymers Limited, burdened by consistent losses and a lack of transparent revenue reporting, is the subject of an open offer from Noize Brands and Lifestyle Limited and Mr. Aditya Chopra. They aim to acquire up to 26% of Jauss Polymers at ₹16.05 per share, significantly below its current trading price and book value, raising serious concerns for existing shareholders. Trading in Jauss Polymers shares is also suspended on the Calcutta Stock Exchange.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:35:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699676d7d25eafd9cd00227c_1771468620143.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IMF Quantifies China's 'Policy Waste' Amid Trade Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IMF-Quantifies-Chinas-Policy-Waste-Amid-Trade-Risk/6996720ed25eafd9cd00081c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IMF-Quantifies-Chinas-Policy-Waste-Amid-Trade-Risk/6996720ed25eafd9cd00081c</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund has issued a stark warning on China's economic trajectory, quantifying "policy waste" from industrial subsidies at approximately 4% of GDP—significantly above European Union levels. Amid persistent deflation and escalating government debt nearing 127% of GDP, the IMF highlights adverse "external imbalances" and calls for a pivot to consumption-led growth. While forecasting 4.5% GDP expansion for 2026, the fund flags heightened downside risks from deepening domestic demand weakness and renewed trade tensions, a concern echoed by Moody's negative outlook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:14:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996720ed25eafd9cd00081b_1771467418155.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alphabet Bets Big on India's AI Infrastructure Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Bets-Big-on-Indias-AI-Infrastructure-Rise/699671bcd25eafd9cd0007a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Bets-Big-on-Indias-AI-Infrastructure-Rise/699671bcd25eafd9cd0007a2</guid><description>Alphabet CEO Sundar Pichai announced a sweeping strategy to solidify India as a global artificial intelligence hub. The initiative involves substantial investment in AI infrastructure, including subsea cables and compute facilities, alongside ambitious skilling programs. This strategic push aims to capitalize on India's burgeoning digital economy and talent pool, positioning Alphabet to leverage AI's transformative potential for both its business and national development.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:13:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699671bcd25eafd9cd0007a1_1771467385785.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Tests Resistance as Select Leaders Defy Macro Gloom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Nifty-Tests-Resistance-as-Select-Leaders-Defy-Macro-Gloom/699671b7d25eafd9cd000788</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Nifty-Tests-Resistance-as-Select-Leaders-Defy-Macro-Gloom/699671b7d25eafd9cd000788</guid><description>The Nifty 50 navigated volatility to close with modest gains, hovering near the 25,819 level. While global cues remain cautious, select heavyweight stocks, particularly in the banking and auto sectors, demonstrated technical strength. This divergence suggests a bifurcating market, with these leaders potentially charting their own course despite broader economic uncertainties and Nifty's struggle to surpass the 26,000 mark.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:13:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699671b7d25eafd9cd000787.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EM Equities Rally Continues: AI Fuels Asia, India Eyes Rebound Amid Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/EM-Equities-Rally-Continues-AI-Fuels-Asia-India-Eyes-Rebound-Amid-Divergence/699671b4d25eafd9cd000771</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/EM-Equities-Rally-Continues-AI-Fuels-Asia-India-Eyes-Rebound-Amid-Divergence/699671b4d25eafd9cd000771</guid><description>Emerging market equities delivered strong returns in 2025, with analysts at Goldman Sachs Asset Management predicting a continued rally in 2026. Key themes include AI-driven innovation in Asia (Taiwan, South Korea), an expected earnings rebound in India, and China's export adaptability. However, high valuations in some markets, limited AI hardware participation for India, and significant geopolitical supply chain risks warrant careful consideration. EMs trade at a substantial discount to US equities, offering potential upside, but specific regional dynamics present a mixed picture.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:13:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699671b4d25eafd9cd000770_1771467323069.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pernod Ricard Eyes India IPO Amid Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pernod-Ricard-Eyes-India-IPO-Amid-Global-Headwinds/699671b4d25eafd9cd00075a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pernod-Ricard-Eyes-India-IPO-Amid-Global-Headwinds/699671b4d25eafd9cd00075a</guid><description>French spirits giant Pernod Ricard SA is reportedly considering an initial public offering (IPO) for its Indian business, a strategic move aimed at unlocking value amidst a challenging global operating environment. This potential listing comes as the company faces sales declines in key Western markets and a significant valuation discount compared to its peers and its own Indian subsidiary's valuation. The Indian market offers robust growth driven by premiumization, presenting an opportunity for Pernod Ricard to tap into higher multiples and bolster shareholder confidence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 02:13:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699671b4d25eafd9cd000759.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys AI Execution Risk, ITC Tax Navigation, LG Margin Ceiling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Infosys-AI-Execution-Risk-ITC-Tax-Navigation-LG-Margin-Ceiling/69966bafd25eafd9cd0004ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Infosys-AI-Execution-Risk-ITC-Tax-Navigation-LG-Margin-Ceiling/69966bafd25eafd9cd0004ae</guid><description>Infosys faces scrutiny over AI execution and limited current revenue contribution, contrasting with its strategic positioning. ITC's price hikes appear defensive against taxes, aiming to buffer volume impacts. LG Electronics' growth prospects are capped by rising competition and commodity costs, limiting margin expansion. Dabur's management transition introduces strategic uncertainty, while Aurobindo Pharma's new drug approval necessitates significant sales investment. These developments highlight nuanced challenges beyond initial analyst ratings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:47:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69966bafd25eafd9cd0004ad.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>