<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:54:39 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Meesho's Post-IPO Earnings: Growth Surges, Margins Squeezed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meeshos-Post-IPO-Earnings-Growth-Surges-Margins-Squeezed/69802a3b47db7081af67ab8a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meeshos-Post-IPO-Earnings-Growth-Surges-Margins-Squeezed/69802a3b47db7081af67ab8a</guid><description>Value e-commerce platform Meesho reported a 26% year-on-year increase in Net Merchandise Value (NMV) to Rs 10,995 crore and a 34% rise in Annual Transacting Users (ATUs) to 25.1 crore in Q3 FY26. However, aggressive scaling of its logistics arm, Valmo, and increased operational costs led to a 12-fold surge in net loss to Rs 491 crore, pressuring contribution margins to 2.3%. Management projects FY26 as the peak for EBITDA losses, anticipating sequential improvement from Q4 FY26 as logistics costs normalize.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Chidambaram Slams Budget: 'Forgotten Schemes, Mismanaged Finances'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Chidambaram-Slams-Budget-Forgotten-Schemes-Mismanaged-Finances/698027de47db7081af679c4b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Chidambaram-Slams-Budget-Forgotten-Schemes-Mismanaged-Finances/698027de47db7081af679c4b</guid><description>Former Finance Minister P. Chidambaram fiercely criticized the latest budget, deeming it a failure in economic strategy and statesmanship. He highlighted the announcement of at least 24 schemes likely to be abandoned, coupled with a poor account of financial management. Chidambaram pointed to significant shortfalls in revenue receipts and a drastic cut in capital expenditure, which has also fallen as a percentage of GDP. He detailed cuts impacting crucial sectors like rural development, agriculture, education, and health.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698027de47db7081af679c4a_1770006846476.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSE Gainers Rise Amidst Market Dip, Sectoral Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BSE-Gainers-Rise-Amidst-Market-Dip-Sectoral-Divergence/6980298a47db7081af67a56d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BSE-Gainers-Rise-Amidst-Market-Dip-Sectoral-Divergence/6980298a47db7081af67a56d</guid><description>Three prominent stocks, Supreme Petrochem Ltd, Uno Minda Ltd, and Marico Ltd, registered significant gains during early trading today, contrasting with the broader market's negative start. The S&amp;P BSE Sensex opened lower, yet these companies saw substantial upward movement without immediate corporate announcements, suggesting market forces are currently influencing their valuations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Delhivery Surges Post-Q3 on Analyst Upgrades and Growth Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Delhivery-Surges-Post-Q3-on-Analyst-Upgrades-and-Growth-Outlook/6980296647db7081af67a46e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Delhivery-Surges-Post-Q3-on-Analyst-Upgrades-and-Growth-Outlook/6980296647db7081af67a46e</guid><description>Delhivery reported a significant Q3FY26 performance, with revenue rising 18% year-on-year to ₹2,805 crore and net profit jumping 58.4% to ₹39.6 crore. The stock reacted positively, gaining over 5% in two trading sessions, buoyed by multiple brokerage upgrades. Analysts cite strong volume growth in express parcel and part-truckload segments, margin expansion, and strategic industry positioning as key drivers for a favorable future outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Msafe Equipments IPO: Subscription Frenzy Signals Strong Market Debut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Msafe-Equipments-IPO-Subscription-Frenzy-Signals-Strong-Market-Debut/6980281247db7081af679e77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Msafe-Equipments-IPO-Subscription-Frenzy-Signals-Strong-Market-Debut/6980281247db7081af679e77</guid><description>Msafe Equipments' initial public offering concluded with extraordinary investor demand, achieving a subscription rate of 166.72 times. This strong response, with bids for 596.36 million shares against 3.57 million offered, highlights significant confidence in the company's growth trajectory and the broader height-safety equipment market. The IPO is set to list on the BSE SME platform on February 4, 2026. The company plans to utilize the capital raised for expanding its manufacturing capabilities and enhancing its rental fleet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980281247db7081af679e76_1770006718402.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Census Gets ₹6K Cr Boost for Digital Rollout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Census-Gets-6K-Cr-Boost-for-Digital-Rollout/698027ef47db7081af679d1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Census-Gets-6K-Cr-Boost-for-Digital-Rollout/698027ef47db7081af679d1e</guid><description>The Union Budget has allocated ₹6,000 crore to conduct India's population census, a significant funding increase marking a new era for the exercise. Delayed for over five years, this decennial count will be fully digital, employing mobile applications and allowing for self-enumeration. It also introduces caste enumeration for the first time, aiming to capture a comprehensive demographic, socioeconomic, and cultural profile of the nation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:30:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698027ef47db7081af679d1d_1770006607105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Markets Plunge on STT Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Markets-Plunge-on-STT-Hike/698027a647db7081af679b05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Markets-Plunge-on-STT-Hike/698027a647db7081af679b05</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 saw major Indian equity indices, the BSE Sensex and NSE Nifty 50, plummet by over 1.8% following its announcement. The sharp decline, attributed to a significant hike in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives and concerns over foreign investor incentives, overshadowed the government's focus on capital expenditure and sector-specific initiatives. Opposition leaders heavily criticized the budget for allegedly ignoring key economic challenges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:28:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698027a647db7081af679b04_1770006509441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Trims Rural Housing Funds, Urban Scheme Gets Modest Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Budget-Trims-Rural-Housing-Funds-Urban-Scheme-Gets-Modest-Boost/6980276547db7081af6799c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Budget-Trims-Rural-Housing-Funds-Urban-Scheme-Gets-Modest-Boost/6980276547db7081af6799c9</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 has revised down allocations for the Pradhan Mantri Awas Yojana-Rural, trimming its FY26 revised estimate by ₹3,332 crore. While PMAY-Urban 2.0 receives a budgeted ₹3,000 crore for FY27, its execution pace appears cautious. The overall housing ministry receives a substantial allocation, with the PM SVANidhi scheme seeing a significant funding increase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:28:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980276547db7081af6799c8_1770006431626.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Tax Clarifications Aim to Cut Litigation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Tax-Clarifications-Aim-to-Cut-Litigation/6980242247db7081af6790c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Tax-Clarifications-Aim-to-Cut-Litigation/6980242247db7081af6790c7</guid><description>India's Budget 2026 includes retrospective clarifications on tax reassessment notices and the validation of assessment orders lacking a Document Identification Number (DIN). Effective April 1, 2021, reassessment notices can be issued by the jurisdictional assessing officer, resolving conflicting court rulings. The DIN clarification, effective October 1, 2019, ensures orders are not invalidated by minor quoting errors. These measures aim to streamline tax administration and manage litigation, though concerns linger regarding retrospective application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:26:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980242247db7081af6790c6_1770006363747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Navigate Growth Budget Amid FII Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Navigate-Growth-Budget-Amid-FII-Headwinds/698026f247db7081af679846</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Navigate-Growth-Budget-Amid-FII-Headwinds/698026f247db7081af679846</guid><description>Indian benchmark indices rose on February 2, 2026, overcoming a flat open as metal and energy stocks buoyed sentiment. The market is digesting a growth-focused Union Budget, expected to boost GDP and corporate earnings. However, sustained FII selling and STT adjustments on derivatives introduce volatility. Analysts advise retail investors to maintain systematic investment plans amidst these crosscurrents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Tumbles Amid Dollar Strength and Fed Policy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Tumbles-Amid-Dollar-Strength-and-Fed-Policy/6980260147db7081af679696</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Tumbles-Amid-Dollar-Strength-and-Fed-Policy/6980260147db7081af679696</guid><description>Gold prices on MCX fell 2.27% to Rs 144,003 per 10 grams on February 2, 2026, pressured by a robust US dollar. Spot gold on Comex dipped to $4,600 before recovering to $4,691 per ounce. The US Federal Reserve maintained its benchmark interest rate, while geopolitical instability continued to swirl globally. Analysts flagged key support levels as traders weighed policy uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:23:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980260147db7081af679695_1770006212083.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 STT Hike Squeezes Arbitrage Fund Returns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Budget-2026-STT-Hike-Squeezes-Arbitrage-Fund-Returns/6980259747db7081af67950b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Budget-2026-STT-Hike-Squeezes-Arbitrage-Fund-Returns/6980259747db7081af67950b</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Budget 2026 introduced a notable increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options, directly impacting the profitability of arbitrage funds. This hike is projected to diminish arbitrage fund returns by an annualized 0.32% to 0.5%, consequently narrowing the post-tax yield differential with liquid funds. Multi-asset allocation funds, however, are expected to experience a minimal impact due to their diversified strategies and lower exposure to pure arbitrage trades.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:21:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980259747db7081af67950a_1770006060219.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: AI, Services Propel Tech-Led Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Budget-2026-AI-Services-Propel-Tech-Led-Growth/6980249847db7081af67921f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Budget-2026-AI-Services-Propel-Tech-Led-Growth/6980249847db7081af67921f</guid><description>Budget 2026 signals a strategic shift towards actionable AI deployment and bolstering the services sector as a primary economic driver. Initiatives focus on enhancing national productivity, broadening economic participation through digital inclusion, and solidifying India's position in emerging technologies like AI and quantum computing. Significant regulatory reforms and tax incentives are introduced to foster global competitiveness, particularly in digital infrastructure and IT services, with specific measures aimed at supporting MSMEs and upskilling the workforce.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:20:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980249847db7081af67921e_1770005948069.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki January Sales Smash Records on Soaring Exports</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-January-Sales-Smash-Records-on-Soaring-Exports/6980258647db7081af679420</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-January-Sales-Smash-Records-on-Soaring-Exports/6980258647db7081af679420</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki India Limited has achieved its highest-ever monthly sales volume in January 2026, selling 236,963 units, a 11.64% year-on-year increase. Exports were the star performer, soaring 88.26% to an all-time high of 51,020 units. Domestic sales saw a marginal growth of 0.34% to 178,300 units.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:18:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mixed Q3 Earnings: Auto, Telecom, Fintech, Agro Sectors Face Investor Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Mixed-Q3-Earnings-Auto-Telecom-Fintech-Agro-Sectors-Face-Investor-Scrutiny/698019fd47db7081af677a24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Mixed-Q3-Earnings-Auto-Telecom-Fintech-Agro-Sectors-Face-Investor-Scrutiny/698019fd47db7081af677a24</guid><description>The February 2nd earnings calendar features Hyundai Motor India, Indus Towers, PB Fintech, and UPL. Hyundai projects steady operating gains, while Indus Towers faces margin pressures. PB Fintech anticipates robust year-on-year growth, contrasting with UPL's expected profit decline. These results will shape market sentiment as the Q3 reporting season unfolds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698019fd47db7081af677a23_1770005169172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Inc's Q3 Earnings Blitz: 650+ Firms, SBI, Airtel, Tata Steel Face Results Gauntlet</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Incs-Q3-Earnings-Blitz-650-Firms-SBI-Airtel-Tata-Steel-Face-Results-Gauntlet/698022ca47db7081af678ec0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Incs-Q3-Earnings-Blitz-650-Firms-SBI-Airtel-Tata-Steel-Face-Results-Gauntlet/698022ca47db7081af678ec0</guid><description>Hundreds of Indian companies, including giants like State Bank of India, Bharti Airtel, and Tata Steel, will unveil their third-quarter financial results this week, from February 2 to 7. Investors are poised to scrutinize revenue, profit margins, and management outlook for insights into industry trends and economic health. This earnings wave, featuring over 650 firms, follows recent market debuts like Bharat Coking Coal Ltd. and could significantly influence stock valuations and sector performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:06:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>VBL Q4 Earnings: Investors Eye Growth Amid Cost Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VBL-Q4-Earnings-Investors-Eye-Growth-Amid-Cost-Pressures/698022ba47db7081af678dc0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VBL-Q4-Earnings-Investors-Eye-Growth-Amid-Cost-Pressures/698022ba47db7081af678dc0</guid><description>Varun Beverages Ltd. is set to unveil its Q4 and full-year CY25 financial results on February 3, 2026. Investors will scrutinize revenue growth, operating margins, and net profit, closely monitoring volume trends and cost pressures. The board will also consider a final dividend proposal. The company’s stock has experienced a notable decline over recent months, facing headwinds despite a recent uptick. This report analyzes the upcoming results against the company's operational context and recent market performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:06:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Record Borrowing Fuels Bond Yield Surge, Tests Rupee</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Record-Borrowing-Fuels-Bond-Yield-Surge-Tests-Rupee/6980224447db7081af678c48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Record-Borrowing-Fuels-Bond-Yield-Surge-Tests-Rupee/6980224447db7081af678c48</guid><description>New Delhi's Union Budget has announced a record gross borrowing target of ₹17.2 lakh crore for the upcoming fiscal year, an 18% increase and above market expectations. This surge in debt supply is immediately pressuring bond yields, pushing the benchmark 10-year government security towards one-year highs. Concurrently, the Indian rupee faces vulnerability, despite modest gains at Monday's open, as the Reserve Bank of India intervenes offshore to stabilize the currency amidst ongoing liquidity concerns and capital flow weakness.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:04:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Metal Stocks Plunge Amid Global Commodity Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Stocks-Plunge-Amid-Global-Commodity-Slump/69801e7d47db7081af6786e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Stocks-Plunge-Amid-Global-Commodity-Slump/69801e7d47db7081af6786e5</guid><description>The Nifty Metal index is leading a broader market sell-off, with key constituents like Vedanta, Hindustan Zinc, and Hindustan Copper experiencing significant market cap erosion. This downturn mirrors global commodity weakness, including sharp declines in copper prices, and is exacerbated by turmoil in China's metals trading sector and a strengthening US dollar.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:02:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69801e7d47db7081af6786e4_1770004802922.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MTAR Q3 Earnings Beat: Precision Engineer Rides Sector Tailwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MTAR-Q3-Earnings-Beat-Precision-Engineer-Rides-Sector-Tailwinds/6980206147db7081af6789d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MTAR-Q3-Earnings-Beat-Precision-Engineer-Rides-Sector-Tailwinds/6980206147db7081af6789d6</guid><description>MTAR Technologies posted a strong third quarter for fiscal year 2026, with consolidated revenue surging 59.3% year-on-year to Rs 278 crore and EBITDA increasing 92.5% to Rs 64 crore. Profit after tax also saw a significant jump of 117.3% to Rs 34.7 crore. The company's order book grew to Rs 2,394 crore, bolstered by Rs 1,370 crore in new orders, positioning it well for sustained growth in the clean energy and aerospace sectors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980206147db7081af6789d5_1770004644276.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dividend Surge: 12 Stocks Go Ex-Dividend Feb 3; Top Payouts Revealed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dividend-Surge-12-Stocks-Go-Ex-Dividend-Feb-3-Top-Payouts-Revealed/69801e9347db7081af6787aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dividend-Surge-12-Stocks-Go-Ex-Dividend-Feb-3-Top-Payouts-Revealed/69801e9347db7081af6787aa</guid><description>Investors are eyeing multiple dividend payouts as five stocks, including Cochin Shipyard and Garden Reach Shipbuilders, prepare to trade ex-dividend on February 3, 2026. These companies, along with seven others like BPCL and Balkrishna Industries, are set to reward shareholders. Garden Reach Shipbuilders declared the highest interim dividend of ₹7.15 per share.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:56:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69801e9347db7081af6787a9_1770004571501.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China Manufacturing PMI Diverges Amid Economic Weakness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/China-Manufacturing-PMI-Diverges-Amid-Economic-Weakness/69801e0b47db7081af67859f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/China-Manufacturing-PMI-Diverges-Amid-Economic-Weakness/69801e0b47db7081af67859f</guid><description>China's manufacturing sector presented conflicting signals in January 2026. The RatingDog private PMI rose slightly to 50.3, suggesting expansion driven by robust exports, while the official PMI fell into contraction at 49.3. This divergence highlights underlying domestic demand weakness, property sector woes, and a cautious government approach to stimulus, despite strong export performance and China's role as a major contributor to global growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Prices Plummet Amid Fed Fears &amp; Budget Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Prices-Plummet-Amid-Fed-Fears-and-Budget-Uncertainty/69801c2a47db7081af67836e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Prices-Plummet-Amid-Fed-Fears-and-Budget-Uncertainty/69801c2a47db7081af67836e</guid><description>Precious metals markets saw dramatic price swings on February 2, 2026. Silver experienced a sharp recovery after a significant daily drop, while gold also saw sharp declines and subsequent rebounds. These movements followed U.S. President Donald Trump's nomination of Kevin Warsh as Federal Reserve Chair, which strengthened the dollar, and the Union Budget 2026, which maintained existing gold import duties. Investors reacted to global developments, profit-taking, and market uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69801c2a47db7081af67836d_1770003896105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: Stability Favors Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Stability-Favors-Investors/6980199947db7081af67779a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Stability-Favors-Investors/6980199947db7081af67779a</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 signals a period of welcome calm for India's personal finance sector, prioritizing consolidation over sweeping reforms. This shift offers investors predictable conditions, allowing for continued long-term wealth creation strategies like Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs). Key fiscal adjustments include an increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on equity derivatives and a tightening of capital gains tax exemptions for Sovereign Gold Bonds (SGBs).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980199947db7081af677799_1770003118738.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto: Q3 Surge Meets Mixed Analyst Views</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Q3-Surge-Meets-Mixed-Analyst-Views/698019cc47db7081af6778ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Q3-Surge-Meets-Mixed-Analyst-Views/698019cc47db7081af6778ef</guid><description>Bajaj Auto posted landmark third-quarter results, with consolidated net profit jumping 25% to ₹2,749 crore and revenue rising 23% to ₹16,204 crore. A strong rebound in exports, crossing 600,000 units, underpinned this performance. Despite the robust financials, analysts remain bifurcated, with some maintaining 'Buy' ratings and others expressing caution due to persistent domestic motorcycle market share erosion and high valuations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:30:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698019cc47db7081af6778ee_1770003012953.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Siliguri-Varanasi Rail Corridor Included, Regional Tourism Feels Ignored</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Siliguri-Varanasi-Rail-Corridor-Included-Regional-Tourism-Feels-Ignored/6980197b47db7081af677676</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Siliguri-Varanasi-Rail-Corridor-Included-Regional-Tourism-Feels-Ignored/6980197b47db7081af677676</guid><description>The Union Budget unveiled plans for seven high-speed rail corridors, including a key link connecting Siliguri to Varanasi. While this infrastructure development is seen as a growth driver for North Bengal, tourism stakeholders expressed disappointment over the lack of specific schemes for the region, particularly concerning Buddhist circuits and mountain trails. Other national tourism initiatives were announced, but their direct benefit to Bengal remains uncertain.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's FY27 Budget: Capex Surge, Defense Hike Amid Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-Budget-Capex-Surge-Defense-Hike-Amid-Global-Headwinds/6980195947db7081af6775bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-Budget-Capex-Surge-Defense-Hike-Amid-Global-Headwinds/6980195947db7081af6775bb</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 allocates a record ₹53.47 lakh crore in total outlays, with capital expenditure reaching ₹12.2 lakh crore and defense spending hitting ₹7.85 lakh crore. This strategy anchors growth through asset creation and enhances economic security against global trade friction and protectionism, aiming for domestic resilience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Budget: Fiscal Centralization Fuels Economic Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Fiscal-Centralization-Fuels-Economic-Strain/6980186f47db7081af6771ab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Fiscal-Centralization-Fuels-Economic-Strain/6980186f47db7081af6771ab</guid><description>The recent Indian Union Budget critically fails to address entrenched economic challenges like inequality and unemployment. Instead, it deepens fiscal centralization, placing significant financial burdens on states through reduced transfers and altered employment scheme funding. This approach prioritizes a controlled public narrative over substantive economic reforms, raising concerns about federal balance and long-term growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980186f47db7081af6771aa_1770002715207.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Cuts TCS, Extends Key Tax Filing Deadlines</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Cuts-TCS-Extends-Key-Tax-Filing-Deadlines/698018ff47db7081af67740a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Cuts-TCS-Extends-Key-Tax-Filing-Deadlines/698018ff47db7081af67740a</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 unveiled changes to tax compliance, notably reducing Tax Collected at Source (TCS) rates on overseas tour packages and Liberalised Remittance Scheme (LRS) remittances. The budget also extends the income tax return (ITR) filing due date for specific business entities and increases the window for filing revised returns, aiming to ease the compliance burden for taxpayers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Market Plunges Amid Growth Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Market-Plunges-Amid-Growth-Fears/698018e247db7081af677312</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Market-Plunges-Amid-Growth-Fears/698018e247db7081af677312</guid><description>Investor confidence faltered significantly post the Union Budget 2026-27, prompting the benchmark Sensex to drop over 1500 points. Analysts point to an alarming credibility gap, fueled by optimistic growth projections amidst a volatile global climate and unaddressed structural economic issues. The budget’s heavy reliance on government capital expenditure, coupled with a lack of clarity on private sector revival and cautious fiscal measures, has investors reassessing the nation's growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Launches Banking Sector Overhaul for Future Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Launches-Banking-Sector-Overhaul-for-Future-Growth/698017f147db7081af677050</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Launches-Banking-Sector-Overhaul-for-Future-Growth/698017f147db7081af677050</guid><description>India's Finance Minister has proposed a comprehensive review of the banking sector through a 'Viksit Bharat' committee, aiming to align it with the nation's next growth phase. This initiative is coupled with the restructuring of public sector NBFCs Power Finance Corporation (PFC) and Rural Electrification Corporation (REC) to enhance scale and efficiency. Additionally, a review of Foreign Exchange Management (Non-debt Instruments) Rules is planned to modernize foreign investment frameworks. These moves build on the banking sector's current strength, marked by robust balance sheets and high profitability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Growth Bets, Sector Support, Mixed Citizen Reaction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Growth-Bets-Sector-Support-Mixed-Citizen-Reaction/6980177447db7081af676ef7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Growth-Bets-Sector-Support-Mixed-Citizen-Reaction/6980177447db7081af676ef7</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 unveils a growth-centric agenda with a significant capital expenditure push and targeted support for manufacturing and MSMEs. While healthcare sees concessions and senior citizens benefit from expanded schemes, the salaried middle class and affordable housing sector express mixed sentiments, highlighting a divergence between macro ambitions and immediate personal financial relief. Market volatility marked the budget's release.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Defence Stocks Tumble After Budget Despite Spending Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stocks-Tumble-After-Budget-Despite-Spending-Hike/698016ff47db7081af676da7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stocks-Tumble-After-Budget-Despite-Spending-Hike/698016ff47db7081af676da7</guid><description>Indian defence stocks experienced a significant sell-off on February 1, 2026, immediately following the Union Budget announcement. Despite a substantial 15.2% increase in the defence outlay to ₹7.85 lakh crore for FY27 and a 18% rise in capital procurement, the market reaction was negative. Investors reacted to unmet expectations and a hike in STT on derivatives, leading to a nearly 9% drop in the Nifty India Defence Index. Companies like Bharat Dynamics, Bharat Electronics, and Data Patterns saw notable declines.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Fuels Tier-2/3 Cities with Rs 5K Cr CER Plan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Budget-2026-Fuels-Tier-23-Cities-with-Rs-5K-Cr-CER-Plan/6980160f47db7081af676c20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Budget-2026-Fuels-Tier-23-Cities-with-Rs-5K-Cr-CER-Plan/6980160f47db7081af676c20</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 introduces City Economic Regions (CERs), allocating ₹5,000 crore over five years to stimulate development in Tier-2 and Tier-3 cities and temple towns. This strategic initiative aims to decentralize economic activity and real estate demand away from congested metros by enhancing infrastructure and fostering region-specific growth drivers like tourism and manufacturing. While welcomed by developers for planned urban expansion, concerns linger over the lack of direct measures for affordable housing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Fiscal Divide Widens: FC16 Report Shifts State Funding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Divide-Widens-FC16-Report-Shifts-State-Funding/6980159c47db7081af676ace</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Divide-Widens-FC16-Report-Shifts-State-Funding/6980159c47db7081af676ace</guid><description>India's 16th Finance Commission has tabled its report, discontinuing grants-in-aid for revenue needs and altering tax devolution criteria. This approach, emphasizing broad-based measures, is projected to disadvantage states with lower fiscal capacity, potentially widening economic disparities across the nation. The shift moves away from granular assessments of individual state needs towards a more aggregated, less targeted fiscal transfer mechanism.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Plunge; Indian Equities Reel from Budget Tax Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Plunge-Indian-Equities-Reel-from-Budget-Tax-Hike/6980142e47db7081af67688d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Plunge-Indian-Equities-Reel-from-Budget-Tax-Hike/6980142e47db7081af67688d</guid><description>Precious metals experienced sharp declines on February 2, 2026, as fears surrounding a potential hawkish Federal Reserve nominee and profit-taking gripped markets. Simultaneously, Indian equity indices Sensex and Nifty suffered significant losses following the Union Budget, primarily due to a proposed increase in Securities Transaction Tax on derivatives, signaling continued market volatility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:04:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Brokerage Bets on ICICI Bank, APL Apollo for 2026 Growth Amid Budget Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerage-Bets-on-ICICI-Bank-APL-Apollo-for-2026-Growth-Amid-Budget-Volatility/6980136547db7081af6766b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerage-Bets-on-ICICI-Bank-APL-Apollo-for-2026-Growth-Amid-Budget-Volatility/6980136547db7081af6766b4</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services has named ICICI Bank and APL Apollo Tubes as its top stock recommendations for the trading week commencing February 2, 2026. The bank's selection hinges on its robust franchise and sustained profitability outlook, while APL Apollo Tubes is favored for its market leadership and aggressive expansion strategy in the steel tubes sector. Both companies face varying market sentiments influenced by the recent Union Budget and broader economic conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:04:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980136547db7081af6766b3_1770001339403.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Inc Gears Up for Q3FY26 Earnings Wave</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Inc-Gears-Up-for-Q3FY26-Earnings-Wave/698012c747db7081af67648a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Inc-Gears-Up-for-Q3FY26-Earnings-Wave/698012c747db7081af67648a</guid><description>Approximately 75 Indian companies, including major players such as Hyundai Motor India (via parent company), Tata Chemicals, and Mahindra Lifespace Developers, are scheduled to report their Q3FY26 financial results on February 2, 2026. The market will be scrutinizing revenue, profit margins, and overall business performance from the October-December 2025 quarter to assess corporate health and gauge broader sectoral trends. Post-announcement conference calls are anticipated for deeper dives into company outlooks and management strategies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698012c747db7081af676489_1770001265754.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Meets Deficit Target Via Capex Cuts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Meets-Deficit-Target-Via-Capex-Cuts/6980134547db7081af6765e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Meets-Deficit-Target-Via-Capex-Cuts/6980134547db7081af6765e9</guid><description>The Indian government successfully met its fiscal deficit target of 4.4% of GDP for FY2025-26. This achievement was primarily engineered through substantial cuts in overall expenditure, particularly capital investment, rather than robust tax collections. Tax revenues missed their target by over Rs 1.6 lakh crore, with GST collections declining. While non-tax revenues offered some relief, the reduction in capital expenditure, including grants to states, lowered effective capital spending and compromised the quality of fiscal management.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Market Sours on Borrowing, Tax Hikes; Focus on Semiconductors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Market-Sours-on-Borrowing-Tax-Hikes-Focus-on-Semiconductors/69800d4b47db7081af67576b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Market-Sours-on-Borrowing-Tax-Hikes-Focus-on-Semiconductors/69800d4b47db7081af67576b</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 saw a sharp market sell-off on Budget Day, with the Sensex and Nifty closing significantly lower amidst investor concerns over increased Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives and higher government borrowing plans. While analysts acknowledged the preservation of fiscal credibility and a strategic pivot towards semiconductors and manufacturing, the market's immediate reaction underscored apprehension regarding liquidity and yield pressures. The budget targets a fiscal deficit of 4.3% for FY27, aims for 10% nominal GDP growth, and significantly boosts capital expenditure, but the scale of gross borrowing has raised eyebrows.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69800d4b47db7081af67576a_1770001152310.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>