<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:47:59 +0000</pubDate><item><title>ITI Ltd Auditors Issue Disclaimer, Cast Doubt on Going Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ITI-Ltd-Auditors-Issue-Disclaimer-Cast-Doubt-on-Going-Concern/698f1a613b0d8ca62d852c75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ITI-Ltd-Auditors-Issue-Disclaimer-Cast-Doubt-on-Going-Concern/698f1a613b0d8ca62d852c75</guid><description>ITI Limited reported a steep 50.27% year-on-year revenue decline for Q3 FY26, plunging to ₹514.65 Cr. Crucially, statutory auditors issued a "Disclaimer of Conclusion" on the financial results, citing insufficient evidence and highlighting a "material uncertainty" regarding the company's going concern status. Despite a ₹18,546 Cr order book and government revival plan, audit qualifications cite issues across revenue recognition, receivables, inventory, and compliance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:34:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f1a613b0d8ca62d852c74.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MFS Intercorp Q3: Revenue Vanishes, Losses Surge 11X</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/MFS-Intercorp-Q3-Revenue-Vanishes-Losses-Surge-11X/698f19d53b0d8ca62d8528d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/MFS-Intercorp-Q3-Revenue-Vanishes-Losses-Surge-11X/698f19d53b0d8ca62d8528d6</guid><description>MFS Intercorp Limited reported a disastrous Q3 FY26, with revenue from operations plummeting 100% YoY to ₹0.00 lakhs. Despite a 48.07% jump in expenses, the company swung to a net loss of ₹-9.91 lakhs from a smaller loss last year. The nine-month period mirrors this decline, showing ₹0.00 revenue and a substantial net loss of ₹-28.14 lakhs, wiping out prior year's marginal profit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:32:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f19d53b0d8ca62d8528d5_1770986090993.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mirza International Acquires German Firm for Global Footwear Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mirza-International-Acquires-German-Firm-for-Global-Footwear-Expansion/698f193e3b0d8ca62d852480</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mirza-International-Acquires-German-Firm-for-Global-Footwear-Expansion/698f193e3b0d8ca62d852480</guid><description>Mirza International Limited has acquired Genesis Brands UG in Germany, establishing it as a wholly-owned subsidiary. This strategic move aims to penetrate and expand the company's presence in the global footwear retail marketing and e-commerce business, enhancing its international footprint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:29:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f193e3b0d8ca62d85247f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VMS Industries Revenue Collapses 91%, Profit Surges 653% Amid Reporting Glitch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VMS-Industries-Revenue-Collapses-91percent-Profit-Surges-653percent-Amid-Reporting-Glitch/698f18dc28145bb675ed3e5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VMS-Industries-Revenue-Collapses-91percent-Profit-Surges-653percent-Amid-Reporting-Glitch/698f18dc28145bb675ed3e5b</guid><description>VMS Industries Limited reported a stark Q3 FY26, with revenue from operations plummeting 91.33% YoY to ₹29.1 Cr. Despite this, net profit surged 653.71% YoY to ₹26.5 Cr, primarily boosted by a tax credit. However, the company flagged an inconsistency in its total income calculation, raising governance concerns. No future guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:28:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f18dc28145bb675ed3e5a_1770985916918.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Arman Holdings Posts Huge Q3 Profit Turnaround, Eyes Diversification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Arman-Holdings-Posts-Huge-Q3-Profit-Turnaround-Eyes-Diversification/698f186c28145bb675ed3b81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Arman-Holdings-Posts-Huge-Q3-Profit-Turnaround-Eyes-Diversification/698f186c28145bb675ed3b81</guid><description>Arman Holdings achieved a dramatic Q3 FY26 turnaround, posting ₹42.29 Lakhs profit before tax compared to a loss last year, with revenue jumping to ₹109.91 Lakhs. The company also revealed plans to significantly diversify into IT, AI, communications, and chemicals by amending its MOA/AOA, signaling a major strategic pivot. With zero outstanding debt, the company is poised for its ambitious expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:26:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f186c28145bb675ed3b80_1770985940392.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SPML Infra Consortium Wins ₹344 Cr Chennai Water Supply Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SPML-Infra-Consortium-Wins-344-Cr-Chennai-Water-Supply-Project/698f17c528145bb675ed36be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SPML-Infra-Consortium-Wins-344-Cr-Chennai-Water-Supply-Project/698f17c528145bb675ed36be</guid><description>SPML Infra, in a consortium with JWIL Infra and Vishnusurya Projects, has been awarded a ₹344.64 crore project by the Chennai Metropolitan Water Supply and Sewerage Board (CMWSSB). The project involves implementing continuous water supply for two Water Distribution Stations under the AMRUT scheme in Chennai. Management highlighted a strategic focus on essential urban services and leveraging expertise in water infrastructure. This order bolsters the company's position in executing complex water projects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:23:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f17c528145bb675ed36bd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CSL Finance Q3 Profit Up 24.7% YoY, But QoQ Earnings Dip Amid RBI Impairment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CSL-Finance-Q3-Profit-Up-247percent-YoY-But-QoQ-Earnings-Dip-Amid-RBI-Impairment/698f17c028145bb675ed367a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CSL-Finance-Q3-Profit-Up-247percent-YoY-But-QoQ-Earnings-Dip-Amid-RBI-Impairment/698f17c028145bb675ed367a</guid><description>CSL Finance Limited posted a strong 24.72% YoY rise in standalone PAT to ₹20.92 Cr for the December quarter. Total income grew 20% YoY to ₹64.44 Cr. However, sequential profits saw a decline, with QoQ PAT down 14.49%. The company also recognized an additional impairment charge due to revised RBI provisioning norms for project finance exposures. Mr. Ayuush Mittaal was appointed as Internal Auditor.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:23:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f17c028145bb675ed3679.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vistar Amar Q3 Profit Surges 656% YoY, Turns Profitable on Massive Revenue Jump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Vistar-Amar-Q3-Profit-Surges-656percent-YoY-Turns-Profitable-on-Massive-Revenue-Jump/698f17a928145bb675ed35cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Vistar-Amar-Q3-Profit-Surges-656percent-YoY-Turns-Profitable-on-Massive-Revenue-Jump/698f17a928145bb675ed35cd</guid><description>Vistar Amar Limited reported a spectacular Q3 FY26, with revenue from operations soaring 656.3% year-on-year to ₹6,592.67 Lacs. The company achieved a significant turnaround from net losses in the prior year periods to a net profit of ₹646.82 Lacs for the quarter and ₹710.09 Lacs for the nine months. EPS also swung from negative to positive, ₹11.23 for Q3 FY26.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:23:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f17a928145bb675ed35cc_1770985897134.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBCC Profit Surges 53% Amidst Governance Woes, Property Disputes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCC-Profit-Surges-53percent-Amidst-Governance-Woes-Property-Disputes/698f16d9d841cb02bc18c4a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCC-Profit-Surges-53percent-Amidst-Governance-Woes-Property-Disputes/698f16d9d841cb02bc18c4a5</guid><description>NBCC India's Q3 FY26 profits surged significantly YoY, with standalone net profit up 52.88% and consolidated up 38.46%, boosted by revenue growth and an ₹8,015.53 Lakh exceptional item reversal. Despite this, the company faces critical governance issues, including a lack of required independent directors, and a multitude of property-related legal disputes, project holds, and significant provisions, casting a shadow over its future prospects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:19:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f16d9d841cb02bc18c4a4_1770985254799.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VMS Industries: Q3 Revenue Surges 767% but Profits Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VMS-Industries-Q3-Revenue-Surges-767percent-but-Profits-Plunge/698f1635d841cb02bc18c05f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VMS-Industries-Q3-Revenue-Surges-767percent-but-Profits-Plunge/698f1635d841cb02bc18c05f</guid><description>VMS Industries reported a massive 767.6% YoY revenue jump to ₹291.17 Cr in Q3 FY26. However, profitability buckled, with PBT down 94.25% and Net Profit falling 44.26% YoY to ₹26.08 Cr. EPS slid 74.23%. For the nine-month period, revenue decreased 54.7%, but net profit surged 6930% from a low base. The auditor issued a standard limited review report.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:16:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f1635d841cb02bc18c05e_1770985148118.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Arcotech Posts Worsening Loss Amidst Auditor Red Flag on Interest Expense</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Arcotech-Posts-Worsening-Loss-Amidst-Auditor-Red-Flag-on-Interest-Expense/698f1603d841cb02bc18bf06</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Arcotech-Posts-Worsening-Loss-Amidst-Auditor-Red-Flag-on-Interest-Expense/698f1603d841cb02bc18bf06</guid><description>Arcotech Limited reported a significant increase in net loss for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹811.91 Lakhs, up from ₹744.58 Lakhs YoY. Total income remains negligible, largely comprising 'other income', while finance costs surged nearly 20% YoY. A critical red flag emerged from the auditor's report identifying a substantial understatement of interest expense, alongside notes indicating business restructuring is under consideration by lenders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:16:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f1603d841cb02bc18bf05_1770985129545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BN Agrochem PAT Plummets 98% Despite Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/BN-Agrochem-PAT-Plummets-98percent-Despite-Revenue-Surge/698f157ed841cb02bc18ba71</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/BN-Agrochem-PAT-Plummets-98percent-Despite-Revenue-Surge/698f157ed841cb02bc18ba71</guid><description>BN Agrochem Limited reported a stark divergence in its Q3 FY26 results. While consolidated revenue from operations surged by an impressive 830.52% year-on-year to ₹792.72 Crores, Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeted by 97.81% to just ₹0.88 Crores. Standalone revenue also grew significantly by 168.40% to ₹68.79 Crores, but standalone PAT collapsed by 95.85% to ₹0.75 Crores. The sharp decline in profitability is partly attributed to a significant tax credit of ₹17.81 Crores booked in the previous year's standalone quarter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:13:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f157ed841cb02bc18ba70.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lasa Supergenics Operations Halted Post-Fire, Faces Uncertain Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Lasa-Supergenics-Operations-Halted-Post-Fire-Faces-Uncertain-Future/698f1521d841cb02bc18b87c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Lasa-Supergenics-Operations-Halted-Post-Fire-Faces-Uncertain-Future/698f1521d841cb02bc18b87c</guid><description>Lasa Supergenics Limited's production remains shut following a major fire on May 18, 2025, that destroyed its primary factory. The company has declared an inability to restart manufacturing due to uninsured losses and pending statutory clearances. Management is exploring contract manufacturing or leasing facilities as alternatives. The auditor's limited review report highlights significant issues, raising concerns about going concern uncertainty and revenue recognition impacted by force majeure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:12:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f1521d841cb02bc18b87b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sunflag Iron Q3: Revenue Up, Cons. Profit Surges, Standalone Profit Plummets.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sunflag-Iron-Q3-Revenue-Up-Cons-Profit-Surges-Standalone-Profit-Plummets/698f1492d841cb02bc18b35a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sunflag-Iron-Q3-Revenue-Up-Cons-Profit-Surges-Standalone-Profit-Plummets/698f1492d841cb02bc18b35a</guid><description>Sunflag Iron &amp; Steel reported Q3 FY26 results with consolidated revenue up 5.66% YoY to ₹942.47 Cr and consolidated net profit soaring 65.93% to ₹59.94 Cr. However, standalone net profit plunged 60.31% YoY to ₹11.67 Cr. A substantial consolidated loss of ₹2183.59 Cr was also recorded due to mark-to-market adjustments on equity investments, alongside an ₹8.70 Cr exceptional loss from labor code changes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:09:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f1492d841cb02bc18b359_1770984803508.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Advance Multitech Posts ₹1 Cr Loss Despite 50% Income Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Advance-Multitech-Posts-1-Cr-Loss-Despite-50percent-Income-Surge/698f1467d841cb02bc18b24a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Advance-Multitech-Posts-1-Cr-Loss-Despite-50percent-Income-Surge/698f1467d841cb02bc18b24a</guid><description>Advance Multitech Limited reported a stark contrast in its Q3 FY26 results, with total income climbing 50.44% YoY to ₹1.04 Cr. However, profitability deteriorated significantly, showing a net loss of ₹1.09 Cr against a profit of ₹0.51 Cr in the prior year. The nine-month period also saw an increased net loss. Despite revenue growth, the company faces substantial profitability challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:09:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f1467d841cb02bc18b249_1770984839226.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HEM Holdings Posts Stellar Q3 Profit Growth, Revenue Surges 189%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/HEM-Holdings-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Profit-Growth-Revenue-Surges-189percent/698f1462d841cb02bc18b1e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/HEM-Holdings-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Profit-Growth-Revenue-Surges-189percent/698f1462d841cb02bc18b1e9</guid><description>HEM Holdings &amp; Trading Limited announced robust Q3 FY26 results, posting a 235.23% YoY jump in net profit to ₹20.08 Lakhs on revenue growth of 189.34% to ₹20.71 Lakhs. The company also achieved a significant turnaround for the nine-month period, swinging from a net loss of ₹(120.30) Lakhs to a profit of ₹55.36 Lakhs. Expenses were down substantially year-on-year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:09:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f1462d841cb02bc18b1e8_1770984721479.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kuantum Papers Plans 735 Cr Capex, Targets 1800 Cr FY27 Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kuantum-Papers-Plans-735-Cr-Capex-Targets-1800-Cr-FY27-Revenue/698f14320fdad2110059538a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kuantum-Papers-Plans-735-Cr-Capex-Targets-1800-Cr-FY27-Revenue/698f14320fdad2110059538a</guid><description>Kuantum Papers reported Q3 FY26 results with 4% sequential revenue growth to INR 290 Crores and a 14% QoQ EBITDA increase to INR 39 Crores, boosting margins. The company outlined a significant INR 735 Crore capex plan for capacity expansion, including upgrades to PM 2 and PM 3. Management targets an annualized revenue run rate of INR 1,800 Crores and INR 300 Crores EBITDA by FY27, signaling aggressive growth ambitions amidst industry revival expectations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:08:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f14320fdad21100595389_1770984651526.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Murudeshwar Ceramics Q3 Profit Skyrockets 145% Driven by Other Income Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Murudeshwar-Ceramics-Q3-Profit-Skyrockets-145percent-Driven-by-Other-Income-Surge/698f134148d8f5c5fee63367</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Murudeshwar-Ceramics-Q3-Profit-Skyrockets-145percent-Driven-by-Other-Income-Surge/698f134148d8f5c5fee63367</guid><description>Murudeshwar Ceramics reported a massive 145% YoY surge in consolidated net profit to ₹409.40 Cr for Q3 FY26. The stellar growth was primarily fueled by an extraordinary 859% YoY jump in 'Other Income' to ₹403.82 Cr. While core revenue grew modestly by 1.92%, expenses rose 10.89%, making the non-operational income the critical driver for the bottom line. Basic EPS climbed 142.86% YoY to ₹0.68.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:04:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f134148d8f5c5fee63366.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SPL Industries Profit Soars on Tax Credit, Revenue Plummets 45%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/SPL-Industries-Profit-Soars-on-Tax-Credit-Revenue-Plummets-45percent/698f133e48d8f5c5fee6334c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/SPL-Industries-Profit-Soars-on-Tax-Credit-Revenue-Plummets-45percent/698f133e48d8f5c5fee6334c</guid><description>SPL Industries reported a staggering 690.9% YoY jump in Net Profit to ₹238.42 Cr for Q3 FY26, largely due to a ₹208.60 Cr deferred tax credit. However, core operations faltered, with Revenue From Operation plummeting 45.2% YoY to ₹1,465.09 Cr and the company slipping into a pre-tax loss. Total Comprehensive Income declined 75.6% YoY, flagging underlying financial deterioration despite the Net Profit surge.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:04:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f133e48d8f5c5fee6334b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Purohit Construction Faces Balance Sheet Anomaly, Capital Erosion Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Purohit-Construction-Faces-Balance-Sheet-Anomaly-Capital-Erosion-Fears/698f12f948d8f5c5fee62fea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Purohit-Construction-Faces-Balance-Sheet-Anomaly-Capital-Erosion-Fears/698f12f948d8f5c5fee62fea</guid><description>Purohit Construction Limited reported a ₹8.72 Lakhs net profit for Q3 FY26, but a significant ₹9.63 Lakhs net loss for the nine-month period. More alarmingly, the standalone balance sheet as of December 31, 2025, exhibits a critical anomaly where total assets do not reconcile with total liabilities and equity. The company's 'Other Equity' has turned negative at ₹(266.09) Lakhs, signalling substantial capital erosion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:03:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f12f948d8f5c5fee62fe9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Switching Tech Bleeds Losses, Net Worth Wiped, Promoter Sells Stake Amid Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Switching-Tech-Bleeds-Losses-Net-Worth-Wiped-Promoter-Sells-Stake-Amid-Pivot/698f128c48d8f5c5fee62dab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Switching-Tech-Bleeds-Losses-Net-Worth-Wiped-Promoter-Sells-Stake-Amid-Pivot/698f128c48d8f5c5fee62dab</guid><description>Switching Technologies Gunther Limited reported a deepening net loss of ₹2.11 Cr in Q3 FY26, a 18.6% YoY deterioration. Revenue slipped 3.9% YoY to ₹1.93 Cr. Accumulated losses have now completely eroded the company's net worth, prompting auditors to flag a 'material uncertainty related to going concern'. Concurrently, a significant event is underway with the proposed sale of a 37.63% promoter stake for ₹2.77 Cr. The company also approved a strategic shift to focus on food processing units.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:01:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f128c48d8f5c5fee62daa.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SPML Infra Secures Rs 344 Cr Chennai Water Project Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SPML-Infra-Secures-Rs-344-Cr-Chennai-Water-Project-Deal/698f124c48d8f5c5fee62b6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SPML-Infra-Secures-Rs-344-Cr-Chennai-Water-Project-Deal/698f124c48d8f5c5fee62b6a</guid><description>SPML Infra, part of a consortium including JWIL Infra and Vishnusurya Projects, has been awarded a Rs 344.64 crore water infrastructure project by the Chennai Metropolitan Water Supply and Sewerage Board (CMWSSB). SPML Infra holds a 26% share in this project under the AMRUT Scheme, which will be executed on a Design, Build, Finance, Operate, and Transfer (DBFOT) model. The company will need to form a Special Purpose Vehicle (SPV) within 30 days.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f124c48d8f5c5fee62b69.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahaalaxmi Texpro Faces Data Glitch; Q3 Results Obscured by Wrong Dates</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Mahaalaxmi-Texpro-Faces-Data-Glitch-Q3-Results-Obscured-by-Wrong-Dates/698f11cd48d8f5c5fee62843</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Mahaalaxmi-Texpro-Faces-Data-Glitch-Q3-Results-Obscured-by-Wrong-Dates/698f11cd48d8f5c5fee62843</guid><description>Mahaalaxmi Texpro's Board approved its Q3 FY25 financial results, but a critical data anomaly has emerged. The disclosed financial tables erroneously display column headers for December 31, 2023, instead of the current reporting period of December 31, 2025. This prevents the reliable extraction of key performance figures, creating significant uncertainty for investors despite a limited review by statutory auditors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:58:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f11cd48d8f5c5fee62842.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Monotype India Q3 Revenue Plunges 58.7%, Posts Quarterly Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Monotype-India-Q3-Revenue-Plunges-587percent-Posts-Quarterly-Loss/698f11c048d8f5c5fee62713</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Monotype-India-Q3-Revenue-Plunges-587percent-Posts-Quarterly-Loss/698f11c048d8f5c5fee62713</guid><description>Monotype India Ltd reported a grim Q3 FY26 with revenue from operations plummeting 58.7% YoY and QoQ to ₹20.42 Cr. The company posted a net loss of ₹0.07 Cr for the quarter. Despite a ₹5.94 Cr profit for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, the sharp quarterly downturn raises concerns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:57:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f11c048d8f5c5fee62712.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sanghvi Movers Expands to KSA, Eyes Margin Boost Amid Wind EPC Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sanghvi-Movers-Expands-to-KSA-Eyes-Margin-Boost-Amid-Wind-EPC-Dip/698f10df48d8f5c5fee61f09</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sanghvi-Movers-Expands-to-KSA-Eyes-Margin-Boost-Amid-Wind-EPC-Dip/698f10df48d8f5c5fee61f09</guid><description>Sanghvi Movers reported ~INR 720 cr revenue in Q3 FY26, buoyed by strong demand and aggressive geographical expansion into KSA and Botswana. The company outlined a substantial INR 629 cr FY26 capex plan and targets fleet utilization of 75-80%. However, the Wind EPC segment saw sharp degrowth, and exceptional items impacted results. Management anticipates margin normalization and improvement from FY27.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:54:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f10df48d8f5c5fee61f08.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharatam Ventures Q3 Loss Widens Sharply Amid Revenue Collapse &amp; Data Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Bharatam-Ventures-Q3-Loss-Widens-Sharply-Amid-Revenue-Collapse-and-Data-Scrutiny/698f107d48d8f5c5fee61c03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Bharatam-Ventures-Q3-Loss-Widens-Sharply-Amid-Revenue-Collapse-and-Data-Scrutiny/698f107d48d8f5c5fee61c03</guid><description>Bharatam Ventures reported dismal Q3 FY26 results, with standalone revenue plunging 61% YoY to ₹0.95 Lakhs and net loss ballooning to ₹104.75 Lakhs. Consolidated revenue fell 18% YoY to ₹1.98 Lakhs, while net loss widened to ₹135.25 Lakhs. The company's reliance on unreviewed subsidiary data for consolidated reporting raises governance concerns, despite auditors deeming it immaterial. No outlook was provided.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:52:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f107d48d8f5c5fee61c02.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hubtown Qualified Audit: Profit Overstated as Firm Plans ₹600 Cr Fundraise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Hubtown-Qualified-Audit-Profit-Overstated-as-Firm-Plans-600-Cr-Fundraise/698f0fde48d8f5c5fee616e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Hubtown-Qualified-Audit-Profit-Overstated-as-Firm-Plans-600-Cr-Fundraise/698f0fde48d8f5c5fee616e2</guid><description>Hubtown Limited disclosed Q3 FY26 results showing a 42.4% YoY revenue drop standalone, yet a 70.8% Net Profit increase. Crucially, the statutory auditor qualified the report due to unprovided interest on inter-corporate deposits, potentially overstating profits. The company also announced plans to raise up to ₹6,000 million (₹600 Crores) via equity and debt instruments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:49:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0fde48d8f5c5fee616e1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Diffusion Engineers Surges on Strong Q3 Earnings and Expansion Plans</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diffusion-Engineers-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Earnings-and-Expansion-Plans/698f0f9348d8f5c5fee61556</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diffusion-Engineers-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Earnings-and-Expansion-Plans/698f0f9348d8f5c5fee61556</guid><description>Diffusion Engineers reported a strong Q3 FY'26 with revenue up 27.31% YoY to ₹100.82 Cr and PAT soaring 69.14% to ₹12.01 Cr. The company targets accelerated 25% revenue growth from FY'27 with new capacities, aiming for a ₹600 Cr topline and 15-16% EBITDA margins. Strategic investments include a 10% stake in an aerospace firm and new railway contracts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:48:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0f9348d8f5c5fee61555.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CCI Fines Intel ₹27.38 Crore for Warranty Abuse in India</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CCI-Fines-Intel-2738-Crore-for-Warranty-Abuse-in-India/698f0efa48d8f5c5fee61086</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CCI-Fines-Intel-2738-Crore-for-Warranty-Abuse-in-India/698f0efa48d8f5c5fee61086</guid><description>The Competition Commission of India (CCI) has slapped a ₹27.38 crore penalty on Intel Corporation. The tech giant abused its dominant market position for PC microprocessors by imposing an unfair, India-specific warranty policy. This discriminatory practice denied warranty services to Indian consumers for genuine processors bought overseas, sparking a probe and a significant ruling on market dominance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:46:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0efa48d8f5c5fee61085.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Safari Industries Eyes ₹500 Cr QIP Amidst FY25 Profit Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Safari-Industries-Eyes-500-Cr-QIP-Amidst-FY25-Profit-Dip/698f0e4148d8f5c5fee609a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Safari-Industries-Eyes-500-Cr-QIP-Amidst-FY25-Profit-Dip/698f0e4148d8f5c5fee609a3</guid><description>Safari Industries is seeking shareholder approval for a ₹500 Crore Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) to fund long-term growth, capacity expansion, and potential acquisitions. Concurrently, it proposes re-appointing MD Sudhir Jatia for five years, who holds a 44.7% stake. This comes as FY25 PAT declined 24% YoY to ₹117.53 Cr, despite Net Sales rising 14.2% to ₹1,769.66 Cr. The company aims to strengthen its capital base and financial flexibility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:42:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0e4148d8f5c5fee609a2.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fraserand Faces Going Concern Doubt Amidst Auditor Red Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Fraserand-Faces-Going-Concern-Doubt-Amidst-Auditor-Red-Flags/698f0da148d8f5c5fee6040e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Fraserand-Faces-Going-Concern-Doubt-Amidst-Auditor-Red-Flags/698f0da148d8f5c5fee6040e</guid><description>Fraserand Company posted a significant 457.5% YoY revenue growth to ₹0.998 million for Q3 FY26, with net loss reducing 85% YoY. However, expenses surged, widening the loss by 145.9% QoQ and deteriorating EPS. Crucially, the auditor flagged material uncertainty about the company's ability to continue as a going concern, citing accumulated losses, doubtful receivables, unverified payables, and pending lawsuits. Trading on the Calcutta Stock Exchange remains suspended.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:40:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0da148d8f5c5fee6040d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lasa Supergenics Production Halts After Fire; Auditor Flags 'Material Misstatements'.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Lasa-Supergenics-Production-Halts-After-Fire-Auditor-Flags-Material-Misstatements/698f0d4048d8f5c5fee5ff54</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Lasa-Supergenics-Production-Halts-After-Fire-Auditor-Flags-Material-Misstatements/698f0d4048d8f5c5fee5ff54</guid><description>Lasa Supergenics faces a severe operational crisis after a major fire destroyed its Lote Parshuram factory and uninsured inventory, leading to a complete production halt. Management is now exploring contract manufacturing and leasing as alternatives. Auditors have issued a cautionary note, raising significant concerns about potential material misstatements and going concern issues within the accompanying financial statement.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:38:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0d4048d8f5c5fee5ff53.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hind Aluminium Posts Profit Turnaround Amid Auditor Red Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hind-Aluminium-Posts-Profit-Turnaround-Amid-Auditor-Red-Flags/698f0cad48d8f5c5fee5fa8c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hind-Aluminium-Posts-Profit-Turnaround-Amid-Auditor-Red-Flags/698f0cad48d8f5c5fee5fa8c</guid><description>Hind Aluminium Industries Limited reported a Q3 FY26 consolidated net profit of ₹152 Cr, turning around from a ₹80 Cr loss in the prior year. However, the company's statutory auditors issued a qualified review report. Significant data inconsistencies and an anomalous standalone revenue surge of over 90,000% YoY raise serious concerns about financial reporting accuracy and reliability, despite strong standalone nine-month profit growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:36:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0cad48d8f5c5fee5fa8b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Company Profit Soars 322% on Revenue Gain and Labour Code Impact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Company-Profit-Soars-322percent-on-Revenue-Gain-and-Labour-Code-Impact/698f0c2648d8f5c5fee5f51d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Company-Profit-Soars-322percent-on-Revenue-Gain-and-Labour-Code-Impact/698f0c2648d8f5c5fee5f51d</guid><description>The company announced a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated net profit soaring 322.17% YoY to ₹329.73 Lakhs on a 9.69% revenue increase to ₹43,008.61 Lakhs. Standalone figures also show strong recovery, with net profit turning around to ₹631.16 Lakhs from a loss. An exceptional item of ₹500.09 Lakhs, due to new labour codes, significantly boosted Profit Before Tax. Auditors provided an unmodified limited review report.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:33:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0c2648d8f5c5fee5f51c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hariyana Ship-Breakers' 1500% Profit Jump Masks Auditor Alarms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hariyana-Ship-Breakers-1500percent-Profit-Jump-Masks-Auditor-Alarms/698f0bb748d8f5c5fee5f244</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hariyana-Ship-Breakers-1500percent-Profit-Jump-Masks-Auditor-Alarms/698f0bb748d8f5c5fee5f244</guid><description>Hariyana Ship-Breakers reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with standalone PAT leaping 1509% YoY to ₹681.89 Lakhs, driven by a 258% surge in Other Income and a 20% drop in expenses. However, the company faces severe investor risks and governance concerns. Auditors flagged substantial unrecovered real estate advances, significant loans to related parties with recoverability doubts, and reliance on unreviewed associate data, casting a shadow over the reported profits.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:32:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0bb748d8f5c5fee5f243.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hubtown Flagged for Unprovided Interest, Plans ₹600 Cr Fundraise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Hubtown-Flagged-for-Unprovided-Interest-Plans-600-Cr-Fundraise/698f0b9c48d8f5c5fee5f121</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Hubtown-Flagged-for-Unprovided-Interest-Plans-600-Cr-Fundraise/698f0b9c48d8f5c5fee5f121</guid><description>Hubtown Limited reported mixed Q3 FY26 results with a significant YoY jump in Net Profit for both standalone (+70.8%) and consolidated (+54.0%) financials. However, statutory auditors noted that interest amounting to ₹56.95 Cr for nine months on inter-corporate deposits was not provided, potentially understating finance costs and overstating profits. The company plans to raise up to ₹6,000 million (₹600 crore) via QIP or preferential allotment, subject to approvals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:31:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0b9c48d8f5c5fee5f120.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Labour Codes Strain IT Margins, But Salary Hikes Hold Steady</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Labour-Codes-Strain-IT-Margins-But-Salary-Hikes-Hold-Steady/698f0ab148d8f5c5fee5e93c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Labour-Codes-Strain-IT-Margins-But-Salary-Hikes-Hold-Steady/698f0ab148d8f5c5fee5e93c</guid><description>India's new labour codes, effective November 2025, are raising company costs for benefits like gratuity and bonus due to revised wage definitions. While overall salary hikes are projected to remain stable at around 9%, the IT sector and other margin-sensitive segments may see moderated increments. Companies are absorbing these costs or setting aside separate budgets, prioritizing talent retention to avoid attrition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:27:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0ab148d8f5c5fee5e93b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Prices Surge ₹1,044; Check 18K, 22K, 24K Rates in Your City</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Surge-1044-Check-18K-22K-24K-Rates-in-Your-City/698f0aaa48d8f5c5fee5e934</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Surge-1044-Check-18K-22K-24K-Rates-in-Your-City/698f0aaa48d8f5c5fee5e934</guid><description>Gold futures rallied on Friday, climbing Rs 1,044 to settle at Rs 1,53,880 per 10 grams. Traders built fresh positions, driven by firm demand in the spot market. Consumers can now check updated prices for 18K, 22K, and 24K gold across key Indian cities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:27:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0aaa48d8f5c5fee5e933.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Avonmore Capital Buys EGE Consultant Amid Mixed Financial Performance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Avonmore-Capital-Buys-EGE-Consultant-Amid-Mixed-Financial-Performance/698f0a8d48d8f5c5fee5e770</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Avonmore-Capital-Buys-EGE-Consultant-Amid-Mixed-Financial-Performance/698f0a8d48d8f5c5fee5e770</guid><description>Avonmore Capital &amp; Management Services approved acquiring 100% of Excelling Geo &amp; Engineering Consultant Private Limited for ₹1 Cr. While consolidated Q3 PAT surged 933% YoY to ₹15.30 Cr, standalone results paint a grim picture with PAT down 91% YoY to ₹0.06 Cr, despite a near 1000% revenue jump. The acquisition aims to bolster its advisory business.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:27:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0a8d48d8f5c5fee5e76f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Setco Auto Consolidated Losses Widen Sharply Amidst SEBI Director Penalties</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Setco-Auto-Consolidated-Losses-Widen-Sharply-Amidst-SEBI-Director-Penalties/698f0a7448d8f5c5fee5e6af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Setco-Auto-Consolidated-Losses-Widen-Sharply-Amidst-SEBI-Director-Penalties/698f0a7448d8f5c5fee5e6af</guid><description>Setco Automotive reported a stark divergence in its Q3 FY26 results, with standalone operations turning profitable while consolidated losses widened significantly to ₹57.18 Cr. The company faces regulatory headwinds, including a SEBI order imposing penalties and market access restrictions on its Executive Directors and Ex-CEO for past non-compliance. Auditors also raised concerns via "Emphasis of Matter" paragraphs on significant NCD redemptions and subsidiary financial health.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:26:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f0a7448d8f5c5fee5e6ae.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>