<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:50:07 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Ola Electric Stock Edges Up on CEO Warrant Stay, But Fundamentals Signal Deep Distress</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Stock-Edges-Up-on-CEO-Warrant-Stay-But-Fundamentals-Signal-Deep-Distress/6995427c3ec8b0ccb20dacb7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Stock-Edges-Up-on-CEO-Warrant-Stay-But-Fundamentals-Signal-Deep-Distress/6995427c3ec8b0ccb20dacb7</guid><description>Ola Electric Mobility shares climbed marginally on February 12, 2026, after the Bombay High Court stayed an arrest warrant against CEO Bhavish Aggarwal. Despite this legal reprieve, the company's third-quarter performance reveals a 55% year-on-year revenue plunge and significant delivery volume decline. Analysts maintain a bearish outlook, citing market share erosion and intense competition from stronger EV players like TVS Motor and Bajaj Auto.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:39:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995427c3ec8b0ccb20dacb6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Netweb Technologies Surges on AI Supercomputer Debut, Valuation Scrutiny Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Netweb-Technologies-Surges-on-AI-Supercomputer-Debut-Valuation-Scrutiny-Looms/6995426d3ec8b0ccb20dac8b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Netweb-Technologies-Surges-on-AI-Supercomputer-Debut-Valuation-Scrutiny-Looms/6995426d3ec8b0ccb20dac8b</guid><description>Netweb Technologies India saw its shares surge on February 18, 2026, following the announcement of its new AI supercomputing systems developed in partnership with Nvidia. The 'Tyrone Camarero Spark,' touted as the world's smallest AI supercomputer, leverages Nvidia's latest GPUs and CPUs in a compact desktop form factor. While the launch taps into India's burgeoning AI ambitions and 'Make in India' initiative, the company faces scrutiny over its premium valuation against a backdrop of intense global competition and rapid technological evolution in the AI hardware sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:39:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995426d3ec8b0ccb20dac8a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GMR Airports: Bullish Target Faces Debt Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/GMR-Airports-Bullish-Target-Faces-Debt-Scrutiny/699542693ec8b0ccb20dac74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/GMR-Airports-Bullish-Target-Faces-Debt-Scrutiny/699542693ec8b0ccb20dac74</guid><description>GMR Airports reported Q3FY26 total income surged to ₹4,082.77 crore, though consolidated profit after tax fell 14% to ₹173.96 crore due to one-time expenses. Elara Capital reiterated a 'Buy' with a ₹140 target, citing margin expansion and project nearing completion. However, leverage is expected to peak, and competitive valuations and sector growth present a complex financial picture.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:39:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699542693ec8b0ccb20dac73_1771389681979.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NDL Ventures Surges on HLF Merger Approval, But Valuation Concerns Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NDL-Ventures-Surges-on-HLF-Merger-Approval-But-Valuation-Concerns-Linger/699541ef3ec8b0ccb20dabf9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NDL-Ventures-Surges-on-HLF-Merger-Approval-But-Valuation-Concerns-Linger/699541ef3ec8b0ccb20dabf9</guid><description>NDL Ventures' shares surged by approximately 20% on the BSE, reaching ₹117.45, following the Competition Commission of India's (CCI) approval for its merger with Hinduja Leyland Finance (HLF). The merger, approved by the RBI in August 2025 and the NDL board in November 2025, will see HLF absorbed into NDL Ventures via a share swap: 25 NDL shares for every 10 HLF shares. Despite the market's initial bullish reaction, NDL Ventures' elevated P/E ratio of around 370x and HLF's asset quality metrics present a complex picture for the combined entity's future valuation and operational synergy realization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:37:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699541ef3ec8b0ccb20dabf8_1771389555391.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India EV Ambition: Manufacturing Edge Amid Policy Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-EV-Ambition-Manufacturing-Edge-Amid-Policy-Risks/6995415a3ec8b0ccb20dab14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-EV-Ambition-Manufacturing-Edge-Amid-Policy-Risks/6995415a3ec8b0ccb20dab14</guid><description>India's electric vehicle (EV) ambitions could slash road transport emissions by 50% by 2050, bolstered by an 80% domestic manufacturing rate, unique among emerging markets. However, this projection hinges critically on policy execution and navigating significant supply chain dependencies, particularly on China. While domestic production offers economic leverage, risks persist regarding component imports, infrastructure, and the pace of sustained localization. Heavy-duty vehicle electrification presents a key future growth area.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:34:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995415a3ec8b0ccb20dab13_1771389377264.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Intel Faces India Fine Over Warranty Policy; Global Parity Risk Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Intel-Faces-India-Fine-Over-Warranty-Policy-Global-Parity-Risk-Looms/6995410a3ec8b0ccb20daab8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Intel-Faces-India-Fine-Over-Warranty-Policy-Global-Parity-Risk-Looms/6995410a3ec8b0ccb20daab8</guid><description>Intel Corporation has been fined $3.01 million by India's Competition Commission (CCI) for abusing its dominant market position through an India-specific warranty policy on microprocessors. The ruling, which equated international policy differentiation with anti-competitive abuse, risks setting a precedent for a 'global parity code,' potentially creating compliance burdens and deterring localized strategies for multinational technology companies. This regulatory action surfaces as Intel navigates a challenging AI pivot amidst significant competition and a semiconductor market reshaped by geopolitical forces.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995410a3ec8b0ccb20daab7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys Bets on AI Modernization Amidst Enterprise Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Bets-on-AI-Modernization-Amidst-Enterprise-Hurdles/699540163ec8b0ccb20da962</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Bets-on-AI-Modernization-Amidst-Enterprise-Hurdles/699540163ec8b0ccb20da962</guid><description>Infosys outlined its AI-led growth strategy at Investor AI Day, projecting significant global job creation and unveiling partnerships like the one with Anthropic. While brokerages reiterate positive stances, citing AI as a structural shift, the company faces substantial enterprise challenges, including the need to modernize costly legacy systems. These complexities, however, present a key services opportunity for Infosys. The firm's valuation, market position, and near-term margin pressures from GenAI efficiency gains are under scrutiny amidst mixed analyst sentiment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:29:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699540163ec8b0ccb20da961_1771389079843.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Neysa's $1.4B Valuation: India's AI Compute Gap Exposed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Neysas-14B-Valuation-Indias-AI-Compute-Gap-Exposed/699540153ec8b0ccb20da94b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Neysas-14B-Valuation-Indias-AI-Compute-Gap-Exposed/699540153ec8b0ccb20da94b</guid><description>AI infrastructure provider Neysa has achieved unicorn status, valued at $1.4 billion following a $600 million equity investment led by global private equity firm Blackstone. The funding, which includes an option for an additional $600 million in debt, will fuel Neysa's aggressive expansion of its Graphics Processing Unit (GPU) capacity. This move addresses a critical demand-supply imbalance in India's AI ecosystem, where projected GPU needs are set to surge dramatically over the next three years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:29:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699540153ec8b0ccb20da94a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emkay Global Profit Plunges 81% in 9 Months Despite Q3 Revenue Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Emkay-Global-Profit-Plunges-81percent-in-9-Months-Despite-Q3-Revenue-Rise/69953e2f3ec8b0ccb20da849</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Emkay-Global-Profit-Plunges-81percent-in-9-Months-Despite-Q3-Revenue-Rise/69953e2f3ec8b0ccb20da849</guid><description>Emkay Global Financial Services reported a challenging nine months ended December 2025, with Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeting 81% year-on-year to ₹95 million, and margins compressing to 3.79%. While Q3 FY26 saw revenue grow 13% year-on-year to ₹918 million, PAT declined 51% to ₹43 million. The company's balance sheet also showed a significant increase in total financial liabilities to ₹15,219 million and a rise in the debt-to-equity ratio to 0.22.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:21:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69953e2f3ec8b0ccb20da848_1771388576838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anil Goel Group Buys Over 5% Stake in Sportking India</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Anil-Goel-Group-Buys-Over-5percent-Stake-in-Sportking-India/69953c523ec8b0ccb20da77b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Anil-Goel-Group-Buys-Over-5percent-Stake-in-Sportking-India/69953c523ec8b0ccb20da77b</guid><description>Veteran investor Anil Kumar Goel and his associates have increased their stake in textile maker Sportking India Limited to 5.04% by acquiring 54,000 equity shares through open market purchases between February 11-13, 2026. This move crosses the crucial 5% threshold under SEBI's substantial acquisition regulations. Notably, the acquirers stated they are not part of Sportking India's promoter group, indicating external investor interest in the company.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:13:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69953c523ec8b0ccb20da77a_1771388103380.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys AI Push: Growth Hopes Clash with Investor Skepticism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Push-Growth-Hopes-Clash-with-Investor-Skepticism/69953b0d3ec8b0ccb20da67f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Push-Growth-Hopes-Clash-with-Investor-Skepticism/69953b0d3ec8b0ccb20da67f</guid><description>Infosys is positioning artificial intelligence as its primary growth engine, projecting a massive market opportunity. Despite bullish commentary from Chairman Nandan Nilekani at its Investor AI Day, the tech giant's stock has seen a substantial year-to-date decline of over 17%, erasing nearly ₹1 trillion in market capitalization. Analysts are split, with some seeing FY26 as a growth cycle bottom while others highlight execution risks and intense competition in the rapidly evolving AI services sector. The company's valuation is now at a multi-year low, reflecting investor caution regarding AI's disruptive potential and Infosys's ability to outpace global peers and emerging AI-native players.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:07:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69953b0d3ec8b0ccb20da67e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Spain Probes X, Meta, TikTok on AI Child Abuse Content</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Spain-Probes-X-Meta-TikTok-on-AI-Child-Abuse-Content/69953a9e3ec8b0ccb20da5cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Spain-Probes-X-Meta-TikTok-on-AI-Child-Abuse-Content/69953a9e3ec8b0ccb20da5cc</guid><description>Spain has ordered prosecutors to investigate social media giants X, Meta, and TikTok for allegedly spreading AI-generated child sexual abuse material. This action escalates a global crackdown on big tech's content moderation and AI practices. The probe, driven by concerns over algorithms amplifying harmful content, follows alarming statistics on AI-driven exploitation. It places immense pressure on platforms to manage risks associated with generative AI, potentially leading to significant fines and operational changes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:05:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69953a9e3ec8b0ccb20da5cb_1771387682350.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tenneco Clean Air's Valuation Faces Heat Amid Labor Code Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tenneco-Clean-Airs-Valuation-Faces-Heat-Amid-Labor-Code-Costs/69953a723ec8b0ccb20da595</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tenneco-Clean-Airs-Valuation-Faces-Heat-Amid-Labor-Code-Costs/69953a723ec8b0ccb20da595</guid><description>Tenneco Clean Air India reported strong Q3 FY26 revenue growth and margin expansion, driven by new product wins and segment performance. However, a significant ₹27.2 crore provision for new labor codes impacted net profit. The company's elevated P/E ratio, considerably higher than peers like Endurance Technologies and Bosch, invites scrutiny, particularly given past revenue contractions and evolving regulatory costs. Positive developments include strategic business wins and benefits from the India-US trade deal easing export tariffs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:05:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69953a723ec8b0ccb20da594_1771387633146.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia-Meta Deal: AI Chip Supply Bolsters CPU Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Meta-Deal-AI-Chip-Supply-Bolsters-CPU-Push/69953a493ec8b0ccb20da534</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Meta-Deal-AI-Chip-Supply-Bolsters-CPU-Push/69953a493ec8b0ccb20da534</guid><description>Nvidia confirmed a multiyear contract to supply Meta Platforms with millions of AI chips, including its current Blackwell and future Rubin AI accelerators, alongside its ARM-based Grace and Vera central processors. This expansion into CPU offerings signals Nvidia's intent to challenge established players like Intel and AMD within data centers. The deal deepens the partnership with Meta, a key Nvidia customer, even as Meta develops its own custom silicon and explores options like Google's Tensor Processing Units. The agreement highlights the surging demand for AI infrastructure and the complex competitive dynamics between hyperscalers and their hardware suppliers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:04:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69953a493ec8b0ccb20da533.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Recovers as Geopolitical Calm Meets Inflation Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Recovers-as-Geopolitical-Calm-Meets-Inflation-Fears/699539853ec8b0ccb20da431</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Recovers-as-Geopolitical-Calm-Meets-Inflation-Fears/699539853ec8b0ccb20da431</guid><description>Silver futures recovered from an intraday low of $72 to hover near $74 per ounce, reversing early session losses driven by de-escalating geopolitical tensions and a strengthening U.S. dollar. Despite short-term headwinds, analysts suggest underlying supportive fundamentals, including central bank diversification and industrial demand, are expected to anchor prices within a $70-$90 range for the foreseeable future.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:01:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699539853ec8b0ccb20da430.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MIDHANI: Growth Amidst Margin Squeeze, Can it Deliver?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/MIDHANI-Growth-Amidst-Margin-Squeeze-Can-it-Deliver/699539853ec8b0ccb20da41a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/MIDHANI-Growth-Amidst-Margin-Squeeze-Can-it-Deliver/699539853ec8b0ccb20da41a</guid><description>Mishra Dhatu Nigam (MIDHANI) posted a 15.8% revenue rise in Q3FY26 due to strong execution in defence and aerospace. However, EBITDA margins contracted 222 basis points to 19.8% on higher input costs. Net profit grew 8.3%, supported by lower depreciation and interest. With a Rs 2,440 crore order book, the company targets 20% revenue growth and 23% EBITDA margins, investing heavily in R&amp;D and facility upgrades to capitalize on an Rs 8,000 crore import substitution market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:01:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699539853ec8b0ccb20da419_1771387406800.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Cloud Softech Secures Govt License for National Internet Service</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Blue-Cloud-Softech-Secures-Govt-License-for-National-Internet-Service/6995388e3ec8b0ccb20da337</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Blue-Cloud-Softech-Secures-Govt-License-for-National-Internet-Service/6995388e3ec8b0ccb20da337</guid><description>Blue Cloud Softech Solutions has received a crucial Letter of Intent from India's Department of Telecommunications for a national Virtual Network Operator (VNO) license. This strategic move positions the company to build a nationwide digital and data-center infrastructure platform, aiming to integrate connectivity, AI, and cloud services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:57:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995388e3ec8b0ccb20da336.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MIDHANI: Growth Surge Meets Margin Squeeze Amid Strategic Bets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MIDHANI-Growth-Surge-Meets-Margin-Squeeze-Amid-Strategic-Bets/6995350d3ec8b0ccb20da21e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MIDHANI-Growth-Surge-Meets-Margin-Squeeze-Amid-Strategic-Bets/6995350d3ec8b0ccb20da21e</guid><description>Mishra Dhatu Nigam Ltd. (MIDHANI) announced a significant 15.8% year-on-year revenue increase for Q3 FY26, driven by robust execution and a Rs 2,590 crore order book. However, EBITDA margins contracted by 222 basis points to 19.8% due to elevated input costs. While net profit rose 8.3%, the company faces valuation challenges, trading at approximately 26 times FY28 estimated earnings, a premium to many peers. Strategic initiatives like import substitution and facility upgrades are key to future profitability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:42:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995350d3ec8b0ccb20da21d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys AI Day: Bullish Targets vs. Stock Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Day-Bullish-Targets-vs-Stock-Slump/699533703ec8b0ccb20da052</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Day-Bullish-Targets-vs-Stock-Slump/699533703ec8b0ccb20da052</guid><description>Infosys Ltd. unveiled its artificial intelligence strategy at its AI Investor Day, projecting a $300-400 billion global AI services market by 2030. New AI services already contribute 5.5% of Q3FY26 revenue. Despite this, analysts maintain a generally positive outlook, with 38 out of 52 recommending a 'Buy' and setting price targets up to ₹2,050. However, the stock closed up 1.88% on Tuesday at ₹1,391.30, remaining down 15% year-to-date, indicating market apprehension persists amidst broader IT sector pressures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:35:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699533703ec8b0ccb20da051.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti eVitara Launch: Aggressive Pricing Risks Margin Erosion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-eVitara-Launch-Aggressive-Pricing-Risks-Margin-Erosion/6995336b3ec8b0ccb20da03b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-eVitara-Launch-Aggressive-Pricing-Risks-Margin-Erosion/6995336b3ec8b0ccb20da03b</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki has entered the mid-size EV segment with its eVitara, starting at ₹10.99 lakh under a Battery-as-a-Service model. Brokerage firm Nomura highlights the aggressive pricing as key to increasing EV penetration but warns of potential profitability concerns. Analysts project combined domestic volumes of 12,000-24,000 units for the eVitara and its Toyota variant over FY26-FY27. The stock, trading around ₹15,192, has seen an 18.8% gain in the past year, with a strong 'Buy' consensus from most analysts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:35:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995336b3ec8b0ccb20da03a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Signature Global Eyes Commercial Leap with RMZ JV</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-Eyes-Commercial-Leap-with-RMZ-JV/6995336a3ec8b0ccb20da024</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-Eyes-Commercial-Leap-with-RMZ-JV/6995336a3ec8b0ccb20da024</guid><description>Signature Global (India) Limited is diversifying into institutional-grade commercial real estate through a 50:50 joint venture with RMZ Group. RMZ will invest ₹1,283 crore into a Special Purpose Vehicle for an 18.5 million sq ft mixed-use project in Gurugram. This strategic move is expected to significantly reduce Signature Global's consolidated net debt, potentially to near zero, while unlocking land value and generating annuity income. Axis Securities reiterates a 'Buy' rating with a target of ₹1,315, citing potential for long-term value creation and lower leverage servicing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:35:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995336a3ec8b0ccb20da023.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AHFCs Navigate Growth Slowdown, Profitability Holds Amidst Falling Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AHFCs-Navigate-Growth-Slowdown-Profitability-Holds-Amidst-Falling-Costs/699533693ec8b0ccb20da00d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AHFCs-Navigate-Growth-Slowdown-Profitability-Holds-Amidst-Falling-Costs/699533693ec8b0ccb20da00d</guid><description>Affordable Housing Finance Companies (AHFCs) saw a slowdown in Q3FY26 asset under management (AUM) growth, with rates moderating to 15-29% from prior double-digit expansion, largely due to high bases and softer disbursement momentum. Despite this, profitability remained healthy, supported by declining funding costs which widened interest spreads for major players like Aptus Value Housing Finance and Home First Finance Company. Analysts view the current disbursement softness as transient, maintaining a positive long-term outlook based on improving margins and diverse liability profiles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:35:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699533693ec8b0ccb20da00c_1771385832532.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Eyes Forex Market Overhaul for Deeper Liquidity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Eyes-Forex-Market-Overhaul-for-Deeper-Liquidity/699532043ec8b0ccb20d9ee5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Eyes-Forex-Market-Overhaul-for-Deeper-Liquidity/699532043ec8b0ccb20d9ee5</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has unveiled draft regulations to enhance flexibility for authorized foreign exchange market participants. These proposals aim to empower banks and primary dealers with greater latitude in hedging exposures, managing balance sheets, and performing market-making functions. Key changes include expanded derivative capabilities and simplified reporting, signaling a strategic push towards a more dynamic and integrated Indian financial market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:29:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699532043ec8b0ccb20d9ee4_1771385468055.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Namo Bharat RRTS: Property Prices Surge Amidst TOD Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Namo-Bharat-RRTS-Property-Prices-Surge-Amidst-TOD-Push/699531f43ec8b0ccb20d9eb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Namo-Bharat-RRTS-Property-Prices-Surge-Amidst-TOD-Push/699531f43ec8b0ccb20d9eb2</guid><description>The imminent full launch of the 82-kilometer Namo Bharat rapid rail transport system (RRTS) and Meerut Metro is expected to significantly boost real estate along the Delhi-Meerut corridor. Property prices near stations have already risen 30-67% over two years, with further appreciation anticipated. Analysts highlight the project's role in fostering Transit-Oriented Development (TOD), promising socioeconomic transformation and new urban hubs, drawing parallels to successful TOD models in global cities. Developers are actively launching new projects, capitalizing on enhanced connectivity and urban planning policies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699531f43ec8b0ccb20d9eb1_1771385412213.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Rout Overshadows Earnings Strength as AI Fears Grip Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IT-Rout-Overshadows-Earnings-Strength-as-AI-Fears-Grip-Market/6995309d3ec8b0ccb20d9dcf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IT-Rout-Overshadows-Earnings-Strength-as-AI-Fears-Grip-Market/6995309d3ec8b0ccb20d9dcf</guid><description>Domestic markets grapple with a severe sell-off in the IT sector, fueled by AI disruption concerns, which erased billions in market value. This starkly contrasts with a better-than-expected Q3 earnings season, where the BSE-500 showed robust 16% PAT growth, and a positive long-term outlook, including a Nifty target of 29,000 by December 2026. While some analysts maintain a constructive stance, focusing on consumer discretionary and financials, the technology sector faces existential questions. The WhiteOak Capital Market Valuation Index slightly declined, suggesting selective opportunities amidst caution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:23:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995309d3ec8b0ccb20d9dce_1771385188451.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axis Bank: NIM Dip, Slippage Rise Cloud 'Buy' Thesis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-NIM-Dip-Slippage-Rise-Cloud-Buy-Thesis/69952bef3ec8b0ccb20d9c39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-NIM-Dip-Slippage-Rise-Cloud-Buy-Thesis/69952bef3ec8b0ccb20d9c39</guid><description>Centrum Securities maintains a 'Buy' rating on Axis Bank with a ₹1,460 target price, citing stabilizing asset quality and bottoming Net Interest Margins (NIMs). However, Q3 FY26 results showed a 9 basis point sequential NIM decline and a rise in new slippages. While the bank projects future NIM expansion, the immediate data presents a mixed picture. Axis Bank's stock has outperformed peers over the past year, but its valuation, at a P/E of approximately 15-16, sits between SBI's lower multiples and those of HDFC and ICICI Banks. The projected 8-9% upside from the target price is modest given potential headwinds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:03:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69952bef3ec8b0ccb20d9c38_1771383917905.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paint Stocks: Muted Views Clash With Elevated Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Paint-Stocks-Muted-Views-Clash-With-Elevated-Valuations/69952be93ec8b0ccb20d9c22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Paint-Stocks-Muted-Views-Clash-With-Elevated-Valuations/69952be93ec8b0ccb20d9c22</guid><description>Leading paint manufacturers like Asian Paints, Berger Paints, and Kansai Nerolac are navigating a challenging environment characterized by muted demand and structural industry concerns. While major brokerages maintain cautious 'hold' ratings, citing elevated valuations and competitive pressures from new entrants like Grasim's Birla Opus, market sentiment remains divided. Despite headwinds, some analysts see potential tailwinds and have issued mixed ratings, leaving investors balancing premium stock prices against a subdued recovery outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69952be93ec8b0ccb20d9c21_1771383920388.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SIP Discipline: The Real Alpha Beyond Market Cycles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/SIP-Discipline-The-Real-Alpha-Beyond-Market-Cycles/69952afa3ec8b0ccb20d9b7e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/SIP-Discipline-The-Real-Alpha-Beyond-Market-Cycles/69952afa3ec8b0ccb20d9b7e</guid><description>Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) show a clear pattern: short-term holdings (1-3 years) are subject to significant volatility and unpredictable outcomes, with potential for steep losses. However, as investment horizons extend to 5-7 years and beyond, SIPs demonstrate a marked decrease in risk and a substantial increase in return consistency, often yielding positive mid-to-double-digit annualized gains. The critical factor for success is not merely market duration but the investor's ability to maintain discipline and overcome behavioral biases that trigger premature exits during market downturns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:59:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69952afa3ec8b0ccb20d9b7d_1771383668558.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KNRCL Lands Chennai Infra Project: Growth Signal or Mounting Risks?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/KNRCL-Lands-Chennai-Infra-Project-Growth-Signal-or-Mounting-Risks/699529953ec8b0ccb20d9ad3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/KNRCL-Lands-Chennai-Infra-Project-Growth-Signal-or-Mounting-Risks/699529953ec8b0ccb20d9ad3</guid><description>KNR Constructions Limited has been awarded a ₹2,163.07 crore contract to build a four-lane elevated corridor along Chennai's East Coast Road. The project, to be executed under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM), has a 1095-day construction period. While this award bolsters the company's order book and signifies continued infrastructure development, it also brings into focus the inherent risks associated with HAM projects and KNRCL's recent performance trends.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:53:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699529953ec8b0ccb20d9ad2_1771383320850.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Recovers, Banks Shine, Auto Ancillaries Show Mixed Signals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Nifty-Recovers-Banks-Shine-Auto-Ancillaries-Show-Mixed-Signals/699524e33ec8b0ccb20d91fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Nifty-Recovers-Banks-Shine-Auto-Ancillaries-Show-Mixed-Signals/699524e33ec8b0ccb20d91fd</guid><description>The Nifty index extended its recovery, filling a previous gap and testing resistance near 26,000, supported by renewed FPI inflows. Bank of Maharashtra garnered a 'Strong Buy' rating from one analyst, contrasting with a 'Hold' consensus, citing strong fundamentals like low NPAs and healthy profit growth, though its P/E is lower than peers. LG Balakrishnan &amp; Bros showed bullish technicals and sector tailwinds but faces headwinds from slowing growth, decreasing market share, and potential overvaluation. The auto ancillary sector, however, shows positive growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:33:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699524e33ec8b0ccb20d91fc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LG India: Goldman Sachs Bets Big as Q4 Earnings Falter</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Goldman-Sachs-Bets-Big-as-Q4-Earnings-Falter/699524e23ec8b0ccb20d91d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Goldman-Sachs-Bets-Big-as-Q4-Earnings-Falter/699524e23ec8b0ccb20d91d5</guid><description>Goldman Sachs has initiated coverage on LG Electronics India with a 'Buy' recommendation and a ₹1,750 price target, signaling a potential 13% upside. This bullish stance is predicated on the company's premiumization strategy and its 'Global South' export-led growth narrative. However, this optimism sharply contrasts with the company's recently reported December quarter performance, which showed a 61.6% plunge in net profit and a 6.4% revenue decline, exacerbated by margin compression due to demand softness and rising input costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699524e23ec8b0ccb20d91d4_1771382156744.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Japan's $550B US Investment: Energy Projects Raise Transition Questions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Japans-550B-US-Investment-Energy-Projects-Raise-Transition-Questions/699524e13ec8b0ccb20d91ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Japans-550B-US-Investment-Energy-Projects-Raise-Transition-Questions/699524e13ec8b0ccb20d91ae</guid><description>Japan has initiated the first phase of its $550 billion US investment commitment, totaling $36 billion for projects including a significant natural gas facility in Ohio, an oil export terminal in the Gulf of Mexico, and a synthetic diamond plant in Georgia. While framed as industrial revitalization and job creation, the focus on fossil fuel infrastructure raises questions about alignment with global energy transition trends and Japan's own carbon neutrality objectives. The nature of the investment, potentially leaning towards loans rather than direct equity, suggests a complex financial arrangement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699524e13ec8b0ccb20d91ad_1771382159405.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PhonePe IPO: Valuation Scrutiny Ahead of Market Debut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PhonePe-IPO-Valuation-Scrutiny-Ahead-of-Market-Debut/699522913ec8b0ccb20d7ebe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PhonePe-IPO-Valuation-Scrutiny-Ahead-of-Market-Debut/699522913ec8b0ccb20d7ebe</guid><description>Macquarie Research anticipates PhonePe's potential $15 billion IPO will spark a near-term re-rating for rival Paytm. The brokerage notes PhonePe's aggressive expansion into financial services distribution, directly challenging Paytm's revenue streams and potentially pressuring margins. Concerns are mounting over PhonePe's high valuation multiples, especially as it remains EBITDA-negative while Paytm has achieved profitability. Regulatory headwinds, including discontinued revenue sources and proposed UPI market share caps, add complexity to PhonePe's outlook and the broader fintech sector's valuation narrative.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:23:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699522913ec8b0ccb20d7ebd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Technical Buys Under Scrutiny: Airtel, Finolex, Coal India</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Technical-Buys-Under-Scrutiny-Airtel-Finolex-Coal-India/6995219d3ec8b0ccb20d7dd5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Technical-Buys-Under-Scrutiny-Airtel-Finolex-Coal-India/6995219d3ec8b0ccb20d7dd5</guid><description>Analyst recommendations highlight Bharti Airtel, Finolex Industries, and Coal India based on technical indicators. Bharti Airtel shows mixed signals with a neutral RSI and divergent MACD readings, while Finolex Industries exhibits evolving bullish momentum. Coal India approaches a confluence support zone, signaling potential reversal after a period of correction. However, a deeper examination of valuations, competitive pressures, and recent performance trends presents a more nuanced perspective than pure technical signals suggest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:19:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995219d3ec8b0ccb20d7dd4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Deep Tech: Frugality Fuels Innovation, But Scaling Capital Gaps Remain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Deep-Tech-Frugality-Fuels-Innovation-But-Scaling-Capital-Gaps-Remain/699521283ec8b0ccb20d7d71</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Deep-Tech-Frugality-Fuels-Innovation-But-Scaling-Capital-Gaps-Remain/699521283ec8b0ccb20d7d71</guid><description>Investors at the India AI Impact Summit 2026 emphasized India's potential for deep tech innovation, driven by frugality and sharp engineering. While AI and deep tech funding surged in 2025, attracting $1.2 billion and $2.1 billion respectively, significant challenges persist. A critical gap in growth-stage capital and the absence of large domestic specialist funds impede global scaling, contrasting with the US and China's robust ecosystems. Policy initiatives like the RDI Fund aim to bridge these gaps, but sustained patient capital remains essential.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:17:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699521283ec8b0ccb20d7d70_1771381172104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI 'Sovereigns' Skyrocket; Valuation, Regulation Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Sovereigns-Skyrocket-Valuation-Regulation-Risks-Loom/69951ddb3ec8b0ccb20d7bf0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Sovereigns-Skyrocket-Valuation-Regulation-Risks-Loom/69951ddb3ec8b0ccb20d7bf0</guid><description>The artificial intelligence sector is experiencing a valuation frenzy, with private powerhouses OpenAI and Anthropic reaching astronomical valuations north of $300 billion, fueled by massive investment rounds. This surge contrasts with the more grounded, yet still significant, market positions of tech titans like Google and Alibaba. While AI adoption accelerates across industries, investors face a complex landscape of intense competition, soaring capital expenditures, and a growing web of global regulatory scrutiny, raising concerns about sustainability and market fragmentation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:03:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69951ddb3ec8b0ccb20d7bef.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goldman's AI Moats: SNOW, MDB, SHOP, CRWD Face Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Goldmans-AI-Moats-SNOW-MDB-SHOP-CRWD-Face-Scrutiny/69951d9f3ec8b0ccb20d7ba3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Goldmans-AI-Moats-SNOW-MDB-SHOP-CRWD-Face-Scrutiny/69951d9f3ec8b0ccb20d7ba3</guid><description>Goldman Sachs has identified Snowflake, MongoDB, Shopify, and CrowdStrike as software companies possessing durable competitive advantages, or "moats," that could shield them from AI-driven disruption. While these firms are lauded for their potential resilience, a closer look reveals differentiated AI positioning, intense competitive dynamics, and significant valuation considerations. Analysts remain divided, with some upgrading stocks like Shopify and MongoDB based on AI tailwinds, while others express caution regarding CrowdStrike's budget exposure and Snowflake's market pressures. The current market sentiment suggests that while AI may create winners, the path to sustained value requires navigating heightened competition and justifying premium valuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:02:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69951d9f3ec8b0ccb20d7ba2.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Stock Crumbles as Analysts Flash 'Sell' Amidst Market Share Collapse</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ola-Electric-Stock-Crumbles-as-Analysts-Flash-Sell-Amidst-Market-Share-Collapse/69951d643ec8b0ccb20d7b78</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ola-Electric-Stock-Crumbles-as-Analysts-Flash-Sell-Amidst-Market-Share-Collapse/69951d643ec8b0ccb20d7b78</guid><description>Ola Electric Mobility's stock plunged to new lows following a critical sell-off triggered by analyst downgrades and reports of substantial market share erosion. Citigroup and Emkay Global Financial Services have issued 'Sell' ratings, citing slowing EV adoption, persistent operational challenges, and intense competition from established automotive giants. Recent quarterly results reveal a dramatic year-over-year revenue decline of 55% and a significant drop in delivery volumes, contrasting sharply with the overall growth in the electric two-wheeler segment. The company's negative profitability and high cash burn are increasingly under scrutiny, overshadowing a recent legal stay on an arrest warrant for its CEO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 02:01:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69951d643ec8b0ccb20d7b77.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Technical Breakouts Signal Bullish Momentum Amidst Market Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Technical-Breakouts-Signal-Bullish-Momentum-Amidst-Market-Caution/69951b8a3ec8b0ccb20d7a67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Technical-Breakouts-Signal-Bullish-Momentum-Amidst-Market-Caution/69951b8a3ec8b0ccb20d7a67</guid><description>Analysts have pinpointed nine stocks poised for short-term gains on February 18th, driven by bullish technical indicators like double-bottom patterns, channel breakouts, and positive RSI readings. Despite a cautiously optimistic market, these selections suggest underlying strength in specific sectors, with targets ranging from INR 160 for Canara Bank to INR 5,000 for Cummins India. However, investors should note the elevated P/E ratios for some names and sector-specific headwinds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 01:53:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69951b8a3ec8b0ccb20d7a66.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIFT City IPO: XED's $12M Debut Tests IFSCA's Global Reach</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/GIFT-City-IPO-XEDs-12M-Debut-Tests-IFSCAs-Global-Reach/6995198d3ec8b0ccb20d795a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/GIFT-City-IPO-XEDs-12M-Debut-Tests-IFSCAs-Global-Reach/6995198d3ec8b0ccb20d795a</guid><description>XED Executive Development is set to launch India's first IPO from GIFT City, aiming to raise US$12 million. The offering, structured in dollar-denominated instruments, will list on NSE International Exchange and India International Exchange, targeting overseas investors under the IFSCA framework. This milestone IPO serves as a critical test for GIFT City's regulatory structure and its potential to attract international capital, despite the modest fundraising amount. The executive education sector is poised for significant growth, with XED competing in a space alongside established global institutions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 01:44:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995198d3ec8b0ccb20d7959.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>