<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:54 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Gig Workers Strike: Regulatory Gap Fuels Platform Turmoil</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Gig-Workers-Strike-Regulatory-Gap-Fuels-Platform-Turmoil/6986d7bdb81b2b81dcfb82ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Gig-Workers-Strike-Regulatory-Gap-Fuels-Platform-Turmoil/6986d7bdb81b2b81dcfb82ac</guid><description>App-based transport workers in India initiated a nationwide six-hour strike, dubbed "All India Breakdown," on February 7, 2026. Organized by the Telangana Gig and Platform Workers Union (TGPWU), the protest targets exploitative pricing, inadequate regulation, and income insecurity. Drivers demand government-notified minimum fares and stricter enforcement of the Motor Vehicle Aggregator Guidelines, 2025, which they claim platforms continuously flout. The strike is expected to disrupt services significantly in major urban centers, increasing pressure on platforms like Uber, Ola, and Rapido to address long-standing driver grievances.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:12:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986d7bdb81b2b81dcfb82ab.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC-Britannia IP Fight: Packaging Battle Signals Fierce FMCG Rivalry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Britannia-IP-Fight-Packaging-Battle-Signals-Fierce-FMCG-Rivalry/6986c842b81b2b81dcfb7444</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Britannia-IP-Fight-Packaging-Battle-Signals-Fierce-FMCG-Rivalry/6986c842b81b2b81dcfb7444</guid><description>ITC Limited has filed a copyright infringement and passing-off suit against Britannia Industries at the Calcutta High Court, alleging Britannia's new cheese-flavored biscuit packaging deceptively mimics ITC's Sunfeast Wowzers line. The legal action underscores the escalating competition and the critical role of distinctive packaging in the Indian FMCG sector. The dispute emerges amidst a dynamic market where premiumization and brand identity are paramount for capturing market share.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:06:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986c842b81b2b81dcfb7443.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways Upgrades Signaling: Efficiency &amp; Safety Drive Infra Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Upgrades-Signaling-Efficiency-and-Safety-Drive-Infra-Boom/6986c7ceb81b2b81dcfb72ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Upgrades-Signaling-Efficiency-and-Safety-Drive-Infra-Boom/6986c7ceb81b2b81dcfb72ed</guid><description>Indian Railways is undertaking a massive overhaul of its signaling infrastructure, integrating electronic interlocking and advanced systems across thousands of stations and level crossings. This initiative aims to dramatically enhance operational safety and efficiency, evidenced by a significant reduction in signaling failures and accidents. The multi-billion dollar upgrade underscores a national infrastructure push, driving investment in related manufacturing and technology sectors, while navigating the inherent complexities of large-scale project execution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:04:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986c7ceb81b2b81dcfb72ec.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eases Jewellery Imports: Consumer Confidence Boosted</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Eases-Jewellery-Imports-Consumer-Confidence-Boosted/6986c6ddb81b2b81dcfb716e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Eases-Jewellery-Imports-Consumer-Confidence-Boosted/6986c6ddb81b2b81dcfb716e</guid><description>India's Baggage Rules 2026 have removed monetary caps on jewelry imports, shifting to a weight-based allowance (40g for women, 20g for others) for duty-free entry. This regulatory update aims to boost consumer confidence by simplifying customs, reducing subjective valuations, and aligning with increasingly globalized purchasing habits. The move supports the informed Indian buyer and acknowledges jewelry as a personal asset, potentially influencing market dynamics amidst evolving preferences for lightweight and lab-grown diamond jewelry.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:00:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986c6ddb81b2b81dcfb716d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zerodha's Kite Terminal Mode: Retail Trading Gets Pro Interface</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zerodhas-Kite-Terminal-Mode-Retail-Trading-Gets-Pro-Interface/6986c147b81b2b81dcfb6d9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zerodhas-Kite-Terminal-Mode-Retail-Trading-Gets-Pro-Interface/6986c147b81b2b81dcfb6d9e</guid><description>Zerodha's Kite platform introduces Terminal Mode beta, enabling extensive screen customization and integrating key trading tools. This move positions Zerodha to cater to demanding traders seeking institutional-grade efficiency, potentially setting a new benchmark in the competitive Indian online brokerage space. The feature allows users to tailor their trading environment for faster decision-making and reduced clutter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:36:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986c147b81b2b81dcfb6d9d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Purple Finance Raises ₹69 Cr Via Warrants, Eyes SME Lending Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Purple-Finance-Raises-69-Cr-Via-Warrants-Eyes-SME-Lending-Expansion/6986c137b81b2b81dcfb6c81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Purple-Finance-Raises-69-Cr-Via-Warrants-Eyes-SME-Lending-Expansion/6986c137b81b2b81dcfb6c81</guid><description>Purple Finance Limited announced a ₹69.30 crore capital infusion through equity warrants, priced at ₹55 each. This marks another significant fundraising since its June 2024 listing, underscoring investor confidence in its SME and retail lending growth strategy. The funds will fuel expansion, supporting its network of 45 branches and approximately ₹210 crore Assets Under Management (AUM) as of January 2026, with a team of 430 employees.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:36:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986c137b81b2b81dcfb6c80.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata-Mercuria JV Targets Global Commodities Amid India Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Tata-Mercuria-JV-Targets-Global-Commodities-Amid-India-Focus/6986bf5cb81b2b81dcfb62a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Tata-Mercuria-JV-Targets-Global-Commodities-Amid-India-Focus/6986bf5cb81b2b81dcfb62a1</guid><description>Tata International and Mercuria Energy Group are establishing a joint venture to enhance global commodity trading across energy, metals, agriculture, and oil/gas. This alliance merges Tata International's established presence, particularly in India, with Mercuria's extensive global trading capabilities. The venture aims to deliver diversified commodity solutions and supply chain services. Operational commencement is contingent on receiving necessary regulatory approvals. The strategic partnership underscores India's significance in global trade and the companies' commitment to governance and responsible growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:28:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986bf5cb81b2b81dcfb62a0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel Profit Soars 9X, Driven by India; UK Woes Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Profit-Soars-9X-Driven-by-India-UK-Woes-Linger/6986baaab81b2b81dcfb5f51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Profit-Soars-9X-Driven-by-India-UK-Woes-Linger/6986baaab81b2b81dcfb5f51</guid><description>Tata Steel's Q3 FY26 net profit skyrocketed to ₹2,730.37 crore, a nine-fold increase from the previous year, propelled by record Indian deliveries and a turnaround in Netherlands operations. Income from operations grew to ₹57,002 crore. However, UK operations continued to incur substantial losses. The company maintained significant capital expenditure while reducing net debt by ₹5,206 crore.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:08:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986baaab81b2b81dcfb5f50.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quadrant Televentures: Board Meets to Discuss Financials Under Insolvency</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Quadrant-Televentures-Board-Meets-to-Discuss-Financials-Under-Insolvency/6986b8cdb81b2b81dcfb5d71</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Quadrant-Televentures-Board-Meets-to-Discuss-Financials-Under-Insolvency/6986b8cdb81b2b81dcfb5d71</guid><description>Quadrant Televentures Limited has called a board meeting for February 11, 2026, to consider its un-audited standalone financial results for the quarter and half-year ended September 30, 2025. The company has been under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) since September 2, 2025, following an NCLT order, with operations managed by the Resolution Professional. The trading window for its securities remains closed until results dissemination.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:00:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986b8cdb81b2b81dcfb5d70.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Purple Finance to Raise ₹69.3 Crore for Expansion Via Warrants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Purple-Finance-to-Raise-693-Crore-for-Expansion-Via-Warrants/6986b850b81b2b81dcfb5c16</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Purple-Finance-to-Raise-693-Crore-for-Expansion-Via-Warrants/6986b850b81b2b81dcfb5c16</guid><description>Purple Finance Limited's board has approved raising ₹69.30 crore by issuing 1.26 crore equity warrants at ₹55 per warrant. The funds are earmarked to strengthen the company's capital base and support ongoing expansion initiatives. This follows previous capital raises and reflects growing investor confidence. As of January 2026, the company operates 45 branches with ₹210 crore in Assets Under Management (AUM).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 03:58:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986b850b81b2b81dcfb5c15.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Threatens 25% Tariffs on India Over Russia Oil Imports</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Threatens-25percent-Tariffs-on-India-Over-Russia-Oil-Imports/6986b23cb81b2b81dcfb5450</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Threatens-25percent-Tariffs-on-India-Over-Russia-Oil-Imports/6986b23cb81b2b81dcfb5450</guid><description>The United States is closely monitoring India's crude oil imports from Russia. Washington has signaled it could reimpose a 25% penalty tariff on Indian goods if New Delhi resumes buying Russian oil. This development jeopardizes the recent interim trade agreement between the two nations, which aimed to reduce tariffs on Indian exports. India's imports of Russian crude have already seen a reduction in recent months.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 03:32:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986b23cb81b2b81dcfb544f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ELSS Funds Deliver Up to 21% CAGR: Tax Savings Meet Equity Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/ELSS-Funds-Deliver-Up-to-21percent-CAGR-Tax-Savings-Meet-Equity-Growth/6986b05ab81b2b81dcfb4e31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/ELSS-Funds-Deliver-Up-to-21percent-CAGR-Tax-Savings-Meet-Equity-Growth/6986b05ab81b2b81dcfb4e31</guid><description>Equity Linked Savings Schemes (ELSS) remain vital for 2026 tax savings, combining Section 80C deductions with equity growth potential. Analysis of five leading ELSS funds reveals compounded annual growth rates between 18.04% and 21.51% over 10 years, highlighting significant performance divergence due to asset allocation, market-cap focus, and cost structures. Investors should note these key differentiators beyond the uniform 3-year lock-in.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 03:24:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986b05ab81b2b81dcfb4e30.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC, Britannia in Packaging Battle: Market Share Fight</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Britannia-in-Packaging-Battle-Market-Share-Fight/6986a9c9b81b2b81dcfb4a5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Britannia-in-Packaging-Battle-Market-Share-Fight/6986a9c9b81b2b81dcfb4a5b</guid><description>ITC has filed an intellectual property infringement case against Britannia at the Calcutta High Court, accusing the rival of copying the trade dress of its 'Sunfeast Wowzers' biscuits. The lawsuit highlights intensifying competition in India's multi-billion dollar biscuit sector, where brand distinctiveness is crucial for market share. The court's decision not to grant an immediate injunction suggests a thorough examination of the claims, leaving the outcome uncertain and signaling potential protracted legal battles between these food giants.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 02:56:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986a9c9b81b2b81dcfb4a5a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Order Surge Masks Mixed Stock Performance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Order-Surge-Masks-Mixed-Stock-Performance/6986a070b81b2b81dcfb24c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Order-Surge-Masks-Mixed-Stock-Performance/6986a070b81b2b81dcfb24c4</guid><description>A wave of significant contract wins totaling over ₹3,000 crore has bolstered order books for Indian companies in the infrastructure, defence, engineering, and automobile sectors. However, the market's response has been bifurcated. While some firms like BHEL and BEL saw their shares decline despite substantial project inflows, others such as Swan Defence and Waaree Energies registered gains. This divergence highlights investor scrutiny beyond headline order values, emphasizing factors like long-term execution, margin sustainability, and overall sector valuations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 02:16:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986a070b81b2b81dcfb24c3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>STT Hike Reshapes Arbitrage vs. Liquid Fund Appeal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/STT-Hike-Reshapes-Arbitrage-vs-Liquid-Fund-Appeal/69869442b81b2b81dcfb1efa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/STT-Hike-Reshapes-Arbitrage-vs-Liquid-Fund-Appeal/69869442b81b2b81dcfb1efa</guid><description>Securities Transaction Tax (STT) hikes, enacted via the Union Budget 2026, have significantly increased transaction costs for arbitrage funds. This erosion of profitability challenges their historical advantage over liquid funds for short-term capital parking. Investors must re-evaluate risk appetites and tax brackets as arbitrage strategies become less cost-efficient, potentially favoring the capital preservation focus of liquid funds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:24:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69869442b81b2b81dcfb1ef9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Households Ditch FDs for Riskier Assets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indian-Households-Ditch-FDs-for-Riskier-Assets/698693c5b81b2b81dcfb1db7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indian-Households-Ditch-FDs-for-Riskier-Assets/698693c5b81b2b81dcfb1db7</guid><description>Driven by inflation eroding traditional savings and a growing appetite for higher returns, Indian households are shifting decisively from fixed deposits and gold to market-linked investments such as mutual funds and equities. This trend is fueled by increased digital accessibility, a younger demographic entering markets, and a fundamental reevaluation of financial security, moving beyond mere preservation to active wealth creation. Despite the clear shift, significant risks persist, particularly concerning speculative trading in derivatives and rising household debt.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:22:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698693c5b81b2b81dcfb1db6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2026 Budget: Regional Growth Push Faces Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Budget-Regional-Growth-Push-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/69869350b81b2b81dcfb1c76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Budget-Regional-Growth-Push-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/69869350b81b2b81dcfb1c76</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 signals a strategic shift from metro-centric growth to a regionally grounded economic architecture. While prioritizing connectivity and empowering smaller cities, the success hinges critically on overcoming implementation hurdles, securing private sector investment, and fostering local capabilities. This transition demands sustained effort and place-based strategies to unlock nationwide economic potential beyond major urban hubs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:20:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69869350b81b2b81dcfb1c75.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defense Bets: Elgi, LMW Valuations Face Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defense-Bets-Elgi-LMW-Valuations-Face-Scrutiny/69868f2ab81b2b81dcfb1904</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defense-Bets-Elgi-LMW-Valuations-Face-Scrutiny/69868f2ab81b2b81dcfb1904</guid><description>India's industrial stalwarts Elgi Equipments and Lakshmi Machine Works (LMW) are increasingly aligning with defense and aerospace ambitions. While investor Nemish Shah has significant stakes in both, their recent stock surges are being questioned against ongoing cyclical vulnerabilities and competitive pressures. Elgi's move into high-pressure naval compressors and LMW's role in fighter jet components are driving valuations, but the market may be overlooking inherent sector risks and the disparity between their core and emergent businesses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868f2ab81b2b81dcfb1903.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Jewellery Sector: Growth Amidst Risks &amp; Divergent Stock Fortunes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Jewellery-Sector-Growth-Amidst-Risks-and-Divergent-Stock-Fortunes/69868f1db81b2b81dcfb1894</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Jewellery-Sector-Growth-Amidst-Risks-and-Divergent-Stock-Fortunes/69868f1db81b2b81dcfb1894</guid><description>India's jewellery market is pivoting from cyclical patterns to a structural shift favouring organized retailers. Thangamayil Jewellery demonstrates high capital efficiency with strong regional performance, while P N Gadgil Jewellers leverages its legacy brand for expansion. Despite sector tailwinds, stock performance varies, highlighting distinct risks and investor perceptions. The market now scrutinizes execution, balance-sheet discipline, and the persistent influence of gold price volatility.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:02:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868f1db81b2b81dcfb1893.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPI Surge Elevates Banking Infrastructure to National Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UPI-Surge-Elevates-Banking-Infrastructure-to-National-Risk/69868ea0b81b2b81dcfb173f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UPI-Surge-Elevates-Banking-Infrastructure-to-National-Risk/69868ea0b81b2b81dcfb173f</guid><description>India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) processed an astounding 21.63 billion transactions in December 2025, pushing total annual volume to ₹230 lakh crore. This exponential growth transforms potential IT infrastructure failures from isolated incidents into national-level risks, compelling banks to adopt inherently resilient and intelligent systems. IBM highlights the necessity of 'engineered-in' availability and cryptographic assurance to safeguard an increasingly vital digital financial ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:00:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868ea0b81b2b81dcfb173e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Power Surge: Valuations Test Growth Horizon</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Surge-Valuations-Test-Growth-Horizon/69868e2bb81b2b81dcfb15e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Surge-Valuations-Test-Growth-Horizon/69868e2bb81b2b81dcfb15e1</guid><description>India's electricity demand hit a record 250 GW in FY25, driven by industrialization and cooling needs, projecting a 2,960 TWh future. Power Grid Corp's substantial capital expenditure plans, Tata Power's aggressive renewable pivot, and Hitachi Energy's robust backlog offer growth prospects. However, Hitachi Energy's elevated valuation and potential execution challenges across all three firms warrant investor caution amidst robust sector tailwinds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:58:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868e2bb81b2b81dcfb15e0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Industrial Push: High Ambition Meets Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Industrial-Push-High-Ambition-Meets-Execution-Hurdles/69868dc3b81b2b81dcfb1429</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Industrial-Push-High-Ambition-Meets-Execution-Hurdles/69868dc3b81b2b81dcfb1429</guid><description>India's latest budget outlines an aggressive strategy to transform into a 'strategic industrial power' by targeting high-entry-barrier sectors like semiconductors, AI, and biologics, alongside niche traditional manufacturing. Significant outlays are allocated for initiatives like the Electronics Initiative (₹40,000 crore) and a substantial CCUS push. However, the plan relies heavily on policy incentives and faces formidable global competition, raising questions about execution feasibility and long-term sustainability against established players.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:56:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868dc3b81b2b81dcfb1428.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Farm Shield Risks Wider Friction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-US-Trade-Deal-Farm-Shield-Risks-Wider-Friction/69868dabb81b2b81dcfb1387</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-US-Trade-Deal-Farm-Shield-Risks-Wider-Friction/69868dabb81b2b81dcfb1387</guid><description>India and the United States have agreed to a trade deal that significantly lowers US tariffs on Indian goods from 50% to 18%. However, India's staunch protection of its agricultural sector, excluding items like rice, wheat, dairy, and GM foods, introduces economic friction. This strategy, aimed at safeguarding domestic farmers, risks alienating the US, limiting technological adoption in agriculture, and potentially undermining broader trade benefits, creating a strategic trade-off that warrants close observation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:56:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868dabb81b2b81dcfb1386.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE Board Approves Long-Delayed IPO via Offer for Sale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/NSE-Board-Approves-Long-Delayed-IPO-via-Offer-for-Sale/69868cbbb81b2b81dcfb11e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/NSE-Board-Approves-Long-Delayed-IPO-via-Offer-for-Sale/69868cbbb81b2b81dcfb11e0</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange (NSE) board has greenlit its long-awaited Initial Public Offering (IPO), structured as an Offer-for-Sale (OFS). This pivotal decision, following SEBI's no-objection certificate, marks the culmination of a ten-year journey obstructed by regulatory and governance challenges. The exchange, valued at an estimated $58 billion in private markets, is set to provide liquidity for major shareholders like LIC and SBI, although the OFS structure means no new capital will be raised for expansion. A dedicated committee has been formed to manage the listing process.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:52:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868cbbb81b2b81dcfb11df.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vidarbha's Green Steel Push: Rs 25K Cr In New Projects, M&amp;M Invests Big</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vidarbhas-Green-Steel-Push-Rs-25K-Cr-In-New-Projects-MandM-Invests-Big/698688a2b81b2b81dcfb0e97</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vidarbhas-Green-Steel-Push-Rs-25K-Cr-In-New-Projects-MandM-Invests-Big/698688a2b81b2b81dcfb0e97</guid><description>Maharashtra's Vidarbha region is charting a course to become India's steel manufacturing epicenter, fueled by substantial new investments. At the Advantage Vidarbha 2026 event, Union Minister Nitin Gadkari highlighted the region's world-class iron ore reserves, envisioning a future centered on green steel production. Mahindra &amp; Mahindra committed ₹15,000 crore for integrated automotive and tractor facilities, while Super Smelters pledged ₹10,100 crore for a new steel plant, totaling over ₹25,100 crore in new project commitments. This strategic push aims to leverage indigenous resources, create significant employment, and potentially lower production costs compared to international competitors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:34:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698688a2b81b2b81dcfb0e96.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel Profit Soars, But Global Woes Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Profit-Soars-But-Global-Woes-Linger/69868882b81b2b81dcfb0dcb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Profit-Soars-But-Global-Woes-Linger/69868882b81b2b81dcfb0dcb</guid><description>Tata Steel reported a significant Q3 FY26 profit increase to ₹2,730 crore, driven by record domestic delivery volumes that surpassed six million tonnes and a 14% increase in operations. Revenue rose 6% to ₹57,002 crore. Despite weak global steel prices and oversupply concerns, a new three-year import tariff is expected to bolster domestic producers. However, international operations, particularly in the UK, continue to face substantial losses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:34:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868882b81b2b81dcfb0dca.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDBI Bank Sale Proceeds: Bids In, But Valuation Hurdles Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDBI-Bank-Sale-Proceeds-Bids-In-But-Valuation-Hurdles-Loom/69868792b81b2b81dcfb0c78</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDBI-Bank-Sale-Proceeds-Bids-In-But-Valuation-Hurdles-Loom/69868792b81b2b81dcfb0c78</guid><description>Financial bids for IDBI Bank's strategic divestment have been submitted, advancing the government's plan to sell a 60.7% stake valued around ₹33,000 crore by March 2026. This marks a crucial step in India's first privatization of a former state-owned bank via a LIC-led rescue, aiming to transfer full management control. However, the deal faces scrutiny over its precedent-setting nature and valuation hurdles.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:30:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868792b81b2b81dcfb0c77.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PFC, REC Boards Greenlight Merger in PSU Power Finance Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PFC-REC-Boards-Greenlight-Merger-in-PSU-Power-Finance-Consolidation/698686a2b81b2b81dcfb0aba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PFC-REC-Boards-Greenlight-Merger-in-PSU-Power-Finance-Consolidation/698686a2b81b2b81dcfb0aba</guid><description>The boards of Power Finance Corporation (PFC) and REC have given their in-principle approval to merge the two state-owned entities. This consolidation aims to create a larger balance sheet and strengthen the non-banking financial company (NBFC) structure as part of government initiatives. The move follows Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Budget announcement outlining a restructuring of these public sector undertakings to improve efficiency and scale, particularly as REC's original mandate for rural electrification evolves.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:26:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698686a2b81b2b81dcfb0ab9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FMCG Giants Boost Ad Spend on Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Giants-Boost-Ad-Spend-on-Margin-Gains/6986835eb81b2b81dcfb0848</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Giants-Boost-Ad-Spend-on-Margin-Gains/6986835eb81b2b81dcfb0848</guid><description>Leading Indian consumer goods manufacturers Dabur India, Godrej Consumer Products, and Bajaj Consumer Care are allocating significant portions of their improved operating margins towards enhanced advertising and promotional activities. This strategic reinvestment, driven by falling commodity prices and benign inflation, aims to capitalize on an anticipated surge in consumer demand expected over the next few quarters, fueled by summer seasonality and upcoming sporting events. While commodity costs ease, companies are choosing market share acquisition over pure margin expansion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:12:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986835eb81b2b81dcfb0847.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>