<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:51:37 +0000</pubDate><item><title>BPCL's Offshore HDD Milestone Boosts Infrastructure Prowess</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BPCLs-Offshore-HDD-Milestone-Boosts-Infrastructure-Prowess/6994a8a9fe3bff43302bb7e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BPCLs-Offshore-HDD-Milestone-Boosts-Infrastructure-Prowess/6994a8a9fe3bff43302bb7e1</guid><description>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Limited (BPCL) has successfully executed a challenging 2.3-kilometer offshore Horizontal Directional Drilling (HDD) crossing as part of the Mumbai-Rasayani Pipeline Project. This milestone, achieved in a difficult inter-tidal zone, underscores BPCL's advanced technical expertise in complex offshore engineering. The achievement reinforces India's drive toward energy logistics self-reliance and demonstrates BPCL's enhanced capability in executing critical infrastructure projects with precision and operational excellence, potentially influencing future project cost-efficiency and risk management.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:43:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994a8a9fe3bff43302bb7e0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mistral AI Acquires Koyeb, Fortifying Full-Stack AI &amp; European Sovereignty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mistral-AI-Acquires-Koyeb-Fortifying-Full-Stack-AI-and-European-Sovereignty/6994a82ffe3bff43302bb74d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mistral-AI-Acquires-Koyeb-Fortifying-Full-Stack-AI-and-European-Sovereignty/6994a82ffe3bff43302bb74d</guid><description>French AI leader Mistral AI has acquired Koyeb, a serverless platform for AI application deployment, in its first major M&amp;A move. This integration aims to accelerate Mistral's 'Mistral Compute' cloud infrastructure initiative, enhance its end-to-end AI solutions, and solidify its commitment to European AI sovereignty. The deal brings Koyeb's team and technology in-house, supporting Mistral's ambitious growth targets and its strategy to compete globally by controlling more of the AI value chain, especially as the AI infrastructure market rapidly expands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:41:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994a82ffe3bff43302bb74c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dabur India Restructures Leadership, Eyes Global and Domestic Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dabur-India-Restructures-Leadership-Eyes-Global-and-Domestic-Growth/6994a567fe3bff43302bb5d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dabur-India-Restructures-Leadership-Eyes-Global-and-Domestic-Growth/6994a567fe3bff43302bb5d8</guid><description>Dabur India announced a significant leadership overhaul, redesignating Mohit Malhotra as Global Chief Executive Officer and appointing Herjit S Bhalla as Chief Executive Officer - India Business. This move coincides with a steady Q3 performance showing 6% revenue growth and 7.3% profit increase, driven by persistent rural demand. The company's P/E ratio stands around 49.2x, with a market capitalization nearing ₹91,000 crore. Analysts maintain a 'Hold' consensus, eyeing potential for both global expansion and continued domestic market share gains.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:29:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994a567fe3bff43302bb5d7_1771351183136.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Easing Signals Double-Edged Sword for Metals Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Tariff-Easing-Signals-Double-Edged-Sword-for-Metals-Sector/6994a565fe3bff43302bb5c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Tariff-Easing-Signals-Double-Edged-Sword-for-Metals-Sector/6994a565fe3bff43302bb5c1</guid><description>The U.S. administration has signaled a potential recalibration of steel and aluminum tariffs, aiming to reduce compliance burdens for businesses. While this move could ease global price pressures and improve trade flows, it introduces specific headwinds for companies like Novelis, a Hindalco subsidiary, which had benefited from tariff-induced supply tightness and elevated premiums. The market is reacting with caution, awaiting further clarity on the scope and implementation of any changes, as demonstrated by mixed reactions in US and Indian stock exchanges. Global steel demand is projected to grow modestly by 1.7% in 2026, while aluminum is expected to outperform with a 3.5% growth, driven by sectors like electric vehicles and renewable energy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:29:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994a565fe3bff43302bb5c0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KOEL Q3 Earnings Soar: Record Sales &amp; Profit, Targets $2 Billion Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KOEL-Q3-Earnings-Soar-Record-Sales-and-Profit-Targets-2-Billion-Revenue/6994a526fe3bff43302bb56c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KOEL-Q3-Earnings-Soar-Record-Sales-and-Profit-Targets-2-Billion-Revenue/6994a526fe3bff43302bb56c</guid><description>Kirloskar Oil Engines Limited (KOEL) delivered a strong performance in Q3 FY'26, with standalone net sales jumping 35% year-on-year to ₹1,371 Crores and net profit surging 80% to ₹102 Crores. Consolidated revenue grew 29% to ₹1,873 Crores, with net profit up 90% to ₹126 Crores. The company also unveiled an ambitious 5-year strategy to achieve $2 billion in revenue by FY'30, supported by a ₹700 Crores capital expenditure plan.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:28:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994a526fe3bff43302bb56b_1771350899123.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bayer's $10.5B Roundup Deal: Financial Strain Meets Strategic Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Bayers-105B-Roundup-Deal-Financial-Strain-Meets-Strategic-Uncertainty/6994a526fe3bff43302bb556</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Bayers-105B-Roundup-Deal-Financial-Strain-Meets-Strategic-Uncertainty/6994a526fe3bff43302bb556</guid><description>Bayer AG is advancing a $10.5 billion settlement to resolve Roundup cancer lawsuits, aiming to cap years of legal battles. The deal aims to settle existing and future claims, but significantly increases litigation provisions to nearly $14 billion and is expected to result in negative free cash flow for 2026. While stock reacted positively to reduced uncertainty, the massive financial burden raises questions about future investments and Bayer's strategic position in a sustainability-focused agrochemical market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:28:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994a526fe3bff43302bb555_1771350895073.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HealthCare Global Enterprises Board to Meet on Rights Issue Terms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HealthCare-Global-Enterprises-Board-to-Meet-on-Rights-Issue-Terms/6994a4cafe3bff43302bb4dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HealthCare-Global-Enterprises-Board-to-Meet-on-Rights-Issue-Terms/6994a4cafe3bff43302bb4dd</guid><description>HealthCare Global Enterprises Limited (HCG) has called a Board of Directors meeting for February 24, 2026. The main agenda is to decide on the crucial terms for its previously approved Rights Issue, which aims to raise up to ₹425 Crores. This includes setting the issue price, entitlement ratio, and record date. The move comes amid ongoing efforts to strengthen its financial position and fund growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:26:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994a4cafe3bff43302bb4dc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pulser International's Profit Jump Masks Dilution, Stock Remains Under Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Pulser-Internationals-Profit-Jump-Masks-Dilution-Stock-Remains-Under-Pressure/6994a434fe3bff43302bb3f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Pulser-Internationals-Profit-Jump-Masks-Dilution-Stock-Remains-Under-Pressure/6994a434fe3bff43302bb3f8</guid><description>Pulser International Ltd. announced a near four-fold increase in net profit to ₹3.29 crore for Q3 FY2025-26, driven by an eight-fold revenue jump to ₹39.64 crore. The company also completed a ₹35.70 crore rights issue for expansion. Despite these figures, the stock trades near its 52-week low, reflecting market skepticism regarding growth sustainability and the impact of dilution. Its P/E ratio remains elevated compared to broader sector averages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:24:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994a434fe3bff43302bb3f7_1771350784677.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Burry's $50 Palantir Bet Highlights Extreme Valuation Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Burrys-50-Palantir-Bet-Highlights-Extreme-Valuation-Risk/6994a381fe3bff43302bb307</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Burrys-50-Palantir-Bet-Highlights-Extreme-Valuation-Risk/6994a381fe3bff43302bb307</guid><description>Investor Michael Burry has revealed a substantial put option position on Palantir Technologies, betting the stock will fall below $50 by 2027. This contrarian stance targets a company demonstrating significant revenue growth, particularly in its US commercial segment, and operating within the booming enterprise AI market. Palantir's stock, however, trades at stratospheric valuation multiples that dwarf historical benchmarks and even dot-com era peaks, creating a stark dichotomy between its growth narrative and fundamental metrics. The market now weighs Burry's deep-value skepticism against robust forward guidance and generally positive analyst sentiment, with the stock down nearly 40% from its November 2025 peak.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:21:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994a381fe3bff43302bb306.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Renewable Firm Defends ₹12,800 Cr Valuation Amidst Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Renewable-Firm-Defends-12800-Cr-Valuation-Amidst-Execution-Hurdles/6994a30bfe3bff43302bb252</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Renewable-Firm-Defends-12800-Cr-Valuation-Amidst-Execution-Hurdles/6994a30bfe3bff43302bb252</guid><description>The company is defending its ₹12,800 crore valuation by emphasizing 15 years of value creation and a robust 6 GW platform. With 2.8 GW operational and 3.2 GW under execution, management points to long-term contracted assets and improving project economics despite falling tariffs. However, the market's 'cooling' sentiment and persistent sector-wide execution challenges, including transmission bottlenecks and PPA delays, cast a shadow over the sustainability of its premium valuation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:19:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994a30bfe3bff43302bb251.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Meta Cites India's 3-Hour Takedown Rule Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meta-Cites-Indias-3-Hour-Takedown-Rule-Strain/6994a309fe3bff43302bb23b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meta-Cites-Indias-3-Hour-Takedown-Rule-Strain/6994a309fe3bff43302bb23b</guid><description>Meta Platforms Inc. has expressed significant operational concerns regarding India's newly implemented three-hour content takedown mandate for social media platforms. Vice President Rob Sherman stated the compressed timeline is "operationally challenging," citing insufficient consultation with the industry. These accelerated rules, especially for sensitive content like non-consensual imagery, are part of a broader global trend of increased platform accountability and mark a new compliance hurdle for tech giants in the critical Indian market. The company, with a P/E ratio around 26.7, faces not only these swift content moderation demands but also ongoing data privacy regulations and evolving AI governance frameworks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:19:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994a309fe3bff43302bb23a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Laxmi Dental Revenue Up, But Costs Bite Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Laxmi-Dental-Revenue-Up-But-Costs-Bite-Margins/6994a036cffb93b3e92a8ab1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Laxmi-Dental-Revenue-Up-But-Costs-Bite-Margins/6994a036cffb93b3e92a8ab1</guid><description>Laxmi Dental Limited reported a 7.1% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹66 crore for Q3 FY26. However, margins were impacted by a significant ₹5.8 crore exceptional charge for the new labor code and US tariffs, leading to a ₹2 crore profit. Despite domestic business softness, the company is banking on digital dentistry, AI, and global expansion, especially with US tariff reductions and an upcoming EU FTA, to drive growth and achieve a target 18-20% EBITDA margin in FY27.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:07:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994a036cffb93b3e92a8ab0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Captain Polyplast Shares Tumble as Q3 Results Contradict Company Claims</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Captain-Polyplast-Shares-Tumble-as-Q3-Results-Contradict-Company-Claims/69949fc3cffb93b3e92a6902</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Captain-Polyplast-Shares-Tumble-as-Q3-Results-Contradict-Company-Claims/69949fc3cffb93b3e92a6902</guid><description>Captain Polyplast Limited reported its Q3 FY26 results, but a stark contradiction emerged. While "highlights" claimed record revenue and profit, the official P&amp;L table showed a decline in both for Q3 and 9M FY26 compared to last year. The company faces challenges with high receivables and low cash despite plans for expansion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:05:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69949fc3cffb93b3e92a6901.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Captain Polyplast Posts Record Q3 Revenue, Eyes Big Solar Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Captain-Polyplast-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-Eyes-Big-Solar-Shift/69949fc0cffb93b3e92a68ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Captain-Polyplast-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-Eyes-Big-Solar-Shift/69949fc0cffb93b3e92a68ec</guid><description>Captain Polyplast reported a strong Q3 FY26 with revenue up 40% and profit up 41%. The company is aggressively shifting its business mix towards solar energy, aiming for a 50-50 split with its micro-irrigation segment in three years, supported by government schemes and a recent GST reduction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:05:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69949fc0cffb93b3e92a68eb.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys AI Pact Fuels India's Tech Race Amid Data Hub Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Pact-Fuels-Indias-Tech-Race-Amid-Data-Hub-Ambitions/69949e64cffb93b3e92a438a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Pact-Fuels-Indias-Tech-Race-Amid-Data-Hub-Ambitions/69949e64cffb93b3e92a438a</guid><description>Infosys shares advanced following its strategic partnership with AI firm Anthropic, signaling a significant pivot towards advanced AI solutions. This coincides with India's ambitious target of attracting $200 billion in data center investments to become a premier global artificial intelligence hub. While broader market indices and other heavyweights showed gains, the IT sector's intensified focus on AI integration and national digital infrastructure development highlights a critical, albeit complex, growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:59:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69949e64cffb93b3e92a4389.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BII Exceeds $1B Climate Goal: India's Green Finance Market Matures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/BII-Exceeds-1B-Climate-Goal-Indias-Green-Finance-Market-Matures/69949e5ccffb93b3e92a4355</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/BII-Exceeds-1B-Climate-Goal-Indias-Green-Finance-Market-Matures/69949e5ccffb93b3e92a4355</guid><description>British International Investment (BII) has exceeded its $1 billion climate finance commitment in India, reaching $1.1 billion by February 2026. The UK's development finance institution announced an additional ₹430 million investment in Turno, an electric vehicle battery infrastructure company, to support its new e-bus division. This milestone highlights India's growing green economy but comes amidst significant investment needs and execution risks for its ambitious net-zero targets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:59:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69949e5ccffb93b3e92a4354.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nissan Gravite Enters India at Aggressive ₹5.65 Lakh, Challenges MPV Incumbents</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nissan-Gravite-Enters-India-at-Aggressive-565-Lakh-Challenges-MPV-Incumbents/69949ca3cffb93b3e92a1331</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nissan-Gravite-Enters-India-at-Aggressive-565-Lakh-Challenges-MPV-Incumbents/69949ca3cffb93b3e92a1331</guid><description>Nissan has launched its new Gravite MPV in India with an aggressive introductory ex-showroom price of ₹5.65 lakh, positioning it as the most affordable seven-seater in its class. Built on the CMF-A+ platform shared with the Renault Triber, the Gravite aims to capture market share in a price-sensitive segment, leveraging cost efficiencies to challenge established players like Maruti Suzuki Ertiga and the Triber itself. This launch is a critical component of Nissan's broader strategy to revive its presence in the Indian automotive market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:51:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69949ca3cffb93b3e92a1330.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Sovereign AI Gambit: $217B Push to Challenge Global Giants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Sovereign-AI-Gambit-217B-Push-to-Challenge-Global-Giants/69949c36cffb93b3e929e842</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Sovereign-AI-Gambit-217B-Push-to-Challenge-Global-Giants/69949c36cffb93b3e929e842</guid><description>India is launching an ambitious $217 billion initiative over two years to build sovereign Artificial Intelligence (AI) models and infrastructure, aiming to counter the dominance of US and Chinese large language models (LLMs). This strategic push focuses on developing AI tailored to India's unique linguistic diversity and "strategic requirements," while also establishing a "techno-legal" governance framework. The plan includes substantial investment in compute infrastructure and deep tech, though significant challenges remain in talent acquisition and competing with established global AI leaders.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:49:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69949c36cffb93b3e929e841_1771347825821.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AM Group Secures Land for $25B Clean Energy AI Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AM-Group-Secures-Land-for-25B-Clean-Energy-AI-Hub/69949c32cffb93b3e929e4eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AM-Group-Secures-Land-for-25B-Clean-Energy-AI-Hub/69949c32cffb93b3e929e4eb</guid><description>AM Group initiated its $25 billion, 1 GW AI compute hub in Greater Noida, securing land via LOI from YEIDA. Promoted by Greenko founders, the project targets 350 MW by 2028 and 1 GW by 2030, integrating owned carbon-free power with 500,000 high-performance chips for competitive AI services and positioning Uttar Pradesh as an AI destination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:49:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69949c32cffb93b3e929e4ea_1771347555851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Major Stake Shifts: Aica Kogyo Eyes Control in Stylam, Promoters Exit Yatra</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Major-Stake-Shifts-Aica-Kogyo-Eyes-Control-in-Stylam-Promoters-Exit-Yatra/69949715cffb93b3e9295ac9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Major-Stake-Shifts-Aica-Kogyo-Eyes-Control-in-Stylam-Promoters-Exit-Yatra/69949715cffb93b3e9295ac9</guid><description>February 17, 2026, saw substantial investor activity. Japanese firm Aica Kogyo aggressively increased its stake in Stylam Industries, now holding 27.12% and launching an open offer, signaling a potential takeover. Conversely, promoters divested from travel platform Yatra Online despite sector tailwinds. In real estate, Brookfield expanded its Nirlon holding while a mutual fund sold, and Arvind SmartSpaces saw promoter buying amid fund selling, even as recent earnings concerns surfaced. These moves highlight divergent strategies across sectors experiencing growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:28:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69949715cffb93b3e9295ac8_1771346568955.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kissht IPO De-Risked: Crisil Upgrade Bolsters Investor Confidence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Kissht-IPO-De-Risked-Crisil-Upgrade-Bolsters-Investor-Confidence/69949706cffb93b3e92950ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Kissht-IPO-De-Risked-Crisil-Upgrade-Bolsters-Investor-Confidence/69949706cffb93b3e92950ea</guid><description>Crisil Ratings elevated Si Creva Capital Services, Kissht's NBFC arm, to A-/Stable long-term and A1 short-term ratings. This upgrade, driven by strong business momentum, improving profitability, and a healthy capital position, significantly de-risks Kissht's upcoming Initial Public Offering (IPO). The enhanced creditworthiness validates the company's digital lending model and disciplined underwriting, a crucial factor for investor confidence and potentially more favorable IPO pricing. Assets under management (AUM) grew robustly to Rs 5,533 crore as of September 30, 2025, from Rs 4,087 crore at the fiscal year-end, primarily due to an expanding unsecured personal loan portfolio.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:27:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69949706cffb93b3e92950e9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Deep Tech: Capital Surge Masks Funding Gaps &amp; Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-Deep-Tech-Capital-Surge-Masks-Funding-Gaps-and-Risk/69949657cffb93b3e9291c28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-Deep-Tech-Capital-Surge-Masks-Funding-Gaps-and-Risk/69949657cffb93b3e9291c28</guid><description>India's deep tech sector has seen substantial investment, aggregating $27.9 billion over the last decade, with its share of total VC funding rising to 15% in 2025. However, this surge masks a growing concentration of capital in later-stage deals, potentially starving early-stage innovation. Despite significant government initiatives like the ₹1 lakh crore RDI Fund and policy shifts extending startup status, challenges persist regarding long gestation periods, technical risk, and international competition. The sector's future competitiveness hinges on overcoming these hurdles and demonstrating sustained global success beyond policy pronouncements.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:24:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69949657cffb93b3e9291c27_1771345852010.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mutual Funds Pivot: Banks Rise, IT Faces AI's Profitability Puzzle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Mutual-Funds-Pivot-Banks-Rise-IT-Faces-AIs-Profitability-Puzzle/699495f4cffb93b3e928fe8b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Mutual-Funds-Pivot-Banks-Rise-IT-Faces-AIs-Profitability-Puzzle/699495f4cffb93b3e928fe8b</guid><description>Indian equity mutual funds are significantly reallocating assets, favoring the banking sector which now commands nearly 22% of AUM, up 31% year-on-year to ₹10.24 lakh crore. Finance sector exposure also climbed. Conversely, IT-Software allocations have decreased from 9.1% to 7.4%, and Pharma's portfolio share has shrunk. This shift signals a preference for perceived stability in banking over the uncertain profitability trajectory of IT firms in the AI era, despite recent AI-related collaborations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:23:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699495f4cffb93b3e928fe8a_1771345617132.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABC Industries Plans ₹13.59 Crore Share Sale to Cut Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/ABC-Industries-Plans-1359-Crore-Share-Sale-to-Cut-Debt/699495eacffb93b3e928fb3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/ABC-Industries-Plans-1359-Crore-Share-Sale-to-Cut-Debt/699495eacffb93b3e928fb3d</guid><description>ABC Industries is calling an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on March 11, 2026, to get shareholder nod for raising up to ₹13.59 crore. The money will come from issuing new shares at ₹64 each. Funds are earmarked for paying down debt, improving working capital, and general corporate needs, signaling a move to strengthen the company's financial health.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699495eacffb93b3e928fb3c_1771345613501.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPFO Rate Decision Nears: Political Maneuvering Meets Fund Realities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFO-Rate-Decision-Nears-Political-Maneuvering-Meets-Fund-Realities/699495e9cffb93b3e928fb27</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFO-Rate-Decision-Nears-Political-Maneuvering-Meets-Fund-Realities/699495e9cffb93b3e928fb27</guid><description>The Employees' Provident Fund Organisation (EPFO) is set to finalize the FY26 EPF interest rate on March 2, with expectations favoring an 8.25% hold for the third consecutive year, driven by upcoming state elections and the need to maintain employee sentiment. This decision impacts over 6 crore members relying on the EPFO's substantial ₹25-26 lakh crore corpus. Recent liberalizations in partial withdrawal provisions also present new dynamics for corpus management and investment strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:23:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699495e9cffb93b3e928fb26.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Suraj Industries Boosts Growth with Policy Changes and VRV Foods Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Suraj-Industries-Boosts-Growth-with-Policy-Changes-and-VRV-Foods-Acquisition/699491afcffb93b3e928f30d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Suraj-Industries-Boosts-Growth-with-Policy-Changes-and-VRV-Foods-Acquisition/699491afcffb93b3e928f30d</guid><description>Suraj Industries Ltd is poised for growth following upcoming revisions to Rajasthan's liquor policy, expected to improve realizations. The company is also acquiring a majority stake in VRV Foods Ltd for Rs 37 crore via a rights issue, and its subsidiary is advancing on a new ENA distillery project set for Q1 FY27 commissioning. These moves aim to enhance diversification, backward integration, and margin efficiency.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:05:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699491afcffb93b3e928f30c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Eases Forex Rules: Banks Eye New Hedging Strategies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Eases-Forex-Rules-Banks-Eye-New-Hedging-Strategies/6994913ecffb93b3e928f27c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Eases-Forex-Rules-Banks-Eye-New-Hedging-Strategies/6994913ecffb93b3e928f27c</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has unveiled draft guidelines to grant authorized entities enhanced flexibility in foreign exchange dealings. This move seeks to empower banks and primary dealers in hedging exposures, managing balance sheets, and market-making, while reducing reporting obligations. The proposed changes aim to bolster their responsiveness to global financial dynamics and improve market efficiency amidst evolving economic conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:03:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994913ecffb93b3e928f27b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tamil Nadu Alleges ₹40,000 Cr Fiscal Hit From Union Policies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tamil-Nadu-Alleges-40000-Cr-Fiscal-Hit-From-Union-Policies/6994913bcffb93b3e928f265</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tamil-Nadu-Alleges-40000-Cr-Fiscal-Hit-From-Union-Policies/6994913bcffb93b3e928f265</guid><description>Tamil Nadu faces significant fiscal pressure, with the Finance Minister alleging Union government policies have caused over ₹40,000 crore in financial strain. This includes revenue shortfalls, unexpected deductions, mandated expenditures, and withheld grants, severely constraining state finances. The situation raises concerns about liquidity, borrowing capacity, and the broader implications for regional economic stability and investment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:03:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994913bcffb93b3e928f264.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambitions Clash with Copyright Hurdles, IT Sector Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambitions-Clash-with-Copyright-Hurdles-IT-Sector-Fears/69948f68cffb93b3e928ee60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambitions-Clash-with-Copyright-Hurdles-IT-Sector-Fears/69948f68cffb93b3e928ee60</guid><description>India is significantly expanding its AI capabilities, boosting compute power with 20,000 new GPUs and projecting over $200 billion in AI investments. However, proposed mandatory licensing for AI training data and recent fears of AI disrupting the IT services sector introduce substantial risks. Despite global recognition, with India ranking third in AI vibrancy, the nation navigates a complex path between fostering innovation and managing regulatory and sector-specific challenges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:55:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948f68cffb93b3e928ee5f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asgard Alcobev Buys Brewery Amidst Declining Paper Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asgard-Alcobev-Buys-Brewery-Amidst-Declining-Paper-Business/69948ee8cffb93b3e928ee0e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asgard-Alcobev-Buys-Brewery-Amidst-Declining-Paper-Business/69948ee8cffb93b3e928ee0e</guid><description>Asgard Alcobev Limited, formerly Banganga Paper Industries, has acquired a 78.90% stake in CMJ Breweries Private Limited, making it a subsidiary. This move diversifies the company into the alcoholic beverages sector, aiming for growth in Northeast India. However, this comes as Asgard Alcobev's standalone turnover shows a significant declining trend over the past three fiscal years.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:53:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948ee8cffb93b3e928ee0d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHIT Sees Record Growth Fueled by Assets, But Debt and Fatalities Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NHIT-Sees-Record-Growth-Fueled-by-Assets-But-Debt-and-Fatalities-Emerge/69948df2cffb93b3e92859c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NHIT-Sees-Record-Growth-Fueled-by-Assets-But-Debt-and-Fatalities-Emerge/69948df2cffb93b3e92859c7</guid><description>National Highways Infrastructure Investment Trust (NHIT) reported a massive 88.1% YoY revenue growth and a 437% jump in PAT for Q3 FY2026, driven by integrating Round 4 (NSPPL) assets. However, total debt soared 79.5% to ₹21,840 Cr, and the Debt Service Coverage Ratio (DSCR) fell to 2.05x. Worryingly, two fatalities were reported, highlighting critical safety concerns.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:49:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948df2cffb93b3e92859c6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asgard Alcobev Buys CMJ Breweries, Shifts Focus to Alcohol</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asgard-Alcobev-Buys-CMJ-Breweries-Shifts-Focus-to-Alcohol/69948c8bcffb93b3e92858b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asgard-Alcobev-Buys-CMJ-Breweries-Shifts-Focus-to-Alcohol/69948c8bcffb93b3e92858b0</guid><description>Asgard Alcobev Limited, formerly Banganga Paper Industries, has acquired a majority stake in CMJ Breweries Private Limited in a significant diversification move. The deal, valued at ₹219.04 crore, involves a share swap and preferential issuances. This marks the company's strategic pivot from paper manufacturing to the alcoholic beverage sector. However, concerns arise from CMJ Breweries' declining turnover and a triggered SEBI open offer due to substantial acquisition rules.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:43:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948c8bcffb93b3e92858af.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Foods &amp; Inns Stocks Dip as Q3 Profit Falls Amidst Investor Clash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Foods-and-Inns-Stocks-Dip-as-Q3-Profit-Falls-Amidst-Investor-Clash/69948c87cffb93b3e9285898</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Foods-and-Inns-Stocks-Dip-as-Q3-Profit-Falls-Amidst-Investor-Clash/69948c87cffb93b3e9285898</guid><description>Foods &amp; Inns Limited reported a challenging Q3 FY26, with revenues flat year-on-year and profit declining significantly. The company cited US tariff uncertainties affecting sales and a rise in short-term debt. A notable point was a defensive exchange between management and an investor during the earnings call, raising governance questions. While the frozen food segment shows strength, the overall picture is clouded by financial pressures and operational headwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:43:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948c87cffb93b3e9285897.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Valecha Engineering Q3 Profit Turns Around, But Auditor Flags Major Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valecha-Engineering-Q3-Profit-Turns-Around-But-Auditor-Flags-Major-Risks/69948b24cffb93b3e928577e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valecha-Engineering-Q3-Profit-Turns-Around-But-Auditor-Flags-Major-Risks/69948b24cffb93b3e928577e</guid><description>Valecha Engineering reported a standalone profit for Q3 FY26, a turnaround from last year. However, consolidated losses persist. Crucially, the auditor's report raises significant concerns about asset recoverability, subsidiary financial distress, and accounting practices, casting a shadow over the results.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:37:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948b24cffb93b3e928577d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHIT to Buy Roads for ₹6,220 Cr, Eyes Equity Raise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NHIT-to-Buy-Roads-for-6220-Cr-Eyes-Equity-Raise/69948ad1cffb93b3e92856de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NHIT-to-Buy-Roads-for-6220-Cr-Eyes-Equity-Raise/69948ad1cffb93b3e92856de</guid><description>National Highways Infra Trust (NHIT) is holding its 6th Extra-Ordinary Meeting on March 12, 2026, to approve the ₹6,220.90 Crore acquisition of 'Round 5 Roads'. The Trust also plans to raise funds through preferential issue and institutional placement to finance this deal and other objectives. Unitholders will vote on these significant proposals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:35:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948ad1cffb93b3e92856dd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asgard Alcobev Buys Breweries, Plans Share Sale Triggering Open Offer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asgard-Alcobev-Buys-Breweries-Plans-Share-Sale-Triggering-Open-Offer/69948acecffb93b3e92856c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asgard-Alcobev-Buys-Breweries-Plans-Share-Sale-Triggering-Open-Offer/69948acecffb93b3e92856c8</guid><description>Asgard Alcobev Limited has approved acquiring 78.90% of CMJ Breweries Private Limited for ₹219 crore via share swap and cash. The company also plans a preferential allotment of shares and warrants at ₹1.45 per unit. This move triggers a SEBI open offer, potentially leading to new promoters taking control.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:35:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948acecffb93b3e92856c7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Great Rotation: Mid-Caps Lead, AI Fuels IT Sector Rebound</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Great-Rotation-Mid-Caps-Lead-AI-Fuels-IT-Sector-Rebound/69948a47cffb93b3e92855f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Great-Rotation-Mid-Caps-Lead-AI-Fuels-IT-Sector-Rebound/69948a47cffb93b3e92855f9</guid><description>A strategic rotation is underway in the Indian equity market, with growth momentum increasingly shifting from Nifty 50 heavyweights to mid and small-cap companies. This broadening of the economic cycle is supported by realistic earnings growth expectations of around 12-15% for 2026, coupled with stabilizing margins. Concurrently, the Information Technology (IT) sector, despite facing headwinds from AI disruption fears and elevated valuations, is being viewed with contrarian optimism by firms like Motilal Oswal AMC, driven by the transformative potential of Artificial Intelligence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:33:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69948a47cffb93b3e92855f8_1771342582757.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ServiceNow Pivots to AI-Executed Workflows, Bets on Trust and India for Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ServiceNow-Pivots-to-AI-Executed-Workflows-Bets-on-Trust-and-India-for-Growth/69948a39cffb93b3e92855db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ServiceNow-Pivots-to-AI-Executed-Workflows-Bets-on-Trust-and-India-for-Growth/69948a39cffb93b3e92855db</guid><description>ServiceNow is intensifying its focus on AI-driven enterprise productivity, preparing for a February 28th launch aimed at enabling an "autonomous workforce." This strategic shift moves beyond AI assistance to AI-executed workflows, a move poised to boost enterprise efficiency and potentially ServiceNow's margins. The company is reinforcing its AI trust and governance framework with its AI Control Tower and Veza acquisition, positioning itself as a secure platform for regulated industries. India plays a dual role, hosting nearly half of its R&amp;D and serving as a key adoption market. Despite recent stock underperformance, analysts maintain a 'Strong Buy' consensus, citing significant upside potential.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:33:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69948a39cffb93b3e92855da_1771342528301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Talks: Pulses Negotiate Beyond Factsheet Revisions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Talks-Pulses-Negotiate-Beyond-Factsheet-Revisions/6994885ccffb93b3e92854c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Talks-Pulses-Negotiate-Beyond-Factsheet-Revisions/6994885ccffb93b3e92854c6</guid><description>Trade negotiations between the United States and India are ongoing regarding agricultural products, specifically pulses, despite their removal from a revised White House factsheet. Sources indicate that while the omission aimed to align the factsheet with the joint statement, discussions on pulses remain active and are expected to be a focus in upcoming Washington meetings. Union Agriculture Minister Shivraj Singh Chouhan has publicly supported the trade deal, emphasizing India's deficit in pulse production and the necessity of imports to meet domestic demand, while criticizing political opposition to the agreement. The intricate nature of agricultural trade encompassing approximately 1,800 tariff lines means not all details are captured in initial joint statements, with further clarity anticipated from face-to-face discussions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:25:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994885ccffb93b3e92854c5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Conglomerates Forge Infrastructure Amid Talent Hunt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Conglomerates-Forge-Infrastructure-Amid-Talent-Hunt/69948767cffb93b3e928540a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Conglomerates-Forge-Infrastructure-Amid-Talent-Hunt/69948767cffb93b3e928540a</guid><description>Reliance Industries and Adani Group are aggressively pursuing AI talent at the India AI Impact Summit, reflecting a broader national strategy to become an AI powerhouse. Significant infrastructure investments, including $100 billion from Adani for data centers and projected national AI investments exceeding $200 billion, underscore this ambition. While talent acquisition is key, the focus is shifting towards comprehensive AI ecosystem development, positioning India as a global hub. This comes as the sector's rapid growth faces scrutiny over talent costs and broader economic headwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:21:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948767cffb93b3e9285409.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>