<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:59:40 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Hariom Pipe Surges to Record Revenue, Bets on Renewables Despite Margin Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hariom-Pipe-Surges-to-Record-Revenue-Bets-on-Renewables-Despite-Margin-Dip/698982f2b81b2b81dcfeaa52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hariom-Pipe-Surges-to-Record-Revenue-Bets-on-Renewables-Despite-Margin-Dip/698982f2b81b2b81dcfeaa52</guid><description>Hariom Pipe Industries achieved record revenues in Q3 and 9MFY26, driven by 21% YoY volume and revenue growth. However, EBITDA margins compressed to 12.47% (Q3) and 12.55% (9MFY26) YoY. Profit after tax grew slower, impacted by higher costs. The company is expanding into renewable energy, with a 60 MW solar LOA. FY25 saw a Net Debt/EBITDA of 2.0 and a low interest cover of 2.85x.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:47:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698982f2b81b2b81dcfeaa51_1770619866773.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MakeMyTrip Taps Premium Travel via Minor Hotels Alliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/MakeMyTrip-Taps-Premium-Travel-via-Minor-Hotels-Alliance/698982c0b81b2b81dcfea972</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/MakeMyTrip-Taps-Premium-Travel-via-Minor-Hotels-Alliance/698982c0b81b2b81dcfea972</guid><description>MakeMyTrip has forged a strategic alliance with Minor Hotels, a global hospitality group, to enhance its international hotel inventory. This move is designed to capture the escalating demand for premium and luxury accommodations from Indian travelers. The collaboration integrates Minor Hotels' extensive portfolio, featuring brands like Anantara and Tivoli, onto the MakeMyTrip platform, aiming to solidify its position in the high-margin segment of India's rapidly expanding outbound tourism market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698982c0b81b2b81dcfea971_1770619881698.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Karnataka Frees Up Land: Taller Projects to Reshape Bengaluru Skyline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Karnataka-Frees-Up-Land-Taller-Projects-to-Reshape-Bengaluru-Skyline/6989826eb81b2b81dcfea7a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Karnataka-Frees-Up-Land-Taller-Projects-to-Reshape-Bengaluru-Skyline/6989826eb81b2b81dcfea7a6</guid><description>Karnataka has eased building regulations in industrial areas, permitting higher Floor Area Ratio (FAR) up to 5.2, purchasable. This policy change is set to spur significant expansion in industrial, commercial, and residential real estate, especially around Bengaluru, addressing land scarcity and boosting economic activity and job creation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:45:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989826eb81b2b81dcfea7a5_1770619657238.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Refiners Tap Venezuelan Crude Amid Geopolitical Realignments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Refiners-Tap-Venezuelan-Crude-Amid-Geopolitical-Realignments/69898257b81b2b81dcfea6de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Refiners-Tap-Venezuelan-Crude-Amid-Geopolitical-Realignments/69898257b81b2b81dcfea6de</guid><description>Indian Oil Corp (IOC) and Hindustan Petroleum Corp (HPCL) have jointly secured two million barrels of Venezuelan Merey crude for April delivery. This marks HPCL's first purchase of Venezuelan oil, while IOC resumes its engagement from 2024. The move signals India's strategic pivot towards diversifying its energy sources and leveraging potentially cost-effective supplies, navigating complex international sanctions and trade agreements. Pricing is benchmarked against Dubai crude, aligning with market rates seen in similar transactions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:44:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69898257b81b2b81dcfea6dd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CG Foods Fined ₹90.9 Lakh for GST Profiteering</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/CG-Foods-Fined-909-Lakh-for-GST-Profiteering/6989823ab81b2b81dcfea5f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/CG-Foods-Fined-909-Lakh-for-GST-Profiteering/6989823ab81b2b81dcfea5f8</guid><description>India's Goods and Services Tax Appellate Tribunal (GSTAT) has ordered instant noodle maker CG Foods to deposit ₹90.9 lakh for unlawfully profiteering by failing to pass on a Goods and Services Tax (GST) rate reduction to consumers. The tribunal rejected CG Foods' defense of rising raw material and freight costs, emphasizing that base prices were increased post-GST cut. This ruling signals a critical compliance checkpoint for Fast-Moving Consumer Goods (FMCG) companies navigating India's complex tax and pricing regulations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:44:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989823ab81b2b81dcfea5f7_1770619593218.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Velocity Bets ₹100 Cr on Integrated Logistics for E-commerce Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Velocity-Bets-100-Cr-on-Integrated-Logistics-for-E-commerce-Dominance/6989814eb81b2b81dcfea418</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Velocity-Bets-100-Cr-on-Integrated-Logistics-for-E-commerce-Dominance/6989814eb81b2b81dcfea418</guid><description>Velocity is investing ₹100 crore over two years to scale Velocity Shipping, its AI-enhanced logistics platform. Funded internally, this move targets critical e-commerce bottlenecks by integrating capital provision with fulfillment services. Velocity Shipping, already contributing 40% of total revenue with 70% MoM growth, seeks to bolster last-mile capabilities and leverage AI for operational efficiency, positioning itself as a comprehensive digital infrastructure provider for India's expanding D2C sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:40:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989814eb81b2b81dcfea417_1770619388500.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Malaysia Pact: De-Dollarization Push and Semiconductor Ties Deepen</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Malaysia-Pact-De-Dollarization-Push-and-Semiconductor-Ties-Deepen/698980dcb81b2b81dcfea26d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Malaysia-Pact-De-Dollarization-Push-and-Semiconductor-Ties-Deepen/698980dcb81b2b81dcfea26d</guid><description>India and Malaysia have inked a raft of agreements, intensifying bilateral cooperation and strategic alignment. A key focus is the push towards using local currencies (Indian Rupee and Malaysian Ringgit) for trade and investment, aiming to reduce dollar dependence. The pact also prioritizes joint ventures in the critical semiconductor sector, leveraging Malaysia's established testing and packaging capabilities with India's manufacturing ambitions. This deepened partnership underscores a broader recalibration of economic and geopolitical influence in the Indo-Pacific, aiming to boost trade beyond $20 billion and build more resilient supply chains.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:38:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698980dcb81b2b81dcfea26c_1770619257977.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SAIL, Ventive Hospitality: Stocks to Watch Amid Growth &amp; Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/SAIL-Ventive-Hospitality-Stocks-to-Watch-Amid-Growth-and-Risk/69897fe5b81b2b81dcfea066</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/SAIL-Ventive-Hospitality-Stocks-to-Watch-Amid-Growth-and-Risk/69897fe5b81b2b81dcfea066</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services has identified Steel Authority of India Limited (SAIL) and Ventive Hospitality as key investment opportunities. SAIL's operational execution and volume growth are strengthening its outlook, while Ventive Hospitality is expanding its luxury hospitality footprint. However, a closer look reveals differing risk profiles, with SAIL facing input cost pressures and Ventive Hospitality grappling with high valuations and recent analyst downgrades. This report dissects their performance against sector trends and peer comparisons.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:34:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897fe5b81b2b81dcfea065_1770618914181.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold's Rebound Faces Macro Data Test, USDINR's Local Influence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Rebound-Faces-Macro-Data-Test-USDINRs-Local-Influence/69897f15b81b2b81dcfe9e83</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Rebound-Faces-Macro-Data-Test-USDINRs-Local-Influence/69897f15b81b2b81dcfe9e83</guid><description>Gold prices have demonstrated a strong V-shaped recovery, surpassing key technical levels and achieving earlier targets. However, the precious metal faces a week of heightened volatility driven by crucial US economic indicators like inflation and retail sales. Market sentiment hinges on the Federal Reserve's policy path. Domestically, the Indian rupee's performance against the dollar significantly influences MCX gold prices, adding a layer of complexity to the broader bullish trend. Central bank buying continues to provide a structural underpinning for demand.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:30:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897f15b81b2b81dcfe9e82_1770618949698.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gargi Fashion Jewellery Revenue Surges 27%, But Margins Contract Amid Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Gargi-Fashion-Jewellery-Revenue-Surges-27percent-But-Margins-Contract-Amid-Expansion/69897ef5b81b2b81dcfe9d6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Gargi-Fashion-Jewellery-Revenue-Surges-27percent-But-Margins-Contract-Amid-Expansion/69897ef5b81b2b81dcfe9d6a</guid><description>PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Limited reported a robust 27.06% YoY revenue growth to ₹46.06 Crores for Q3 FY26. However, profit after tax (PAT) grew slower at 15.92% YoY to ₹10.60 Crores, leading to a compression in net profit margins to 22.99% from 25.23% last year. The company expanded its retail footprint by opening 16 new stores and raised funds via a preferential issue to support growth initiatives. Other income also saw a significant jump.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:30:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897ef5b81b2b81dcfe9d69_1770618920163.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paisalo Digital: AI Drive Fuels Growth, Valuations Under Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digital-AI-Drive-Fuels-Growth-Valuations-Under-Scrutiny/69897ca1b81b2b81dcfe996e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digital-AI-Drive-Fuels-Growth-Valuations-Under-Scrutiny/69897ca1b81b2b81dcfe996e</guid><description>Paisalo Digital achieved a record quarterly Profit After Tax (PAT) of ₹663 million, up 6% year-on-year, with Assets Under Management (AUM) rising 16% to ₹55,082 million for Q3 FY26. Disbursements increased 7%, supported by 492 new touchpoints and a customer base of 14 million. The company is aggressively integrating artificial intelligence across its operations, aiming to enhance lending, risk management, and customer journeys to secure future growth within the MSME sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:20:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897ca1b81b2b81dcfe996d_1770618625414.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tax Reform Faces Bureaucratic Friction, Clouding Investor Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Reform-Faces-Bureaucratic-Friction-Clouding-Investor-Outlook/69897c5db81b2b81dcfe97cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Reform-Faces-Bureaucratic-Friction-Clouding-Investor-Outlook/69897c5db81b2b81dcfe97cb</guid><description>Senior tax officials are reportedly seeking access to anonymized appeal orders without clear legal standing, creating significant friction for India's "faceless" tax administration. This challenge threatens the core principles of transparency and efficiency intended by the National Faceless Appeal Scheme and the upcoming Draft Income Tax Rules 2026. Such bureaucratic resistance could undermine India's progress in enhancing ease of doing business and attracting foreign direct investment, signaling potential caution for market participants.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:19:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897c5db81b2b81dcfe97ca_1770618421283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Gain on Trade Deals; Analysts Urge Buy-the-Dip Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Gain-on-Trade-Deals-Analysts-Urge-Buy-the-Dip-Strategy/69897c3ab81b2b81dcfe96a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Gain-on-Trade-Deals-Analysts-Urge-Buy-the-Dip-Strategy/69897c3ab81b2b81dcfe96a6</guid><description>Indian equities have climbed over 5% in the past fortnight, driven by progress on free trade agreements with the European Union and the United States. Despite a budget day dip due to a securities transaction tax hike, the Sensex and Nifty 50 are trading higher. Analysts suggest most positives are now priced in, advising investors to hold existing positions and accumulate stocks on market corrections for long-term value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:18:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897c3ab81b2b81dcfe96a5_1770618424554.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trade Deal Sparks Gems Rally; Earnings Shine</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Trade-Deal-Sparks-Gems-Rally-Earnings-Shine/69897c2ab81b2b81dcfe961b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Trade-Deal-Sparks-Gems-Rally-Earnings-Shine/69897c2ab81b2b81dcfe961b</guid><description>Gems and jewellery stocks rallied sharply, with Goldiam International and Kalyan Jewellers leading gains up to 18% on Monday. The surge followed a US-India trade deal framework potentially reducing diamond tariffs and strong Q3 FY26 earnings reports. Key exporters like Goldiam saw revenue rise 18% and profit jump 37%, while Kalyan Jewellers reported a 90% PAT increase. The sector benefits from potential zero tariffs on cut and polished diamonds, reversing a trend of 44% export decline to the US market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:18:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897c2ab81b2b81dcfe961a_1770618255549.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Banks Surge: SBI Fuels Rally, But Sustainability Questions Arise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Surge-SBI-Fuels-Rally-But-Sustainability-Questions-Arise/69897adbb81b2b81dcfe93c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Surge-SBI-Fuels-Rally-But-Sustainability-Questions-Arise/69897adbb81b2b81dcfe93c8</guid><description>State Bank of India's robust third-quarter earnings have ignited a significant rally in public sector banks, pushing the Nifty PSU Bank index to unprecedented levels. Strong loan growth and improved operational efficiency at SBI, coupled with a broader market sentiment favoring state-run lenders, have driven outperformance against the Nifty 50. However, concerns are surfacing regarding the sustainability of these gains, the widening gap between credit and deposit growth rates, and the valuation premium some private sector banks command.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:12:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897adbb81b2b81dcfe93c7_1770618176160.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC Bank Adjusts Lending Rates Selectively Amidst Stable RBI Stance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-Bank-Adjusts-Lending-Rates-Selectively-Amidst-Stable-RBI-Stance/69897abcb81b2b81dcfe92ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-Bank-Adjusts-Lending-Rates-Selectively-Amidst-Stable-RBI-Stance/69897abcb81b2b81dcfe92ec</guid><description>HDFC Bank has implemented a marginal reduction of up to 5 basis points in its Marginal Cost of Funds-based Lending Rates (MCLR) across specific loan tenures, effective February 7. This move, occurring despite the Reserve Bank of India holding its policy repo rate steady, highlights the bank's independent management of funding costs and liquidity. The selective nature of the rate cut suggests a strategic approach to optimizing its lending portfolio and balancing competitive pressures with margin considerations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:12:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897abcb81b2b81dcfe92eb_1770618107317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samsung's AI Surge Contrasts Groww's Lock-In Liquidity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Samsungs-AI-Surge-Contrasts-Growws-Lock-In-Liquidity/69897a70b81b2b81dcfe9182</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Samsungs-AI-Surge-Contrasts-Growws-Lock-In-Liquidity/69897a70b81b2b81dcfe9182</guid><description>Samsung Electronics is experiencing a surge, driven by its expanding capacity in AI chip production, specifically HBM4 memory chips. This comes as Indian fintech Groww (Billionbrains Garage Ventures Ltd.) faces a liquidity event with shareholder lock-in periods expiring, potentially releasing shares worth nearly ₹8,600 crore into the market, with Groww's portion alone valued at approximately ₹2,525 crore. This divergence highlights contrasting market drivers: global technological advancement versus domestic capital market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:10:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897a70b81b2b81dcfe9181_1770618005979.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Surges on FII Return, Trade Deal Hype; SBI Hits Record</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Market-Surges-on-FII-Return-Trade-Deal-Hype-SBI-Hits-Record/69897a44b81b2b81dcfe908d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Market-Surges-on-FII-Return-Trade-Deal-Hype-SBI-Hits-Record/69897a44b81b2b81dcfe908d</guid><description>Dalal Street experienced a significant upswing, driven by renewed foreign institutional investor (FII) inflows and optimism surrounding an interim India-US trade agreement. The benchmark Sensex and Nifty indices saw substantial gains on February 9, 2026. State Bank of India (SBI) shares surged to a record high, propelled by stellar December quarter results and an upgraded loan growth forecast. The Nifty PSU Bank index also posted strong gains, reflecting broad sector strength.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897a44b81b2b81dcfe908c_1770617766661.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Legal GCC Surge: Efficiency Gains Mask Evolving Regulatory Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Legal-GCC-Surge-Efficiency-Gains-Mask-Evolving-Regulatory-Risks/69897957b81b2b81dcfe8ebc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Legal-GCC-Surge-Efficiency-Gains-Mask-Evolving-Regulatory-Risks/69897957b81b2b81dcfe8ebc</guid><description>Global Capability Centres (GCCs) in India are rapidly expanding their legal operations, leveraging a vast talent pool and cost advantages. This trend, driven by efficiency gains and India's common law heritage, presents significant opportunities. However, multinational corporations must contend with an intricate and evolving regulatory landscape, including new data protection laws and complex labour codes, which introduce substantial compliance challenges and operational risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:06:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897957b81b2b81dcfe8ebb_1770617747643.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exide Industries Surges Past ₹4,000 Cr Revenue Amidst Cost Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Exide-Industries-Surges-Past-4000-Cr-Revenue-Amidst-Cost-Headwinds/698978b4b81b2b81dcfe8cfe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Exide-Industries-Surges-Past-4000-Cr-Revenue-Amidst-Cost-Headwinds/698978b4b81b2b81dcfe8cfe</guid><description>Exide Industries reported Q3 FY2025-26 sales crossing INR4,000 crores, a 5% YoY increase, driven by strong auto OEM (+25%) and aftermarket growth. Despite significant material cost pressures and a weakening rupee, the company maintained its EBITDA margin at 11.7% YoY, achieving sequential QoQ improvements through cost excellence and product mix optimization. Future growth hinges on recovering telecom and export segments, with strategic investments in lithium-ion and data center opportunities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:03:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698978b4b81b2b81dcfe8cfd_1770617487835.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gallantt Ispat Misses Q3 Estimates; Sees Profit Drop Amid Steel Prices</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gallantt-Ispat-Misses-Q3-Estimates-Sees-Profit-Drop-Amid-Steel-Prices/6989788db81b2b81dcfe8bdb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gallantt-Ispat-Misses-Q3-Estimates-Sees-Profit-Drop-Amid-Steel-Prices/6989788db81b2b81dcfe8bdb</guid><description>Gallantt Ispat reported a Q3 FY26 revenue of ₹1,089 Cr, down 2.7% YoY, and PAT of ₹100 Cr, down 14.0% YoY. This missed analyst expectations for significant growth. The decline was attributed to softer steel price realisations. However, the nine-month period showed resilience with revenue up 1% and EBITDA up 10%, driven by operational efficiencies and margin expansion to 17.45%. The company, with a low Debt/Equity of 0.1x, is planning ₹3,000 Cr capex for integration and expansion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:02:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989788db81b2b81dcfe8bda_1770617291294.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Prices Surge in India Amidst Dollar Weakness, Geopolitical Tensions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Surge-in-India-Amidst-Dollar-Weakness-Geopolitical-Tensions/69897865b81b2b81dcfe8ae5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Surge-in-India-Amidst-Dollar-Weakness-Geopolitical-Tensions/69897865b81b2b81dcfe8ae5</guid><description>Gold prices in India saw a notable increase on February 9, 2026, with 24-carat gold reaching ₹157,450 per 10 grams. This surge is primarily fueled by a weakening US dollar, robust buying from China's central bank, and escalating geopolitical tensions. However, Indian prices remain substantially higher than international benchmarks like Dubai, and the market faces ongoing volatility influenced by central bank policies and upcoming economic data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:02:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897865b81b2b81dcfe8ae4_1770617137088.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Seven Investors Launch ₹1.42 Cr Open Offer for Nirbhay Colours India Amidst Name Change</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Seven-Investors-Launch-142-Cr-Open-Offer-for-Nirbhay-Colours-India-Amidst-Name-Change/698977ebb81b2b81dcfe892b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Seven-Investors-Launch-142-Cr-Open-Offer-for-Nirbhay-Colours-India-Amidst-Name-Change/698977ebb81b2b81dcfe892b</guid><description>A consortium of seven investors, including Seher Retail Private Limited, has launched an open offer to acquire up to 42.38% of Nirbhay Colours India Limited for ₹1.42 crore at ₹10 per share. The move signals a change in control and management, with plans for expansion and diversification. Nirbhay Colours, a BSE-listed textile firm, has a history of regulatory penalties for late filings, and is undergoing a name change to Craftroot Retail Limited. The offer period runs from February 3 to February 16, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:00:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698977ebb81b2b81dcfe892a_1770616994895.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Surges 4.13% on Global Cues, Eyes $80 Mark</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-413percent-on-Global-Cues-Eyes-80-Mark/69897777b81b2b81dcfe87cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-413percent-on-Global-Cues-Eyes-80-Mark/69897777b81b2b81dcfe87cc</guid><description>Silver prices in India surged 4.13% on February 9, 2026, with 1 kg reaching ₹260,310. The metal's climb, pushing towards $80 on COMEX, was fueled by renewed investor aggression after a sharp sell-off. Global events, including Japan's election results and US-Iran talks, alongside anticipation of key US economic data, are shaping sentiment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:58:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897777b81b2b81dcfe87cb_1770616860545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paisalo Digital Posts Record PAT, Eyes AI-First Future with Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digital-Posts-Record-PAT-Eyes-AI-First-Future-with-Growth/6989760db81b2b81dcfe85ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digital-Posts-Record-PAT-Eyes-AI-First-Future-with-Growth/6989760db81b2b81dcfe85ee</guid><description>Paisalo Digital reported its highest-ever quarterly Profit After Tax (PAT) of Rs 663 Mn, up 29% QoQ and 6% YoY, for Q3FY26. Assets Under Management (AUM) grew 16% YoY to Rs 55,082 Mn, supported by an 18% YoY jump in Total Income. The company is strategically pivoting to an AI-first approach, aiming to leverage technology for sustainable growth. Asset quality improved with GNPA at 0.83% and NNPA at 0.66%, while the cost of borrowing decreased significantly.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:52:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989760db81b2b81dcfe85ed_1770616445917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCC: JJM Payments Boost Outlook, Q4 Execution Eyed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-JJM-Payments-Boost-Outlook-Q4-Execution-Eyed/6989751bb81b2b81dcfe844d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-JJM-Payments-Boost-Outlook-Q4-Execution-Eyed/6989751bb81b2b81dcfe844d</guid><description>NCC Limited is set for a Q4 FY26 execution ramp-up, bolstered by the commencement of Jal Jeevan Mission (JJM) project payments from January 2026. These anticipated receipts, expected to be substantial in February and March, aim to significantly reduce the company's working capital cycle and debt levels. This financial uplift follows a challenging Q3 FY26 marked by continued revenue declines and profitability dips, primarily attributed to delayed project clearances and JJM payment issues. Despite these headwinds, NCC maintains a robust order book, positioning it to benefit from increased government infrastructure expenditure and a more favorable payment environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:48:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989751bb81b2b81dcfe844c_1770616205465.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Tariffs Cut, But Geopolitical Leash Tightens</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Cut-But-Geopolitical-Leash-Tightens/69897340b81b2b81dcfe8258</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Cut-But-Geopolitical-Leash-Tightens/69897340b81b2b81dcfe8258</guid><description>India and the United States have established a framework for an Interim Trade Agreement, lowering US reciprocal tariffs on key Indian exports to 18%. This pact mandates India cease Russian oil imports, committing to US energy purchases. While offering immediate relief to sectors like textiles and leather, the deal's reliance on US energy supply and geopolitical alignment introduces strategic risks, overshadowing short-term tariff gains.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:40:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897340b81b2b81dcfe8257_1770615797886.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lloyds Engineering: Promoter Exit Fuels Consolidation Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Engineering-Promoter-Exit-Fuels-Consolidation-Play/69897264b81b2b81dcfe8019</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Engineering-Promoter-Exit-Fuels-Consolidation-Play/69897264b81b2b81dcfe8019</guid><description>Lloyds Engineering Works Ltd. saw its share price advance following a substantial block deal where promoter entities likely divested approximately 9% of their holdings. This transaction occurred shortly after the company reported a robust 69.5% year-on-year increase in net profit for its third quarter, alongside revenue growth. The stake acquisition by Triveni Earth Movers, and the company's recent approval for a multi-entity merger, suggest a strategic reorientation aimed at consolidating operations and enhancing its market position within the industrial engineering sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:36:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897264b81b2b81dcfe8018_1770615606300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sun TV Jumps on IPL Asset Hype Despite Weak Q3 Operations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Sun-TV-Jumps-on-IPL-Asset-Hype-Despite-Weak-Q3-Operations/6989724fb81b2b81dcfe7f6c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Sun-TV-Jumps-on-IPL-Asset-Hype-Despite-Weak-Q3-Operations/6989724fb81b2b81dcfe7f6c</guid><description>Sun TV Network shares climbed on Monday, February 9, breaking a losing streak, even as the company reported a decline in EBITDA and net profit for Q3 FY26. This rally appears driven by optimism surrounding the valuation of its IPL franchise, Sunrisers Hyderabad, overshadowing a challenging operational quarter marked by increased expenses and a drag on advertising revenue. While subscription income showed growth, rising costs significantly compressed operating margins, leading to a lower bottom line.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:36:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989724fb81b2b81dcfe7f6b_1770615554005.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashiana Housing Books ₹767 Cr Gurugram Project, Surpasses ₹2000 Cr FY Sales</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ashiana-Housing-Books-767-Cr-Gurugram-Project-Surpasses-2000-Cr-FY-Sales/698970e2b81b2b81dcfe7b8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ashiana-Housing-Books-767-Cr-Gurugram-Project-Surpasses-2000-Cr-FY-Sales/698970e2b81b2b81dcfe7b8e</guid><description>Ashiana Housing reported strong sales momentum, converting INR 767.23 crores for its Gurugram project "Ashiana Aaroham" (Phase 1 &amp; 2). The company has now surpassed INR 2,000 crores in total area booked for the current fiscal year, underscoring robust customer demand and effective project execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:30:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698970e2b81b2b81dcfe7b8d_1770615264833.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Automotive Axles Posts 6% Revenue Growth, Margins Expand Amidst Analyst Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Automotive-Axles-Posts-6percent-Revenue-Growth-Margins-Expand-Amidst-Analyst-Concerns/69897096b81b2b81dcfe7a00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Automotive-Axles-Posts-6percent-Revenue-Growth-Margins-Expand-Amidst-Analyst-Concerns/69897096b81b2b81dcfe7a00</guid><description>Automotive Axles reported a Q3 FY26 revenue of ₹562 crore, marking a 6% year-on-year (YoY) increase and a significant 21% sequential jump. EBITDA rose 14% YoY to ₹72.5 crore, with margins expanding by 93 basis points YoY to 12.9%. An ₹11.9 crore exceptional item related to wage code implementation impacted PBT. Despite growth, analysts expressed concern over the company's performance lagging industry rates. The FY27 outlook remains uncertain.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:28:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69897096b81b2b81dcfe79ff_1770615150552.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Surges to Record High on Stellar Q3; Valuation Nears Threshold</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Surges-to-Record-High-on-Stellar-Q3-Valuation-Nears-Threshold/6989706ab81b2b81dcfe78f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Surges-to-Record-High-on-Stellar-Q3-Valuation-Nears-Threshold/6989706ab81b2b81dcfe78f3</guid><description>State Bank of India (SBI) shares reached a new peak, surging nearly 6% following its strongest-ever quarterly profit of ₹21,028 crore for Q3 FY26. This robust performance, marked by significant asset quality improvements and strong loan growth, has garnered widespread 'Buy' ratings from brokerages. However, underlying concerns regarding deposit growth lagging advances and potential margin pressures, coupled with a valuation that is starting to reflect recent gains, warrant a closer examination of sustainability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:28:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989706ab81b2b81dcfe78f2_1770615060671.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Embraer Deepens India Ties, Bolstering Global Aerospace Supply Chain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Embraer-Deepens-India-Ties-Bolstering-Global-Aerospace-Supply-Chain/69896f0cb81b2b81dcfe7749</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Embraer-Deepens-India-Ties-Bolstering-Global-Aerospace-Supply-Chain/69896f0cb81b2b81dcfe7749</guid><description>Embraer is significantly enhancing its supply chain and manufacturing presence in India, establishing a key strategic hub. This move, ahead of Brazilian President Lula da Silva's visit, signals Embraer's commitment to India as a critical partner in its global operations, leveraging the nation's growing aerospace capabilities for defense and civil aviation. The expansion includes exploring local assembly, supplier development across various manufacturing domains, and deeper industrial cooperation, aligning with India's 'Make in India' and 'Aatmanirbhar Bharat' initiatives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:22:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69896f0cb81b2b81dcfe7748_1770614661243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China Speculation Fuels Metals Rally: Bubble Risk Looms?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/China-Speculation-Fuels-Metals-Rally-Bubble-Risk-Looms/69896d25b81b2b81dcfe74ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/China-Speculation-Fuels-Metals-Rally-Bubble-Risk-Looms/69896d25b81b2b81dcfe74ed</guid><description>Chinese speculators, flush with liquidity and starved for investment options, are driving metals prices to historic peaks. Copper, gold, and silver have surged as surplus cash bypasses China's weak real economy—marked by subdued consumption and contracting fixed-asset investment—to fuel futures markets. This rally, exceeding economic fundamentals, risks asset inflation as capital chases returns, diverging sharply from sluggish physical demand and presenting a potential bubble scenario.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:14:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69896d25b81b2b81dcfe74ec_1770614348079.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Startup Paradox: Local Founders Eclipse Returnees in Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Paradox-Local-Founders-Eclipse-Returnees-in-Growth/69896cbfb81b2b81dcfe734d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Paradox-Local-Founders-Eclipse-Returnees-in-Growth/69896cbfb81b2b81dcfe734d</guid><description>A new study reveals India's "returnee paradox," finding homegrown founders now outperform overseas-experienced peers in crucial commercial metrics like valuation and revenue, despite returnees retaining early-stage funding advantages. This signals a significant maturation of India's tech ecosystem, where deep local market understanding has surpassed the value of international exposure for long-term business success.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:12:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69896cbfb81b2b81dcfe734c_1770614286709.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Banks Soar to Record High on SBI's Stellar Earnings Beat</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Soar-to-Record-High-on-SBIs-Stellar-Earnings-Beat/69896caab81b2b81dcfe7273</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Soar-to-Record-High-on-SBIs-Stellar-Earnings-Beat/69896caab81b2b81dcfe7273</guid><description>The Nifty PSU Bank index soared to a new all-time high, climbing nearly 4% on Monday. State Bank of India's strong Q3FY26 results, featuring robust profit growth and revised credit guidance, powered the rally. Several brokerages reiterated buy ratings on SBI, citing its industry-leading asset quality and resilient margins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:12:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69896caab81b2b81dcfe7272_1770614120989.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Patanjali Foods: Block Deal Sparks Volatility Amid Sector Tailwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Patanjali-Foods-Block-Deal-Sparks-Volatility-Amid-Sector-Tailwinds/69896c37b81b2b81dcfe7123</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Patanjali-Foods-Block-Deal-Sparks-Volatility-Amid-Sector-Tailwinds/69896c37b81b2b81dcfe7123</guid><description>Patanjali Foods Ltd. shares experienced a notable dip on Monday, February 9, as substantial block deals transacted over 1.48% of the company's equity. While the immediate market reaction suggests selling pressure, the unidentified nature of buyers and sellers injects an element of speculation. This activity occurs against a backdrop of stated growth ambitions and a generally optimistic forecast for the Indian Fast-Moving Consumer Goods (FMCG) sector, prompting a closer look at the underlying dynamics beyond the immediate price movement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:10:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69896c37b81b2b81dcfe7122_1770613980243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Flex Office: Growth Sparks Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Flex-Office-Growth-Sparks-Valuation-Concerns/69896989b81b2b81dcfe6e90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Flex-Office-Growth-Sparks-Valuation-Concerns/69896989b81b2b81dcfe6e90</guid><description>India's flexible office market is projected to hit 100 million sq ft by year-end, with listed players like Smartworks, Awfis, and WeWork India dominating over 30 million sq ft. While demand drivers like GCC expansion and enterprise preference fuel growth, Awfis's current 45x P/E ratio and broader market consolidation trends suggest emerging valuation pressures and heightened competition among rapidly scaling operators. Future growth hinges on operational efficiency and market saturation risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:58:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69896989b81b2b81dcfe6e8f_1770613391536.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AESL Secures Japanese Green Finance for Major HVDC Transmission Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/AESL-Secures-Japanese-Green-Finance-for-Major-HVDC-Transmission-Project/69896964b81b2b81dcfe6d95</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/AESL-Secures-Japanese-Green-Finance-for-Major-HVDC-Transmission-Project/69896964b81b2b81dcfe6d95</guid><description>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd. (AESL) has finalized substantial long-term financing from a consortium of Japanese banks, led by MUFG Bank and SMBC, for its ambitious ±800 kV HVDC transmission project. This 950-kilometer corridor will evacuate 6,000 MW of renewable energy from Rajasthan to Uttar Pradesh, slated for commissioning by 2029. The funding, secured under AESL's sustainable debt framework, reinforces the company's commitment to developing India's green transmission backbone and aligns with global ESG standards. This development positions AESL to accelerate renewable integration and enhance grid stability for energy-intensive regions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:58:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69896964b81b2b81dcfe6d94_1770613443785.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Surges Past ICICI Bank in Market Cap on Strong Q3 Earnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Surges-Past-ICICI-Bank-in-Market-Cap-on-Strong-Q3-Earnings/698968ecb81b2b81dcfe6be9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Surges-Past-ICICI-Bank-in-Market-Cap-on-Strong-Q3-Earnings/698968ecb81b2b81dcfe6be9</guid><description>State Bank of India (SBI) shares surged over 6%, hitting a new 52-week high, after reporting robust December quarter FY26 earnings that surpassed expectations. This performance propelled SBI's market capitalization past ICICI Bank, making it India's second-largest listed bank by valuation. The bank's standalone net profit climbed 24.5% year-on-year, supported by steady net interest income and improved asset quality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698968ecb81b2b81dcfe6be8_1770613193414.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>