<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:26:34 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Simplex Castings Q3 PAT Plummets 24%, Board Approves ₹50 Cr Fundraise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Simplex-Castings-Q3-PAT-Plummets-24percent-Board-Approves-50-Cr-Fundraise/69870295b81b2b81dcfbd3a4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Simplex-Castings-Q3-PAT-Plummets-24percent-Board-Approves-50-Cr-Fundraise/69870295b81b2b81dcfbd3a4</guid><description>Simplex Castings reported a challenging third quarter for FY26, with Profit After Tax (PAT) declining 24.3% year-on-year to ₹476.09 Lakhs, despite a 41.3% revenue growth for the nine-month period. Revenue for the quarter itself dipped 0.8% YoY. A prior period income item boosted 'Other Income'. The board also approved raising up to ₹50.15 Crores via a preferential issue at ₹494 per share.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Patspin India Faces 'Going Concern' Doubt; Losses Widen Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Patspin-India-Faces-Going-Concern-Doubt-Losses-Widen-Sharply/69870274b81b2b81dcfbd29a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Patspin-India-Faces-Going-Concern-Doubt-Losses-Widen-Sharply/69870274b81b2b81dcfbd29a</guid><description>Patspin India's Q3 FY26 results reveal a significant increase in net losses and cash burn, prompting auditors to issue a 'going concern' warning. The company faces a severely eroded net worth and sub-standard loan classifications, though it plans manufacturing resumption and debt restructuring to mitigate these critical issues.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:14:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69870274b81b2b81dcfbd299_1770456366617.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chemplast Sanmar Reports Steep Loss and Revenue Fall, Outlook Unclear</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Chemplast-Sanmar-Reports-Steep-Loss-and-Revenue-Fall-Outlook-Unclear/69870261b81b2b81dcfbd1e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Chemplast-Sanmar-Reports-Steep-Loss-and-Revenue-Fall-Outlook-Unclear/69870261b81b2b81dcfbd1e4</guid><description>Chemplast Sanmar Limited has announced dismal financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Both standalone and consolidated revenues saw sharp year-on-year declines, with standalone revenue falling 13.9% and consolidated revenue dropping 20.9% in Q3. Profitability took a severe hit, with standalone operations swinging to a net loss of ₹56.50 Cr from a profit of ₹135.53 Cr a year ago. Consolidated net loss widened to ₹119.20 Cr. The company provided no forward-looking guidance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:14:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69870261b81b2b81dcfbd1e3_1770456252939.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Patspin India Faces Going Concern Threat Amid Widening Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Patspin-India-Faces-Going-Concern-Threat-Amid-Widening-Losses/698701edb81b2b81dcfbd078</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Patspin-India-Faces-Going-Concern-Threat-Amid-Widening-Losses/698701edb81b2b81dcfbd078</guid><description>Patspin India's Q3 FY26 results reveal a widening net loss of ₹321 Lakhs against ₹276 Lakhs YoY, with revenue from operations at ₹1,100 Lakhs, up 1.9% YoY. The nine-month period saw a net loss of ₹860 Lakhs. Crucially, statutory auditors L.U. Krishnan &amp; Co. have raised a material uncertainty regarding the company's ability to continue as a going concern, citing recurring losses, cash flow issues, and sub-standard lender accounts. The company plans to mitigate these risks by resuming cotton yarn manufacturing and seeking debt restructuring.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:12:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698701edb81b2b81dcfbd077_1770456081188.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chemplast Sanmar Q3 Losses Skyrocket 146% on Plummeting Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Chemplast-Sanmar-Q3-Losses-Skyrocket-146percent-on-Plummeting-Revenue/69870176b81b2b81dcfbced0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Chemplast-Sanmar-Q3-Losses-Skyrocket-146percent-on-Plummeting-Revenue/69870176b81b2b81dcfbced0</guid><description>Chemplast Sanmar's Q3 FY26 performance signals deep trouble, with consolidated net losses surging 146% year-on-year to ₹119.20 crore from ₹48.82 crore. Revenue from operations saw a sharp 21.0% decline to ₹835.14 crore, while total expenses jumped 22.3% to ₹1,003.31 crore. Standalone results mirrored this trend with losses widening to ₹56.50 crore on a 14.1% revenue drop. Both key business segments reported operating losses for the quarter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:10:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69870176b81b2b81dcfbcecf_1770455966792.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ventive Hospitality Zooms 300% PAT, Revenue Jumps 27% on Strong Q3</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ventive-Hospitality-Zooms-300percent-PAT-Revenue-Jumps-27percent-on-Strong-Q3/69870080b81b2b81dcfbcc87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ventive-Hospitality-Zooms-300percent-PAT-Revenue-Jumps-27percent-on-Strong-Q3/69870080b81b2b81dcfbcc87</guid><description>Ventive Hospitality reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with Profit After Tax soaring over 300% year-on-year to ₹140.4 crore, driven by a 27% consolidated revenue jump to ₹722 crore. EBITDA rose 25% to ₹348 crore, with margins holding strong at 48%. Hospitality revenue alone climbed 35% YoY, and EBITDA margins expanded 5 percentage points to 40%. The company highlighted the successful integration of Hilton Goa and a robust development pipeline, expressing confidence in continued momentum into FY27.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:06:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69870080b81b2b81dcfbcc86_1770455885380.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goldiam International Surges on 37% PAT Growth Driven by Lab-Grown Diamonds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Goldiam-International-Surges-on-37percent-PAT-Growth-Driven-by-Lab-Grown-Diamonds/69870009b81b2b81dcfbcaf3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Goldiam-International-Surges-on-37percent-PAT-Growth-Driven-by-Lab-Grown-Diamonds/69870009b81b2b81dcfbcaf3</guid><description>Goldiam International Limited posted a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated PAT surging 37.4% YoY to ₹684 million, driven by its strategic pivot to lab-grown diamonds (LGDs), which now constitute over 90% of sales. Revenue grew 18% YoY to ₹3,397 million, supported by an expanding omnichannel presence and the ORIGEM retail brand. The company maintained its debt-free status with strong liquidity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:04:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69870009b81b2b81dcfbcaf2_1770455669058.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCL's Q3 Surge: Dividend Declared Amidst Valuation &amp; Market Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/HCLs-Q3-Surge-Dividend-Declared-Amidst-Valuation-and-Market-Headwinds/6986ffc4b81b2b81dcfbc98f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/HCLs-Q3-Surge-Dividend-Declared-Amidst-Valuation-and-Market-Headwinds/6986ffc4b81b2b81dcfbc98f</guid><description>Hindustan Copper Limited (HCL) posted robust third-quarter FY26 results, with revenue soaring 109.7% year-on-year to ₹687.34 crore and net profit jumping 148% to ₹156.30 crore. The company also declared an interim dividend of ₹1 per share. However, the stock remains pressured by a strengthening U.S. dollar and volatile copper prices, while trading at a significantly higher valuation compared to its industry peers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:03:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986ffc4b81b2b81dcfbc98e_1770455515490.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goldiam Surges on 37% PAT Growth, B2B Dominance, and Dividend Payout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Goldiam-Surges-on-37percent-PAT-Growth-B2B-Dominance-and-Dividend-Payout/6986ffa8b81b2b81dcfbc863</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Goldiam-Surges-on-37percent-PAT-Growth-B2B-Dominance-and-Dividend-Payout/6986ffa8b81b2b81dcfbc863</guid><description>Goldiam International reported a robust Q3 FY2026 with consolidated revenue up 18% YoY to ₹3397 million and PAT soaring 37% YoY to ₹684 million. EBITDA margins expanded 210 bps to 26.7%. The B2B jewellery export business, led by Lab Grown Diamonds (LGD) contributing 90.5% of export mix, and growing online revenue, drove performance. The B2C ORIGEM brand plans 20 new stores. The company also declared a ₹2.75 per share interim dividend.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:02:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986ffa8b81b2b81dcfbc862_1770455345087.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Captain Polyplast Posts Robust Q3 Growth, But Segment Performance Diverges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Captain-Polyplast-Posts-Robust-Q3-Growth-But-Segment-Performance-Diverges/6986ff91b81b2b81dcfbc78f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Captain-Polyplast-Posts-Robust-Q3-Growth-But-Segment-Performance-Diverges/6986ff91b81b2b81dcfbc78f</guid><description>Captain Polyplast Limited posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with standalone revenue surging 40.87% YoY to ₹126.33 crore and PAT jumping 41.66% to ₹12.58 crore. Sequential growth was even more pronounced, as PAT rose 592.46% QoQ. The core micro-irrigation segment (Segment 1) drove this performance, while the IOCL polymer distribution segment (Segment 2) saw revenue decline and turned loss-making. The company provided no forward-looking guidance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:02:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986ff91b81b2b81dcfbc78e_1770455386695.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Filatex India Profit Surges 24% On Higher Margins, Expansion Fuels Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Filatex-India-Profit-Surges-24percent-On-Higher-Margins-Expansion-Fuels-Growth/6986ff68b81b2b81dcfbc637</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Filatex-India-Profit-Surges-24percent-On-Higher-Margins-Expansion-Fuels-Growth/6986ff68b81b2b81dcfbc637</guid><description>Filatex India reported a strong Q3FY26 with standalone PAT up 16.68% YoY to ₹55.34 crore, driven by a 24.16% surge in EBITDA to ₹93.58 crore and improved margins. Despite a marginal dip in revenue and sales volume, the company is advancing key expansion projects and inked a strategic MoU with Decathlon for recycled polyester. Management eyes growth from supportive policies and sustainability trends.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986ff68b81b2b81dcfbc636_1770455182612.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goldiam International Surges 18% in Q3, Driven by Lab-Grown Diamonds and B2C Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Goldiam-International-Surges-18percent-in-Q3-Driven-by-Lab-Grown-Diamonds-and-B2C-Growth/6986ff3eb81b2b81dcfbc553</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Goldiam-International-Surges-18percent-in-Q3-Driven-by-Lab-Grown-Diamonds-and-B2C-Growth/6986ff3eb81b2b81dcfbc553</guid><description>Goldiam International Ltd. reported strong Q3 FY2026 results, with consolidated revenue up 18% year-on-year to ₹3397 million and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 37% to ₹684 million. EBITDA grew 28.2% to ₹908 million, expanding margins to 26.7%. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, revenue rose 29.8% and PAT jumped 42%. Key growth drivers include lab-grown diamond jewellery exports, contributing 90.5% to export sales, and a significant increase in online revenue to 31.6%. The company's B2C brand, ORIGEM, is set for aggressive expansion with plans for 12-14 new stores by fiscal year-end. An interim dividend of ₹2.75 per share was recommended.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:00:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986ff3eb81b2b81dcfbc552_1770455056829.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Posts Strong Q3; Loan Growth Soars, Margin Headwinds Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Posts-Strong-Q3-Loan-Growth-Soars-Margin-Headwinds-Emerge/6986ff1fb81b2b81dcfbc46d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Posts-Strong-Q3-Loan-Growth-Soars-Margin-Headwinds-Emerge/6986ff1fb81b2b81dcfbc46d</guid><description>State Bank of India announced a significant 24.49% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹21,028 crore for Q3 FY26, driven by broad-based loan growth across all segments. While net interest income and asset quality showed improvement, the bank's domestic Net Interest Margin (NIM) at 3.12% indicates emerging margin pressures within the sector, despite a 15.14% rise in overall advances. Digital channels continue to see increased adoption.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:00:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986ff1fb81b2b81dcfbc46c_1770455067595.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sapphire Foods Slips into Deeper Loss; Eyes Merger with Devyani International</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sapphire-Foods-Slips-into-Deeper-Loss-Eyes-Merger-with-Devyani-International/6986fd68b81b2b81dcfbc0c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sapphire-Foods-Slips-into-Deeper-Loss-Eyes-Merger-with-Devyani-International/6986fd68b81b2b81dcfbc0c9</guid><description>Sapphire Foods India Limited reported a significant widening of its consolidated net loss to ₹48.08 million in Q3 FY26, a sharp reversal from a profit last year. Standalone revenues also declined 20.2% YoY for the nine-month period. In a strategic move, the company's board approved a merger with Devyani International Limited, proposing a share swap ratio of 177 Devyani shares for every 100 Sapphire shares.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:52:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986fd68b81b2b81dcfbc0c8_1770454744077.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Windsor Machines: ₹25 Cr Deal for Unitech Stake, Vatva Unit Sale Signals Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Windsor-Machines-25-Cr-Deal-for-Unitech-Stake-Vatva-Unit-Sale-Signals-Shift/6986fd5ab81b2b81dcfbc029</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Windsor-Machines-25-Cr-Deal-for-Unitech-Stake-Vatva-Unit-Sale-Signals-Shift/6986fd5ab81b2b81dcfbc029</guid><description>Windsor Machines Limited is strategically repositioning, approving a ₹24.99 Cr preferential allotment for a 59.52% stake in Unitech Workholding Systems. Simultaneously, the company will sell its Vatva unit assets to fund its expanded Rajkot plant CapEx, which has been increased by ₹60 Cr to ₹225 Cr. This move aims for operational consolidation and future growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:52:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986fd5ab81b2b81dcfbc028_1770454578241.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silverline Technologies Resubmits Results After BSE Query, Reports Huge YoY Profit Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silverline-Technologies-Resubmits-Results-After-BSE-Query-Reports-Huge-YoY-Profit-Surge/6986fd3bb81b2b81dcfbbf45</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silverline-Technologies-Resubmits-Results-After-BSE-Query-Reports-Huge-YoY-Profit-Surge/6986fd3bb81b2b81dcfbbf45</guid><description>Silverline Technologies is resubmitting its standalone financial results for Q2 FY26 and H1 FY26 after a BSE query flagged discrepancies. The company cited clerical errors for the issues concerning EPS and cash flow. Despite the compliance hiccup, reported revenue surged approximately 14,300% YoY for Q2 FY26 and 22,000% for net profit. However, profits declined 35% quarter-on-quarter, and the balance sheet shows a sharp increase in assets and current liabilities.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:52:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986fd3bb81b2b81dcfbbf44_1770454559012.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goldiam International Surges on Strong Q3 Results, Global Expansion Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Goldiam-International-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Results-Global-Expansion-Push/6986fcd9b81b2b81dcfbbd53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Goldiam-International-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Results-Global-Expansion-Push/6986fcd9b81b2b81dcfbbd53</guid><description>Goldiam International reported robust Q3 FY2026 results, with consolidated revenue climbing 18% YoY to ₹3397 million and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 37% YoY to ₹684 million. For nine months FY2026, revenue grew 30% and PAT rose 42%. Key drivers include strong B2B jewellery exports, a growing contribution from Lab Grown Diamonds (LGD), and promising traction for its B2C ORIGEM brand. The company also declared an interim dividend of ₹2.75 per share.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:50:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986fcd9b81b2b81dcfbbd52_1770454366812.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sambandam Mills Credit Rating Downgraded Over Weak Liquidity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Sambandam-Mills-Credit-Rating-Downgraded-Over-Weak-Liquidity/6986fcc1b81b2b81dcfbbc86</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Sambandam-Mills-Credit-Rating-Downgraded-Over-Weak-Liquidity/6986fcc1b81b2b81dcfbbc86</guid><description>Infomerics Valuation and Ratings has downgraded Sambandam Spinning Mills Limited's credit ratings for bank loan and fixed deposit facilities totaling ₹115.57 Crore. The long-term rating for bank facilities (₹94.32 Cr) moved to IVR BB/Stable from IVR BB+/Stable, and fixed deposits (₹12.00 Cr) also fell to IVR BB/Stable. This downgrade stems from weak liquidity and debt protection metrics in FY25, alongside susceptibility to raw material price volatility and intense industry competition, despite operational improvements.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:50:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986fcc1b81b2b81dcfbbc85_1770454315884.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Material Depot bags $10M to disrupt India's home interiors market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Material-Depot-bags-10M-to-disrupt-Indias-home-interiors-market/6986fbd0b81b2b81dcfbba78</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Material-Depot-bags-10M-to-disrupt-Indias-home-interiors-market/6986fbd0b81b2b81dcfbba78</guid><description>Home interiors platform Material Depot has secured $10 million in Series A funding, co-led by Accel and Stellaris Venture Partners. The capital infusion will bolster its technology backbone, expand its product portfolio, and scale its offline presence across India. Founded in 2022, the startup aims to address the high-stress, low-trust experience of building and renovating homes in India by combining design intelligence with a responsive supply chain.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:46:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986fbd0b81b2b81dcfbba77_1770454090970.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Transchem Revenue Plummets 92% YoY, Profits Tied to Other Income</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Transchem-Revenue-Plummets-92percent-YoY-Profits-Tied-to-Other-Income/6986fb61b81b2b81dcfbb8ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Transchem-Revenue-Plummets-92percent-YoY-Profits-Tied-to-Other-Income/6986fb61b81b2b81dcfbb8ef</guid><description>Transchem Limited reported a drastic Q3 FY26 performance, with revenue from operations plunging 92.17% year-on-year to ₹20.60 Lakhs. Despite a 49.25% drop in net profit YoY to ₹193.54 Lakhs, the company's profitability relied heavily on ₹224.78 Lakhs in 'Other Income'. Quarter-on-quarter, revenue remained flat at ₹20.60 Lakhs, but net profit surged 118.64% due to a substantial rise in 'Other Income'. The nine-month period saw a 92.77% YoY decline in revenue and a 71.55% drop in net profit. No future outlook was provided.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:44:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986fb61b81b2b81dcfbb8ee_1770454075324.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supra Pacific Financial Services Revises Rights Issue Goal to Repay Loans</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Supra-Pacific-Financial-Services-Revises-Rights-Issue-Goal-to-Repay-Loans/6986fa81b81b2b81dcfbb6b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Supra-Pacific-Financial-Services-Revises-Rights-Issue-Goal-to-Repay-Loans/6986fa81b81b2b81dcfbb6b7</guid><description>Supra Pacific Financial Services Limited's Board has approved a significant alteration to its ₹500 Crore Rights Issue objectives, now explicitly including the repayment of borrowings. This strategic move aims to optimize the company’s capital structure, cut interest expenses, and enhance its Debt-to-Equity ratio, bolstering its financial health for future lending operations. Infomerics Valuation and Rating Ltd has been appointed as the Monitoring Agency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:40:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986fa81b81b2b81dcfbb6b6_1770453764904.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Belrise Industries Merges Promoters, Enters Aerospace; Q3 Profit Surges 26%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Belrise-Industries-Merges-Promoters-Enters-Aerospace-Q3-Profit-Surges-26percent/6986fa6ab81b2b81dcfbb5df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Belrise-Industries-Merges-Promoters-Enters-Aerospace-Q3-Profit-Surges-26percent/6986fa6ab81b2b81dcfbb5df</guid><description>Belrise Industries reported an 8% YoY revenue increase to INR 23,405 million and a 26% YoY jump in adjusted PAT to INR 1,268 million for Q3 FY26. The company approved a promoter entity merger valued near book, expected to be EPS-accretive and boost market share. It also announced its strategic entry into aerospace and defense via acquisition and partnership, diversifying revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:40:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986fa6ab81b2b81dcfbb5de_1770453692103.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Hits Record Profit, NPAs Hit Two-Decade Lows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Hits-Record-Profit-NPAs-Hit-Two-Decade-Lows/6986f9f0b81b2b81dcfbb47a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Hits-Record-Profit-NPAs-Hit-Two-Decade-Lows/6986f9f0b81b2b81dcfbb47a</guid><description>State Bank of India reported its highest-ever quarterly net profit of ₹21,028 crores in Q3 FY26, a 24.49% YoY jump. The bank achieved record operational performance with a 39.54% YoY rise in operating profit and saw Gross and Net NPAs fall to over two-decade lows at 1.57% and 0.39% respectively. While Net Interest Margins saw a marginal dip, the bank highlighted strong growth in non-interest income and continued digital transformation via YONO.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:38:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986f9f0b81b2b81dcfbb479_1770453593600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Hits Record Profit; Advances Surge 15% Amidst Asset Quality Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Hits-Record-Profit-Advances-Surge-15percent-Amidst-Asset-Quality-Gains/6986f97ab81b2b81dcfbb315</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Hits-Record-Profit-Advances-Surge-15percent-Amidst-Asset-Quality-Gains/6986f97ab81b2b81dcfbb315</guid><description>State Bank of India achieved its highest-ever quarterly net profit of ₹21,028 Crores in Q3FY26, surging 24.49% year-on-year. This stellar performance was underpinned by a robust 15.14% YoY growth in total advances to ₹46.84 Trillion and an improvement in asset quality, with the Gross NPA ratio falling to 15-month lows of 1.57%. Operating Profit also jumped 39.54% YoY to ₹32,862 Crores, and Net Interest Income rose 9.04% YoY to ₹45,190 Crores. Notably, the bank did not provide specific forward-looking guidance or management outlook in its release.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:36:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986f97ab81b2b81dcfbb314_1770453480014.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alfred Herbert India Q3 Profit Skyrockets 102500% on Asset Sales; Data Anomaly Noted</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Alfred-Herbert-India-Q3-Profit-Skyrockets-102500percent-on-Asset-Sales-Data-Anomaly-Noted/6986f811b81b2b81dcfbb163</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Alfred-Herbert-India-Q3-Profit-Skyrockets-102500percent-on-Asset-Sales-Data-Anomaly-Noted/6986f811b81b2b81dcfbb163</guid><description>Alfred Herbert (India) Limited reported extraordinary Q3FY26 results, with consolidated profit soaring 102500% YoY to ₹1,672.20 Cr, driven by significant asset disposals and fair value gains. Standalone profit also jumped 1815.3% to ₹31.24 Cr. However, the company provided no forward-looking guidance, and a potential data anomaly was noted in consolidated nine-month figures, raising questions about operational health and future outlook.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:30:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986f811b81b2b81dcfbb162_1770453171357.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pearl Global: Tariff Relief Fuels Growth, Diversification Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Pearl-Global-Tariff-Relief-Fuels-Growth-Diversification-Key/6986f541b81b2b81dcfbaf0c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Pearl-Global-Tariff-Relief-Fuels-Growth-Diversification-Key/6986f541b81b2b81dcfbaf0c</guid><description>Pearl Global Industries posted a 13.2% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹3,711 crore for the first nine months of FY26, alongside a 14% rise in Adjusted EBITDA to ₹333 crore and profit after tax of ₹189 crore. Management highlights the rollback of elevated US tariffs as a significant turning point, projecting enhanced profitability and sustained growth. The company's diversified manufacturing footprint across multiple countries has been crucial in navigating global supply chain pressures.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:18:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986f541b81b2b81dcfbaf0b_1770452429069.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Posts Steady Growth, Boosted By ₹3026 Cr Yes Bank Divestment Profit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Posts-Steady-Growth-Boosted-By-3026-Cr-Yes-Bank-Divestment-Profit/6986f4cbb81b2b81dcfbad98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Posts-Steady-Growth-Boosted-By-3026-Cr-Yes-Bank-Divestment-Profit/6986f4cbb81b2b81dcfbad98</guid><description>State Bank of India reported steady year-on-year growth for Q3 FY26. Standalone net profit rose 4.30% to ₹21,028.15 Crore, while consolidated net profit increased 1.73% to ₹21,876.04 Crore. A significant ₹3,026.57 Crore profit from the divestment of Yes Bank shares was recognized as an exceptional item, boosting overall profitability. The bank also saw its net worth surge to ₹4.73 Lakh Crore.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:16:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986f4cbb81b2b81dcfbad97_1770452292666.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Atul Auto Posts Strong Q3 Revenue, PAT Surges Over 100% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Atul-Auto-Posts-Strong-Q3-Revenue-PAT-Surges-Over-100percent-YoY/6986f1fcb81b2b81dcfbab2f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Atul-Auto-Posts-Strong-Q3-Revenue-PAT-Surges-Over-100percent-YoY/6986f1fcb81b2b81dcfbab2f</guid><description>Atul Auto Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 financial results, showcasing strong year-on-year growth. Standalone revenue climbed 22.3% to ₹21,418 lakhs, while PAT surged 81.5% to ₹1,815 lakhs. Consolidated PAT doubled, leaping 104.8% to ₹1,458 lakhs. The nine-month period also demonstrated significant increases in revenue and profit. An exceptional item related to new Labour Codes was noted.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:04:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986f1fcb81b2b81dcfbab2e_1770451568093.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prataap Snacks: Record Revenue Masks Margin Squeeze &amp; CAPEX Needs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Prataap-Snacks-Record-Revenue-Masks-Margin-Squeeze-and-CAPEX-Needs/6986f028b81b2b81dcfba903</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Prataap-Snacks-Record-Revenue-Masks-Margin-Squeeze-and-CAPEX-Needs/6986f028b81b2b81dcfba903</guid><description>Prataap Snacks Limited (PSL) announced its highest-ever quarterly revenue of Rs 461.6 crore for Q3 FY26, coupled with a return to profitability with a PAT of Rs 5.7 crore, reversing a year-ago loss. However, margin pressures from rising palm oil prices and a Rs 425 crore investment in a new manufacturing facility present key challenges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:56:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986f028b81b2b81dcfba902_1770451201235.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Consumer Buys Australian Firm, Bets Big on Global Health Drinks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Consumer-Buys-Australian-Firm-Bets-Big-on-Global-Health-Drinks/6986f019b81b2b81dcfba824</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Consumer-Buys-Australian-Firm-Bets-Big-on-Global-Health-Drinks/6986f019b81b2b81dcfba824</guid><description>Reliance Consumer Products Limited (RCPL), the FMCG arm of Reliance Industries, has acquired a majority stake in Australia-based Goodness Group Global. This strategic move expands RCPL into the Australian consumer goods market, significantly strengthening its global health-focused FMCG portfolio. The partnership aims to grow brands like Nexba and PACE internationally, with a key focus on expansion into India, leveraging RCPL's robust supply chain and distribution capabilities.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:56:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986f019b81b2b81dcfba823_1770451138042.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Grid Bottleneck Threatens Energy Demand Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Global-Grid-Bottleneck-Threatens-Energy-Demand-Surge/6986ef2db81b2b81dcfba69b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Global-Grid-Bottleneck-Threatens-Energy-Demand-Surge/6986ef2db81b2b81dcfba69b</guid><description>Global electricity demand is set for its most robust sustained growth in decades, driven by electrification, data centers, and cooling needs. However, the International Energy Agency (IEA) highlights a critical bottleneck: insufficient investment in grid infrastructure. Over 2,500 gigawatts of generation and storage projects are stalled in connection queues, and annual grid investment must jump 50% to $600 billion by 2030 to avert significant delays and meet projected demand.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:52:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986ef2db81b2b81dcfba69a_1770450869810.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Myntra Hires Google Vet for AI, Scalability Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Myntra-Hires-Google-Vet-for-AI-Scalability-Push/6986eddfb81b2b81dcfba445</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Myntra-Hires-Google-Vet-for-AI-Scalability-Push/6986eddfb81b2b81dcfba445</guid><description>Myntra has appointed Pramod Adiddam, a seasoned technologist from Google and Instacart, as its new Chief Technology Officer. This strategic move signals an intensified focus on advancing the company's technology roadmap, emphasizing innovation, platform elasticity, and the integration of advanced capabilities like agentic AI to support aggressive growth in India's competitive fashion e-commerce sector. Adiddam's expertise is expected to be crucial as Myntra, a key player within the Flipkart ecosystem owned by Walmart, navigates evolving consumer demands, particularly from Gen Z, and expands its high-growth beauty segment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:46:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986eddfb81b2b81dcfba444_1770450641688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kotak Denies IDBI Bid Amidst Conflicting Reports</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kotak-Denies-IDBI-Bid-Amidst-Conflicting-Reports/6986edcab81b2b81dcfba360</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kotak-Denies-IDBI-Bid-Amidst-Conflicting-Reports/6986edcab81b2b81dcfba360</guid><description>Kotak Mahindra Bank has formally denied submitting a financial bid for IDBI Bank Ltd. as part of the ongoing disinvestment process. This clarification on February 7, 2026, directly contrasts with earlier media reports suggesting Kotak's participation. The Department of Investment and Public Asset Management (DIPAM) confirmed on February 6, 2026, that financial bids have been received for IDBI Bank and are under evaluation, adding layers of confusion to the protracted sale. The government and LIC are divesting a 60.72% stake, a process that has faced multiple delays since its inception in October 2022.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:46:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986edcab81b2b81dcfba35f_1770450531247.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Consumer Expands Down Under, Eyes Global Beverage Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Consumer-Expands-Down-Under-Eyes-Global-Beverage-Growth/6986ed49b81b2b81dcfba1db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Consumer-Expands-Down-Under-Eyes-Global-Beverage-Growth/6986ed49b81b2b81dcfba1db</guid><description>Reliance Consumer Products (RCPL) has acquired a 75% stake in Australia's Goodness Group Global for A$25.4 million ($16.6 million USD). This strategic move marks RCPL’s entry into the Australian market and bolsters its global 'better-for-you' beverage portfolio with brands like Nexba and PACE. Leveraging Goodness Group's innovation and RCPL's extensive distribution, the partnership aims to expand health-focused beverages internationally, particularly in India, capitalizing on surging consumer demand for healthier options.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:44:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986ed49b81b2b81dcfba1da_1770450384712.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PhonePe’s Strategic Shift: How Investing in Own Infrastructure is Building a Future-Ready Fintech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PhonePes-Strategic-Shift-How-Investing-in-Own-Infrastructure-is-Building-a-Future-Ready-Fintech/6986ebc961c5e428c6617a8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PhonePes-Strategic-Shift-How-Investing-in-Own-Infrastructure-is-Building-a-Future-Ready-Fintech/6986ebc961c5e428c6617a8e</guid><description>PhonePe is making a massive move by investing Rs 33.73 billion to build its own technology foundation, moving away from relying on external providers. This strategy aims to lower costs per transaction and boost speed, though it comes with the heavy responsibility of managing complex systems. By securing its own data and hardware, PhonePe is positioning itself for sustainable profits and a strong competitive edge ahead of its expected IPO.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:38:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/phonepay.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BEML Approves ₹1,500 Cr Greenfield Rail Plant in Madhya Pradesh</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BEML-Approves-1500-Cr-Greenfield-Rail-Plant-in-Madhya-Pradesh/6986eb68b81b2b81dcfb9fd0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BEML-Approves-1500-Cr-Greenfield-Rail-Plant-in-Madhya-Pradesh/6986eb68b81b2b81dcfb9fd0</guid><description>BEML Limited has greenlit a ₹1,500 Crore investment for a new Greenfield Rail Manufacturing facility, codenamed 'BRAHMA', near Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh. Approved by the Board on February 6, 2026, the facility aims to bolster BEML's manufacturing might and tap into surging rail sector demand. The project will be executed in phases over five years and financed via long-term debt, signaling a strategic push for future revenue growth and market leadership in rail manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:36:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986eb68b81b2b81dcfb9fcf_1770449880764.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSIL Plant Shuts Without Notice; Lessee Vanraj Steels Halts Operations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BSIL-Plant-Shuts-Without-Notice-Lessee-Vanraj-Steels-Halts-Operations/6986e911b81b2b81dcfb961b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BSIL-Plant-Shuts-Without-Notice-Lessee-Vanraj-Steels-Halts-Operations/6986e911b81b2b81dcfb961b</guid><description>Bihar Sponge Iron Limited (BSIL) disclosed that its manufacturing plant operations, leased to M/s Vanraj Steels Private Limited, were unexpectedly suspended on February 6, 2026. BSIL stated it received no prior official communication from Vanraj Steels regarding this closure. The sudden, unannounced halt creates significant operational uncertainty and raises questions about the future revenue generation from the leased facility. Investors await further updates on the situation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:26:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986e911b81b2b81dcfb961a_1770449289494.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bihar Sponge Iron Plant Shut Abruptly By Lessee, Operations Halted Without Notice</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bihar-Sponge-Iron-Plant-Shut-Abruptly-By-Lessee-Operations-Halted-Without-Notice/6986e822b81b2b81dcfb9490</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bihar-Sponge-Iron-Plant-Shut-Abruptly-By-Lessee-Operations-Halted-Without-Notice/6986e822b81b2b81dcfb9490</guid><description>Bihar Sponge Iron Limited (BSIL) disclosed to the BSE that its manufacturing facilities, leased to M/s Vanraj Steels Private Limited under a December 30, 2020 agreement, were abruptly shut down on the evening of February 6, 2026. BSIL has received no official communication from Vanraj Steels regarding the closure's duration or reasons, highlighting a significant operational disruption taken without prior notice. Further updates will be provided as the company receives them.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:22:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986e822b81b2b81dcfb948f_1770449072564.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Buys Australian Nexba Maker for Global FMCG Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Buys-Australian-Nexba-Maker-for-Global-FMCG-Push/6986e732b81b2b81dcfb92f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Buys-Australian-Nexba-Maker-for-Global-FMCG-Push/6986e732b81b2b81dcfb92f7</guid><description>Reliance Consumer Products Limited (RCPL) has acquired a majority stake in Australia's Goodness Group Global Pty. Ltd. (GGG), the parent of 'Better-For-You' beverage brand Nexba. This strategic move marks RCPL's entry into the Australian market and strengthens its global health-based beverage portfolio, with plans to expand Nexba brands, including Pat Cummins' PACE hydration line, into India and other international markets. The acquisition underscores Reliance's ambition to become a significant global FMCG player.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:18:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986e732b81b2b81dcfb92f6_1770448790301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Consumer Buys Australian BFY Beverage Firm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Consumer-Buys-Australian-BFY-Beverage-Firm/6986e5ceb81b2b81dcfb913c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Consumer-Buys-Australian-BFY-Beverage-Firm/6986e5ceb81b2b81dcfb913c</guid><description>Reliance Consumer Products (RCPL), the FMCG arm of Reliance Industries, has acquired a majority stake in Australia's Goodness Group Global. This move integrates brands like Nexba and PACE into RCPL's health-focused portfolio, accelerating its global expansion in the 'better-for-you' beverage segment. The deal signals a strategic shift towards premium, health-conscious products, leveraging RCPL's extensive distribution network while aiming to capture growth in a market valued at over $140 billion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:12:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6986e5ceb81b2b81dcfb913b_1770448465445.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>