<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:31:24 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Kavach Countdown Extended! Railways Misses Another Deadline – Will 2026 Deliver Safety on Mumbai-Delhi Routes?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Kavach-Countdown-Extended-Railways-Misses-Another-Deadline-Will-2026-Deliver-Safety-on-Mumbai-Delhi-Routes/694fcbfe4342f77179d936ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Kavach-Countdown-Extended-Railways-Misses-Another-Deadline-Will-2026-Deliver-Safety-on-Mumbai-Delhi-Routes/694fcbfe4342f77179d936ac</guid><description>Indian Railways has missed its second deadline for installing the Kavach automatic train protection system on the crucial New Delhi-Mumbai and New Delhi-Howrah routes. While 25% of the work is commissioned, officials now aim for operationalization by 2026. The system, designed to enhance safety by automatically applying brakes, faces challenges including an insufficient number of approved manufacturers to expedite deployment across the vast railway network.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:58:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fcbfe4342f77179d936ab_1766837357723.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Laxmi Organic Denies Hazardous Waste Claims: Here's How They Ensure Safety!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Laxmi-Organic-Denies-Hazardous-Waste-Claims-Heres-How-They-Ensure-Safety/694fcb3a4342f77179d935fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Laxmi-Organic-Denies-Hazardous-Waste-Claims-Heres-How-They-Ensure-Safety/694fcb3a4342f77179d935fb</guid><description>Laxmi Organic Industries Ltd denies allegations of hazardous effluent discharge from its Lote, Maharashtra facility. The company asserts full compliance with Indian environmental regulations, stating all emissions are treated and disposed of at government-approved facilities, utilizing closed-loop systems. LOIL distinguishes its practices from the Miteni incident in Italy, which involved direct river contamination. The company emphasizes its commitment to transparency and responsible manufacturing of essential products.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:55:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fcb3a4342f77179d935fa_1766837329528.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Ethanol Floodgates Open for India: Record Exports in 2025 Signal Massive Energy Trade Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Ethanol-Floodgates-Open-for-India-Record-Exports-in-2025-Signal-Massive-Energy-Trade-Boom/694fca764342f77179d9350d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Ethanol-Floodgates-Open-for-India-Record-Exports-in-2025-Signal-Massive-Energy-Trade-Boom/694fca764342f77179d9350d</guid><description>United States ethanol exports to India are poised for a record year in 2025. Volumes shipped from January to September 2025 have already exceeded total shipments for 2022 and 2023, nearing 2020 levels. India imports this fuel ethanol for its industrial sector, which allows its domestic ethanol production to meet ambitious fuel blending targets. This trend is a significant part of India's increasing energy import bill from the US.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:53:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fca764342f77179d9350c_1766836927291.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's M&amp;A Market Set For Strategic Shake-Up: Will 2026 Spark a New Era of Smart Deals?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-MandA-Market-Set-For-Strategic-Shake-Up-Will-2026-Spark-a-New-Era-of-Smart-Deals/694fc2bb4342f77179d92b59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-MandA-Market-Set-For-Strategic-Shake-Up-Will-2026-Spark-a-New-Era-of-Smart-Deals/694fc2bb4342f77179d92b59</guid><description>India's mergers and acquisitions activity is unlikely to see a volume rebound in 2026, shifting instead towards fewer, more strategic transactions. Following a sharp correction after the 2021-22 bull run, dealmaking has become cautious, with a focus on profitability-anchored growth. Key sectors like consumer brands, healthcare, and SaaS are expected to lead, driven by disciplined execution rather than sheer scale. Equity is also set to play a larger role as an acquisition currency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fc2bb4342f77179d92b58_1766835009630.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zepto Files for $1.3 Billion IPO: India's Youngest Startup Gears Up for Stock Market Debut!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Zepto-Files-for-13-Billion-IPO-Indias-Youngest-Startup-Gears-Up-for-Stock-Market-Debut/694fc1ff4342f77179d92a3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Zepto-Files-for-13-Billion-IPO-Indias-Youngest-Startup-Gears-Up-for-Stock-Market-Debut/694fc1ff4342f77179d92a3f</guid><description>Quick commerce leader Zepto has reportedly filed confidential draft papers with India's SEBI for an Initial Public Offering (IPO) aiming to raise approximately $1.3 billion (around ₹11,600 crore). This move, expected in July-September 2026, would make Zepto the youngest VC-funded startup in India to go public, navigating a competitive landscape against rivals like Blinkit and Swiggy Instamart.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:18:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fc1ff4342f77179d92a3e_1766834960631.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GCL Aims for 5X Revenue Growth to ₹5,000 Cr by 2030, Eyes Breakfast &amp; Kids Markets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GCL-Aims-for-5X-Revenue-Growth-to-5000-Cr-by-2030-Eyes-Breakfast-and-Kids-Markets/694fbaf94342f77179d92499</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GCL-Aims-for-5X-Revenue-Growth-to-5000-Cr-by-2030-Eyes-Breakfast-and-Kids-Markets/694fbaf94342f77179d92499</guid><description>Ghodawat Consumer Limited (GCL) targets a massive fivefold revenue increase to ₹5,000 crore by 2030, up from ₹1,200 crore. The FMCG firm plans aggressive expansion into the breakfast and kids' product segments, including launching 'Lunch Bites' beetroot chips for children. GCL is also shifting towards an asset-light manufacturing model, aiming for 60% outsourcing by 2030. The company is exploring a potential Initial Public Offering (IPO) within the next five years and expanding its premium product range.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:48:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fbaf94342f77179d92498_1766832995433.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Taiwanese Tech Giant Teema Set to Launch Massive Tech Park in India – Huge Investment Incoming?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Taiwanese-Tech-Giant-Teema-Set-to-Launch-Massive-Tech-Park-in-India-Huge-Investment-Incoming/694fba654342f77179d923bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Taiwanese-Tech-Giant-Teema-Set-to-Launch-Massive-Tech-Park-in-India-Huge-Investment-Incoming/694fba654342f77179d923bb</guid><description>Taiwanese electronics association Teema, led by Foxconn chairman Young Liu, is considering Uttar Pradesh's Yamuna Expressway Industrial Development Authority (Yeida) region for a major technology park. This initiative aims to create advanced, AI-integrated, and ESG-focused manufacturing hubs, mirroring Taiwan's successful model. The park would be located near a proposed Foxconn outsourced semiconductor assembly and test (OSAT) facility, boosting Taiwan's global competitiveness and supply chain expansion in India, particularly in northern states.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:42:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fba654342f77179d923ba_1766833043623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Startup Cities 2025: Bengaluru Leads, Mumbai &amp; Gurugram Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Startup-Cities-2025-Bengaluru-Leads-Mumbai-and-Gurugram-Surge/694fb2a74342f77179d91c4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Startup-Cities-2025-Bengaluru-Leads-Mumbai-and-Gurugram-Surge/694fb2a74342f77179d91c4c</guid><description>Bengaluru remains India's top startup hub in 2025, anchoring the ecosystem according to a new report by IDFC FIRST Private Banking and Hurun India. While Bengaluru leads with 88 founders and 52 company headquarters, a slight decline indicates a diffusion of entrepreneurial activity. Mumbai and Gurugram are rapidly gaining ground, with Mumbai hosting 83 founders and 41 companies, and Gurugram featuring 32 founders and 36 companies. The report highlights a diversifying landscape and the significant role of educational institutions in nurturing entrepreneurs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:10:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fb2a74342f77179d91c4b_1766830996111.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Shocking AI Overhaul: New Rules Could Reshape Global Tech!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Chinas-Shocking-AI-Overhaul-New-Rules-Could-Reshape-Global-Tech/694fb1784342f77179d91abb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Chinas-Shocking-AI-Overhaul-New-Rules-Could-Reshape-Global-Tech/694fb1784342f77179d91abb</guid><description>China has released draft regulations for human-like AI systems, mandating that providers ensure their services are ethical, secure, and transparent. Users will need to be informed when interacting with AI, with notifications required at login, every two hours, or upon detecting overdependence. The rules also stipulate security assessments and adherence to 'core socialist values,' with proposals open for public comment until January 25.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:05:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fb1784342f77179d91aba_1766830657442.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Diamond Power Infrastructure Secures ₹66 Crore Power Cable Deal, Boosting Infrastructure Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diamond-Power-Infrastructure-Secures-66-Crore-Power-Cable-Deal-Boosting-Infrastructure-Sector/694fada24342f77179d91757</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diamond-Power-Infrastructure-Secures-66-Crore-Power-Cable-Deal-Boosting-Infrastructure-Sector/694fada24342f77179d91757</guid><description>Diamond Power Infrastructure Ltd has received a letter of intent from Hild Projects Private Limited for a ₹66.18 crore power cable supply order. The contract is scheduled for execution between January 1, 2026, and June 30, 2026. This order win highlights the company's continued success in securing business linked to ongoing investments in India's power transmission and infrastructure projects.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:50:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fada24342f77179d91756_1766829530289.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Consumer Payout Bonanza! ₹45 Crore Refunds Disbursed Across India – Are You Covered?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Consumer-Payout-Bonanza-45-Crore-Refunds-Disbursed-Across-India-Are-You-Covered/694fad544342f77179d916f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Consumer-Payout-Bonanza-45-Crore-Refunds-Disbursed-Across-India-Are-You-Covered/694fad544342f77179d916f8</guid><description>The Department of Consumer Affairs has facilitated ₹45 crore in refunds across 31 sectors over eight months (April 25 to December 26, 2025), handling 67,265 grievances via the National Consumer Helpline. E-commerce led with ₹32 crore, followed by travel and tourism, agency services, electronics, and airlines, demonstrating robust consumer redressal efforts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:50:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fad544342f77179d916f7_1766829457533.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹10 Lakh Crore &amp; Doubling! India's ETF Boom You Can't Ignore - Zerodha Reveals Shocking Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/10-Lakh-Crore-and-Doubling-Indias-ETF-Boom-You-Cant-Ignore-Zerodha-Reveals-Shocking-Growth/694fab304342f77179d914c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/10-Lakh-Crore-and-Doubling-Indias-ETF-Boom-You-Cant-Ignore-Zerodha-Reveals-Shocking-Growth/694fab304342f77179d914c0</guid><description>India's Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) industry has surged past a landmark ₹10 lakh crore in Assets Under Management (AUM) by October 2025, doubling its size in just three years. Zerodha Fund House reports a seven-fold increase in ETF trading volumes since 2019-20, reaching ₹3.83 lakh crore in FY 2024-25. Retail investor accounts have grown eight-fold in five years, exceeding three crore folios, driven by a preference for low-cost, transparent investments and easier digital access. Diversification into gold and silver ETFs is also accelerating.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:40:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fab304342f77179d914bf_1766828947102.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Smallcaps Skyrocket! 50+ Stocks Jump 10-34% As Indian Markets Outperform!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Smallcaps-Skyrocket-50-Stocks-Jump-10-34percent-As-Indian-Markets-Outperform/694fa5344342f77179d90fc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Smallcaps-Skyrocket-50-Stocks-Jump-10-34percent-As-Indian-Markets-Outperform/694fa5344342f77179d90fc3</guid><description>Indian equity markets ended a shortened week positively, with the BSE Smallcap index outperforming, rising 1 percent. Over 50 small-cap stocks surged between 10% and 34%. Sectoral performance was mixed, with Defence and Metals leading gains. Foreign Institutional Investors continued selling, but Domestic Institutional Investors provided strong support with significant buying. The market outlook remains cautious due to the upcoming earnings season and global factors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:12:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa5344342f77179d90fc2_1766827394006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DMart's Bold Expansion: Will Store Growth Boost Long-Term Cash Flow Amid Digital Rivals' Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/DMarts-Bold-Expansion-Will-Store-Growth-Boost-Long-Term-Cash-Flow-Amid-Digital-Rivals-Surge/694fa4b54342f77179d90f3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/DMarts-Bold-Expansion-Will-Store-Growth-Boost-Long-Term-Cash-Flow-Amid-Digital-Rivals-Surge/694fa4b54342f77179d90f3b</guid><description>Indian retailer DMart is prioritizing long-term cash flow through aggressive store expansion, adding 15-20% annually. CLSA reports this strategy will lead to negative near-term free cash flow. While quick commerce apps like JioMart and Blinkit see user growth, CLSA expects physical stores to remain crucial, as DMart expands its lower-priced private-label brands.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:10:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa4b54342f77179d90f3a_1766827285446.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oracle's $300 Billion AI Dream Shattered? Stock Plummets 40% - What Investors MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Oracles-300-Billion-AI-Dream-Shattered-Stock-Plummets-40percent-What-Investors-MUST-Know/694fa3bd4342f77179d90dae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Oracles-300-Billion-AI-Dream-Shattered-Stock-Plummets-40percent-What-Investors-MUST-Know/694fa3bd4342f77179d90dae</guid><description>Oracle's stock surged on AI optimism and a massive OpenAI deal, but has since fallen nearly 40%. Investors are reassessing profitability due to lower margins in AI infrastructure compared to legacy software, soaring capital expenditure leading to negative free cash flow, significant reliance on a few large customers like OpenAI, and increased debt. The dream run revealed the capital-intensive economics of AI infrastructure, a stark contrast to Oracle's traditional software business.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:08:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa3bd4342f77179d90dad_1766827008299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Green Hydrogen Dream Stalls: Billions Pledged, But Projects Remain Stuck!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Hydrogen-Dream-Stalls-Billions-Pledged-But-Projects-Remain-Stuck/694fa3d24342f77179d90dff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Hydrogen-Dream-Stalls-Billions-Pledged-But-Projects-Remain-Stuck/694fa3d24342f77179d90dff</guid><description>India's ambitious plan to become a global green hydrogen hub is facing significant delays. Nearly two years after launching the National Green Hydrogen Mission, most announced projects are still on paper. Data shows only 2.8% of planned capacity is operational, with 94% at the announcement stage due to unresolved issues like uncertain demand, high costs, and lack of infrastructure. Experts express concern that many announced capacities may not materialize, hindering India's export and domestic production targets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:07:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa3d24342f77179d90dfe_1766827143065.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zepto's $1.3 Billion IPO Ambition Unveiled! Quick Commerce Giant Files Secret Draft Papers with SEBI – Is This India's Next Big Listing?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Zeptos-13-Billion-IPO-Ambition-Unveiled-Quick-Commerce-Giant-Files-Secret-Draft-Papers-with-SEBI-Is-This-Indias-Next-Big-Listing/694fa2de4342f77179d90cb1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Zeptos-13-Billion-IPO-Ambition-Unveiled-Quick-Commerce-Giant-Files-Secret-Draft-Papers-with-SEBI-Is-This-Indias-Next-Big-Listing/694fa2de4342f77179d90cb1</guid><description>Quick commerce leader Zepto has submitted draft IPO papers to India's market regulator SEBI for a potential $1.3 billion (approximately ₹11,682 Cr) public offering. Led by Aadit Palicha, the company aims to raise around ₹11,000 Cr via a fresh issuance of shares, with early investors also expected to participate in an offer for sale. Shareholder approval for the IPO was secured in December.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:04:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa2de4342f77179d90cb0_1766826778369.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>No Big Jump? Indian Railways Budget 2026: Funding Unchanged, But Vande Bharat &amp; Bullet Trains STILL Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/No-Big-Jump-Indian-Railways-Budget-2026-Funding-Unchanged-But-Vande-Bharat-and-Bullet-Trains-STILL-Ahead/694fa24d4342f77179d90bb1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/No-Big-Jump-Indian-Railways-Budget-2026-Funding-Unchanged-But-Vande-Bharat-and-Bullet-Trains-STILL-Ahead/694fa24d4342f77179d90bb1</guid><description>The Gross Budgetary Support (GBS) for Indian Railways in the 2026-27 Union Budget is expected to remain largely the same as the current Rs 2.52 lakh crore, as infrastructure upgrades are progressing well. While overall funding may be steady, allocations will be adjusted to prioritize the bullet train project, track safety, and decongestion. Funding for new Vande Bharat and Amrit Bharat trains will also increase, focusing on passenger experience and punctuality. Railway electrification is nearing 99.2% completion, reducing diesel costs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:00:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa24d4342f77179d90bb0_1766826668372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC AMC vs ICICI Prudential AMC: Which Fund House Wins? Experts Break Down Stock Picks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-AMC-vs-ICICI-Prudential-AMC-Which-Fund-House-Wins-Experts-Break-Down-Stock-Picks/694f9dc14342f77179d9070e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-AMC-vs-ICICI-Prudential-AMC-Which-Fund-House-Wins-Experts-Break-Down-Stock-Picks/694f9dc14342f77179d9070e</guid><description>Analysts compare HDFC Asset Management Company and ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company, two leading Indian AMCs. The analysis covers fundamental strengths, including revenue, net profit, and assets under management (AUM), alongside technical views. ICICI Prudential AMC shows higher revenue and AUM, while HDFC AMC leads in net profit margin due to operational efficiency. Both are key players in India's growing mutual fund sector, offering distinct investment profiles for investors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 08:42:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f9dc14342f77179d9070d_1766825587851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mangaluru Set to Dominate Data Centres? Study Reveals Shocking Cost Savings!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mangaluru-Set-to-Dominate-Data-Centres-Study-Reveals-Shocking-Cost-Savings/694f9a794342f77179d903c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mangaluru-Set-to-Dominate-Data-Centres-Study-Reveals-Shocking-Cost-Savings/694f9a794342f77179d903c1</guid><description>A new study by Karnataka Digital Economy Mission (KDEM) and Deloitte India identifies Mangaluru as India's next cost-efficient data centre hub. Leveraging its strategic coastal location, robust power infrastructure, and lower land leasing rates (approx. ₹7.69/sq ft), Mangaluru offers a significant cost advantage over cities like Mumbai and Chennai. This positioning is crucial for supporting India's projected 10-12 GW data centre capacity by 2030, catering to cloud computing and AI demands.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 08:28:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f9a794342f77179d903c0_1766824783713.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock Your Child's Future: The Simple Way to Invest with Direct Mutual Funds!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Your-Childs-Future-The-Simple-Way-to-Invest-with-Direct-Mutual-Funds/694f956a4342f77179d8fe9d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Your-Childs-Future-The-Simple-Way-to-Invest-with-Direct-Mutual-Funds/694f956a4342f77179d8fe9d</guid><description>Forget special 'child plans.' Low-cost direct mutual funds offer a simpler, more effective way to invest for your child. An adult guardian manages the investment until the child turns 18, ensuring disciplined long-term growth with lower expenses and greater transparency than traditional insurance-linked schemes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 08:04:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f956a4342f77179d8fe9c_1766823427041.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digantara Secures $50M Series B Funding to Lead Space Surveillance &amp; Missile Tracking!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Digantara-Secures-50M-Series-B-Funding-to-Lead-Space-Surveillance-and-Missile-Tracking/694f95184342f77179d8fe18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Digantara-Secures-50M-Series-B-Funding-to-Lead-Space-Surveillance-and-Missile-Tracking/694f95184342f77179d8fe18</guid><description>Deep-tech space company Digantara has successfully raised $50 million in its Series B funding round from a mix of new and existing investors, including 360 ONE Asset, Peak XV, and Kalaari Capital. Trilegal advised Digantara on the transaction. The significant capital infusion will fuel Digantara's international expansion, enhance its satellite manufacturing capabilities, and broaden its focus to include missile detection and tracking.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 08:03:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f95184342f77179d8fe17_1766823282414.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Overhauls Capital Markets: New 'Securities Markets Code 2025' Promises Clarity, Efficiency, and Global Standards!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/India-Overhauls-Capital-Markets-New-Securities-Markets-Code-2025-Promises-Clarity-Efficiency-and-Global-Standards/694f94cc4342f77179d8fd40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/India-Overhauls-Capital-Markets-New-Securities-Markets-Code-2025-Promises-Clarity-Efficiency-and-Global-Standards/694f94cc4342f77179d8fd40</guid><description>India's Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has introduced the Securities Markets Code Bill, 2025, aiming to consolidate three key laws—Securities Contracts (Regulation) Act, 1956, SEBI Act, 1992, and Depositories Act, 1996—into a single, unified statute. This move is set to simplify compliance, enhance regulatory enforcement, and align India's capital markets with global best practices, fostering greater investor confidence and efficiency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 08:03:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f94cc4342f77179d8fd3f_1766823185573.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hintastica Sells Telangana Manufacturing Facility to Racold in Strategic Asset-Light Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hintastica-Sells-Telangana-Manufacturing-Facility-to-Racold-in-Strategic-Asset-Light-Shift/694f94f04342f77179d8fd8b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hintastica-Sells-Telangana-Manufacturing-Facility-to-Racold-in-Strategic-Asset-Light-Shift/694f94f04342f77179d8fd8b</guid><description>Hintastica Private Limited has divested its water heater manufacturing facility in Telangana to Ariston Water Heating Products India Private Limited, known as Racold. This strategic move supports Hintastica's transition to an asset-light operating model, allowing it to focus on market development and product innovation. Racold's acquisition aims to bolster its 'Made-in-India' production capabilities. JSA Advocates &amp; Solicitors advised Hintastica on the transaction.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 08:03:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f94f04342f77179d8fd8a_1766823259184.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tamil Nadu Textile Crisis: Mills Slash Production by 50% Amid Soaring Cotton Waste Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Tamil-Nadu-Textile-Crisis-Mills-Slash-Production-by-50percent-Amid-Soaring-Cotton-Waste-Costs/694f935d4342f77179d8fbb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Tamil-Nadu-Textile-Crisis-Mills-Slash-Production-by-50percent-Amid-Soaring-Cotton-Waste-Costs/694f935d4342f77179d8fbb2</guid><description>Over 600 open-end spinning mills in Tamil Nadu have reduced production by 50% due to significant losses. Rising cotton waste prices, particularly comber noil, coupled with falling cotton and yarn prices, have severely squeezed profit margins. The association is urging the government to control cotton waste prices, lower electricity tariffs, and curb exports to stabilize the sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 07:56:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f935d4342f77179d8fbb1_1766822826329.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CarDekho Doubles Down on Edtech: $10 Million Investment to Supercharge CollegeDekho's Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/CarDekho-Doubles-Down-on-Edtech-10-Million-Investment-to-Supercharge-CollegeDekhos-Growth/694f92f04342f77179d8fae4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/CarDekho-Doubles-Down-on-Edtech-10-Million-Investment-to-Supercharge-CollegeDekhos-Growth/694f92f04342f77179d8fae4</guid><description>CarDekho Group has invested an additional $10 million in Gurugram-based edtech platform CollegeDekho. This follow-on funding will fuel CollegeDekho's expansion into tier-II and tier-III cities, deepen engagement with educational institutions, and broaden its offerings. Now profitable, CollegeDekho aims to leverage technology to improve student outcomes and bridge the education-employability gap. CarDekho Group, a unicorn, holds approximately a 40% stake in the company.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 07:54:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f92f04342f77179d8fae3_1766822715289.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FMCG Sector Roars Back: GST Woes End, Strong Demand Expected as Companies Normalize Operations!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Sector-Roars-Back-GST-Woes-End-Strong-Demand-Expected-as-Companies-Normalize-Operations/694f91fe4342f77179d8f9cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Sector-Roars-Back-GST-Woes-End-Strong-Demand-Expected-as-Companies-Normalize-Operations/694f91fe4342f77179d8f9cd</guid><description>India's Fast-Moving Consumer Goods (FMCG) sector is stabilizing operations after recent Goods and Services Tax (GST) rate adjustments on everyday items. Companies like Dabur, Emami, and Godrej Consumer Products have returned production to full capacity, rebuilding inventories. Executives anticipate a significant recovery in consumer demand and sales starting from the January-March quarter, following the resolution of pricing and packaging issues.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 07:52:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f91fe4342f77179d8f9cc_1766822462824.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CNG Price Drop Alert! India's New Gas Rules Slash Fuel Costs - Are YOU Ready for Savings?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/CNG-Price-Drop-Alert-Indias-New-Gas-Rules-Slash-Fuel-Costs-Are-YOU-Ready-for-Savings/694f8b6a4342f77179d8f24e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/CNG-Price-Drop-Alert-Indias-New-Gas-Rules-Slash-Fuel-Costs-Are-YOU-Ready-for-Savings/694f8b6a4342f77179d8f24e</guid><description>THINK Gas will lower CNG and Domestic PNG prices across several Indian states starting January 1, 2026. These reductions, up to ₹2.50/kg for CNG and ₹5/SCM for PNG, are a direct result of the Petroleum and Natural Gas Regulatory Board's (PNGRB) new Unified Tariff (UFT) framework. This reform aims to decrease pipeline transportation costs, making natural gas more affordable for consumers and encouraging its wider use. THINK Gas's MD &amp; CEO, Abhilesh Gupta, praised the move as consumer-centric and beneficial for CGD expansion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 07:24:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f8b6a4342f77179d8f24d_1766820791445.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wow! Momo Bags ₹75 Cr From Ace Investor Madhusudan Kela, Fuels Massive Expansion Plans!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Wow-Momo-Bags-75-Cr-From-Ace-Investor-Madhusudan-Kela-Fuels-Massive-Expansion-Plans/694f8abe4342f77179d8ef38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Wow-Momo-Bags-75-Cr-From-Ace-Investor-Madhusudan-Kela-Fuels-Massive-Expansion-Plans/694f8abe4342f77179d8ef38</guid><description>Quick service restaurant chain Wow! Momo has secured INR 75 crore in a bridge funding round led by Singularity AMC founder Madhusudan Kela. The capital will fuel expansion into over 100 cities, product innovation, and drive towards profitability. This investment follows previous participation from Malaysia's sovereign wealth fund Khazanah Nasional Berhad and Haldiram's promoter Kamal Agarwal, as Wow! Momo aims to significantly scale its operations and FMCG portfolio, targeting an IPO in 2027.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 07:21:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f8abe4342f77179d8ef37_1766820619943.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Poised for FDI Surge in 2026: Giants Invest Billions as Policies Shine!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Poised-for-FDI-Surge-in-2026-Giants-Invest-Billions-as-Policies-Shine/694f8a074342f77179d8ee5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Poised-for-FDI-Surge-in-2026-Giants-Invest-Billions-as-Policies-Shine/694f8a074342f77179d8ee5d</guid><description>India expects robust Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) growth in 2026, driven by strong economic fundamentals, attractive policies, and significant investment commitments. Major global firms like Microsoft, Amazon, and Google plan billions in investments, alongside new trade pacts like the EFTA agreement which has already seen Roche Pharma commit ₹17,000 crore. Government reforms enhancing ease of doing business and decriminalizing offenses are key attractors, aiming to surpass the USD 80.5 billion FDI seen in 2024-25.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 07:18:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f8a074342f77179d8ee5c_1766820439570.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking Returns: This Large-Cap Fund is the ONLY One Delivering 20%+ Growth Long-Term! Find Out Why!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Shocking-Returns-This-Large-Cap-Fund-is-the-ONLY-One-Delivering-20percent-Growth-Long-Term-Find-Out-Why/694f84294342f77179d8e97d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Shocking-Returns-This-Large-Cap-Fund-is-the-ONLY-One-Delivering-20percent-Growth-Long-Term-Find-Out-Why/694f84294342f77179d8e97d</guid><description>Nippon India Large Cap Fund is the sole large-cap fund to consistently achieve over 20% annualised returns for both 3-year and 5-year periods, significantly outperforming category averages. Launched in 2013, it has delivered 16.34% since inception and tracks the BSE 100 TRI benchmark. With ₹50,312 crore Assets Under Management, it shows strong investor trust. The fund's portfolio is tilted towards financials and consumption sectors, holding top stocks like HDFC Bank and Reliance Industries, while exhibiting controlled risk and strong risk-adjusted performance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:52:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f84294342f77179d8e97c_1766819058302.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCX Stock Split Alert: Your 100 Shares Turn into 500! Key Date &amp; Details Inside!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Stock-Split-Alert-Your-100-Shares-Turn-into-500-Key-Date-and-Details-Inside/694f7e3b4342f77179d8e493</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Stock-Split-Alert-Your-100-Shares-Turn-into-500-Key-Date-and-Details-Inside/694f7e3b4342f77179d8e493</guid><description>Multi-Commodity Exchange (MCX) has announced a 1:5 stock split, meaning each Rs 10 face value share will be divided into five Rs 2 face value shares. This corporate action will increase the number of shares held by investors, for instance, 100 shares will become 500, without changing the total investment value. The record date for shareholders eligible for this split is January 02, 2026. The company's stock has shown strong performance recently.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 06:27:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f7e3b4342f77179d8e492_1766817420188.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Next Week: 6 Stocks Face Bonus, Splits, Rights – Your Investor Guide!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Next-Week-6-Stocks-Face-Bonus-Splits-Rights-Your-Investor-Guide/694f76be4342f77179d8de67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Next-Week-6-Stocks-Face-Bonus-Splits-Rights-Your-Investor-Guide/694f76be4342f77179d8de67</guid><description>Six Indian companies are set to go ex-date next week for significant corporate actions including bonus issues, stock splits, share consolidation, and rights issues. Shareholders must hold shares before the respective ex-dates, between December 29, 2025, and January 2, 2026, to be eligible for these benefits. Actions range from A-1 Ltd's 300% bonus and stock split to MCX's stock split, aiming to enhance share affordability and liquidity for investors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 05:54:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f76be4342f77179d8de66_1766815495371.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trading Secret Revealed: Experts Say DON'T Adjust Your Trades in These 5 Crucial Situations!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Trading-Secret-Revealed-Experts-Say-DONT-Adjust-Your-Trades-in-These-5-Crucial-Situations/694f75d44342f77179d8dd78</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Trading-Secret-Revealed-Experts-Say-DONT-Adjust-Your-Trades-in-These-5-Crucial-Situations/694f75d44342f77179d8dd78</guid><description>Shubham Agarwal, CEO of Quantsapp, warns derivatives traders against making adjustments in five critical market conditions. He advises against modifying trades during strong trends, when losses approach predefined limits, close to expiry, during event-driven volatility, or when adjustments increase risk. Knowing when not to adjust is key to reducing losses and ensuring sustainable trading.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 05:50:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f75d44342f77179d8dd77_1766815282498.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Solarworld Energy Soars: Bags Massive ₹725 Crore NTPC Renewable Project Order!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Solarworld-Energy-Soars-Bags-Massive-725-Crore-NTPC-Renewable-Project-Order/694f72074342f77179d8da4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Solarworld-Energy-Soars-Bags-Massive-725-Crore-NTPC-Renewable-Project-Order/694f72074342f77179d8da4a</guid><description>Solarworld Energy Solutions has secured a significant Engineering, Procurement, and Construction (EPC) order worth ₹725.33 crore from NTPC Renewable Energy Ltd. The contract is for developing a 250 MWac grid-connected solar PV project, slated for completion in fiscal year 2026-27. This latest win follows another recent order worth ₹806.40 crore for Battery Energy Storage Systems, bolstering the company's order book to ₹3,223 crore as of October 31.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 05:36:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f72074342f77179d8da49_1766814312602.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Booze Industry Set for Massive Growth: From Cheap Drinks to Premium Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Booze-Industry-Set-for-Massive-Growth-From-Cheap-Drinks-to-Premium-Future/694f6ebd4342f77179d8d2cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Booze-Industry-Set-for-Massive-Growth-From-Cheap-Drinks-to-Premium-Future/694f6ebd4342f77179d8d2cb</guid><description>India's alcoholic beverage sector is maturing, moving beyond price sensitivity towards value creation. CRISIL Ratings forecasts 8-10% revenue growth for FY26, potentially reaching ₹5,30,000 crore. However, fragmented state regulations pose challenges to innovation and sustained growth, according to Diageo India's Chief Commercial Officer Jagbir Singh Sidhu.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 05:21:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f6ebd4342f77179d8d2ca_1766813446099.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Dairy Crunch Looms: Farmers' Woes, Demand Surge Set Stage for Price Hikes Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Dairy-Crunch-Looms-Farmers-Woes-Demand-Surge-Set-Stage-for-Price-Hikes-Ahead/694f6cd94342f77179d8d0c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Dairy-Crunch-Looms-Farmers-Woes-Demand-Surge-Set-Stage-for-Price-Hikes-Ahead/694f6cd94342f77179d8d0c5</guid><description>India's dairy sector faces a supply crunch and margin pressure heading into 2026. After disruptions and a temporary surplus from a production surge, early rains and regional conflicts have tightened supply. Robust festive and GST-driven demand has eroded inventories, leading to increased milk procurement costs. Dairy companies are now considering price hikes and focus on value-added products amid evolving distribution channels.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 05:13:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f6cd94342f77179d8d0c4_1766813236641.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Dairy Sector Warns of Tight Supply and Margin Squeeze by 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Dairy-Sector-Warns-of-Tight-Supply-and-Margin-Squeeze-by-2026/694f6b034342f77179d8ce99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Dairy-Sector-Warns-of-Tight-Supply-and-Margin-Squeeze-by-2026/694f6b034342f77179d8ce99</guid><description>India's dairy sector anticipates tighter supply and margin recalibration by 2026. Following past disruptions and a temporary surplus from late 2024, unseasonal rains and geopolitical events have tightened milk output. Robust demand, supported by GST adjustments, is increasing pressure, leading companies to explore selective price hikes and a strategic shift towards value-added products and evolving distribution models.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 05:05:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f6b034342f77179d8ce98_1766812514783.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Sector Roars Back: GST Cuts Ignite Sales Surge! What's Next for 2026?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Sector-Roars-Back-GST-Cuts-Ignite-Sales-Surge-Whats-Next-for-2026/694f65714342f77179d8c8df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Sector-Roars-Back-GST-Cuts-Ignite-Sales-Surge-Whats-Next-for-2026/694f65714342f77179d8c8df</guid><description>India's auto sector saw a strong performance in 2025, largely driven by the government's GST rate cuts on vehicles ahead of the festive season. This measure sparked a significant buying frenzy, boosting sales by 20% in November 2025 compared to the previous year. Passenger vehicle sales grew 18.7%, while overall sales for April-November 2025 increased by approximately 3%. Experts anticipate continued stable demand in 2026, with a focus on SUVs and EVs, though growth may be more selective, driven by execution and new model launches rather than broad momentum. Price hikes are also expected across segments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 04:37:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f65714342f77179d8c8de_1766811298245.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-NZ FTA Signed: Your Gateway to 1.4 Billion Consumers Unlocked! Jobs, Income Surge Expected!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-NZ-FTA-Signed-Your-Gateway-to-14-Billion-Consumers-Unlocked-Jobs-Income-Surge-Expected/694f5e504342f77179d8bd49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-NZ-FTA-Signed-Your-Gateway-to-14-Billion-Consumers-Unlocked-Jobs-Income-Surge-Expected/694f5e504342f77179d8bd49</guid><description>New Zealand Prime Minister Christopher Luxon announced the finalization of a Free Trade Agreement with India, hailed as a major step towards doubling bilateral trade to $5 billion within five years and attracting $20 billion in New Zealand investment over 15 years. The deal eliminates tariffs on 100% of Indian exports, boosting sectors like textiles and auto parts, while India offers concessions on 95% of its imports, protecting sensitive industries like dairy. It also includes new visa pathways for 5,000 Indian professionals annually.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 04:11:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f5e504342f77179d8bd48_1766809236152.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>