<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:25:31 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Dynacons Systems Bags HUGE ₹249 Crore RBI Contract – Is This IT Giant's Next Big Leap?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Dynacons-Systems-Bags-HUGE-249-Crore-RBI-Contract-Is-This-IT-Giants-Next-Big-Leap/695412394342f77179ec7615</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Dynacons-Systems-Bags-HUGE-249-Crore-RBI-Contract-Is-This-IT-Giants-Next-Big-Leap/695412394342f77179ec7615</guid><description>Dynacons Systems &amp; Solutions Ltd announced a significant win, securing a ₹249.15 crore contract from the Reserve Bank of India for its Enterprise Applications Platform (EAP). This five-year, consumption-based project includes implementation, maintenance, and learning services for the EAP software, which aims to provide foundational infrastructure for developing and managing enterprise applications at scale across all RBI locations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:47:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695412394342f77179ec7614_1767117561528.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI PAUSE ALERT! Distributors Demand Halt on Loss-Making Quick-Commerce IPOs Amidst Investor Risk Fears!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-PAUSE-ALERT-Distributors-Demand-Halt-on-Loss-Making-Quick-Commerce-IPOs-Amidst-Investor-Risk-Fears/695411a94342f77179ec7526</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-PAUSE-ALERT-Distributors-Demand-Halt-on-Loss-Making-Quick-Commerce-IPOs-Amidst-Investor-Risk-Fears/695411a94342f77179ec7526</guid><description>India's FMCG distributors' body, AICPDF, has urged market regulator SEBI to pause Initial Public Offerings (IPOs) for quick-commerce firms operating at a loss. Citing significant investor risks and potential damage to the retail trade ecosystem, AICPDF highlighted that valuations are often based on market share rather than profits. The federation also pointed to ongoing Competition Commission of India (CCI) investigations into anti-competitive practices by these firms, arguing that allowing IPOs now could unfairly transfer risks to small retail investors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:44:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695411a94342f77179ec7525_1767117299758.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Metal Shockwave: Ajay Kedia Predicts Silver's 10% Crash, Gold Volatility &amp; Oil's Fate!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/2026-Metal-Shockwave-Ajay-Kedia-Predicts-Silvers-10percent-Crash-Gold-Volatility-and-Oils-Fate/69540ce64342f77179ec6de7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/2026-Metal-Shockwave-Ajay-Kedia-Predicts-Silvers-10percent-Crash-Gold-Volatility-and-Oils-Fate/69540ce64342f77179ec6de7</guid><description>Ajay Kedia, MD at Kedia Commodities, forecasts a volatile 2026 for precious metals and oil. He anticipates a potential 10% crash in silver and significant gold volatility, citing CME margin hikes and global growth concerns. Kedia expects Brent crude to trade between $58-66 per barrel in Q1 2026, with potential geopolitical spikes. Investors await US Federal Reserve minutes and expected interest rate cuts for clearer market direction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:18:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69540ce64342f77179ec6de6_1767116359405.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PM Modi's Big Push: Coal &amp; Mines Review Signals Massive Growth Targets and Critical Minerals Strategy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/PM-Modis-Big-Push-Coal-and-Mines-Review-Signals-Massive-Growth-Targets-and-Critical-Minerals-Strategy/69540adb4342f77179ec68ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/PM-Modis-Big-Push-Coal-and-Mines-Review-Signals-Massive-Growth-Targets-and-Critical-Minerals-Strategy/69540adb4342f77179ec68ea</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi is chairing a crucial two-day review of the Coal and Mines Ministries on January 2 and 3. Discussions will focus on boosting coal production to 1.5 billion metric tonnes by 2030, enhancing mine efficiency, and advancing the National Critical Minerals Mission. The mission includes a ₹1,500 crore incentive scheme for recycling critical minerals from sources like e-waste and battery scrap, aiming to strengthen domestic supply chains and reduce import dependency.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:17:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69540adb4342f77179ec68e9_1767115573522.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Grayscale Sparks AI Revolution: First U.S. Bittensor ETP Filing Hints at Mainstream Crypto Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Grayscale-Sparks-AI-Revolution-First-US-Bittensor-ETP-Filing-Hints-at-Mainstream-Crypto-Boom/69540b854342f77179ec6a8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Grayscale-Sparks-AI-Revolution-First-US-Bittensor-ETP-Filing-Hints-at-Mainstream-Crypto-Boom/69540b854342f77179ec6a8e</guid><description>Digital asset manager Grayscale has filed with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for the first U.S.-listed Exchange Traded Product (ETP) offering exposure to Bittensor's TAO token. This move aims to provide U.S. investors with regulated access to decentralized artificial intelligence within mainstream crypto markets. The proposed Grayscale Bittensor Trust, ticker GTAO, would hold TAO, which boasts a market capitalization of approximately $2.3 billion. Grayscale's chairman highlighted this as a pioneering step in the rapidly evolving decentralized AI space, signaling growing institutional appetite for regulated crypto investment products.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:15:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69540b854342f77179ec6a8d_1767116014791.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Airport vs. Telecom Giants: Massive RoW Clash Erupts Over Sky-High Charges, Passenger Connectivity at Stake!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Adani-Airport-vs-Telecom-Giants-Massive-RoW-Clash-Erupts-Over-Sky-High-Charges-Passenger-Connectivity-at-Stake/69540a624342f77179ec6782</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Adani-Airport-vs-Telecom-Giants-Massive-RoW-Clash-Erupts-Over-Sky-High-Charges-Passenger-Connectivity-at-Stake/69540a624342f77179ec6782</guid><description>India's top telcos, represented by COAI, accuse Adani Group's Navi Mumbai International Airport of denying Right of Way (RoW) for 4G/5G infrastructure and demanding exorbitant charges of ₹92 lakhs per month per operator. The airport operator denies the claims, labels it 'cartelisation,' and asserts readiness to proceed with its own infrastructure and BSNL testing, promising free Wi-Fi while awaiting telco agreements on fair rates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:12:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69540a624342f77179ec6781_1767115915531.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cement Giants Halt M&amp;A Race: Why Adani &amp; UltraTech Are Pausing Big Deals!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Giants-Halt-MandA-Race-Why-Adani-and-UltraTech-Are-Pausing-Big-Deals/69540aa24342f77179ec680c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Giants-Halt-MandA-Race-Why-Adani-and-UltraTech-Are-Pausing-Big-Deals/69540aa24342f77179ec680c</guid><description>Major cement companies in India, including Adani Group and UltraTech Cement, are expected to pause merger and acquisition activities until the first half of 2026. This strategic shift prioritizes integrating previously acquired assets over pursuing new deals. The slowdown follows an intense consolidation period, with Adani Group focusing on merging subsidiaries like ACC, Sanghi Industries, and Orient Cement into Ambuja Cements. Analysts suggest a lack of attractive acquisition targets and the need for significant turnaround efforts on remaining assets also contribute to the pause. While deal-making cools, focus returns to pricing dynamics, demand growth driven by housing and infrastructure, and ongoing capacity additions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:09:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69540aa24342f77179ec680b_1767115818832.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock Your Wealth: See How Top Investments Performed Over Time for Big Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Unlock-Your-Wealth-See-How-Top-Investments-Performed-Over-Time-for-Big-Gains/695409044342f77179ec6485</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Unlock-Your-Wealth-See-How-Top-Investments-Performed-Over-Time-for-Big-Gains/695409044342f77179ec6485</guid><description>A new illustration reveals the long-term performance of various financial asset classes available to Indian investors. By examining five-year returns, it helps filter out short-term market fluctuations, identify consistent performers across market cycles, and avoid focusing too much on recent trends. This guide is designed to assist investors in rebalancing their portfolios effectively, reducing exposure to overvalued assets and increasing holdings in those with positive momentum, ensuring risk management aligned with long-term financial objectives.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:08:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695409044342f77179ec6484_1767115079500.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exotel's AI Leap: From Losses to ₹65 Cr Profit Turnaround in FY25!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Exotels-AI-Leap-From-Losses-to-65-Cr-Profit-Turnaround-in-FY25/695404784342f77179ec5c78</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Exotels-AI-Leap-From-Losses-to-65-Cr-Profit-Turnaround-in-FY25/695404784342f77179ec5c78</guid><description>AI-first customer experience platform Exotel has achieved a significant financial turnaround in FY25, swinging to an EBITDA profit of ₹34 crore and a year-on-year recovery of ₹65 crore. This success is attributed to a strategic shift focusing on higher-value, AI-embedded solutions rather than volume-led growth, with AI products now driving substantial expansion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:47:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695404784342f77179ec5c77_1767113917918.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Navi Mumbai Airport Surges Past 25,000 Passengers in First 5 Days!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Navi-Mumbai-Airport-Surges-Past-25000-Passengers-in-First-5-Days/6954033c4342f77179ec5953</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Navi-Mumbai-Airport-Surges-Past-25000-Passengers-in-First-5-Days/6954033c4342f77179ec5953</guid><description>Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA), operated by Adani Group, has achieved a significant milestone, welcoming over 25,000 passengers within its first five days of commercial flight operations. The airport recorded a total of 26,021 travelers, including 12,431 arrivals and 13,590 departures, reflecting strong initial demand. Passenger volumes peaked over the weekend, and the airport managed 162 scheduled air traffic movements during this period.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:42:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954033c4342f77179ec5952_1767113725496.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Secret Auto Empire: How 50% of South African Cars Are Linked to India Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Secret-Auto-Empire-How-50percent-of-South-African-Cars-Are-Linked-to-India-Revealed/695402f04342f77179ec58ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Secret-Auto-Empire-How-50percent-of-South-African-Cars-Are-Linked-to-India-Revealed/695402f04342f77179ec58ad</guid><description>A report reveals India's significant automotive presence in South Africa, stating that by 2025, half of the cars sold there will be connected to India. This connection comes from Indian manufacturers like Mahindra and Tata, or through components sourced from India. Notably, 36% of South Africa's vehicle sales in 2024 originated from India, surpassing Chinese imports. This trend, driven by India's cost-effective manufacturing, is a concern for South Africa's local auto industry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:40:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695402f04342f77179ec58ac_1767113675018.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Bond Market Set for Revolution: NSDL to Launch Game-Changing Platform for Retail Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Bond-Market-Set-for-Revolution-NSDL-to-Launch-Game-Changing-Platform-for-Retail-Investors/695402b34342f77179ec5827</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Bond-Market-Set-for-Revolution-NSDL-to-Launch-Game-Changing-Platform-for-Retail-Investors/695402b34342f77179ec5827</guid><description>National Stock Depository Limited (NSDL) is building a new platform to simplify bond selling for retail investors. This move aims to significantly boost liquidity and participation in the corporate bond market by eliminating tedious paperwork and multi-day settlement processes. The initiative, mandated by SEBI, is expected to bring the ease of equity trading to fixed-income investments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:39:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695402b34342f77179ec5826_1767113470337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axis MF's 2026 Bond Forecast: Will Flattening Yield Curve Unlock New Investment Fortunes?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Axis-MFs-2026-Bond-Forecast-Will-Flattening-Yield-Curve-Unlock-New-Investment-Fortunes/6953fd9d4342f77179ec4d76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Axis-MFs-2026-Bond-Forecast-Will-Flattening-Yield-Curve-Unlock-New-Investment-Fortunes/6953fd9d4342f77179ec4d76</guid><description>Axis Mutual Fund predicts India's bond market will see a flattening yield curve in 2026, moving away from the steep curves of recent years. This shift is driven by the Reserve Bank of India's expected pause on interest rates, normalization of liquidity, and potential inflows from Indian government bonds joining global indices. Axis MF suggests a 'barbell' investment strategy, focusing on short-term AA corporate bonds for accrual and long-term government bonds for tactical gains, to navigate this environment while managing risks like higher government borrowing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:09:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953fd9d4342f77179ec4d75_1767112617791.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver SOAR Past Stocks: The SHOCKING Truth Behind Their Record Rally Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-SOAR-Past-Stocks-The-SHOCKING-Truth-Behind-Their-Record-Rally-Revealed/6953fdaa4342f77179ec4dd5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-SOAR-Past-Stocks-The-SHOCKING-Truth-Behind-Their-Record-Rally-Revealed/6953fdaa4342f77179ec4dd5</guid><description>In 2025, gold and silver prices surged dramatically, outperforming global stock markets despite strong economic growth. This rally, driven by a weaker US dollar, fears of unsustainable debt, AI stock bubble concerns, and anticipation of further quantitative easing, has significant implications. For India, it means a potential wealth effect and increased gold-backed lending, but also vigilance over rising ETF inflows and imports. Investors are advised to adjust return expectations for 2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:08:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953fdaa4342f77179ec4dd4_1767112367419.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EU's Carbon Tax Set to Devastate Indian Steel &amp; Aluminium Exports: Are Companies Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/EUs-Carbon-Tax-Set-to-Devastate-Indian-Steel-and-Aluminium-Exports-Are-Companies-Ready/6953fd464342f77179ec4c50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/EUs-Carbon-Tax-Set-to-Devastate-Indian-Steel-and-Aluminium-Exports-Are-Companies-Ready/6953fd464342f77179ec4c50</guid><description>The European Union's new Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (CBAM), effective from Thursday, poses a significant threat to Indian steel and aluminium exporters. This emissions-based tax on imports will likely compress profit margins and reduce competitiveness, especially as Indian production methods, like blast furnaces, are more carbon-intensive. Companies are exploring alternative markets in Africa and West Asia, while the government seeks exemptions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:08:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953fd464342f77179ec4c4f_1767112209789.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mega Healthcare Merger Alert! Aster DM Healthcare Eyes Quality Domination in Landmark Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Mega-Healthcare-Merger-Alert-Aster-DM-Healthcare-Eyes-Quality-Domination-in-Landmark-Deal/6953fcb94342f77179ec4aba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Mega-Healthcare-Merger-Alert-Aster-DM-Healthcare-Eyes-Quality-Domination-in-Landmark-Deal/6953fcb94342f77179ec4aba</guid><description>Aster DM Healthcare is merging with Quality Care India Ltd, backed by Blackstone, to form 'Aster DM Quality Care Ltd'. This move, part of a record hospital M&amp;A wave, prioritizes clinical governance and patient outcomes over sheer scale. The combined entity will be a top hospital chain in India, enhancing presence across nine states and Bangladesh. The merger targets completion by Q1 FY27, signaling a quality-first approach to consolidation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:08:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953fcb94342f77179ec4ab9_1767112095769.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian AI Startups Thrive: Funding Flows Amid Global Concerns By Carving Unique Niches!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indian-AI-Startups-Thrive-Funding-Flows-Amid-Global-Concerns-By-Carving-Unique-Niches/6953fc8e4342f77179ec4a30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indian-AI-Startups-Thrive-Funding-Flows-Amid-Global-Concerns-By-Carving-Unique-Niches/6953fc8e4342f77179ec4a30</guid><description>Despite global AI stock market jitters and investor wariness, Indian AI startups are demonstrating resilience. With around 1,400 startups, 451 have raised $4.9 billion, focusing on sector-specific problems rather than competing with giants. B2B solutions, particularly in BFSI and healthcare, are driving revenue, while AI itself boosts efficiency. The Asia-Pacific AI market is growing rapidly, with Indian firms leveraging cost advantages to build world-class products for global clients.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953fc8e4342f77179ec4a2f_1767112005967.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Promoters Exit Taj GVK Hotels: Huge Stake Sale Sparks Investor Jitters!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Promoters-Exit-Taj-GVK-Hotels-Huge-Stake-Sale-Sparks-Investor-Jitters/6953f86f4342f77179e9b0f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Promoters-Exit-Taj-GVK-Hotels-Huge-Stake-Sale-Sparks-Investor-Jitters/6953f86f4342f77179e9b0f3</guid><description>Promoters of Taj GVK Hotels &amp; Resorts divested nearly 4% of their equity stake through open market transactions on December 30. Starlight Trust and Moonshot Trust sold a combined stake for over ₹105 crore. Nippon India's Alternate Investment Funds (AIF) were significant buyers, acquiring shares at approximately ₹420 each. The news led to a slight dip in Taj GVK Hotels' stock price.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:45:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953f86f4342f77179e9b0f2_1767111253887.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Flight Chaos: Aviation Minister Reviews Crucial Report on Massive Disruptions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Flight-Chaos-Aviation-Minister-Reviews-Crucial-Report-on-Massive-Disruptions/6953f7af4342f77179e99c33</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Flight-Chaos-Aviation-Minister-Reviews-Crucial-Report-on-Massive-Disruptions/6953f7af4342f77179e99c33</guid><description>Civil Aviation Minister Ram Mohan Naidu announced that the ministry is analyzing a report on the recent massive flight disruptions by IndiGo, which caused over 1,600 flight cancellations. The disruptions were linked to inadequate planning of new pilot rest norms. The Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA) has already taken action, including reducing IndiGo's winter schedule and issuing show-cause notices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:43:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953f7af4342f77179e99c32_1767111001415.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pharma Giants Face Deadline Crisis: Will India Extend Crucial Manufacturing Rules Amidst Widespread Non-Compliance?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-Giants-Face-Deadline-Crisis-Will-India-Extend-Crucial-Manufacturing-Rules-Amidst-Widespread-Non-Compliance/6953f6f44342f77179e98cb6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-Giants-Face-Deadline-Crisis-Will-India-Extend-Crucial-Manufacturing-Rules-Amidst-Widespread-Non-Compliance/6953f6f44342f77179e98cb6</guid><description>The Indian government may extend the deadline for new Schedule M manufacturing guidelines for small and medium-sized pharmaceutical units. Around 75% of these units have not begun required upgradation work due to practical issues, lack of clarity, and financial constraints. Pharma associations are appealing for an extension until December 2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953f6f44342f77179e98cb5_1767110680247.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India's Bold Leap: New Budget Taxis Launched for Drivers! Big Earnings Potential Unlocked?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-Indias-Bold-Leap-New-Budget-Taxis-Launched-for-Drivers-Big-Earnings-Potential-Unlocked/6953f75f4342f77179e99b6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-Indias-Bold-Leap-New-Budget-Taxis-Launched-for-Drivers-Big-Earnings-Potential-Unlocked/6953f75f4342f77179e99b6a</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India has entered the commercial mobility sector with the launch of its dedicated taxi models, the Prime HB hatchback and Prime SD sedan. These vehicles are designed for fleet operators and taxi entrepreneurs, emphasizing low operating costs, reliability, and comfort. Powered by a 1.2-litre engine with petrol and CNG options, they feature essential safety and convenience features. The Prime HB is priced at ₹5,99,900 and the Prime SD at ₹6,89,900, with bookings open, promising high uptime and reduced maintenance to enhance driver earnings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:39:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953f75f4342f77179e99b69_1767110859815.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Spending SHOCKER: VCs Reveal 2026 Budget Bombshell for Enterprises!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Spending-SHOCKER-VCs-Reveal-2026-Budget-Bombshell-for-Enterprises/6953f5f24342f77179e9871d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Spending-SHOCKER-VCs-Reveal-2026-Budget-Bombshell-for-Enterprises/6953f5f24342f77179e9871d</guid><description>Venture capitalists predict enterprises will significantly increase AI budgets in 2026, but this spending will be highly concentrated. Investors anticipate companies will shift from experimenting with numerous AI tools to investing in fewer, proven vendors. This consolidation trend could lead to a challenging market for AI startups, favoring those with strong differentiation and proprietary data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:32:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953f5f24342f77179e9871c_1767110540162.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Gold Hoard Shatters Records: Is Your Household Wealth Bigger Than The Nation's Economy?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Gold-Hoard-Shatters-Records-Is-Your-Household-Wealth-Bigger-Than-The-Nations-Economy/6953f5b64342f77179e98407</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Gold-Hoard-Shatters-Records-Is-Your-Household-Wealth-Bigger-Than-The-Nations-Economy/6953f5b64342f77179e98407</guid><description>The value of gold held by Indian households may have surged past $5 trillion, potentially exceeding India's entire Gross Domestic Product (GDP) of approximately $4.1 trillion. While this represents significant household wealth, much of it, particularly jewellery, is not actively monetized or invested in productive assets, presenting an economic paradox for India as the world's second-largest gold consumer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:32:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953f5b64342f77179e98406_1767110864787.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Government Revamps SARFAESI Act: Special Funds Empowered, Borrower Delays Targeted!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Government-Revamps-SARFAESI-Act-Special-Funds-Empowered-Borrower-Delays-Targeted/6953f0174342f77179e77c18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Government-Revamps-SARFAESI-Act-Special-Funds-Empowered-Borrower-Delays-Targeted/6953f0174342f77179e77c18</guid><description>The Indian government is planning to amend the SARFAESI Act to allow Special Situation Funds to directly participate in recovering dues from stressed assets. This move aims to speed up the resolution of bad loans. Additionally, a new rule will mandate borrowers to submit objections within 30 days of receiving a demand notice, preventing delays and improving the ease of doing business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:18:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953f0174342f77179e77c17_1767108898119.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>🚨 ₹700 Crore Block Deal Alert! Privi Speciality Chemicals Faces Massive Stake Sale - Investors On Edge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/700-Crore-Block-Deal-Alert-Privi-Speciality-Chemicals-Faces-Massive-Stake-Sale-Investors-On-Edge/6953ef7d4342f77179e76a92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/700-Crore-Block-Deal-Alert-Privi-Speciality-Chemicals-Faces-Massive-Stake-Sale-Investors-On-Edge/6953ef7d4342f77179e76a92</guid><description>A significant shareholder of Privi Speciality Chemicals Ltd is set to offload up to 6.32% of the company's stock through a block deal, valued at approximately ₹700 crore. The sale is priced between ₹2,835-₹2,850 per share, a discount of over 11% to the current market price. This follows a previous promoter stake sale in June, which reduced their holding to 69.96%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:17:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ef7d4342f77179e76a91_1767109001875.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shankh Airlines Takes Flight! India's New Airline Launches in January, Aiming to Make Flying Affordable for All!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Shankh-Airlines-Takes-Flight-Indias-New-Airline-Launches-in-January-Aiming-to-Make-Flying-Affordable-for-All/6953ef1b4342f77179e76094</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Shankh-Airlines-Takes-Flight-Indias-New-Airline-Launches-in-January-Aiming-to-Make-Flying-Affordable-for-All/6953ef1b4342f77179e76094</guid><description>Shankh Airlines is set to launch operations in the first half of January with an initial fleet of three Airbus aircraft. Led by Chairman Shravan Kumar Vishwakarma, the airline aims to make air travel accessible and affordable for middle-class passengers and first-time flyers, challenging the perception of flying as a luxury. Initial routes will connect Lucknow to major cities like Delhi and Mumbai, with plans for expansion across Uttar Pradesh and eventually the entire country. The airline is backed by its parent company with no funding constraints.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:12:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ef1b4342f77179e76093_1767108689054.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Delhi Metro's 2025: Massive Expansion, Groundbreaking Tech &amp; Global Deals Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Delhi-Metros-2025-Massive-Expansion-Groundbreaking-Tech-and-Global-Deals-Revealed/6953ef194342f77179e76061</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Delhi-Metros-2025-Massive-Expansion-Groundbreaking-Tech-and-Global-Deals-Revealed/6953ef194342f77179e76061</guid><description>Delhi Metro Rail Corporation (DMRC) had a landmark year in 2025, marked by significant expansion, technological innovation, and national recognition. Key developments included the foundation stone for the 26.5-km Rithala-Narela-Nathupur corridor and passenger services commencing on a Phase IV segment. The network expanded to 394.448 km with 289 stations. DMRC achieved complex engineering feats like tunnelling under operational lines. Digital strides were made with the Sarthi-Momentum 2.0 app, ONDC integration, and 'DMRC Pay'. Partnerships with Indian Railways and international bodies were strengthened, alongside sustainability initiatives and national awards. A new Delhi Metro Museum also opened.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:12:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ef194342f77179e76060_1767108563388.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Plummets: Asia's Worst Performer in 2025! Will US Trade Deal Save It?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Plummets-Asias-Worst-Performer-in-2025-Will-US-Trade-Deal-Save-It/6953eec44342f77179e75d4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Plummets-Asias-Worst-Performer-in-2025-Will-US-Trade-Deal-Save-It/6953eec44342f77179e75d4d</guid><description>The Indian Rupee faced a volatile 2025, depreciating 5% to become Asia's worst-performing currency. Factors like US tariffs, geopolitical tensions (Russia-Ukraine, Israel-Iran), and significant foreign outflows pressured the INR. The Reserve Bank of India intervened to curb sharp fluctuations, but a US trade deal is seen as crucial for future stability. Analysts project continued pressure in early 2026, with varying forecast ranges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:09:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953eec44342f77179e75d4c_1767108399857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unleashes Rs 4,666 Crore Defence Blitz: Bharat Forge &amp; Italian Firm Secure HUGE Contracts! What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Unleashes-Rs-4666-Crore-Defence-Blitz-Bharat-Forge-and-Italian-Firm-Secure-HUGE-Contracts-Whats-Next/6953ee1f4342f77179e75b4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Unleashes-Rs-4666-Crore-Defence-Blitz-Bharat-Forge-and-Italian-Firm-Secure-HUGE-Contracts-Whats-Next/6953ee1f4342f77179e75b4c</guid><description>India's Ministry of Defence has signed defence contracts worth ₹4,666 crore with Bharat Forge and PLR Systems for over 4.25 lakh Close Quarter Battle (CQB) Carbines, aligning with the 'Aatmanirbhar Bharat' initiative. Additionally, a ₹1,896 crore deal was finalized with Italy's WASS Submarine Systems for 48 Heavy Weight Torpedoes for the Indian Navy's Kalvari Class submarines. These procurements aim to modernize armed forces, enhance combat capabilities, and boost indigenous defence manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:08:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ee1f4342f77179e75b4b_1767108434102.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's IT Hiring Set for Smart Comeback in 2026: Niche Skills Drive Recovery!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-IT-Hiring-Set-for-Smart-Comeback-in-2026-Niche-Skills-Drive-Recovery/6953ee1e4342f77179e75b1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-IT-Hiring-Set-for-Smart-Comeback-in-2026-Niche-Skills-Drive-Recovery/6953ee1e4342f77179e75b1e</guid><description>India's IT sector saw cautious hiring in 2025, focusing on AI, data, cloud, and cybersecurity skills rather than mass recruitment. Industry experts predict a selective recovery in 2026, emphasizing targeted, skills-based hiring. Mid-career professionals are in high demand, while fresher intake remains limited, reflecting a structural shift towards specialized talent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:08:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ee1e4342f77179e75b1d_1767108369924.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Luxury Secret: How Young &amp; Small-Town Shoppers Are Igniting a Massive Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Luxury-Secret-How-Young-and-Small-Town-Shoppers-Are-Igniting-a-Massive-Boom/6953edd44342f77179e75a15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Luxury-Secret-How-Young-and-Small-Town-Shoppers-Are-Igniting-a-Massive-Boom/6953edd44342f77179e75a15</guid><description>Tata CLiQ's luxury segment is experiencing strong double-digit growth, driven by a surge in demand from younger consumers and shoppers in non-metro cities. Rising disposable incomes and the expansion of India's middle class are fueling this premiumization trend. Over half of Tata CLiQ's luxury business now comes from non-metro markets, as India is poised to become the world's third-largest consumer market by 2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:08:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953edd44342f77179e75a14_1767108217840.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2025 Leap: Government Unleashes Sweeping Labour Reforms &amp; Social Security Boost – Are You Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-Leap-Government-Unleashes-Sweeping-Labour-Reforms-and-Social-Security-Boost-Are-You-Ready/6953ecba4342f77179e7551a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-Leap-Government-Unleashes-Sweeping-Labour-Reforms-and-Social-Security-Boost-Are-You-Ready/6953ecba4342f77179e7551a</guid><description>India's government is driving major reforms in 2025, implementing four new labour codes to modernize regulations, simplify compliance, and enhance worker welfare. Key initiatives include expanding social security for gig and platform workers, launching EPFO 3.0 for easier fund access, and the Pradhan Mantri Viksit Bharat Rozgar Yojana aimed at creating over 3.5 crore jobs. These reforms seek to boost employment, improve working conditions, and significantly increase social protection coverage across the nation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:07:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ecba4342f77179e75519_1767107848081.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Ministry Awards HUGE ₹1,661 Crore Carbine Contract to Bharat Forge: 'Make in India' Milestone!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Ministry-Awards-HUGE-1661-Crore-Carbine-Contract-to-Bharat-Forge-Make-in-India-Milestone/6953ed1d4342f77179e757df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Ministry-Awards-HUGE-1661-Crore-Carbine-Contract-to-Bharat-Forge-Make-in-India-Milestone/6953ed1d4342f77179e757df</guid><description>Bharat Forge has secured its largest ever small arms contract, valued at ₹1,661.9 crore, from the Defence Ministry. The deal involves supplying 2,55,128 CQB Carbines (5.56×45 mm) to the Indian Army over five years. This indigenously designed and developed weapon underscores the 'Atmanirbhar Bharat' mission, boosting domestic defense manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:07:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ed1d4342f77179e757de_1767107972066.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Takeover! See How Nearly HALF of South Africa's Cars Now Have an Indian Link!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Takeover-See-How-Nearly-HALF-of-South-Africas-Cars-Now-Have-an-Indian-Link/6953e7444342f77179e6e3b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Takeover-See-How-Nearly-HALF-of-South-Africas-Cars-Now-Have-an-Indian-Link/6953e7444342f77179e6e3b1</guid><description>A report reveals that by 2025, almost half of cars sold in South Africa will be connected to India. This includes vehicles manufactured by Indian giants like Mahindra and Tata, or cars from Japanese and Korean brands assembled using Indian components or from Indian plants, notably Maruti Suzuki. This trend, driven by India's manufacturing cost advantages, sees Indian imports surpassing Chinese brands and causing concern for South Africa's local automotive industry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:46:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e7444342f77179e6e3b0_1767106456275.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airport Blocks Telecom Giants! Govt Intervention Sought in RoW Row</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airport-Blocks-Telecom-Giants-Govt-Intervention-Sought-in-RoW-Row/6953e7bf4342f77179e6e4a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airport-Blocks-Telecom-Giants-Govt-Intervention-Sought-in-RoW-Row/6953e7bf4342f77179e6e4a2</guid><description>The telecom industry body COAI has urged the Department of Telecom (DoT) to intervene against Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIAL). COAI alleges NMIAL is denying essential Right of Way (RoW) permissions for deploying telecom infrastructure and imposing exclusive, costly network usage, impacting major players like Bharti Airtel, Reliance Jio, and Vodafone Idea.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:46:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e7bf4342f77179e6e4a1_1767106652540.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Market Rocket Fuel? CIO Unlocks 2026 Boom Secrets &amp; IPO Valuations!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Market-Rocket-Fuel-CIO-Unlocks-2026-Boom-Secrets-and-IPO-Valuations/6953e62e4342f77179e6e03b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Market-Rocket-Fuel-CIO-Unlocks-2026-Boom-Secrets-and-IPO-Valuations/6953e62e4342f77179e6e03b</guid><description>Sankaran Naren, CIO of ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund, predicts India's equities will outperform globally by 2026, especially if the US market corrects. He notes India is now relatively cheaper than peers. While small-caps have cooled, mid-caps remain elevated due to low floating stock. Naren advises retail investors to maintain asset allocation and a long-term view, and stresses that a healthy IPO market hinges on reasonable pricing to sustain its boom.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:38:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e62e4342f77179e6e03a_1767106341461.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PM Modi's Bold Vision: Reforms for India's Global Economic Dominance Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PM-Modis-Bold-Vision-Reforms-for-Indias-Global-Economic-Dominance-Revealed/6953e6314342f77179e6e071</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PM-Modis-Bold-Vision-Reforms-for-Indias-Global-Economic-Dominance-Revealed/6953e6314342f77179e6e071</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi met with economists to discuss critical reforms needed across sectors for long-term growth and global integration. He emphasized making India a global hub for international markets, aligning with the Viksit Bharat 2047 aspiration. Discussions focused on enhancing productivity, leveraging AI, and scaling Digital Public Infrastructure. Economists shared insights suggesting that ongoing reforms will solidify India's position as one of the world's fastest-growing economies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:37:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e6314342f77179e6e070_1767106270794.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor Strikes Deal: Big Boost for Commercial Vehicle Sales &amp; EV Push!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Strikes-Deal-Big-Boost-for-Commercial-Vehicle-Sales-and-EV-Push/6953e65d4342f77179e6e0e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Strikes-Deal-Big-Boost-for-Commercial-Vehicle-Sales-and-EV-Push/6953e65d4342f77179e6e0e8</guid><description>TVS Motor Company has partnered with Manba Finance, an NBFC, to offer retail finance solutions for its commercial mobility portfolio. This aims to improve vehicle affordability and access to financing for customers across India, focusing on three-wheelers (ICE and EV). The collaboration seeks to strengthen the ecosystem, penetrate rural markets, and support last-mile entrepreneurs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:37:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e65d4342f77179e6e0e7_1767107233505.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shalini Bhupal Buys Taj GVK Stake for ₹592 Cr, IHCL Exits! What Happens Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shalini-Bhupal-Buys-Taj-GVK-Stake-for-592-Cr-IHCL-Exits-What-Happens-Next/6953e1504342f77179e6d5ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shalini-Bhupal-Buys-Taj-GVK-Stake-for-592-Cr-IHCL-Exits-What-Happens-Next/6953e1504342f77179e6d5ce</guid><description>Shalini Bhupal, a promoter shareholder, has acquired a 25.52% stake in Taj GVK Hotels &amp; Resorts Ltd from The Indian Hotels Company Ltd (IHCL) for ₹592 crore. This transaction leads to the termination of agreements between the two companies, resulting in IHCL directors stepping down and Taj GVK Hotels preparing to remove 'Taj' from its corporate name. IHCL will continue operating existing hotels under current agreements.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:15:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e1504342f77179e6d5cd_1767104968220.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PowerGrid Bags Rs 2,000 Crore Battery Storage Project in Andhra Pradesh: What It Means for India's Energy Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/PowerGrid-Bags-Rs-2000-Crore-Battery-Storage-Project-in-Andhra-Pradesh-What-It-Means-for-Indias-Energy-Future/6953e15a4342f77179e6d5fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/PowerGrid-Bags-Rs-2000-Crore-Battery-Storage-Project-in-Andhra-Pradesh-What-It-Means-for-Indias-Energy-Future/6953e15a4342f77179e6d5fb</guid><description>Power Grid Corporation of India Limited (PowerGrid) has been awarded a major bid to set up a 2,000 MWh battery energy storage system in Andhra Pradesh. This project, operating under a build-own-operate model and supported by Viability Gap Funding, aims to enhance grid flexibility, reliability, and renewable energy integration. A specific 150 MW unit will be installed at Kalikiri. The award date was December 29, 2025, though PowerGrid shares saw a slight dip on December 30.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:15:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e15a4342f77179e6d5fa_1767104974452.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>