<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 21:16:19 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Big Win! Wipro's Santoor Overtakes HUL's Lifebuoy in Massive Indian Soap Market Shake-up!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Big-Win-Wipros-Santoor-Overtakes-HULs-Lifebuoy-in-Massive-Indian-Soap-Market-Shake-up/694b0602e10c98d0787a220c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Big-Win-Wipros-Santoor-Overtakes-HULs-Lifebuoy-in-Massive-Indian-Soap-Market-Shake-up/694b0602e10c98d0787a220c</guid><description>Wipro Consumer Care's Santoor has reportedly become India's largest soap brand, surpassing Hindustan Unilever's Lifebuoy. Wipro estimates Santoor's 2025 revenue at ₹2,850 crore. However, this claim is contested, as AC Nielsen data shows Lifebuoy and Lux with higher market share. Wipro argues Nielsen's rural representation is inadequate for their strong performance in specific states. Hindustan Unilever stated they rely on multiple data sources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 21:03:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b0602e10c98d0787a220b_1766524498706.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Export Shock: SUVs CRUSH Cars in Stunning Global Shift! See The Numbers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Export-Shock-SUVs-CRUSH-Cars-in-Stunning-Global-Shift-See-The-Numbers/694b062de10c98d0787a2245</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Export-Shock-SUVs-CRUSH-Cars-in-Stunning-Global-Shift-See-The-Numbers/694b062de10c98d0787a2245</guid><description>India's automotive export landscape is undergoing a major transformation as utility vehicles (SUVs, MPVs) are now outpacing traditional passenger cars. November marked a historic first, with UV exports exceeding car shipments. This trend, driven by demand for higher-value vehicles and compact models, is expected to continue, positioning India as a key manufacturing hub for SUVs and signaling a new era for its auto sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 21:03:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Shockwave from Tata Motors: Foreign EV Makers Must Invest in India or Face Blockade!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Shockwave-from-Tata-Motors-Foreign-EV-Makers-Must-Invest-in-India-or-Face-Blockade/694b05f8e10c98d0787a21dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Shockwave-from-Tata-Motors-Foreign-EV-Makers-Must-Invest-in-India-or-Face-Blockade/694b05f8e10c98d0787a21dd</guid><description>Tata Motors, India's leading EV manufacturer, is urging multinational electric vehicle companies, including those from China, to prioritize local investment. CEO Shailesh Chandra stated that foreign players must not only tap into India's vast EV market but also commit to building capabilities, creating local jobs, and increasing localization. Tata Motors itself plans a significant investment of up to ₹18,000 crore by 2029-30, aiming to launch five new EV models and maintain a dominant 45-50% market share.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 21:03:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Refurbished Phone Surge: How India's Market is Doubling Down on Growth Despite Giant Exits!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Refurbished-Phone-Surge-How-Indias-Market-is-Doubling-Down-on-Growth-Despite-Giant-Exits/694af4c4c53538a89e11115b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Refurbished-Phone-Surge-How-Indias-Market-is-Doubling-Down-on-Growth-Despite-Giant-Exits/694af4c4c53538a89e11115b</guid><description>India's organized refurbished smartphone market is poised for double-digit growth this year, bouncing back strongly after Amazon and Flipkart exited the segment. A successful festive season and strategic expansion into laptops and smartwatches have revitalized sales. Companies are increasingly focusing on direct-to-consumer channels, with key players like Cashify projecting significant revenue increases and improved trade-in volumes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:50:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694af4c4c53538a89e11115a_1766520310896.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samsonite Shrugs Off Discount Rivals! India Demand Surges Amid Travel Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Samsonite-Shrugs-Off-Discount-Rivals-India-Demand-Surges-Amid-Travel-Boom/694af4acc53538a89e111119</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Samsonite-Shrugs-Off-Discount-Rivals-India-Demand-Surges-Amid-Travel-Boom/694af4acc53538a89e111119</guid><description>Samsonite is maintaining its premium pricing strategy in India, resisting deep discounts offered by smaller, digital-first luggage startups. Despite near-term market share pressure, the company sees strong demand driven by normalizing domestic travel, weddings, and religious tourism. India is now Samsonite's third-largest market, outperforming slower growth in developed economies, with American Tourister leading the recovery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:49:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694af4acc53538a89e111118_1766520184818.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Private Markets Boom: Domestic Giants Poised to Ignite Next Growth Phase!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Private-Markets-Boom-Domestic-Giants-Poised-to-Ignite-Next-Growth-Phase/694aee74c53538a89e110ee3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Private-Markets-Boom-Domestic-Giants-Poised-to-Ignite-Next-Growth-Phase/694aee74c53538a89e110ee3</guid><description>India's private markets have seen remarkable growth over the last decade, quadrupling investments to ₹4.68 trillion in 2024 from ₹1.26 trillion in 2015. This expansion, driven by factors like rising wealth and supportive policies, is expected to continue. Domestic institutions are identified as crucial for unlocking the next level of growth in this sector, which operates outside traditional stock and bond markets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:25:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aee74c53538a89e110ee2_1766518462057.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai Land Frenzy: Record ₹2,250 Crore Bid Ignites Developer Race for Prime Mahalaxmi Plot!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mumbai-Land-Frenzy-Record-2250-Crore-Bid-Ignites-Developer-Race-for-Prime-Mahalaxmi-Plot/694aeb51c53538a89e110cde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mumbai-Land-Frenzy-Record-2250-Crore-Bid-Ignites-Developer-Race-for-Prime-Mahalaxmi-Plot/694aeb51c53538a89e110cde</guid><description>The Railway Land Development Authority (RLDA) received its highest-ever bid of ₹2,250 crore for a 2.5-acre land parcel in Mumbai's Mahalaxmi locality. Dineshchandra R Agrawal Infracon was the highest bidder, showcasing strong developer confidence in prime urban real estate. This auction for a 99-year lease sets a new benchmark, though high costs pose potential project completion challenges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:09:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aeb51c53538a89e110cdd_1766517664874.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bristol Myers Squibb Taps AI for Lightning-Fast Drug Launches in India, Shaking Up Pharma!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Bristol-Myers-Squibb-Taps-AI-for-Lightning-Fast-Drug-Launches-in-India-Shaking-Up-Pharma/694aeb61c53538a89e110d30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Bristol-Myers-Squibb-Taps-AI-for-Lightning-Fast-Drug-Launches-in-India-Shaking-Up-Pharma/694aeb61c53538a89e110d30</guid><description>Bristol Myers Squibb is making India a critical growth engine, leveraging artificial intelligence to dramatically accelerate drug launches and commercialization. The company is investing over $100 million in a new Gen AI hub in Mumbai, aiming to cut drug commercialization timelines from months to as little as two weeks. This strategic move supports a robust pipeline of new medicines across oncology, haematology, cardiovascular, and immunology, preparing BMS for future patent cliffs and enhancing patient access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:09:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aeb61c53538a89e110d2f_1766517914553.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HMEL Unleashes Rs 2,600 Crore Plan: Petrochemical Boom and Fuel Stations Across Punjab!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/HMEL-Unleashes-Rs-2600-Crore-Plan-Petrochemical-Boom-and-Fuel-Stations-Across-Punjab/694aeb22c53538a89e110caa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/HMEL-Unleashes-Rs-2600-Crore-Plan-Petrochemical-Boom-and-Fuel-Stations-Across-Punjab/694aeb22c53538a89e110caa</guid><description>HPCL Mittal Energy Ltd (HMEL) plans a significant ₹2,600 crore investment to establish a new petrochemical facility at its Bathinda refinery, focusing on polypropylene downstream industries and fine chemicals. The company is also entering the fuel retailing business, planning petrol pumps across Punjab offering petrol, diesel, CNG, and EV charging. This move aims to bolster its role as a major polypropylene supplier and expand its market presence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aeb22c53538a89e110ca9_1766517618569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Novelis Secures $800 Million Loan to Recover from US Plant Fires, Boosting Hindalco's Operations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Novelis-Secures-800-Million-Loan-to-Recover-from-US-Plant-Fires-Boosting-Hindalcos-Operations/694aeab3c53538a89e110c04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Novelis-Secures-800-Million-Loan-to-Recover-from-US-Plant-Fires-Boosting-Hindalcos-Operations/694aeab3c53538a89e110c04</guid><description>Hindalco's US subsidiary, Novelis, has raised an $800 million five-year term loan from Mitsubishi UFJ Financial Group, Standard Chartered, and HSBC. The funds will infuse equity into Novelis, primarily to cover elevated capital needs following recent fires at its Oswego, New York facility, which is vital for supplying aluminum sheets to U.S. automakers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:07:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aeab3c53538a89e110c03_1766517597318.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GST Revolution: 2025 Tax Overhaul Promises Massive Savings &amp; Boost for Consumers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GST-Revolution-2025-Tax-Overhaul-Promises-Massive-Savings-and-Boost-for-Consumers/694ae16a6c8849bc229f6899</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GST-Revolution-2025-Tax-Overhaul-Promises-Massive-Savings-and-Boost-for-Consumers/694ae16a6c8849bc229f6899</guid><description>In 2025, India's Goods and Services Tax (GST) underwent its most significant reform since 2017. The government replaced the four-slab structure with a streamlined two-slab system, significantly reducing taxes on essential goods, daily-use items, vehicles, and insurance premiums. This 'GST 2.0' aims to stimulate consumption and simplify compliance for businesses while keeping revenue stable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:22:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ae16a6c8849bc229f6898_1766515391507.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Endurance Technologies Suffers Cyber Attack: Is Your Data Safe? Investors on Edge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Endurance-Technologies-Suffers-Cyber-Attack-Is-Your-Data-Safe-Investors-on-Edge/694ae0746c8849bc229f3eb6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Endurance-Technologies-Suffers-Cyber-Attack-Is-Your-Data-Safe-Investors-on-Edge/694ae0746c8849bc229f3eb6</guid><description>Endurance Technologies Ltd. disclosed a cybersecurity incident affecting its IT infrastructure on Tuesday, December 23. The auto component maker stated that immediate measures were taken to isolate systems and initiate remediation. The company currently assesses no material impact on its operations or financial standing, though a detailed investigation is ongoing. Despite the reassurance, shares of Endurance Technologies Ltd. declined 2.13% to ₹2,600.00 on the NSE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:22:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ae0746c8849bc229f3eb5_1766515060776.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Union Bank of India Slashes Home &amp; Vehicle Loan Rates - Borrowers Rejoice!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Union-Bank-of-India-Slashes-Home-and-Vehicle-Loan-Rates-Borrowers-Rejoice/694adfc06c8849bc229eeb07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Union-Bank-of-India-Slashes-Home-and-Vehicle-Loan-Rates-Borrowers-Rejoice/694adfc06c8849bc229eeb07</guid><description>Union Bank of India has announced a significant reduction in its home loan interest rates by 0.30% and vehicle loan rates by 0.40%. This move follows the Reserve Bank of India's recent cut in the repo rate, aiming to pass on benefits to borrowers. The bank's financial results showed a slight revenue decline but stable net profit.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694adfc06c8849bc229eeb06_1766514910416.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's 2025 Masterstroke: Indian Banking Reset Sparks Growth &amp; Consolidation Wave!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-2025-Masterstroke-Indian-Banking-Reset-Sparks-Growth-and-Consolidation-Wave/694ae0906c8849bc229f5002</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-2025-Masterstroke-Indian-Banking-Reset-Sparks-Growth-and-Consolidation-Wave/694ae0906c8849bc229f5002</guid><description>In 2025, the Reserve Bank of India, under Governor Sanjay Malhotra, launched a sweeping regulatory overhaul, enacting over 80 changes to simplify rules, boost bank balance sheets, and revive credit growth. This strategic shift moves Indian banking from crisis-era caution to growth-era dynamism, facilitating consolidation, encouraging foreign investment, and preparing the sector for India's next economic cycle.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:21:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ae0906c8849bc229f5001_1766515145145.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RVNL Shake-Up: New CMD Takes Charge Amidst Profit Dip! What Investors Must Know</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/RVNL-Shake-Up-New-CMD-Takes-Charge-Amidst-Profit-Dip-What-Investors-Must-Know/694adf376c8849bc229e13c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/RVNL-Shake-Up-New-CMD-Takes-Charge-Amidst-Profit-Dip-What-Investors-Must-Know/694adf376c8849bc229e13c8</guid><description>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL) has announced a significant leadership change, appointing Saleem Ahmad as its new Chairman and Managing Director effective December 23, 2025. This transition occurs as the company reported a 19.7% year-on-year drop in net profit for the September quarter, settling at ₹230.3 crore. Despite a 5.5% increase in revenue to ₹5,123 crore, profitability faced pressure with EBITDA declining 20.3% and margins narrowing to 4.2%. Investors are watching closely to see how the new leadership navigates these financial headwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:21:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694adf376c8849bc229e13c7_1766514923370.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Nuclear Ambitions Soar: Investors Urge Independent Advisory Body to Navigate Sector Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Nuclear-Ambitions-Soar-Investors-Urge-Independent-Advisory-Body-to-Navigate-Sector-Growth/694add91edf7500b47749596</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Nuclear-Ambitions-Soar-Investors-Urge-Independent-Advisory-Body-to-Navigate-Sector-Growth/694add91edf7500b47749596</guid><description>Prospective investors in India's newly opened nuclear power sector are calling for an independent advisory body. This entity would provide crucial techno-commercial support, covering design, engineering, site selection, and policy guidance to help new private players navigate the highly regulated industry. Experts like Amit Sharma of Tata Consulting Engineers and a government panel have recommended such a body, noting that the state-owned Nuclear Power Corporation of India may not have the capacity to support all emerging companies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:15:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694add91edf7500b47749595_1766514172486.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shockwaves in Indian Markets: Retail Investors Flee Stocks, Highest Outflows Since 2019!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Shockwaves-in-Indian-Markets-Retail-Investors-Flee-Stocks-Highest-Outflows-Since-2019/694addc1edf7500b4774a993</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Shockwaves-in-Indian-Markets-Retail-Investors-Flee-Stocks-Highest-Outflows-Since-2019/694addc1edf7500b4774a993</guid><description>Indian stock markets witnessed significant activity in 2025, with retail investors pulling out ₹8,461 crore, the highest since 2019. Foreign Portfolio Investors (FPIs) recorded their largest ever outflows at ₹1.58 lakh crore. In contrast, Domestic Institutional Investors (DIIs) made record investments, infusing ₹7.61 lakh crore. While the overall investor base grew, the pace of new registrations slowed, influenced by global headwinds. The market capitalization of NSE-listed companies increased, with the Nifty 50 showing gains, though small-cap indices declined.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:13:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694addc1edf7500b4774a992_1766514187597.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Income Tax Nudge: 15 Lakh Taxpayers Revise Returns Amidst Bogus Donation Probe!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Income-Tax-Nudge-15-Lakh-Taxpayers-Revise-Returns-Amidst-Bogus-Donation-Probe/694adb9eedf7500b47740f9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Income-Tax-Nudge-15-Lakh-Taxpayers-Revise-Returns-Amidst-Bogus-Donation-Probe/694adb9eedf7500b47740f9e</guid><description>India's Income Tax Department has reported over 15 lakh taxpayers have revised their returns for Assessment Year 2025-26. This follows a 'NUDGE' campaign targeting incorrect deductions, especially concerning donations to unrecognized political parties and charitable institutions. Additionally, over 21 lakh taxpayers updated their returns this fiscal, contributing ₹2,500 crore in taxes. The deadline for revisions is December 31, 2025, after which updated ITRs will be necessary.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:06:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694adb9eedf7500b47740f9d_1766513666432.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC Bank Q3 Earnings Date Revealed! Investors Brace for Jan 17 Announcement – What to Watch For!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-Bank-Q3-Earnings-Date-Revealed-Investors-Brace-for-Jan-17-Announcement-What-to-Watch-For/694ad92fedf7500b47736d6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-Bank-Q3-Earnings-Date-Revealed-Investors-Brace-for-Jan-17-Announcement-What-to-Watch-For/694ad92fedf7500b47736d6d</guid><description>HDFC Bank has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on Saturday, January 17, 2026, to approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ending December 31, 2025. Investors await the Q3 FY26 earnings report, with the trading window for bank securities closing from December 25, 2025, to January 19, 2026. This announcement sets expectations for the earnings season.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ad92fedf7500b47736d6c_1766513054862.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NTPC Launches Massive Green Hydrogen Project! 🚀 What Investors MUST Know NOW!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Launches-Massive-Green-Hydrogen-Project-What-Investors-MUST-Know-NOW/694ad8baedf7500b47736d01</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Launches-Massive-Green-Hydrogen-Project-What-Investors-MUST-Know-NOW/694ad8baedf7500b47736d01</guid><description>NTPC, India's power giant, announced plans to establish a 1 tonne per day green hydrogen plant at Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh. The project, spearheaded by NTPC's R&amp;D wing NETRA, will utilize advanced plasma gasification technology to convert waste into hydrogen. This initiative aligns with NTPC's ambitious expansion goals for renewable energy capacity by 2032 and 2037, signalling a significant step towards cleaner energy solutions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:52:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ad8baedf7500b47736d00_1766513056294.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Telecom Duopoly: Jio &amp; Airtel Eye Price Hikes &amp; Premium Growth by 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Indias-Telecom-Duopoly-Jio-and-Airtel-Eye-Price-Hikes-and-Premium-Growth-by-2026/694ad7dbedf7500b47736beb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Indias-Telecom-Duopoly-Jio-and-Airtel-Eye-Price-Hikes-and-Premium-Growth-by-2026/694ad7dbedf7500b47736beb</guid><description>India's telecom sector is set to remain a duopoly dominated by Reliance Jio and Bharti Airtel through 2026, with Vodafone Idea facing challenges. Analysts predict a tariff hike of 10-12% in early 2025, as companies shift focus from subscriber growth to premiumization, higher Average Revenue Per User (ARPU), and enterprise 5G solutions driven by AI workloads. Success will hinge on executing pricing strategies and expanding high-value offerings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:44:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ad7dbedf7500b47736bea_1766512884251.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Talks Intensify: Will Exporters Finally Secure Deeper Market Access?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Talks-Intensify-Will-Exporters-Finally-Secure-Deeper-Market-Access/694ad0dcedf7500b4771cbfc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Talks-Intensify-Will-Exporters-Finally-Secure-Deeper-Market-Access/694ad0dcedf7500b4771cbfc</guid><description>India is actively engaged in high-level trade discussions with the United States, aiming to secure deeper market access for its exporters and resolve existing tariff challenges. Commerce Secretary Rajesh Agrawal expressed optimism about concluding these talks soon, which are crucial for restoring substantial bilateral trade. The negotiations are part of efforts to finalize a comprehensive Bilateral Trade Agreement (BTA) with the goal of significantly increasing trade volume between the two nations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:14:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ad0dcedf7500b4771cbfb_1766511576287.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma's Bold China Play: Boosting Stake for Global Dominance!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharmas-Bold-China-Play-Boosting-Stake-for-Global-Dominance/694acffdedf7500b4771cad4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharmas-Bold-China-Play-Boosting-Stake-for-Global-Dominance/694acffdedf7500b4771cad4</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma's Dutch subsidiary, Helix Healthcare BV, is increasing its stake in its Chinese joint venture, Luoxin Aurovitas Pharma, by 20% for over $5 million. This move is set to raise Aurobindo's stake to 50% by Q1 2026, with plans to acquire full 100% ownership by December 2029 for an additional $18.9 million. The expansion aims to boost manufacturing capacity for inhalation products and cater to growing market demand.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:12:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acffdedf7500b4771cad3_1766510858795.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Unleashes ₹2 Lakh Crore Liquidity Lifeline: Banking System Set for Major Support!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Unleashes-2-Lakh-Crore-Liquidity-Lifeline-Banking-System-Set-for-Major-Support/694acf2cedf7500b4771c735</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Unleashes-2-Lakh-Crore-Liquidity-Lifeline-Banking-System-Set-for-Major-Support/694acf2cedf7500b4771c735</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India announced a significant liquidity infusion, planning to purchase ₹2 lakh crore of government securities and conduct a $10 billion dollar-rupee swap auction. These measures, scheduled between December 29, 2025, and January 22, 2026, aim to ease conditions and ensure orderly liquidity in the banking system amidst evolving market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:12:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acf2cedf7500b4771c734_1766510735349.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Chaos Prompts Govt Action: New Airlines Get Green Light to Fly!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Chaos-Prompts-Govt-Action-New-Airlines-Get-Green-Light-to-Fly/694ace4bedf7500b477173da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Chaos-Prompts-Govt-Action-New-Airlines-Get-Green-Light-to-Fly/694ace4bedf7500b477173da</guid><description>The Indian government has issued No Objection Certificates (NOCs) to two new airlines, Al Hind Air and FlyExpress, this week, with Shankh Air having already received one. This move aims to boost competition and provide more choices for Indian flyers, following disruptions caused by IndiGo's schedule issues. The Aviation Ministry is encouraging new players in the rapidly growing Indian aviation market, despite industry concerns about high operating costs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:10:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ace4bedf7500b477173d9_1766510234717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metropolis Healthcare's Ameera Shah Reveals Secret to Margin Recovery &amp; Explosive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Metropolis-Healthcares-Ameera-Shah-Reveals-Secret-to-Margin-Recovery-and-Explosive-Growth/694acd19edf7500b47717291</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Metropolis-Healthcares-Ameera-Shah-Reveals-Secret-to-Margin-Recovery-and-Explosive-Growth/694acd19edf7500b47717291</guid><description>Metropolis Healthcare is outperforming rivals in India's organized diagnostics sector, driven by strong demand for preventive health packages and specialized tests. Promoter Ameera Shah expects continued revenue growth and margin recovery, despite a temporary drag from a past acquisition. The company plans strategic expansion through new collection centers and acquisitions to fuel its medium-term growth strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:54:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acd19edf7500b47717290_1766509965510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Exports to Sri Lanka SOAR 17%! Vehicles &amp; Ships Lead Massive Surge - Are You Invested?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Exports-to-Sri-Lanka-SOAR-17percent-Vehicles-and-Ships-Lead-Massive-Surge-Are-You-Invested/694acbcbedf7500b477171a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Exports-to-Sri-Lanka-SOAR-17percent-Vehicles-and-Ships-Lead-Massive-Surge-Are-You-Invested/694acbcbedf7500b477171a7</guid><description>India's exports to Sri Lanka surged by 17% year-on-year, reaching $3,364.49 million from April to November 2025. This significant growth was predominantly fueled by a remarkable 318% increase in vehicle exports and a 115% rise in ship exports. Other sectors like machinery, pharmaceuticals, and chemicals also contributed to this strong trade performance, highlighting India's expanding export footprint and robust economic ties with Sri Lanka.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acbcbedf7500b477171a6_1766509786237.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Next Tech Frontier: BYT Capital Launches ₹180 Crore Deep-Tech Fund Targeting Hardware Powerhouses!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Next-Tech-Frontier-BYT-Capital-Launches-180-Crore-Deep-Tech-Fund-Targeting-Hardware-Powerhouses/694acb05edf7500b477170e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Next-Tech-Frontier-BYT-Capital-Launches-180-Crore-Deep-Tech-Fund-Targeting-Hardware-Powerhouses/694acb05edf7500b477170e2</guid><description>BYT Capital has launched a ₹180-crore early-stage fund to invest in India's deep-tech sector, with a strong emphasis on hardware and foundational technologies. The fund, primarily backed by ultra-high-net-worth individuals and family offices, will support 18-20 startups over four years, focusing on areas like space-tech, robotics, life sciences, and clean energy. With 55% reserved for follow-on investments, BYT Capital aims to foster long-term growth, addressing a gap in growth-stage capital while signalling strong investor confidence in India's deep-tech future.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:53:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acb05edf7500b477170e1_1766509392387.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shyam Dhani IPO Crushes Expectations: 241x Subscribed on Day 2, GMP Rockets to 88%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shyam-Dhani-IPO-Crushes-Expectations-241x-Subscribed-on-Day-2-GMP-Rockets-to-88percent/694acab5edf7500b47717041</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shyam-Dhani-IPO-Crushes-Expectations-241x-Subscribed-on-Day-2-GMP-Rockets-to-88percent/694acab5edf7500b47717041</guid><description>Rajasthan-based Shyam Dhani Industries' IPO is generating huge investor excitement, receiving an overwhelming 241 times subscription on its second day of bidding. The company aims to raise ₹38.48 crore through fresh issue of shares priced at ₹65-70. Grey market investors are equally bullish, with the grey market premium (GMP) surging to an impressive 88 percent, reflecting strong demand across retail, non-institutional, and institutional categories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:51:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acab5edf7500b47717040_1766509342990.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto's Motorcycle Dominance Erodes as TVS and Hero Surge Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Autos-Motorcycle-Dominance-Erodes-as-TVS-and-Hero-Surge-Ahead/694aca11edf7500b47716f07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Autos-Motorcycle-Dominance-Erodes-as-TVS-and-Hero-Surge-Ahead/694aca11edf7500b47716f07</guid><description>Bajaj Auto is losing significant market share in its key motorcycle segments, particularly the 125cc and 150-250cc categories. Data shows Bajaj's overall motorcycle market share dropped from 18.5% in FY20 to 16.6% in FY25, further to 16% year-to-date FY26. Meanwhile, TVS Motor Company has seen its market share climb from 15.5% to nearly 19% in the same period, while Hero MotoCorp maintains its leading position. The 125cc segment, crucial for new buyers, sees TVS Motor significantly expanding its lead.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:45:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aca11edf7500b47716f06_1766509171550.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Poised for Manufacturing Boom? Samsung India Boss Reveals Major Shift Away From China!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Poised-for-Manufacturing-Boom-Samsung-India-Boss-Reveals-Major-Shift-Away-From-China/694ac9ededf7500b47716ec3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Poised-for-Manufacturing-Boom-Samsung-India-Boss-Reveals-Major-Shift-Away-From-China/694ac9ededf7500b47716ec3</guid><description>Samsung India's chief, JB Park, believes global brands are actively de-coupling from China for manufacturing, with India emerging as a prime destination. He cited India's Production Linked Incentive (PLI) schemes and its growing consumer market as key attractors. Park also highlighted India's strong engineering talent pool, crucial for global innovations in areas like semiconductors and AI, and noted Samsung India contributes significantly to global revenues, expecting this to grow. He also touched upon competition and the need to develop manpower proficient in automation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:41:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac9ededf7500b47716ec2_1766509239107.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Leap: Samsung Invests Billions, Joins PLI Scheme for Component Manufacturing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-AI-Leap-Samsung-Invests-Billions-Joins-PLI-Scheme-for-Component-Manufacturing/694ac40bedf7500b47716895</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-AI-Leap-Samsung-Invests-Billions-Joins-PLI-Scheme-for-Component-Manufacturing/694ac40bedf7500b47716895</guid><description>Samsung is significantly investing in India's Artificial Intelligence (AI) ecosystem and participating in the government's Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme for display modules. The company sees immense potential in India, aiming to transition its mass market offerings to premium. Samsung India has no immediate plans for an Initial Public Offering (IPO) on local stock exchanges. This strategic shift, particularly the focus on AI transformation over the next 30 years, leverages India's talent pool for global R&amp;D efforts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:16:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac40bedf7500b47716894_1766507829731.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JK Tyre's Bold Move: Cavendish Merger Unlocks Massive Growth Potential! See How!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JK-Tyres-Bold-Move-Cavendish-Merger-Unlocks-Massive-Growth-Potential-See-How/694ac3c7edf7500b477167da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JK-Tyres-Bold-Move-Cavendish-Merger-Unlocks-Massive-Growth-Potential-See-How/694ac3c7edf7500b477167da</guid><description>JK Tyre &amp; Industries has successfully completed the merger of its subsidiary, Cavendish Industries Ltd. This strategic integration aims to unlock significant value through enhanced operational synergies, economies of scale, a diversified product portfolio, and an expanded distribution network. Cavendish, acquired in 2016, manufactured truck/bus radial, truck/bus bias, and two/three-wheeler tires. Its capacity utilization has dramatically increased from 30% to 95% post-acquisition, contributing substantially to JK Tyre's overall operations. This merger reinforces JK Tyre's strategy of sustainable growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:16:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac3c7edf7500b477167d9_1766507662356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emerging Markets Shock: Are They Outperforming Due to Smart Policies or Just Pure Luck?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Emerging-Markets-Shock-Are-They-Outperforming-Due-to-Smart-Policies-or-Just-Pure-Luck/694ac40eedf7500b477168c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Emerging-Markets-Shock-Are-They-Outperforming-Due-to-Smart-Policies-or-Just-Pure-Luck/694ac40eedf7500b477168c0</guid><description>A recent IMF analysis revisits a 1993 paper, questioning the remarkable growth of emerging market economies (EMDEs), particularly in Asia. Despite global uncertainties like geopolitical tensions and trade wars, these regions show resilient and higher GDP growth compared to advanced economies. The IMF points to improved monetary and fiscal policy frameworks, including central bank independence and inflation targeting, as key drivers. However, the analysis prompts a deeper look, suggesting factors like global value chains and trade might also play significant roles beyond conventional economic policies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:13:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac40eedf7500b477168bf_1766507814446.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver ETFs Outshine Gold in 2025: Massive 137% Returns Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-ETFs-Outshine-Gold-in-2025-Massive-137percent-Returns-Revealed/694ac2b2edf7500b47716657</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-ETFs-Outshine-Gold-in-2025-Massive-137percent-Returns-Revealed/694ac2b2edf7500b47716657</guid><description>In 2025, Indian Silver ETFs delivered an astonishing 137% year-to-date return, nearly doubling the 73% gain from Gold ETFs. This surge was fueled by robust industrial demand, growing adoption in renewable energy, significant investor inflows, and supply constraints. The total Assets Under Management (AUM) for silver ETFs expanded sharply to ₹49,075 crore by November 2025, with trading volumes soaring by 560% due to increased participation from corporates and High Net Worth Individuals (HNIs). Nippon India Silver ETF led the market in liquidity and AUM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:13:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac2b2edf7500b47716656_1766507415677.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Unlocks Massive Value: Two Giants Set for Stock Market Debut!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Unlocks-Massive-Value-Two-Giants-Set-for-Stock-Market-Debut/694ac1bfedf7500b477164a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Unlocks-Massive-Value-Two-Giants-Set-for-Stock-Market-Debut/694ac1bfedf7500b477164a3</guid><description>Coal India's board has approved the in-principle listing of its two largest coal-producing subsidiaries, Mahanadi Coalfields and South Eastern Coalfields, following a directive from the Ministry of Coal. This strategic move aims to unlock value and provide investors with direct access to these key mining operations, building on previous IPO plans for other subsidiaries like CMPDI and BCCL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:13:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac1bfedf7500b477164a2_1766507405382.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sky's the Limit: Salesforce Partners Indian Drone Pioneer Garuda Aerospace for Global Expansion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Skys-the-Limit-Salesforce-Partners-Indian-Drone-Pioneer-Garuda-Aerospace-for-Global-Expansion/694ac136edf7500b47716423</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Skys-the-Limit-Salesforce-Partners-Indian-Drone-Pioneer-Garuda-Aerospace-for-Global-Expansion/694ac136edf7500b47716423</guid><description>US tech giant Salesforce has partnered with Chennai-based Garuda Aerospace, an Indian drone manufacturer. The collaboration aims to revolutionize Garuda's customer lifecycle, streamline operations, and fuel its expansion into Southeast Asia and Africa using Salesforce's unified intelligent platform. This digital transformation will enhance customer relationships and drive business growth across agriculture, defense, and infrastructure sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:12:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac136edf7500b47716422_1766507070652.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India's Bold Move: Board Approves Listing of Key Subsidiaries MCL &amp; SECL - What Investors Must Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-Indias-Bold-Move-Board-Approves-Listing-of-Key-Subsidiaries-MCL-and-SECL-What-Investors-Must-Know/694abed4edf7500b47716144</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-Indias-Bold-Move-Board-Approves-Listing-of-Key-Subsidiaries-MCL-and-SECL-What-Investors-Must-Know/694abed4edf7500b47716144</guid><description>Coal India Limited's Board of Directors has granted in-principle approval for the listing of its two major subsidiaries, Mahanadi Coalfields Limited (MCL) and South Eastern Coalfields Limited (SECL). This decision, following a directive from the Ministry of Coal, targets listing in the upcoming financial year 2027 and is contingent upon securing all necessary regulatory approvals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:53:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694abed4edf7500b47716143_1766506996395.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCS Q3 Earnings &amp; Dividend Alert! Key Dates for Investors Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Q3-Earnings-and-Dividend-Alert-Key-Dates-for-Investors-Revealed/694abe11edf7500b47715fde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Q3-Earnings-and-Dividend-Alert-Key-Dates-for-Investors-Revealed/694abe11edf7500b47715fde</guid><description>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) has announced its board meeting schedule for January 12, 2026, to approve its Q3 FY26 financial results. Investors will also be watching for the potential declaration of a third interim dividend, with a record date set for January 17, 2026. The company last reported a 1.4% profit rise in Q2 FY26.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:53:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694abe11edf7500b47715fdd_1766506579442.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Lands Big US Deal: Eye Drug NUFYMCO Set for US Launch! See What It Means for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Lands-Big-US-Deal-Eye-Drug-NUFYMCO-Set-for-US-Launch-See-What-It-Means-for-Investors/694abeb4edf7500b477160e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Lands-Big-US-Deal-Eye-Drug-NUFYMCO-Set-for-US-Launch-See-What-It-Means-for-Investors/694abeb4edf7500b477160e1</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences has partnered with Swiss company Bioeq AG to market NUFYMCO, an interchangeable biosimilar for macular degeneration treatment, in the United States. Zydus Lifesciences Global FZE will handle US commercialization, while Bioeq manages development and manufacturing. The drug, NUFYMCO, received US FDA approval on December 18, 2025, for treating conditions like wet age-related macular degeneration and diabetic macular edema. This collaboration expands Zydus's US biosimilar portfolio.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:53:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694abeb4edf7500b477160e0_1766506276768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>