<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:24:39 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Meesho's IPO Hype Fades: Logistics Woes Clash with Market Roar</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meeshos-IPO-Hype-Fades-Logistics-Woes-Clash-with-Market-Roar/6993798a7f94dd9d4c959bdd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meeshos-IPO-Hype-Fades-Logistics-Woes-Clash-with-Market-Roar/6993798a7f94dd9d4c959bdd</guid><description>The initial market euphoria surrounding Meesho's December 2025 IPO has significantly diminished, with investor focus now shifting to the operational realities of its logistics division. Despite strong revenue increases, the company continues to report substantial net losses, highlighting critical challenges in converting aggressive scaling into durable economic advantages. The high price-to-book valuation, while common in high-growth sectors, faces increasing pressure from operational complexities and competitive dynamics within India's rapidly expanding e-commerce logistics market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:09:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993798a7f94dd9d4c959bdc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BofA's India Push: Growth Bets Tempered by Compliance Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/BofAs-India-Push-Growth-Bets-Tempered-by-Compliance-Hurdles/699371797f94dd9d4c959829</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/BofAs-India-Push-Growth-Bets-Tempered-by-Compliance-Hurdles/699371797f94dd9d4c959829</guid><description>Bank of America is increasing its exposure to India, citing the nation's burgeoning middle class, skilled talent, and reformist government as key drivers. However, this strategic expansion is shadowed by significant operational complexities, including substantial data localization costs and the lingering impact of past regulatory investigations into its Indian securities unit. The bank's commitment to corporate and investment banking in India faces a complex balancing act between capitalizing on market opportunities and meticulously navigating stringent compliance requirements.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:35:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699371797f94dd9d4c959828_1771270793939.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gupta Power Bidding War: Giants Eye Distressed Infrastructure Asset</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gupta-Power-Bidding-War-Giants-Eye-Distressed-Infrastructure-Asset/699371707f94dd9d4c959812</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gupta-Power-Bidding-War-Giants-Eye-Distressed-Infrastructure-Asset/699371707f94dd9d4c959812</guid><description>A diverse group of industrial leaders, including Vedanta, Havells India, and UltraTech Cement, have submitted expressions of interest to acquire the debt-burdened Gupta Power Infrastructure, which faces admitted claims of ₹4,240 crore. The company's ongoing insolvency proceedings have attracted a wide range of players, from specialized engineering firms to financial institutions, highlighting a strategic scramble for assets within India's expanding power and infrastructure sectors ahead of the February 20 resolution plan deadline.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:35:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699371707f94dd9d4c959811.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent Bets on Tier 3/4 Towns: High-Stakes Growth Amid Valuation Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Bets-on-Tier-34-Towns-High-Stakes-Growth-Amid-Valuation-Risk/6993716f7f94dd9d4c9597fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Bets-on-Tier-34-Towns-High-Stakes-Growth-Amid-Valuation-Risk/6993716f7f94dd9d4c9597fb</guid><description>Trent is channeling two-thirds of its new store openings into India's Tier 3 and Tier 4 towns, aiming to capture future growth potential. This strategic pivot follows a robust Q3 FY26 where revenue climbed 15% year-on-year. However, the company faces the considerable challenge of accelerating fashion adoption and income growth in less developed markets, a high-stakes gambit that could strain margins and test its premium valuation amidst recent stock volatility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:35:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993716f7f94dd9d4c9597fa.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pharma Giants Sun Pharma &amp; Glenmark Embrace AI for Drug Development</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-Giants-Sun-Pharma-and-Glenmark-Embrace-AI-for-Drug-Development/6993716c7f94dd9d4c9597e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-Giants-Sun-Pharma-and-Glenmark-Embrace-AI-for-Drug-Development/6993716c7f94dd9d4c9597e4</guid><description>Indian pharmaceutical leaders Sun Pharma and Glenmark Pharmaceuticals are integrating Artificial Intelligence (AI) to revolutionize drug discovery and development. This strategic pivot aims to significantly reduce timelines and costs associated with bringing new medicines to market, signaling a broader industry trend towards innovation over traditional generics. While AI adoption is accelerating globally, with significant investment pouring into the sector, these Indian firms are poised to leverage the technology to enhance their competitive edge in the evolving pharmaceutical landscape.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993716c7f94dd9d4c9597e3_1771270731779.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Apollo, Bharti Face Integration Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Apollo-Bharti-Face-Integration-Hurdles/6993716c7f94dd9d4c9597cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Apollo-Bharti-Face-Integration-Hurdles/6993716c7f94dd9d4c9597cd</guid><description>While industry leaders envision India's AI-driven future, significant challenges in infrastructure, talent, and regulatory clarity temper optimistic projections for companies like Apollo Hospitals and Bharti Airtel. Apollo is investing in AI for healthcare delivery, planning strategic demergers and expansion, but faces breakeven delays and execution risks. Bharti Airtel leverages AI for its cloud platform and network optimization, yet faces a high P/E ratio and slower growth forecasts compared to market averages. Both companies operate within a complex evolving regulatory environment, necessitating a pragmatic approach to harness AI's potential.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993716c7f94dd9d4c9597cc_1771270652743.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Retail's ₹215T Boom: AI &amp; Strategy Key to Outpacing Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Retails-215T-Boom-AI-and-Strategy-Key-to-Outpacing-Competition/699371697f94dd9d4c9597b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Retails-215T-Boom-AI-and-Strategy-Key-to-Outpacing-Competition/699371697f94dd9d4c9597b6</guid><description>India's retail sector is projected to expand to ₹210-215 trillion by 2035, driven by robust economic growth and consumption. However, organized retailers are seeing their growth advantage over the broader market diminish, signaling increased competition. Success will hinge on leveraging artificial intelligence at scale and executing sharply defined consumer strategies, rather than relying on broad expansion or discount tactics. Companies must focus on creating differentiated value propositions to navigate evolving consumer demands for personalization and convenience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:35:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699371697f94dd9d4c9597b5_1771270646267.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Temple Town Real Estate Boom: Bubble or Sustainable Growth?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Temple-Town-Real-Estate-Boom-Bubble-or-Sustainable-Growth/699371677f94dd9d4c95979f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Temple-Town-Real-Estate-Boom-Bubble-or-Sustainable-Growth/699371677f94dd9d4c95979f</guid><description>Property developers are capitalizing on a surge in religious tourism and significant government infrastructure investment in India's temple towns, leading to rapid real estate development and price appreciation. However, the boom raises questions about market sustainability, developer financial health, and the potential for over-commercialization to dilute the spiritual appeal of these destinations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:35:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699371677f94dd9d4c95979e_1771270633391.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FDC Overhaul: Regulatory Labyrinth and Pharma's Strategic Crossroads</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-FDC-Overhaul-Regulatory-Labyrinth-and-Pharmas-Strategic-Crossroads/699369ee823bbe715bcaa9a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-FDC-Overhaul-Regulatory-Labyrinth-and-Pharmas-Strategic-Crossroads/699369ee823bbe715bcaa9a1</guid><description>India's drug regulators are re-evaluating 29 fixed-dose combination (FDC) drugs, primarily vitamin and mineral formulations, for potential prohibition due to lack of therapeutic justification. This move continues a protracted regulatory saga, recalling past bans and legal challenges. Companies face strategic uncertainty as the sector grapples with evolving standards, R&amp;D imperatives, and market access implications from such prolonged regulatory scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:03:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699369ee823bbe715bcaa9a0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 5G Slicing Push: Net Neutrality Faces Regulatory Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Indias-5G-Slicing-Push-Net-Neutrality-Faces-Regulatory-Test/699369ed823bbe715bcaa98a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Indias-5G-Slicing-Push-Net-Neutrality-Faces-Regulatory-Test/699369ed823bbe715bcaa98a</guid><description>Indian telecom giants like Reliance Jio and Airtel are urging the Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI) to update 2016 net neutrality regulations to permit 5G network slicing for premium services. This technology allows for partitioned networks, enabling differentiated speeds and quality for specific use cases like gaming or guaranteed upload speeds. While operators cite massive 5G investment ROI, regulators worldwide are navigating how to balance this with open internet principles, creating a complex scenario for India's digital future.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:03:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699369ed823bbe715bcaa989.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai Airport Cargo Halt Signals Adani's NMIA Strategic Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbai-Airport-Cargo-Halt-Signals-Adanis-NMIA-Strategic-Push/6993635b823bbe715bca3716</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbai-Airport-Cargo-Halt-Signals-Adanis-NMIA-Strategic-Push/6993635b823bbe715bca3716</guid><description>Mumbai International Airport Ltd (MIAL), operated by the Adani Group, plans to suspend dedicated cargo aircraft operations from August 2026 to May 2027 for infrastructure upgrades. The International Air Transport Association (IATA) has expressed significant concern due to a perceived lack of engagement and potential operational disruptions. This move is interpreted by some as a strategic play to channel traffic to the upcoming Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA), which is set to launch its cargo terminal with substantial capacity, potentially accelerating its integration into the logistics network while the established hub undergoes upgrades.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:35:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993635b823bbe715bca3715.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shreeji Shipping Contract Voided by Troubled KTLP Creditors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Shreeji-Shipping-Contract-Voided-by-Troubled-KTLP-Creditors/69936089823bbe715bc9e5a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Shreeji-Shipping-Contract-Voided-by-Troubled-KTLP-Creditors/69936089823bbe715bc9e5a0</guid><description>Shreeji Shipping Global Limited has received a significant setback as its critical Port Handling Agreement with Karanja Terminals and Logistics Private Limited (KTLP) has been declared "void ab initio" by KTLP's Committee of Creditors. KTLP is currently undergoing insolvency proceedings. This decision poses a substantial risk to Shreeji's operations and expected revenues, prompting the company to review the matter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:23:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69936089823bbe715bc9e59f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jio Builds India's AI Backbone</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Jio-Builds-Indias-AI-Backbone/69936017823bbe715bc9e527</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Jio-Builds-Indias-AI-Backbone/69936017823bbe715bc9e527</guid><description>Reliance Jio Chairman Akash Ambani showcased the company's extensive AI ecosystem at the India AI Impact Summit 2026, presenting the foundational Jio AI Stack designed for scalable deployment. The initiative spans critical sectors including cultural preservation with Jio Sanskriti AI, healthcare via Jio Arogya AI, personalized education with Jio Shiksha, and smart living solutions through Jio AI Home. This strategic push aligns with India's digital transformation agenda, positioning Jio as a key enabler of national AI adoption and indigenous technological advancement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:21:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69936017823bbe715bc9e526.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Megamont Transforms: Global Trading Pivot Post-Acquisition.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Megamont-Transforms-Global-Trading-Pivot-Post-Acquisition/69935c4e823bbe715bc9e2b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Megamont-Transforms-Global-Trading-Pivot-Post-Acquisition/69935c4e823bbe715bc9e2b1</guid><description>Megamont Limited, formerly V.R.Woodart, has unveiled its first consolidated results after acquiring Nidimo Mont and Parent Mont. The company is now a global player in stainless steel trading and commodity arbitrage, reporting ¥314.58 crore revenue and ¥3.27 crore net profit in Q3 FY26. However, consolidated year-on-year data is missing, and margins are thin at 1.46% EBITDA. The strategy focuses on capital-efficient trading and global price discovery.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69935c4e823bbe715bc9e2b0_1771265901046.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Institutional Bets Signal Sector Shifts: EIL, Aye Finance Lead Bulk Deals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Institutional-Bets-Signal-Sector-Shifts-EIL-Aye-Finance-Lead-Bulk-Deals/69935bda823bbe715bc9e217</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Institutional-Bets-Signal-Sector-Shifts-EIL-Aye-Finance-Lead-Bulk-Deals/69935bda823bbe715bc9e217</guid><description>Bulk deal activity on February 16 saw Goldman Sachs significantly expand its stake in Aye Finance, while BofA Securities Europe SA initiated a substantial position in Engineers India (EIL). Craft Emerging Market Fund PCC entered Easy Trip Planners, and Pine Oak Global Fund acquired shares in Vardhman Polytex amidst a notable exit by Ekjot Singh Chawla. These transactions highlight strategic institutional conviction and potential sector rotations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69935bda823bbe715bc9e216.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dalio: World Order Breakdown Favors Gold Over Crypto</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dalio-World-Order-Breakdown-Favors-Gold-Over-Crypto/69935a8d823bbe715bc99263</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dalio-World-Order-Breakdown-Favors-Gold-Over-Crypto/69935a8d823bbe715bc99263</guid><description>Ray Dalio's 'Stage 6' of the Big Cycle signals a breakdown in global financial order, compelling investors to prioritize capital preservation over speculative growth. This macro shift elevates gold, with its millennia-long track record as a store of value, above cryptocurrencies, which face inherent digital and regulatory risks. While gold ETFs saw record inflows in 2025 and central banks are aggressively accumulating the metal, Bitcoin grapples with volatility and a shorter history, positioning gold as the favored asset for survival in uncertain times.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:57:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69935a8d823bbe715bc99262.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes 'De Minimis' FDI Rule to Speed Up Small Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-De-Minimis-FDI-Rule-to-Speed-Up-Small-Investments/69935983823bbe715bc9791e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-De-Minimis-FDI-Rule-to-Speed-Up-Small-Investments/69935983823bbe715bc9791e</guid><description>India is reassessing Press Note 3, introduced in April 2020, to facilitate smaller foreign direct investments (FDI). The proposed 'de minimis' threshold aims to shift minor investments from a case-by-case approval process to automatic clearance, reducing compliance burdens and accelerating capital flow. While the core security vetting for investments from bordering nations, particularly China, remains intact, this recalibration seeks to balance national security with economic facilitation, especially for sectors needing capital but lacking sensitive technologies. This policy adjustment aligns with India's broader industrial objectives, including the 'Make in India' initiative.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:53:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69935983823bbe715bc9791d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Extends Iran-Linked Flight Cuts; Operational Strain Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Extends-Iran-Linked-Flight-Cuts-Operational-Strain-Mounts/699354e3823bbe715bc8e6bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Extends-Iran-Linked-Flight-Cuts-Operational-Strain-Mounts/699354e3823bbe715bc8e6bc</guid><description>IndiGo has extended flight cancellations for routes serving Tbilisi, Almaty, Baku, and Tashkent until March 28, 2026, citing ongoing geopolitical developments impacting Iranian airspace. This decision escalates operational challenges, forcing the airline to adopt longer, costlier flight paths. The disruption adds to existing pressures on IndiGo's high-utilization model, compounding concerns about fleet efficiency and competitive positioning amidst heightened regional instability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:33:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699354e3823bbe715bc8e6bb_1771263678537.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Burry's Palantir Critique Fuels Valuation Fears Amidst AI Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Burrys-Palantir-Critique-Fuels-Valuation-Fears-Amidst-AI-Rally/699354a7823bbe715bc8d1fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Burrys-Palantir-Critique-Fuels-Valuation-Fears-Amidst-AI-Rally/699354a7823bbe715bc8d1fe</guid><description>Michael Burry has intensified his scrutiny of Palantir Technologies (PLTR), combining allegations of "covert smear campaigns" with a bleak technical forecast predicting a sharp stock decline. This comes despite Palantir's recent surge, fueled by AI optimism, which has pushed its market capitalization to over $313 billion. Burry questions the company's financial reporting and historical profitability, suggesting current high valuations may be unsustainable, especially as the broader tech sector faces increased scrutiny over AI-driven growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699354a7823bbe715bc8d1fd_1771263438508.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Holds Rates: Growth vs. Inflation Balancing Act</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Holds-Rates-Growth-vs-Inflation-Balancing-Act/699353ee823bbe715bc8b638</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Holds-Rates-Growth-vs-Inflation-Balancing-Act/699353ee823bbe715bc8b638</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has maintained its key policy rates, signalling a neutral stance to manage inflation risks even as economic growth remains robust. Despite projections of strong GDP expansion in FY27, the central bank is cautious, balancing domestic stability against global headwinds like geopolitical tensions and capital flow volatility. Inflation, though showing moderation in core components, is influenced by food normalization and commodity price movements, necessitating continued vigilance and limiting scope for immediate rate cuts. Financial conditions remain generally stable, supported by strong credit growth, but are subject to external pressures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:29:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699353ee823bbe715bc8b637.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Health Budget: Ambition vs. Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Health-Budget-Ambition-vs-Execution-Hurdles/69935346823bbe715bc8b5b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Health-Budget-Ambition-vs-Execution-Hurdles/69935346823bbe715bc8b5b9</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 targets a major pivot in India's health policy, focusing on biopharmaceuticals, clinical trials, and preventive care. While a ₹10,000 crore 'Biopharma SHAKTI' initiative signals intent to boost domestic manufacturing and innovation, historical underinvestment in R&amp;D, significant systemic healthcare challenges, and intense global competition pose substantial execution risks. The budget's success hinges on overcoming these deep-rooted issues.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:26:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69935346823bbe715bc8b5b8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Salzer Electronics Q3 Revenue Jumps 24%, Smart Meter Woes Plague Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Salzer-Electronics-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-24percent-Smart-Meter-Woes-Plague-Growth/6993510f823bbe715bc8ae4b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Salzer-Electronics-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-24percent-Smart-Meter-Woes-Plague-Growth/6993510f823bbe715bc8ae4b</guid><description>Salzer Electronics Limited posted a strong 24% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹424 Crores for Q3 FY26. However, the company's earnings call highlighted significant investor concerns regarding the slow execution and profitability of its smart meter division. While industrial switchgear and wires &amp; cables segments performed well, input cost volatility and low margins in cables segment impacted overall profitability, pushing EBITDA growth to a modest 4%. Management reiterated revenue guidance but targets a better EBITDA margin in FY27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:17:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993510f823bbe715bc8ae4a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lenskart Revenue Soars 37%, Profit Triples Amidst Smart Glasses Launch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskart-Revenue-Soars-37percent-Profit-Triples-Amidst-Smart-Glasses-Launch/6993510e823bbe715bc8ae35</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskart-Revenue-Soars-37percent-Profit-Triples-Amidst-Smart-Glasses-Launch/6993510e823bbe715bc8ae35</guid><description>Lenskart Solutions Limited reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with revenue jumping 37% year-on-year to ₹2,308 Cr. Profit after tax (PAT) tripled to ₹133 Cr, driven by strong sales growth and significant margin expansion. The company also announced plans for a smart glasses launch in Q4 FY26, signaling a push into wearable technology.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993510e823bbe715bc8ae34.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PIGL Jumps on Order Wins, But Margins Show Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PIGL-Jumps-on-Order-Wins-But-Margins-Show-Strain/69934d50823bbe715bc8aced</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PIGL-Jumps-on-Order-Wins-But-Margins-Show-Strain/69934d50823bbe715bc8aced</guid><description>Power and Instrumentation (Gujarat) Limited (PIGL) posted a strong 43.2% year-on-year revenue jump in Q3 FY26, driven by ₹124.17 Cr in new orders. However, profitability faced pressure with net profit rising only 11.9% and margins contracting. The company also launched a new busduct system, aiming to boost future growth, but investors should note a rise in standalone debt and a decline in interest coverage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:01:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69934d50823bbe715bc8acec_1771261380519.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 'Create in India' Mission: Ambition Meets Execution Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Create-in-India-Mission-Ambition-Meets-Execution-Reality/699346e22e6a0b8ae17d5865</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Create-in-India-Mission-Ambition-Meets-Execution-Reality/699346e22e6a0b8ae17d5865</guid><description>India's 'Create in India' mission targets a global creative hub status, leveraging robust digital infrastructure and a skilled workforce. The initiative aims to bolster the 'Orange Economy' sectors like AVGC, gaming, and digital media, building on recent policy momentum and industry support frameworks. However, success hinges on navigating significant execution challenges and fierce global competition, particularly concerning AI integration and IP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:33:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699346e22e6a0b8ae17d5864_1771259738721.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Max Estates Q3: Sales Boom, Debt Controlled, Future Looks Bright</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-Q3-Sales-Boom-Debt-Controlled-Future-Looks-Bright/699346c02e6a0b8ae17d583d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-Q3-Sales-Boom-Debt-Controlled-Future-Looks-Bright/699346c02e6a0b8ae17d583d</guid><description>Max Estates reported robust Q3 FY'26 results, driven by strong residential presales exceeding ₹7,500 Crores across key projects and a significant 38% YoY rise in lease rental income to ₹115 Crores. The company aims to add 1-2 million sq ft annually in residential and commercial spaces, maintaining a net debt of ₹414 Crores with healthy cash reserves. Management expressed confidence in the demand for premium properties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:33:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699346c02e6a0b8ae17d583c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks Plunge Amid AI Trust Deficit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Plunge-Amid-AI-Trust-Deficit/699345e32e6a0b8ae17d5735</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Plunge-Amid-AI-Trust-Deficit/699345e32e6a0b8ae17d5735</guid><description>Leading Indian IT firms TCS, Infosys, HCL Technologies, and Wipro have experienced significant stock market declines over the past year, ranging from 14% to 31%, fueled by escalating anxieties over artificial intelligence disruption. Despite management's consistent use of optimistic language in public disclosures, the market's reaction suggests a deep trust deficit, particularly as the industry grapples with AI's potential to automate core IT services and impact non-AI business segments. This current phase contrasts sharply with past technological shifts, raising concerns about the sector's future adaptability and shareholder value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699345e32e6a0b8ae17d5734.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks Brace for Regulatory Overhaul, Deposit Scramble &amp; InvIT Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Brace-for-Regulatory-Overhaul-Deposit-Scramble-and-InvIT-Risks/699345da2e6a0b8ae17d571b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Brace-for-Regulatory-Overhaul-Deposit-Scramble-and-InvIT-Risks/699345da2e6a0b8ae17d571b</guid><description>Indian banks face a confluence of challenges, including a shift to risk-based deposit insurance premiums and ongoing discussions around Cash Reserve Ratio (CRR) abolition. These regulatory evolutions occur amidst fierce competition for deposits from mutual funds and bond markets. Concurrently, Real Estate and Infrastructure Investment Trusts (REITs and InvITs) are undergoing regulatory refinements, but risks associated with higher leverage and greenfield projects persist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:29:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699345da2e6a0b8ae17d571a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Payments: Value-Add Needs Infrastructure Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Digital-Payments-Value-Add-Needs-Infrastructure-Boost/6993457f2e6a0b8ae17d56b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Digital-Payments-Value-Add-Needs-Infrastructure-Boost/6993457f2e6a0b8ae17d56b0</guid><description>India's digital payment ecosystem, led by UPI and RuPay, has achieved significant transaction volume growth. However, a new report from the Department of Financial Services emphasizes that its future potential remains largely untapped due to persistent infrastructure deficits and reliability issues, especially in rural regions. The focus is shifting towards integrating value-added services like micro-credit and insurance, but this must be paralleled by substantial investments in digital infrastructure to ensure scalability and trust.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:27:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993457f2e6a0b8ae17d56af_1771259368382.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Eases ECB Rules: Capital Infusion vs. Financial Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Eases-ECB-Rules-Capital-Infusion-vs-Financial-Risk/699341232e6a0b8ae17d54e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Eases-ECB-Rules-Capital-Infusion-vs-Financial-Risk/699341232e6a0b8ae17d54e0</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has significantly amended its External Commercial Borrowing (ECB) framework, removing restrictions on borrowing costs and average maturity periods to streamline foreign capital access for Indian businesses. The changes aim to boost investment by expanding eligible borrowers and lenders and easing end-use restrictions, allowing ECB proceeds for land and immovable property acquisition. However, the move also introduces potential risks related to increased external debt and currency volatility, necessitating careful monitoring.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:09:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699341232e6a0b8ae17d54df.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Yields Stubbornly High Amid Record Debt Supply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Yields-Stubbornly-High-Amid-Record-Debt-Supply/699341232e6a0b8ae17d54c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Yields-Stubbornly-High-Amid-Record-Debt-Supply/699341232e6a0b8ae17d54c8</guid><description>India's February 12 debt switch operation offered little lasting relief to the bond market. Despite repurchasing ₹75,500 crore in securities, benchmark 10-year yields remain elevated near 6.67%, pressured by record FY27 gross borrowing targets of ₹17.2 trillion. Analysts anticipate yields to stay range-bound, reflecting structural supply-demand imbalances and the end of the rate-cut cycle, with potential for a move closer to 7% as fresh supply materializes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:09:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699341232e6a0b8ae17d54c7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Britannia's 'Startup' Gambit: High Stakes Against Regional Rivals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannias-Startup-Gambit-High-Stakes-Against-Regional-Rivals/69933fbd2e6a0b8ae17d53b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannias-Startup-Gambit-High-Stakes-Against-Regional-Rivals/69933fbd2e6a0b8ae17d53b6</guid><description>Britannia Industries is adopting a "startup mentality" and increasing e-commerce investment to counter agile regional competitors. While commodity prices stabilize, improving margins and enabling a 17% year-on-year profit jump in Q3 FY26, the company's premium valuation and past growth rates raise questions about the sustainability and cost-effectiveness of this aggressive strategy against smaller, entrenched players. Analyst sentiment remains largely positive, but concerns linger over execution risk and whether scale can truly outmaneuver niche market insights.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:03:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69933fbd2e6a0b8ae17d53b5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's DRE Boom Faces Grid Strain, Cost Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-DRE-Boom-Faces-Grid-Strain-Cost-Hurdles/69933f202e6a0b8ae17d5338</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-DRE-Boom-Faces-Grid-Strain-Cost-Hurdles/69933f202e6a0b8ae17d5338</guid><description>While India's India Energy Stack (IES) and AI promise to accelerate distributed renewable energy (DRE), the rapid expansion strains existing grid infrastructure. Integrating millions of 'prosumers' and managing bidirectional power flow necessitates substantial, costly upgrades. The drive for lower power costs faces headwinds from these essential investments and the precarious financial state of distribution companies, raising questions about the pace and sustainability of the transition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:00:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69933f202e6a0b8ae17d5337.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Texmaco Rail Falls Despite ₹247 Cr Order Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Texmaco-Rail-Falls-Despite-247-Cr-Order-Boost/69933a952e6a0b8ae17d4bfd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Texmaco-Rail-Falls-Despite-247-Cr-Order-Boost/69933a952e6a0b8ae17d4bfd</guid><description>Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering secured two new orders totaling over ₹247 crore on February 16, 2026, for signaling equipment in Mumbai and OHE maintenance. Despite this influx of business, the company's shares declined, reflecting persistent investor worries about shrinking profit margins and a challenging market environment. The stock's proximity to its 52-week low underscores a broader bearish sentiment despite sector-wide infrastructure investment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:41:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69933a952e6a0b8ae17d4bfc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Trade Gap Widens on Gold; US Tariff Cuts Spark Hope</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Gap-Widens-on-Gold-US-Tariff-Cuts-Spark-Hope/699338472e6a0b8ae17d4a84</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Gap-Widens-on-Gold-US-Tariff-Cuts-Spark-Hope/699338472e6a0b8ae17d4a84</guid><description>India's merchandise trade deficit surged to a three-month high of $34.68 billion in January 2026, primarily fueled by a 19.19% year-on-year import increase, largely driven by gold and silver inflows. Exports showed minimal growth at 0.61%. However, recent US tariff reductions and an interim trade agreement inject optimism regarding future export competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:31:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699338472e6a0b8ae17d4a83_1771256009545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Arihant Foundations Surges 93% Revenue on Robust Project Pipeline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Arihant-Foundations-Surges-93percent-Revenue-on-Robust-Project-Pipeline/699338382e6a0b8ae17d4a67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Arihant-Foundations-Surges-93percent-Revenue-on-Robust-Project-Pipeline/699338382e6a0b8ae17d4a67</guid><description>Arihant Foundations &amp; Housing Limited reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue soaring 93.6% year-on-year to ₹90.1 Cr. The company also revealed a significant project pipeline valued at ₹6,376 Cr Gross Development Value (GDV), signaling robust future growth under its ambitious FY25-FY30 roadmap focused on redevelopment and commercial expansion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699338382e6a0b8ae17d4a66.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Franklin Templeton India's SIP Strength: Retail Resilience in Volatile January</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Franklin-Templeton-Indias-SIP-Strength-Retail-Resilience-in-Volatile-January/699337922e6a0b8ae17d49af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Franklin-Templeton-Indias-SIP-Strength-Retail-Resilience-in-Volatile-January/699337922e6a0b8ae17d49af</guid><description>Franklin Templeton India's Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) book demonstrated resilience in January 2026, attracting steady inflows of Rs 31,000 crore despite market fluctuations. This sustained retail investor participation, a trend unbroken for 59 consecutive months in equity schemes, underscores the enduring appeal of disciplined investing. The fund house also highlighted robust long-term performance across its Mid Cap, Large Cap, and Value funds, reinforcing the efficacy of SIPs as a wealth-building tool.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:28:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699337922e6a0b8ae17d49ae_1771255830866.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Premium Grocers Bet on Quality, Not Speed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Premium-Grocers-Bet-on-Quality-Not-Speed/699331432e6a0b8ae17d47de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Premium-Grocers-Bet-on-Quality-Not-Speed/699331432e6a0b8ae17d47de</guid><description>While quick-commerce leaders like Blinkit and Zepto focus on speed, premium Indian grocery startups FirstClub and Pluckk are carving out a niche by emphasizing quality, clean labels, and transparency. FirstClub reports 45% month-on-month growth and a leading ₹1,170 average order value, while Pluckk leverages direct farmer sourcing for its ₹800-1,000 AOV. These companies aim to democratize premium offerings, appealing to an expanding consumer base willing to pay for ingredient assurance, and positioning themselves for quicker profitability through higher basket sizes and gross margins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:01:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699331432e6a0b8ae17d47dd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sical Logistics Rights Issue: ₹930 Cr Raise Amidst High Debt &amp; MPS Deadline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Sical-Logistics-Rights-Issue-930-Cr-Raise-Amidst-High-Debt-and-MPS-Deadline/699330b92e6a0b8ae17d474f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Sical-Logistics-Rights-Issue-930-Cr-Raise-Amidst-High-Debt-and-MPS-Deadline/699330b92e6a0b8ae17d474f</guid><description>Sical Logistics is launching a ₹930.3 crore rights issue at ₹64 per share to address high borrowings and general corporate needs. A crucial aspect is the promoter group waiving their rights entitlement to meet Minimum Public Shareholding norms by February 2026, highlighting past compliance issues. Investors must weigh this capital raise against substantial existing debt, ongoing litigation, and a history of financial distress.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:59:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699330b92e6a0b8ae17d474e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bimetal Bearings Sees Profit Drop 28% Quarter-on-Quarter</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bimetal-Bearings-Sees-Profit-Drop-28percent-Quarter-on-Quarter/6993303f2e6a0b8ae17d46e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bimetal-Bearings-Sees-Profit-Drop-28percent-Quarter-on-Quarter/6993303f2e6a0b8ae17d46e5</guid><description>Bimetal Bearings Limited reported a 17.89% year-on-year increase in total income for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. However, profit after tax saw a significant sequential decline of 28.50% compared to the previous quarter, raising concerns about margin pressure. For the nine months, profit growth was minimal despite strong revenue gains.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:57:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993303f2e6a0b8ae17d46e4_1771253946631.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>