<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:29 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Skipper Stock Rockets? Brokerage Initiates 'Buy' with 17% Upside Target of ₹490!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Skipper-Stock-Rockets-Brokerage-Initiates-Buy-with-17percent-Upside-Target-of-490/695348f84342f77179e52c67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Skipper-Stock-Rockets-Brokerage-Initiates-Buy-with-17percent-Upside-Target-of-490/695348f84342f77179e52c67</guid><description>Systematix Institutional Equities has launched coverage on Skipper Limited, India's largest transmission line tower manufacturer, with a 'Buy' rating and a ₹490 target price, suggesting a 17% upside. The firm highlights Skipper's robust ₹8,800 crore order book, projected 20% revenue CAGR, significant capacity expansion plans to double output, and an ambitious goal of achieving 50% of revenue from exports, driven by India's substantial infrastructure spending.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695348f84342f77179e52c66_1767065916732.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Stocks Surge: Motilal Oswal Picks 4 'Buy' Bets with 35% Upside Potential!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stocks-Surge-Motilal-Oswal-Picks-4-Buy-Bets-with-35percent-Upside-Potential/695348a14342f77179e52b7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stocks-Surge-Motilal-Oswal-Picks-4-Buy-Bets-with-35percent-Upside-Potential/695348a14342f77179e52b7c</guid><description>Motilal Oswal has identified four defence stocks – Bharat Electronics, Hindustan Aeronautics, Bharat Dynamics, and Astra Microwave Products – as 'buy' recommendations, projecting up to 35% upside. This positive outlook follows the Defence Acquisition Council's recent approval of defence proposals worth ₹79,000 crore, significantly boosting the sector's capital outlay to ₹33 lakh crore. The brokerage firm believes these approvals will strengthen order inflows for key defence Public Sector Undertakings and select private players over the next few years.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:27:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695348a14342f77179e52b7b_1767065993591.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Prices Plummet: Investors Book Profits After Record Highs Shattered! What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Prices-Plummet-Investors-Book-Profits-After-Record-Highs-Shattered-Whats-Next/6953483e4342f77179e5282d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Prices-Plummet-Investors-Book-Profits-After-Record-Highs-Shattered-Whats-Next/6953483e4342f77179e5282d</guid><description>Gold and silver prices have fallen from record highs as investors book profits after a rapid rally, especially in silver which saw an 8.7% single-day drop. Indian markets showed mixed trends. Despite the pullback, both metals remain significantly up year-to-date, influenced by factors like US interest rate cut hopes and a strengthening dollar.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:24:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953483e4342f77179e5282c_1767065899371.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Hidden Export Powerhouse: Why Services, Not Just IT, Will Drive Future Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Hidden-Export-Powerhouse-Why-Services-Not-Just-IT-Will-Drive-Future-Growth/6953473a4342f77179e52346</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Hidden-Export-Powerhouse-Why-Services-Not-Just-IT-Will-Drive-Future-Growth/6953473a4342f77179e52346</guid><description>India's future growth lies in expanding service exports, leveraging its large, young population to counter global goods trade barriers. Services are growing globally twice as fast as goods, and India's share has risen to 4.2%, making it the eighth largest exporter. Key sectors include IT, medical tourism, financial services, and skilled trades, offering significant economic potential.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:22:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953473a4342f77179e52345_1767065552572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Meta's AI Leap: WhatsApp &amp; Instagram Set for Smarter Future After Manus Acquisition!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Metas-AI-Leap-WhatsApp-and-Instagram-Set-for-Smarter-Future-After-Manus-Acquisition/6953460e4342f77179e52061</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Metas-AI-Leap-WhatsApp-and-Instagram-Set-for-Smarter-Future-After-Manus-Acquisition/6953460e4342f77179e52061</guid><description>Meta has acquired Manus, a Singapore-based AI startup known for its advanced AI agents that can act autonomously. The deal, with undisclosed financial terms, aims to integrate Manus's technology into Meta's platforms like WhatsApp and Instagram, enhancing user experience and business applications. This acquisition underscores Meta's significant investment in AI development and its race against competitors in the burgeoning AI landscape. Manus reported a revenue run rate of $125 million and a valuation near $500 million prior to the acquisition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953460e4342f77179e52060_1767065174257.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Set for Shocking Gap-Down Open? Expiry Day Volatility &amp; Global Sell-off Trigger Alarm!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Nifty-Set-for-Shocking-Gap-Down-Open-Expiry-Day-Volatility-and-Global-Sell-off-Trigger-Alarm/695345ba4342f77179e51f5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Nifty-Set-for-Shocking-Gap-Down-Open-Expiry-Day-Volatility-and-Global-Sell-off-Trigger-Alarm/695345ba4342f77179e51f5b</guid><description>Indian markets are poised for a bearish opening on Tuesday, with Nifty expected to gap down around 100 points due to weak global trends and heavy foreign investor selling. Analysts anticipate high volatility on the monthly F&amp;O expiry day, despite positive November IIP data showing a 6.7% factory output growth. Key stocks to watch include Waaree Energies, InterGlobe Aviation (IndiGo), Grasim Industries, Hindalco Industries, and Rail Vikas Nigam Limited (RVNL), while Angel One is flagged for potential selling.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695345ba4342f77179e51f5a_1767065114512.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty F&amp;O Expiry Nears: 26,000 Key Hurdle, 25,860 Crucial Support – What Analysts Say!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-FandO-Expiry-Nears-26000-Key-Hurdle-25860-Crucial-Support-What-Analysts-Say/695340fa4342f77179e515f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-FandO-Expiry-Nears-26000-Key-Hurdle-25860-Crucial-Support-What-Analysts-Say/695340fa4342f77179e515f0</guid><description>Nifty faces selling pressure near 26,000-26,100 resistance after shedding points, slipping below its 20-day moving average. Analysts see support around 25,860. Derivatives data shows cautiousness with heavy call writing at 26,000 strike and put writing at 25,900, suggesting a guarded market ahead of expiry. FIIs maintain a bearish stance in futures, while DIIs and retail investors are more bullish.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:54:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695340fa4342f77179e515ef_1767063879806.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Crypto Surge 2025: Record Adoption Meets Tightening Grip! What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Crypto-Surge-2025-Record-Adoption-Meets-Tightening-Grip-Whats-Next/695341264342f77179e516b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Crypto-Surge-2025-Record-Adoption-Meets-Tightening-Grip-Whats-Next/695341264342f77179e516b1</guid><description>India leads global crypto adoption in 2025 despite strict regulations. The Financial Intelligence Unit is enforcing rules against offshore platforms, pushing for structured participation. Wider adoption, especially in smaller cities, is seen alongside innovation in DeFi and Web3. Challenges remain with high taxes, prompting calls for clearer policies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:54:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695341264342f77179e516b0_1767064075300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Dips, Silver Skyrockets: Why This Price Split Matters for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Dips-Silver-Skyrockets-Why-This-Price-Split-Matters-for-Your-Investments/695340ab4342f77179e51537</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Dips-Silver-Skyrockets-Why-This-Price-Split-Matters-for-Your-Investments/695340ab4342f77179e51537</guid><description>Gold prices fell as traders booked profits, with the US Federal Reserve's upcoming meeting minutes being a key factor. Thin volumes may cause further volatility. Meanwhile, silver prices continued a strong rally, hitting record highs driven by prolonged physical supply deficits, declining inventories, and sustained demand. Silver has surged over 160% this year, with analysts pointing to structural market stress.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:52:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695340ab4342f77179e51536_1767063883958.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Breaks $120K! US Regulation Sparks Crypto Frenzy &amp; Global Inflows – Is 2025 the Big Turning Point?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Breaks-120K-US-Regulation-Sparks-Crypto-Frenzy-and-Global-Inflows-Is-2025-the-Big-Turning-Point/69533f7b4342f77179e512a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Breaks-120K-US-Regulation-Sparks-Crypto-Frenzy-and-Global-Inflows-Is-2025-the-Big-Turning-Point/69533f7b4342f77179e512a5</guid><description>In 2025, the cryptocurrency sector reached an inflection point driven by US regulatory actions and President Trump's endorsement, pushing Bitcoin to record highs above $120,000. Landmark bills like the Genius Act and Clarity Act provided a clearer stance, boosting institutional confidence and leading to approvals for Solana, XRP, and Dogecoin ETFs. US spot Bitcoin ETFs saw billions in inflows. India maintained its lead in crypto adoption, with local exchanges seeing increased institutional investment and SIPs, despite a restrictive tax environment. Global regulatory clarity is now a key growth driver, with experts emphasizing the need for timely policy action in India.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:47:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69533f7b4342f77179e512a4_1767063515461.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver CRASHES 11% After Record Rally Past $84! Is the Bull Run Over? 🚨</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-CRASHES-11percent-After-Record-Rally-Past-84-Is-the-Bull-Run-Over/69533e9d4342f77179e51075</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-CRASHES-11percent-After-Record-Rally-Past-84-Is-the-Bull-Run-Over/69533e9d4342f77179e51075</guid><description>Silver prices plummeted 11% on Monday, marking their biggest intraday drop since September 2020, following a record rally that pushed prices past $84 an ounce. Gold also saw a significant fall. Profit-taking, thin holiday trading, and overheated market indicators are cited as reasons for the sharp correction. Heavy buying in China had previously fueled the surge, leading to record premiums in Shanghai. Exchanges like CME Group are raising margins to curb speculation amid signs of strain in the physical silver market. Investors are now questioning the future direction of silver prices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:43:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69533e9d4342f77179e51074_1767063312134.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2025: Indian Tech Giants Face Profitability Test Amidst Record IPOs &amp; Mixed Fortunes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/2025-Indian-Tech-Giants-Face-Profitability-Test-Amidst-Record-IPOs-and-Mixed-Fortunes/69533dbc4342f77179e50e65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/2025-Indian-Tech-Giants-Face-Profitability-Test-Amidst-Record-IPOs-and-Mixed-Fortunes/69533dbc4342f77179e50e65</guid><description>India's consumer tech giants navigated a challenging 2025, shifting from hypergrowth to profitability pressures. While startups saw record IPOs, many debuted with mixed post-listing performance. Companies like Urban Company, Swiggy, Lenskart, Zomato, PhonePe, and Zepto experienced significant events including IPOs, major funding rounds, strategic expansions, and profitability concerns, setting the stage for continued scrutiny in 2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:39:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69533dbc4342f77179e50e64_1767063313983.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rural Jobs Revolution: India's MGNREGA Rebranded With Massive Changes Sparking Investor Alarms!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rural-Jobs-Revolution-Indias-MGNREGA-Rebranded-With-Massive-Changes-Sparking-Investor-Alarms/695338da4342f77179e4eadc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rural-Jobs-Revolution-Indias-MGNREGA-Rebranded-With-Massive-Changes-Sparking-Investor-Alarms/695338da4342f77179e4eadc</guid><description>India's flagship rural employment program, MGNREGA, has been restructured and renamed Viksit Bharat-Guarantee for Rozgar and Ajeevika Mission (Gramin). Key changes include a new Centre-state funding model (60:40), a shift to a top-down approach, and reoriented objectives towards growth and infrastructure aligned with Viksit Bharat@2047. This transforms the program from an open-ended guarantee to a planned, rules-based allocation, raising concerns about increased financial obligations for states and potential exclusion of vulnerable households.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:17:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695338da4342f77179e4eadb_1767061885510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Next Billion Consumers: Brands Race to Win Hearts (and Wallets) in Small Towns!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Next-Billion-Consumers-Brands-Race-to-Win-Hearts-and-Wallets-in-Small-Towns/695336044342f77179e4e667</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Next-Billion-Consumers-Brands-Race-to-Win-Hearts-and-Wallets-in-Small-Towns/695336044342f77179e4e667</guid><description>Companies are shifting focus from India's affluent metros to its vast "next billion" consumers in smaller towns. This involves retooling products, pricing, logistics, and marketing to meet the unique demands of price-conscious yet aspirational shoppers. The boom in discretionary spending in these emerging cities is creating a new growth battleground for retail, delivery services, and digital platforms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 02:06:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695336044342f77179e4e666_1767061140507.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI War Heats Up: Nvidia Strikes $20 Billion Deal to Lock Down Groq's Game-Changing Chip Tech!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-War-Heats-Up-Nvidia-Strikes-20-Billion-Deal-to-Lock-Down-Groqs-Game-Changing-Chip-Tech/695333af4342f77179e4e34b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-War-Heats-Up-Nvidia-Strikes-20-Billion-Deal-to-Lock-Down-Groqs-Game-Changing-Chip-Tech/695333af4342f77179e4e34b</guid><description>Nvidia has signed a $20 billion licensing agreement with AI startup Groq, securing access to its specialized inference-chip technology. This strategic move aims to bolster Nvidia's position in the critical AI inference market and prevent rivals from acquiring Groq's advanced capabilities. The deal signifies a major comeback for Groq, which once faced severe financial difficulties, and promises substantial returns for its founder Jonathan Ross and key investors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:59:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695333af4342f77179e4e34a_1767060466600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Tumble: Will Indian Stocks Follow? Watch These 6 Key Cues Today!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Tumble-Will-Indian-Stocks-Follow-Watch-These-6-Key-Cues-Today/695332d04342f77179e4e1de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Tumble-Will-Indian-Stocks-Follow-Watch-These-6-Key-Cues-Today/695332d04342f77179e4e1de</guid><description>Global markets are trading lower, with Japan's Nikkei down 0.49% and US markets like the Dow Jones falling 0.51%. This sentiment may impact the Indian stock market's opening. GIFT Nifty futures are trading slightly down. Investors should watch crude oil prices, FII/DII net activity (FIIs sold ₹2,759.89 crore, DIIs bought ₹2,643.85 crore on Dec 29), and USD/INR movement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:54:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695332d04342f77179e4e1dd_1767060280289.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Angel One Stock Plummets: Is ₹2,040 the Next Stop? Expert Warns of Major Fall!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Angel-One-Stock-Plummets-Is-2040-the-Next-Stop-Expert-Warns-of-Major-Fall/6953325b4342f77179e4e110</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Angel-One-Stock-Plummets-Is-2040-the-Next-Stop-Expert-Warns-of-Major-Fall/6953325b4342f77179e4e110</guid><description>Angel One's stock has fallen over 30% in a month, breaking below the ₹2,450 support level. Technical analysis reveals a confirmed Head and Shoulder pattern and a breach of the 50-day moving average, signaling a likely further decline. The stock may head towards ₹2,040 in the near term, prompting caution for investors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:53:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953325b4342f77179e4e10f_1767060159286.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Sounding Alarm: India's Banking-NBFC Links Now Top Focus Amid Global Uncertainty!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Sounding-Alarm-Indias-Banking-NBFC-Links-Now-Top-Focus-Amid-Global-Uncertainty/6953320c4342f77179e4e043</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Sounding-Alarm-Indias-Banking-NBFC-Links-Now-Top-Focus-Amid-Global-Uncertainty/6953320c4342f77179e4e043</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is significantly increasing its focus on the intricate relationships between banks and non-banking financial companies (NBFCs). Concerned that these growing interconnections could amplify financial shocks in an uncertain global environment, the RBI is prioritizing financial stability through robust supervision and macroprudential frameworks. While NBFCs have shown strong credit expansion, stress is noted in the microfinance sector, underscoring the need for enhanced oversight of leverage and liquidity risks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:49:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953320c4342f77179e4e042_1767060058664.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>World Bank Showdown: Oswal's Axis International Claims $29 Billion from Guinea Over Mining Rights Revocation!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/World-Bank-Showdown-Oswals-Axis-International-Claims-29-Billion-from-Guinea-Over-Mining-Rights-Revocation/6953318a4342f77179e4df6f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/World-Bank-Showdown-Oswals-Axis-International-Claims-29-Billion-from-Guinea-Over-Mining-Rights-Revocation/6953318a4342f77179e4df6f</guid><description>Axis International, controlled by Indian-origin billionaire Pankaj Oswal, has initiated international arbitration seeking at least $28.9 billion in compensation from the Republic of Guinea. The UAE-based firm alleges unlawful termination of its mining rights for a major bauxite operation, claiming authorities seized equipment and froze bank accounts despite the mine being operational. The case was filed at the International Centre for the Settlement of Investment Disputes (ICSID), an arm of the World Bank.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:49:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953318a4342f77179e4df6e_1767059912955.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump Hints at Firing Fed Chief Powell &amp; Picks New Fed Chair Soon! Will Markets Roar?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trump-Hints-at-Firing-Fed-Chief-Powell-and-Picks-New-Fed-Chair-Soon-Will-Markets-Roar/695330934342f77179e4de07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trump-Hints-at-Firing-Fed-Chief-Powell-and-Picks-New-Fed-Chair-Soon-Will-Markets-Roar/695330934342f77179e4de07</guid><description>President Donald Trump indicated he has a preferred candidate for the next U.S. Federal Reserve chair and plans to announce them by January. He also expressed a desire to fire current Fed Chair Jerome Powell, even musing about a potential lawsuit for "gross incompetence," though he previously backed down from seeking Powell's ouster due to market backlash. Powell's term as chair ends in May 2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:45:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695330934342f77179e4de06_1767059676295.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stranded Homebuyers Rejoice: NCLT Orders Fresh Bidding for Batanagar Land, Offering Hope for 2300 Families!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Stranded-Homebuyers-Rejoice-NCLT-Orders-Fresh-Bidding-for-Batanagar-Land-Offering-Hope-for-2300-Families/69532da24342f77179e4da92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Stranded-Homebuyers-Rejoice-NCLT-Orders-Fresh-Bidding-for-Batanagar-Land-Offering-Hope-for-2300-Families/69532da24342f77179e4da92</guid><description>The National Company Law Tribunal's Calcutta bench has ordered a re-bidding of 'Parcel 3', a 12.33-acre land parcel in the Batanagar township belonging to the bankrupt Riverbank Developers Pvt Ltd. This decision aims to resolve the long-standing issue for over 2,300 homebuyers whose apartments remain unfinished. The tribunal recognized homebuyers as a distinct class of creditors, stating they cannot be compelled to complete the project themselves, a ruling that could impact other stalled real estate projects in India.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:30:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69532da24342f77179e4da91_1767058965580.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gujarat Kidney IPO Listing: Flat Debut Expected? Investors Watch Muted GMP!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Gujarat-Kidney-IPO-Listing-Flat-Debut-Expected-Investors-Watch-Muted-GMP/69532cf04342f77179e4d9ab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Gujarat-Kidney-IPO-Listing-Flat-Debut-Expected-Investors-Watch-Muted-GMP/69532cf04342f77179e4d9ab</guid><description>Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality Hospital's Initial Public Offering (IPO) is poised for a flat listing on December 30th. The IPO, priced at ₹114, has a low Grey Market Premium (GMP) of approximately 1.32% (₹1.5 per share), indicating limited listing gains. The ₹251 crore issue saw strong retail investor demand, subscribing 19.04 times, while institutional participation was more measured. Proceeds will fund acquisitions, expansion, and debt repayment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:30:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69532cf04342f77179e4d9aa_1767058735570.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Retail Investors Ignoring Fundamentals? Saurabh Mukherjea Issues Stark Warning on Small-Cap Frenzy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Retail-Investors-Ignoring-Fundamentals-Saurabh-Mukherjea-Issues-Stark-Warning-on-Small-Cap-Frenzy/69532a784342f77179e4d6a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Retail-Investors-Ignoring-Fundamentals-Saurabh-Mukherjea-Issues-Stark-Warning-on-Small-Cap-Frenzy/69532a784342f77179e4d6a6</guid><description>Saurabh Mukherjea, founder of Marcellus Investment Managers, warns that retail investors are losing sight of fundamentals in small and mid-cap stocks, likening the situation to the 2004-2014 Indian real estate boom. He advises increasing allocation to large-cap stocks, ceasing F&amp;O trading, and considering global investments, noting that while small/mid-cap valuations are stretched, quality large-caps offer room for growth and re-rating.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:20:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69532a784342f77179e4d6a5_1767058120012.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Stock Market Set for Massive Overhaul: New Code Promises Safer, Cheaper Trading!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Stock-Market-Set-for-Massive-Overhaul-New-Code-Promises-Safer-Cheaper-Trading/69532aab4342f77179e4d6f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Stock-Market-Set-for-Massive-Overhaul-New-Code-Promises-Safer-Cheaper-Trading/69532aab4342f77179e4d6f2</guid><description>India's Finance Minister introduced a Securities Markets Code Bill to reform market clearing and settlement. The proposed agency-based clearing system aims to enhance legal certainty, reduce Karvy-like risks, and improve capital efficiency. This reform seeks to lower trading costs and boost safety for investors by adopting global best practices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:17:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69532aab4342f77179e4d6f1_1767058257652.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Energy Revolution: Natural Gas Surge &amp; Top Stock Pick Set to Ignite Market Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Revolution-Natural-Gas-Surge-and-Top-Stock-Pick-Set-to-Ignite-Market-Growth/695326464342f77179e4d347</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Revolution-Natural-Gas-Surge-and-Top-Stock-Pick-Set-to-Ignite-Market-Growth/695326464342f77179e4d347</guid><description>India's oil and gas sector is undergoing a major transition, with natural gas becoming a key energy source. Policy reforms, infrastructure expansion like city gas distribution, and rising CNG adoption are driving strong medium- to long-term growth. Motilal Oswal Financial Services highlights the sector's positive outlook, identifying Mahanagar Gas as a top investment with a target price of ₹1,700, predicting an 11% volume CAGR.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:02:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695326464342f77179e4d346_1767057061317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Fines on Banks Shrink Dramatically in 2025: More Cases, Smaller Penalties Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Fines-on-Banks-Shrink-Dramatically-in-2025-More-Cases-Smaller-Penalties-Revealed/695325e24342f77179e4d279</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Fines-on-Banks-Shrink-Dramatically-in-2025-More-Cases-Smaller-Penalties-Revealed/695325e24342f77179e4d279</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) imposed lower fines on banks in 2025, with the median penalty nearly halved compared to previous years. While the number of penalty instances increased to 38 from 26 in 2023 and 30 in 2024, the total fines collected were ₹25.5 crore, down from ₹29.5 crore in 2024 and ₹53.3 crore in 2023. Experts suggest a shift towards a more consultative approach by the RBI, alongside improved compliance by banks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:56:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695325e24342f77179e4d278_1767056930497.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apollo Tyres: Big Sponsorship Cost to Cap Profit Gains? Stock Outlook Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Apollo-Tyres-Big-Sponsorship-Cost-to-Cap-Profit-Gains-Stock-Outlook-Revealed/695325754342f77179e4d1a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Apollo-Tyres-Big-Sponsorship-Cost-to-Cap-Profit-Gains-Stock-Outlook-Revealed/695325754342f77179e4d1a0</guid><description>Apollo Tyres faces margin pressure despite healthy demand in India, as weak demand persists in Europe. A significant ₹580 crore sponsorship deal for the Indian cricket team, spread over two and a half years, is expected to constrain near-term margin expansion from Q3 onwards. While Q2 FY26 Ebitda margins rose to 14.9% partly due to softening raw material costs, these costs are now expected to remain stable due to INR depreciation and supply disruptions. The stock trades at 19x FY27 earnings, with challenges in balancing market share and profitability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:56:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695325754342f77179e4d19f_1767056857650.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MarketSmith India's Top Stock Picks: Unlocking Investment Opportunities in Karur Vysya Bank &amp; VST Tillers Tractors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/MarketSmith-Indias-Top-Stock-Picks-Unlocking-Investment-Opportunities-in-Karur-Vysya-Bank-and-VST-Tillers-Tractors/695325824342f77179e4d1f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/MarketSmith-Indias-Top-Stock-Picks-Unlocking-Investment-Opportunities-in-Karur-Vysya-Bank-and-VST-Tillers-Tractors/695325824342f77179e4d1f2</guid><description>MarketSmith India has identified two promising stock recommendations: Karur Vysya Bank, citing its strong South Indian franchise, improving asset quality, and digital initiatives, and V.S.T Tillers Tractors, noting its leadership in power tillers, debt-free status, and consistent demand. The Indian equity markets closed cautiously subdued on Monday, with Nifty 50 and Sensex experiencing declines amid broad-based selling.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:56:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695325824342f77179e4d1f1_1767056939787.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's E-commerce Takeover: Amazon, Flipkart, Meesho Race to Dominate Chatbot Shopping!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-E-commerce-Takeover-Amazon-Flipkart-Meesho-Race-to-Dominate-Chatbot-Shopping/695324fb4342f77179e4d0b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-E-commerce-Takeover-Amazon-Flipkart-Meesho-Race-to-Dominate-Chatbot-Shopping/695324fb4342f77179e4d0b3</guid><description>The e-commerce landscape is rapidly shifting from keyword searches to AI-powered chatbots like ChatGPT and Google Gemini guiding consumer purchases. Major online retailers including Amazon, Flipkart, and Meesho are racing to optimize their product listings for these 'shopping agents' as they become critical for visibility. Experts predict AI shopping agents could influence up to 25% of e-commerce sales by 2030, forcing companies to adapt or risk disappearing from search results.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:56:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695324fb4342f77179e4d0b2_1767056712347.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>5 Midcap Stocks That Skyrocketed in 2025: Are You Holding Them?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/5-Midcap-Stocks-That-Skyrocketed-in-2025-Are-You-Holding-Them/695324444342f77179e4d007</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/5-Midcap-Stocks-That-Skyrocketed-in-2025-Are-You-Holding-Them/695324444342f77179e4d007</guid><description>Despite valuation concerns, five midcap stocks, primarily from finance and e-commerce, emerged as top wealth creators in 2025, delivering returns up to 119%. L&amp;T Finance led the pack with a 119% surge, followed by Aditya Birla Capital (89.6%), Muthoot Finance (81%), AU Small Finance Bank (77.55%), and FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) (62.47%). These stocks defied market skepticism to offer significant gains for investors over the past twelve months.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:52:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695324444342f77179e4d006_1767056524055.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Raja Venkatraman's Top Picks: Can These 3 Stocks Beat the Bearish Market?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Raja-Venkatramans-Top-Picks-Can-These-3-Stocks-Beat-the-Bearish-Market/69531ee74342f77179e4c97a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Raja-Venkatramans-Top-Picks-Can-These-3-Stocks-Beat-the-Bearish-Market/69531ee74342f77179e4c97a</guid><description>Amidst ongoing bearish pressure in Indian markets and cautious sentiment ahead of monthly expiry, analyst Raja Venkatraman has identified three trading opportunities. He recommends buying Housing and Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO) above ₹230, Lloyds Metals and Energy Limited above ₹1395, and selling Cyient below ₹1080. The market saw broad-based selling on Monday, with the Nifty closing lower.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:29:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69531ee74342f77179e4c979_1767055145813.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai's Reign Ends? Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Set to Snatch India's Coveted No. 2 Auto Spot!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundais-Reign-Ends-Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Set-to-Snatch-Indias-Coveted-No-2-Auto-Spot/69531daa4342f77179e4c857</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundais-Reign-Ends-Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Set-to-Snatch-Indias-Coveted-No-2-Auto-Spot/69531daa4342f77179e4c857</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra is projected to overtake Hyundai Motor India for the second position in the Indian passenger vehicle market by the end of 2025. Hyundai is expected to fall to fourth place, behind M&amp;M and Tata Motors. This marks Hyundai's first loss of its long-held second rank since 2019, driven by M&amp;M's successful new model launches and facelifts, while Hyundai faces pressure from an intensifying market and a slower product cycle.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69531daa4342f77179e4c856_1767054833000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Shifts Gears: Electric Buses &amp; Trucks Take Center Stage for 2026, Leaving 2-Wheelers Behind!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Shifts-Gears-Electric-Buses-and-Trucks-Take-Center-Stage-for-2026-Leaving-2-Wheelers-Behind/695318e64342f77179e4c4ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Shifts-Gears-Electric-Buses-and-Trucks-Take-Center-Stage-for-2026-Leaving-2-Wheelers-Behind/695318e64342f77179e4c4ec</guid><description>India is prioritizing electric buses and trucks, along with charging infrastructure, for 2026 under the ₹10,900 crore PM E-Drive scheme. This strategic shift moves away from incentives for electric two- and three-wheelers, which are set to expire in March 2026. The focus is on mass transport to combat rising air pollution, despite challenges like high costs and supply chain dependencies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:02:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695318e64342f77179e4c4eb_1767053627097.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market 2026: Experts Reveal SHOCKING Outlook as Global Rivals SOAR – What Lies Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Market-2026-Experts-Reveal-SHOCKING-Outlook-as-Global-Rivals-SOAR-What-Lies-Ahead/6953186d4342f77179e4c3e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Market-2026-Experts-Reveal-SHOCKING-Outlook-as-Global-Rivals-SOAR-What-Lies-Ahead/6953186d4342f77179e4c3e0</guid><description>Indian stock markets, Nifty 50 and Sensex, are trailing global peers in 2025. Experts predict a range-bound market in the first half of 2026 due to global headwinds, with a potential rally in the second half driven by returning foreign investment and expected double-digit earnings growth. Investment focus is shifting towards domestic manufacturing and resilient financials, while risks include global volatility and potential corrections in small and mid-cap stocks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:02:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953186d4342f77179e4c3df_1767053577076.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indians Book Holiday Escapes Last Minute! Is Your Travel Stock Ready for This Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indians-Book-Holiday-Escapes-Last-Minute-Is-Your-Travel-Stock-Ready-for-This-Surge/695318584342f77179e4c3b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indians-Book-Holiday-Escapes-Last-Minute-Is-Your-Travel-Stock-Ready-for-This-Surge/695318584342f77179e4c3b5</guid><description>Indian travellers are embracing last-minute holiday bookings, with nearly half of all trips planned within 15 days of departure, a significant jump from last year. Popular international destinations include Thailand, Dubai, and Vietnam, while domestic favourites like Udaipur and Dehradun are also seeing increased interest. This trend highlights a shift towards impulse-driven, short-haul international travel and experience-focused domestic getaways.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:01:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695318584342f77179e4c3b4_1767053601540.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>