<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:49:54 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Xiaomi's India Tax Fight: A Test for Global Manufacturing Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Xiaomis-India-Tax-Fight-A-Test-for-Global-Manufacturing-Ambitions/699ec2ec04a25a58c8542594</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Xiaomis-India-Tax-Fight-A-Test-for-Global-Manufacturing-Ambitions/699ec2ec04a25a58c8542594</guid><description>Xiaomi has escalated its dispute over a $72 million Indian tax demand related to royalty payments to the Supreme Court. The company argues the tribunal ruling undervalues imports and risks undermining India's manufacturing sector. This case, involving contract manufacturers like Flex and Foxconn, is a critical test for India's regulatory framework and foreign investment climate, with significant financial stakes for Xiaomi and broader implications for companies relying on technology licensing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:37:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ec2ec04a25a58c8542593_1772012518455.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UP-Japan MoUs: ₹11,000 Cr Pledges Spark Growth Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UP-Japan-MoUs-11000-Cr-Pledges-Spark-Growth-Hopes/699ec1cf04a25a58c85423df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UP-Japan-MoUs-11000-Cr-Pledges-Spark-Growth-Hopes/699ec1cf04a25a58c85423df</guid><description>Uttar Pradesh secured memorandums of understanding totaling approximately ₹11,000 crore during Chief Minister Yogi Adityanath's Japan visit. Agreements span agricultural equipment, industrial machinery, automotive components, electronics, and hospitality. These pacts aim to enhance manufacturing capacity and industrial collaboration between the state and Japanese enterprises, fostering technological advancement and economic momentum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Castrol India FY25 Report Out; AGM Set March 30 Amidst bp Ownership Review</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Castrol-India-FY25-Report-Out-AGM-Set-March-30-Amidst-bp-Ownership-Review/699ec1cf04a25a58c85423c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Castrol-India-FY25-Report-Out-AGM-Set-March-30-Amidst-bp-Ownership-Review/699ec1cf04a25a58c85423c8</guid><description>Castrol India will hold its 48th Annual General Meeting (AGM) on March 30, 2026, releasing its FY2025 Annual Report featuring ₹5,722 Crore revenue and ₹9.60 EPS. Parent bp plc's strategic review of its global lubricants business, including a stake sale to Stonepeak, is ongoing, expected to conclude by end of 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Growth Outlook: Tariff Calm Masks Deflationary Shadows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Outlook-Tariff-Calm-Masks-Deflationary-Shadows/699ebdc204a25a58c8541f42</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Outlook-Tariff-Calm-Masks-Deflationary-Shadows/699ebdc204a25a58c8541f42</guid><description>While trade tariff fears have subsided, India's FY27 growth outlook faces lingering global disinflationary pressures, particularly from China's persistent producer price drops. Despite Morgan Stanley's stable forecast, analyst consensus shows varied GDP projections (6.2%-7.4% real GDP). Domestic demand softness and structural market volatility present significant headwinds, suggesting the economic 'all clear' may be premature.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:15:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ebdc204a25a58c8541f41_1772011912458.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Datamatics Stock Slides on Subsidiary Liquidation Amid Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Datamatics-Stock-Slides-on-Subsidiary-Liquidation-Amid-Profit-Slump/699ebd9904a25a58c8541f04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Datamatics-Stock-Slides-on-Subsidiary-Liquidation-Amid-Profit-Slump/699ebd9904a25a58c8541f04</guid><description>Datamatics Global Services Ltd. shares plummeted over 5%, marking their steepest fall since February 20, after announcing the liquidation of its Netherlands-based subsidiary, effective February 18, 2026. This event compounds a difficult third quarter, which saw net profit plunge 51.04% year-on-year despite a 19.89% revenue increase. Analysts have lowered earnings estimates, though a 'Buy' rating and revised target price remain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:15:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ebd9904a25a58c8541f03_1772011088363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCS Embraces AI, Willing to Cannibalize Revenue for Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Embraces-AI-Willing-to-Cannibalize-Revenue-for-Growth/699ebd4604a25a58c8541e10</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Embraces-AI-Willing-to-Cannibalize-Revenue-for-Growth/699ebd4604a25a58c8541e10</guid><description>TCS is proactively integrating artificial intelligence across its operations, encouraging its 6 lakh+ employees to achieve AI fluency. CEO K. Krithivasan stated the company is "not afraid" of AI, even if it means cannibalizing existing revenues, viewing it as a necessary step for long-term strategic advantage and customer value. A key observation is a generational divide in AI adoption, with senior employees reportedly slower to develop AI solutions compared to younger, more proficient staff. TCS is also exploring AI governance models and aims to leverage AI for increased productivity and enhanced customer benefits, positioning AI as a board-level imperative. The company has already reported $1.5 billion in annualized AI revenue, with a 16.3% quarter-on-quarter growth in AI services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:13:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ebd4604a25a58c8541e0f_1772011608155.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Midcaps: Growth Prospects Tainted by Volatility?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/India-Midcaps-Growth-Prospects-Tainted-by-Volatility/699ebd3604a25a58c8541df6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/India-Midcaps-Growth-Prospects-Tainted-by-Volatility/699ebd3604a25a58c8541df6</guid><description>Indian midcap equities are projected for substantial growth, with earnings expected to rise 21% annually for the next two years, fueled by economic expansion and policy support. Key sectors like technology, consumption, energy, and renewables present opportunities. However, midcaps are inherently sensitive to market volatility and macroeconomic shifts. Investors must adopt a long-term perspective, recognizing that while mutual funds offer a less turbulent route, risks of corrections persist, especially given current valuations that are near historical averages. The broader Indian economy's robust growth trajectory provides a supportive backdrop, though sector-specific challenges, particularly in renewables regarding infrastructure, warrant attention.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:13:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ebd3604a25a58c8541df5_1772011020595.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>REITs Reshape Indian Real Estate: Liquidity Meets Legacy Assets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/REITs-Reshape-Indian-Real-Estate-Liquidity-Meets-Legacy-Assets/699ebcf504a25a58c8541d76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/REITs-Reshape-Indian-Real-Estate-Liquidity-Meets-Legacy-Assets/699ebcf504a25a58c8541d76</guid><description>Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs) are fundamentally altering India's property investment landscape, injecting institutional liquidity into a traditionally illiquid asset class. Offering higher dividend yields and professional management compared to direct property ownership, REITs are attracting discerning investors. Despite market volatility, the sector's resilience and the robust growth in commercial real estate fundamentals suggest a maturing investment avenue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:12:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ebcf504a25a58c8541d75_1772011733770.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCS Bull Case Faces Sector Storm: AI Hype vs. Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Bull-Case-Faces-Sector-Storm-AI-Hype-vs-Reality/699ebc4204a25a58c8541bac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Bull-Case-Faces-Sector-Storm-AI-Hype-vs-Reality/699ebc4204a25a58c8541bac</guid><description>Brokerage firm CLSA reiterates an 'Outperform' rating on Tata Consultancy Services (TCS), targeting Rs 2,686, citing Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) implementation and enterprise AI adoption as key growth drivers. This optimistic outlook persists despite a significant 20% decline in the Nifty IT index this month, highlighting a divergence between analyst sentiment and broader market pressures. The expanded ServiceNow partnership and projected market growth for system management software are foundational to CLSA's view, yet critical downside risks remain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Oswal Greentech Appoints New Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer Jhanwar</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Oswal-Greentech-Appoints-New-Company-Secretary-and-Compliance-Officer-Jhanwar/699ebc3a04a25a58c8541b93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Oswal-Greentech-Appoints-New-Company-Secretary-and-Compliance-Officer-Jhanwar/699ebc3a04a25a58c8541b93</guid><description>Oswal Greentech Limited has appointed Mrs. Purva Jhanwar as its new Company Secretary (KMP) and Compliance Officer, effective March 1, 2026. This move follows the resignation of Mrs. Sonal Gupta. Mrs. Jhanwar, a qualified Chartered Accountant and Company Secretary, brings expertise in corporate laws and SEBI regulations, strengthening the company's governance framework.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:09:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ebc3a04a25a58c8541b92_1772012090545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE IX Global Access: Indian Retail Eyes Global Stocks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NSE-IX-Global-Access-Indian-Retail-Eyes-Global-Stocks/699ebc3904a25a58c8541b75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NSE-IX-Global-Access-Indian-Retail-Eyes-Global-Stocks/699ebc3904a25a58c8541b75</guid><description>The NSE International Exchange (NSE IX) has launched its Global Access platform, offering Indian retail investors unprecedented access to over 30 international markets, beginning with the US. Key features include fractional share trading, allowing investment in portions of high-priced stocks like Apple (AAPL), and full compliance with the RBI's Liberalised Remittance Scheme (LRS). This initiative, based in GIFT City, aims to democratize global investing for Indians, though it necessitates careful navigation of currency risks and tax implications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:09:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Agri Exports Shielded: RoDTEP Cuts Spark Sectoral Divide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Agri-Exports-Shielded-RoDTEP-Cuts-Spark-Sectoral-Divide/699ebbee04a25a58c8541ac6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Agri-Exports-Shielded-RoDTEP-Cuts-Spark-Sectoral-Divide/699ebbee04a25a58c8541ac6</guid><description>India's Remission of Duties and Taxes on Exported Products (RoDTEP) scheme will see a 45% budget cut for FY27, slashing benefits by half for most sectors. However, agriculture and live animal products are exempt due to their high utilization of the scheme, having accounted for nearly a third of total disbursements in FY23. This strategic move prioritizes key performing sectors amidst fiscal constraints, creating a stark divide in export incentive support.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fed's AI Worry: Labor Disruption May Hamper Rate Cuts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Feds-AI-Worry-Labor-Disruption-May-Hamper-Rate-Cuts/699eba2304a25a58c85418da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Feds-AI-Worry-Labor-Disruption-May-Hamper-Rate-Cuts/699eba2304a25a58c85418da</guid><description>Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook has cautioned that artificial intelligence is initiating a significant reorganization of the U.S. labor market, potentially leading to a rise in unemployment that traditional monetary policy tools may struggle to address without increasing inflation. This technological shift also injects uncertainty into forecasts for the neutral interest rate. With the unemployment rate at 4.3% and inflation at 2.4% as of January 2026, the Federal Reserve faces a complex challenge in calibrating policy amidst these profound structural changes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>US Oil Output Surges Amid Venezuela Partnership Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/US-Oil-Output-Surges-Amid-Venezuela-Partnership-Shift/699eb9f204a25a58c8541863</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/US-Oil-Output-Surges-Amid-Venezuela-Partnership-Shift/699eb9f204a25a58c8541863</guid><description>President Donald Trump highlighted record U.S. natural gas production and a significant increase in oil output, driven by a "drill, baby, drill" policy. He also announced a new strategic partnership with Venezuela, importing over 80 million barrels of oil. Despite claims of falling gas prices below $2.30 per gallon, national averages indicate higher figures, suggesting a divergence between presidential rhetoric and market reality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:59:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eb9f204a25a58c8541862_1772010407379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Mega-Deals Spur Markets, Valuations and Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Mega-Deals-Spur-Markets-Valuations-and-Risks-Loom/699eb98d04a25a58c85417a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Mega-Deals-Spur-Markets-Valuations-and-Risks-Loom/699eb98d04a25a58c85417a0</guid><description>Asian equity markets reached new highs, fueled by sustained artificial intelligence enthusiasm and Wall Street's positive close. A monumental multi-year AI chip deal between Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) and Meta Platforms, valued at over $100 billion and including equity warrants for Meta, was a key highlight. Despite broad gains and significant corporate partnerships, elevated technology valuations, concentration risks in the AI sector, and ongoing geopolitical tensions temper the bullish sentiment, raising questions about the long-term sustainability of the rally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:57:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eb98d04a25a58c854179f_1772009998497.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Simplex Castings EGM March 2 For ₹49.9 Cr Preferential Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Simplex-Castings-EGM-March-2-For-499-Cr-Preferential-Issue/699eb96204a25a58c8541761</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Simplex-Castings-EGM-March-2-For-499-Cr-Preferential-Issue/699eb96204a25a58c8541761</guid><description>Simplex Castings Ltd. will hold an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on March 2, 2026, to seek shareholder approval for a preferential issue of approximately ₹49.90 crore. These funds are designated for capital expenditure and working capital needs, with utilization expected within 24 months. Notably, no existing promoters or directors are participating in this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:57:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eb96204a25a58c8541760_1772009948980.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Telcos Face Legal AGR Path: India Tightens Telecom Rules</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Telcos-Face-Legal-AGR-Path-India-Tightens-Telecom-Rules/699eb8f004a25a58c854168b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Telcos-Face-Legal-AGR-Path-India-Tightens-Telecom-Rules/699eb8f004a25a58c854168b</guid><description>Telecom Minister Jyotiraditya Scindia has firmly stated that telcos seeking relief on Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) dues must follow Vodafone Idea's legal route, effectively ruling out further direct government intervention. This stance, coupled with expedited satellite internet rollout plans and the enforcement of strict SIM-binding norms for OTT platforms, signals a recalibration of India's telecommunications regulatory environment. The government prioritizes market-driven resolutions for legacy issues while simultaneously fostering growth in future connectivity technologies under a security-first approach.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:55:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eb8f004a25a58c854168a_1772009838728.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India IT Exodus Over AI Fears Masks Hidden Opportunities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-IT-Exodus-Over-AI-Fears-Masks-Hidden-Opportunities/699eb69e04a25a58c8541440</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-IT-Exodus-Over-AI-Fears-Masks-Hidden-Opportunities/699eb69e04a25a58c8541440</guid><description>Global investors are significantly underweight India, particularly its IT sector, due to escalating concerns over Artificial Intelligence's disruptive potential. This pessimism, amplified by the MSCI India index's reduced weightage, overlooks the gradual nature of AI adoption and the sector's historical adaptability. The intense focus on AI's threat is obscuring broader opportunities within India and the potential risk of missing a market rebound.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fredun Pharma Rating Upgraded to BBB+ by Infomerics; ₹156 Cr Facilities Impacted</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Fredun-Pharma-Rating-Upgraded-to-BBB-by-Infomerics-156-Cr-Facilities-Impacted/699eb4b004a25a58c8541241</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Fredun-Pharma-Rating-Upgraded-to-BBB-by-Infomerics-156-Cr-Facilities-Impacted/699eb4b004a25a58c8541241</guid><description>Infomerics has upgraded Fredun Pharmaceuticals' credit rating for ₹156.17 crore in long-term bank facilities to IVR BBB+ (Stable). The upgrade reflects improved operational performance, a stronger financial profile, and disciplined capital management in FY24-FY25. This move is expected to bolster the company's financial flexibility and institutional credibility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>US Solar Duties Spike: Waaree Faces Trade Storm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/US-Solar-Duties-Spike-Waaree-Faces-Trade-Storm/699eb44804a25a58c8541161</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/US-Solar-Duties-Spike-Waaree-Faces-Trade-Storm/699eb44804a25a58c8541161</guid><description>The US Department of Commerce has imposed preliminary countervailing duties of 126% on solar imports from India, triggering sharp sell-offs in Indian solar stocks like Waaree Energies and Premier Energies. Waaree cited its expanding US manufacturing capacity as a buffer, aiming to service its significant US order book, but the steep tariffs raise questions about the long-term viability of this strategy against persistent trade protectionism. The move adds substantial uncertainty to an already dynamic global solar market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr Reddy's Joins Generic Semaglutide Race: Price War Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Joins-Generic-Semaglutide-Race-Price-War-Looms/699eb35004a25a58c8540f8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Joins-Generic-Semaglutide-Race-Price-War-Looms/699eb35004a25a58c8540f8e</guid><description>Dr Reddy's Laboratories is poised to launch its generic semaglutide injection, tentatively named Obeda, in India by March 2026, coinciding with the expiry of patent protection. This move escalates an aggressive race among Indian pharmaceutical firms vying for market share in the rapidly growing diabetes and obesity treatment sector. The company plans sharp, competitive pricing, potentially undercutting branded versions by up to 60%, signaling a significant shift towards affordability and increased patient access in a market with high unmet needs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:31:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eb35004a25a58c8540f8d_1772009570516.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Polycab Surges on Strong Demand; Premium Valuation Debated</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Polycab-Surges-on-Strong-Demand-Premium-Valuation-Debated/699eb34d04a25a58c8540f77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Polycab-Surges-on-Strong-Demand-Premium-Valuation-Debated/699eb34d04a25a58c8540f77</guid><description>Polycab India's stock price has seen significant gains, driven by strong demand momentum and expanding market share in the wires and cables segment. Brokerage firms maintain a positive outlook, citing growth strategies and favorable industry trends. The company's proactive commodity price management and premiumisation efforts are key to its margin expansion strategy, while global sourcing shifts offer export opportunities. However, its valuation, trading above the industry P/E, prompts a closer look at future growth sustainability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:31:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eb34d04a25a58c8540f76_1772008405931.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shemaroo Entertainment: HC Quashes ₹267 Cr Tax Action Against Top Brass</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Shemaroo-Entertainment-HC-Quashes-267-Cr-Tax-Action-Against-Top-Brass/699eb00004a25a58c8540b9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Shemaroo-Entertainment-HC-Quashes-267-Cr-Tax-Action-Against-Top-Brass/699eb00004a25a58c8540b9c</guid><description>Shemaroo Entertainment secured a major legal victory as the Bombay High Court quashed show cause notices and an Order-in-Original against its Joint Managing Director, Chief Executive Officer, and Chief Financial Officer. The court deemed these actions without jurisdiction. This outcome resolves potential penalties amounting to approximately Rs. 267 crores related to alleged inadmissible Input Tax Credit (ITC) and other tax demands, with the company confirming no material financial impact.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eb00004a25a58c8540b9b_1772008368016.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>[Company Name] Approves ₹35 Cr TMT Bar Mill Expansion; Capacity to Hit 150k TPA</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Company-Name-Approves-35-Cr-TMT-Bar-Mill-Expansion-Capacity-to-Hit-150k-TPA/699eaf7004a25a58c85409d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Company-Name-Approves-35-Cr-TMT-Bar-Mill-Expansion-Capacity-to-Hit-150k-TPA/699eaf7004a25a58c85409d6</guid><description>The Board of Directors has approved the establishment of a new Rolling Mill at Bilaspur, India, to manufacture TMT Bars. This expansion will add 150,000 tons per annum (TPA) capacity with an estimated project cost of ₹35 Crores plus GST, targeted for completion by FY2026-27. Funding will primarily be from internal accruals, supplemented by potential promoter loans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:14:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eaf7004a25a58c85409d5_1772008200621.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auto Stocks Surge: Policy Boost Meets Valuation Questions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Stocks-Surge-Policy-Boost-Meets-Valuation-Questions/699eaedd04a25a58c85407df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Stocks-Surge-Policy-Boost-Meets-Valuation-Questions/699eaedd04a25a58c85407df</guid><description>The Nifty Auto index climbed nearly 2% on Wednesday, driven by expectations of steady growth and policy tailwinds. Key players like Hero MotoCorp and Bosch saw significant gains. However, a closer look reveals pockets of high valuation and emerging risks related to the EV transition, tempering the broad optimism. Analysts foresee moderate growth ahead, signaling a cautious outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:12:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eaedd04a25a58c85407de_1772007754494.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Prices Surge: Private Firms Outpace PSUs Amid Demand Uptick</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Prices-Surge-Private-Firms-Outpace-PSUs-Amid-Demand-Uptick/699eaedb04a25a58c85407c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Prices-Surge-Private-Firms-Outpace-PSUs-Amid-Demand-Uptick/699eaedb04a25a58c85407c8</guid><description>Domestic steel prices are expected to rise in Q4FY26, driven by seasonal demand and reduced import competition. Private sector companies like JSW Steel and Jindal Steel &amp; Power are better positioned than public sector undertakings (PSUs) such as SAIL, which faces risks from aggressive expansion plans. Hot rolled coil prices have already seen significant increases, signaling improving margins despite rising input costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:12:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eaedb04a25a58c85407c7_1772008312199.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jubilant FoodWorks' Growth Drive Meets Market Skepticism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Jubilant-FoodWorks-Growth-Drive-Meets-Market-Skepticism/699eaed104a25a58c8540790</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Jubilant-FoodWorks-Growth-Drive-Meets-Market-Skepticism/699eaed104a25a58c8540790</guid><description>Jubilant FoodWorks (JFL) aims for a 15% revenue and EBITDA growth through store expansion and like-for-like sales increases. Despite a positive analyst consensus and price targets indicating significant upside, the company's stock has fallen over 26% in the past year. This performance divergence highlights potential investor concerns regarding execution risks and the impact of shifting consumer demand toward value offerings within India's competitive quick-service restaurant (QSR) sector. Competitors like Westlife Foodworld and Sapphire Foods India are also facing significant stock declines and operational challenges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:12:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eaed104a25a58c854078f_1772007454534.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Divergent Fortunes: Usha Martin Gains Amidst Regulatory Snag, Jai Balaji Surges on Thin Ice</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Divergent-Fortunes-Usha-Martin-Gains-Amidst-Regulatory-Snag-Jai-Balaji-Surges-on-Thin-Ice/699eaeb104a25a58c85406fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Divergent-Fortunes-Usha-Martin-Gains-Amidst-Regulatory-Snag-Jai-Balaji-Surges-on-Thin-Ice/699eaeb104a25a58c85406fe</guid><description>Heavy trading volumes propelled Usha Martin and Jai Balaji Industries shares higher on Wednesday. While Usha Martin's upward momentum is buttressed by its market leadership and sound financials, Jai Balaji Industries' surge occurs despite a precipitous 90.4% year-on-year profit decline in Q3 FY26 and weak technical indicators, suggesting speculative trading over fundamental conviction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:11:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eaeb104a25a58c85406fd_1772008556629.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dimon Warns of 2008 Echoes, Cites AI as New Crisis Driver</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Dimon-Warns-of-2008-Echoes-Cites-AI-as-New-Crisis-Driver/699eae3004a25a58c8540569</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Dimon-Warns-of-2008-Echoes-Cites-AI-as-New-Crisis-Driver/699eae3004a25a58c8540569</guid><description>JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon expressed significant anxiety over current financial market conditions, drawing parallels to the pre-2008 era. He warned that speculative behavior by some lenders, combined with rapid AI-driven industry shifts, could trigger systemic risks. Dimon highlighted that elevated asset prices and aggressive competition for profits mask accumulating dangers, suggesting that unlike the 2008 crisis which stemmed from housing, the next major disruption might originate from software and AI-impacted sectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HOEC Appoints New MD &amp; CEO; Ex-Gujarat CS Jagadip Narayan Singh Becomes Chairman</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/HOEC-Appoints-New-MD-and-CEO-Ex-Gujarat-CS-Jagadip-Narayan-Singh-Becomes-Chairman/699eae0804a25a58c85404dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/HOEC-Appoints-New-MD-and-CEO-Ex-Gujarat-CS-Jagadip-Narayan-Singh-Becomes-Chairman/699eae0804a25a58c85404dd</guid><description>Hindustan Oil Exploration Company Limited (HOEC) has announced significant leadership changes. Baroruchi Mishra, with over 35 years in the Oil &amp; Gas sector, will take over as Managing Director &amp; CEO. Former Gujarat Chief Secretary Jagadip Narayan Singh has been appointed Chairman. These appointments follow the resignation of current MD Ramasamy Jeevanandam and require shareholder approval.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:08:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eae0804a25a58c85404dc_1772009162169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariffs Hit Solar Stocks; IT Rebounds Amidst AI Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/US-Tariffs-Hit-Solar-Stocks-IT-Rebounds-Amidst-AI-Fears/699eac9104a25a58c854007a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/US-Tariffs-Hit-Solar-Stocks-IT-Rebounds-Amidst-AI-Fears/699eac9104a25a58c854007a</guid><description>The Indian equity market displayed a bifurcated performance on February 25, 2026. The solar energy sector faced significant headwinds as preliminary U.S. duties of 126% on imports from India triggered sharp declines in companies like Waaree Energies and Vikram Solar, driven by their export exposure. Conversely, the IT sector staged a robust rebound, with the Nifty IT index climbing over 3%, led by HCL Technologies and Infosys, as immediate concerns around AI disruption eased. Natco Pharma surged on regulatory approval for Semaglutide, and Larsen &amp; Toubro advanced on substantial new orders, while Indian Railway Finance Corporation fell due to a government stake sale via OFS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:02:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eac9104a25a58c8540079_1772008616021.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Infra Boom: Capital Goods Stocks Face Valuation Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Infra-Boom-Capital-Goods-Stocks-Face-Valuation-Hurdles/699eac6004a25a58c853ffdb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Infra-Boom-Capital-Goods-Stocks-Face-Valuation-Hurdles/699eac6004a25a58c853ffdb</guid><description>India's FY27 Union Budget allocates a record ₹12.2 trillion for infrastructure, a 11% YoY jump, directly benefiting the capital goods sector. Companies like ABB India, Cummins India, Jyoti CNC Automation, and CG Power are poised for demand. However, steep valuations, margin pressures, and strategic diversification into new areas like semiconductors are critical factors investors must scrutinize. While order books are strong, execution and competitive pressures define the near-term outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Coforge Wins $158M Contract Amid IT Sector Turmoil</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-Wins-158M-Contract-Amid-IT-Sector-Turmoil/699eac5804a25a58c853ffba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-Wins-158M-Contract-Amid-IT-Sector-Turmoil/699eac5804a25a58c853ffba</guid><description>Coforge has secured a significant five-year, $158 million contract with a UK-based client, bolstering its order book and revenue visibility. This win comes as the IT sector grapples with AI-driven disruption fears and a notable stock price decline for Coforge itself. Despite broader market sentiment, the company reported strong Q3FY26 results, with profit up 16% year-on-year and revenue up 28.5%. Coforge's strategic focus on AI platforms is positioned to capitalize on evolving client demands, potentially driving future growth and ancillary revenue streams. The market, however, remains cautious due to valuation concerns and sector-wide headwinds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vikram Solar: N-TOPCon Order Boosted Amidst Tariff Turmoil</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Vikram-Solar-N-TOPCon-Order-Boosted-Amidst-Tariff-Turmoil/699eac4104a25a58c853ff6f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Vikram-Solar-N-TOPCon-Order-Boosted-Amidst-Tariff-Turmoil/699eac4104a25a58c853ff6f</guid><description>Vikram Solar has secured a 378 MW order for advanced N-TOPCon solar modules from NTPC Green Energy and Indian Oil for a Gujarat project. This deal highlights the company's technological progression and ability to secure large utility-scale contracts. Despite a significant 416% year-over-year profit jump in Q3 FY26 and a robust 10.6 GW order book, Vikram Solar's share price declined by over 5% on February 25, 2026. The market reaction was primarily driven by concerns over preliminary US import duties on solar products, overshadowing the positive operational and technological developments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Growth Engine: Optimism Meets Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Engine-Optimism-Meets-Global-Headwinds/699eac1e04a25a58c853fee8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Engine-Optimism-Meets-Global-Headwinds/699eac1e04a25a58c853fee8</guid><description>The Indian economy is projected to maintain strong growth, with FY26 GDP forecasts ranging from 6.6% to 8.1% depending on the estimate. Despite this resilience, highlighted by the Finance Minister, the nation navigates significant global uncertainties, including trade tensions and geopolitical risks. Proactive government measures in trade policy, investment treaties, and privatization are being emphasized to safeguard domestic industries and bolster economic stability. However, underlying concerns remain regarding the impact of external shocks and structural vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Markets: Resilience Tested Amid Geopolitical Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Resilience-Tested-Amid-Geopolitical-Jitters/699eabe304a25a58c853fe48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Resilience-Tested-Amid-Geopolitical-Jitters/699eabe304a25a58c853fe48</guid><description>Equity markets are signaling potential expansion after a nine-month consolidation, boosted by strong corporate performance and the India-EU Free Trade Agreement. However, recent volatility on February 19, 2026, driven by geopolitical tensions and interest rate worries, highlights underlying risks, particularly for mid and small-cap stocks trading at elevated valuations. While sectors like banking, auto, and capital goods are favored, challenges persist, including potential margin squeezes in banking and input cost pressures in cement. Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL) faces scrutiny over its high P/E ratio, and Adani Ports exhibits expensive valuations despite a 'Buy' rating from some analysts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:59:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eabe304a25a58c853fe47_1772007825027.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki's Green Logistics: Carbon Credits Boost ESG?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzukis-Green-Logistics-Carbon-Credits-Boost-ESG/699eabce04a25a58c853fe31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzukis-Green-Logistics-Carbon-Credits-Boost-ESG/699eabce04a25a58c853fe31</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki's Gujarat in-plant railway siding achieved world recognition as the first Verra-registered Modal Shift Transportation Project, projected to generate 1.7 lakh carbon credits over a decade. This initiative leverages rail transport for vehicle dispatches, significantly reducing CO2 emissions. The move enhances the company's sustainability profile, tapping into India's rapidly expanding voluntary carbon market, estimated to reach over $1.1 billion by 2030. While lauded for operational efficiency and environmental responsibility, the actual financial yield from these credits and their long-term impact on the company's valuation warrant scrutiny amidst evolving sector trends.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Udayshivakumar Infra Promoter Buys 1.38 Lakh Shares, Raises Stake to 66.19%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Udayshivakumar-Infra-Promoter-Buys-138-Lakh-Shares-Raises-Stake-to-6619percent/699eaa5f04a25a58c853fc12</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Udayshivakumar-Infra-Promoter-Buys-138-Lakh-Shares-Raises-Stake-to-6619percent/699eaa5f04a25a58c853fc12</guid><description>Udayshivakumar Infra's Promoter and Managing Director has acquired 1,38,521 equity shares worth ₹41.20 lakh through open market purchases. This transaction, on February 24, 2026, nudged the promoter's stake up from 65.94% to 66.19%. The move signals continued confidence from the company's leadership amid ongoing infrastructure development.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:53:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eaa5f04a25a58c853fc11_1772006086840.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T Wins Big in Global Grid Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-Wins-Big-in-Global-Grid-Expansion/699ea80c04a25a58c853f995</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-Wins-Big-in-Global-Grid-Expansion/699ea80c04a25a58c853f995</guid><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro's Power Transmission &amp; Distribution division secured significant EPC orders for high-voltage substations and transmission lines in India and the Middle East. These complex, international wins bolster its order book, now exceeding ₹7.33 lakh crore, and align with L&amp;T's strategic positioning for global grid modernization and energy transition investments. The company's stock reflects this strong performance, trading near its 52-week high.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:43:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ea80c04a25a58c853f994_1772005574984.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nisus Finance Invests ₹247 Cr in Dubai Real Estate; Fund Expands UAE Portfolio</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nisus-Finance-Invests-247-Cr-in-Dubai-Real-Estate-Fund-Expands-UAE-Portfolio/699ea80804a25a58c853f97e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nisus-Finance-Invests-247-Cr-in-Dubai-Real-Estate-Fund-Expands-UAE-Portfolio/699ea80804a25a58c853f97e</guid><description>Nisus Finance has committed ₹247 crore (AED 100 million) to acquire residential apartments in Majan, Dubai, through its Nisus High Yield Growth Fund. This marks the fund's fourth property investment in the UAE and is part of the company's planned $500 million deployment in the region. The investment targets a Grade A, fully occupied asset, underscoring Nisus Finance's strategy to expand its international real estate portfolio and its confidence in Dubai's evolving residential landscape.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>