<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:50:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>USFDA Issues 11 Observations at Aurobindo Pharma's Unit III; Shares Under Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/USFDA-Issues-11-Observations-at-Aurobindo-Pharmas-Unit-III-Shares-Under-Pressure/6989383cb81b2b81dcfe0d87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/USFDA-Issues-11-Observations-at-Aurobindo-Pharmas-Unit-III-Shares-Under-Pressure/6989383cb81b2b81dcfe0d87</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma Ltd. shares are poised for a weak opening as the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) issued 11 observations following an inspection of its Unit III manufacturing facility. This facility produces formulations. The inspection, conducted from January 27 to February 6, adds to existing regulatory concerns at the site, which previously received an Official Action Indicated status in May 2024 and a warning letter in August 2024. Aurobindo Pharma shares closed 1.13% higher at ₹1,195 on Friday, remaining flat year-to-date.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:28:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989383cb81b2b81dcfe0d86_1770600650397.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samsung's HBM4 Race: Chasing SK Hynix, Nvidia Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Samsungs-HBM4-Race-Chasing-SK-Hynix-Nvidia-Key/6989382cb81b2b81dcfe0ca4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Samsungs-HBM4-Race-Chasing-SK-Hynix-Nvidia-Key/6989382cb81b2b81dcfe0ca4</guid><description>Samsung Electronics Co. is initiating mass production of HBM4 memory chips, a critical component for AI infrastructure, with immediate plans to supply Nvidia Corp.'s upcoming Vera Rubin accelerators. This move signals Samsung's intensified efforts to challenge SK Hynix Inc.'s current dominance in the high-bandwidth memory market. While the HBM sector experiences unprecedented demand, Samsung's aggressive timeline and market share aspirations are under scrutiny against SK Hynix's established position and production stability. Broader memory shortages also continue to impact various technology segments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:28:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989382cb81b2b81dcfe0ca3_1770600605839.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fractal Analytics IPO Opens Amid Valuation Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Opens-Amid-Valuation-Debate/69893213b81b2b81dcfe09e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Opens-Amid-Valuation-Debate/69893213b81b2b81dcfe09e3</guid><description>Fractal Analytics' ₹2,834 crore Initial Public Offering (IPO) opened for subscription on February 9, 2026. The artificial intelligence solutions provider is seeking to capitalize on robust enterprise AI demand, but faces a divided market sentiment. While analysts acknowledge its 'pure-play' AI status and turnaround financials, concerns over its elevated valuation multiples and execution risks, including client attrition, temper enthusiasm, leading to mixed brokerage ratings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:02:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69893213b81b2b81dcfe09e2_1770599080592.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Corporates: Profit Surges Mask Margin Squeeze &amp; Regulatory Shadows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Corporates-Profit-Surges-Mask-Margin-Squeeze-and-Regulatory-Shadows/698930adb81b2b81dcfe07d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Corporates-Profit-Surges-Mask-Margin-Squeeze-and-Regulatory-Shadows/698930adb81b2b81dcfe07d6</guid><description>State Bank of India reported its highest-ever quarterly profit, bolstered by credit growth and asset quality improvements. Tata Steel also saw a significant profit jump, outperforming peers. Meanwhile, the IDBI Bank divestment process advanced with financial bids received. Conversely, Sonata Software and Oswal Pumps experienced margin compression despite revenue growth, while Go Digit General Insurance faces regulatory scrutiny with a GST intelligence search. Reliance Industries expanded its consumer goods footprint internationally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:56:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698930adb81b2b81dcfe07d5_1770598870772.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Nuclear Push: Valuations Clash With Execution Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Nuclear-Push-Valuations-Clash-With-Execution-Risks/6989305ab81b2b81dcfe05fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Nuclear-Push-Valuations-Clash-With-Execution-Risks/6989305ab81b2b81dcfe05fe</guid><description>India's nuclear energy expansion is accelerating, supported by the SHANTI Bill and Budget 2026 incentives. However, critical suppliers MTAR Technologies and Azad Engineering trade at premium valuations (P/E ~158x and ~87x respectively), while HCC, a major EPC player, exhibits a significantly lower P/E (~31x) coupled with declining stock performance. Investors weigh policy tailwinds against company-specific execution capabilities and valuation disparities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:54:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989305ab81b2b81dcfe05fd_1770598730979.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Surges, But Sector Divergence Signals Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nifty-Surges-But-Sector-Divergence-Signals-Caution/69893037b81b2b81dcfe0553</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nifty-Surges-But-Sector-Divergence-Signals-Caution/69893037b81b2b81dcfe0553</guid><description>The Nifty surged past 26,000, driven by renewed FII interest and tariff positivity, particularly benefiting the financial services sector. However, underlying market breadth shows weakness, with the IT index faltering and the realty sector showing only technical recovery signs amidst broader consolidation. Divergent momentum indicators across key indices suggest sustainability concerns for the current rally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:54:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69893037b81b2b81dcfe0552_1770598578238.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2047 Goal: Reforms Lag, Investor Risk Premium Grows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2047-Goal-Reforms-Lag-Investor-Risk-Premium-Grows/69892f45b81b2b81dcfe03c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2047-Goal-Reforms-Lag-Investor-Risk-Premium-Grows/69892f45b81b2b81dcfe03c0</guid><description>Achieving 'Viksit Bharat' by 2047 necessitates a sustained average growth of 7.8-8% and a capital investment increase to 40% of GDP, requiring significant private sector participation. However, persistent institutional weaknesses, including a notoriously slow contract enforcement system ranking 163rd globally, and bureaucratic inefficiencies, are creating a substantial risk premium for investors. These structural impediments, alongside a low Rule of Law score (86th globally), contrast with other economic progress and sector-specific reforms, casting doubt on the pace of achieving ambitious development targets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:50:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69892f45b81b2b81dcfe03bf_1770598358503.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Inc's Labour Code Provisions Signal Shifting Cost Structures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Incs-Labour-Code-Provisions-Signal-Shifting-Cost-Structures/69892ed0b81b2b81dcfe0254</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Incs-Labour-Code-Provisions-Signal-Shifting-Cost-Structures/69892ed0b81b2b81dcfe0254</guid><description>Indian corporations, particularly Nifty 50 entities, are setting aside substantial funds to comply with the newly enacted Labour Codes. In the October-December 2025 quarter, provisions totaled over ₹13,307 crore across 41 companies. The IT sector, led by giants like TCS and Infosys, bore a significant portion of this outlay, reporting one-time charges that impacted quarterly profits. While some sectors like banking and infrastructure also made provisions, there's a notable variance in the amounts and approaches taken, with some major conglomerates claiming a 'not material' impact.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:48:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69892ed0b81b2b81dcfe0253_1770598208905.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Loan Books Swell 13% as Capex Revival Fuels Corporate Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Loan-Books-Swell-13percent-as-Capex-Revival-Fuels-Corporate-Demand/69892b86b81b2b81dcfdfffc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Loan-Books-Swell-13percent-as-Capex-Revival-Fuels-Corporate-Demand/69892b86b81b2b81dcfdfffc</guid><description>Corporate loan growth in India is surging, with lenders reporting a revival driven by increased capital expenditure and working capital needs. Sectors like oil and gas, infrastructure, metals, and power are leading the demand. Major banks such as State Bank of India (SBI) and Axis Bank have posted significant year-on-year increases in their corporate loan books, signaling robust economic activity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:34:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69892b86b81b2b81dcfdfffb_1770597393372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tech Push: Companies Leapfrog China FDI Approval Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Tech-Push-Companies-Leapfrog-China-FDI-Approval-Hurdles/69892a98b81b2b81dcfdfe7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Tech-Push-Companies-Leapfrog-China-FDI-Approval-Hurdles/69892a98b81b2b81dcfdfe7b</guid><description>Indian manufacturers Dixon Technologies and PG Electroplast are advancing significant joint ventures and technical alliances with Chinese firms, commencing factory construction and machinery orders despite awaiting Press Note 3 (PN3) government clearance. This proactive approach, driven by a need to leverage Chinese technology and avoid business plan disruptions, signals a high-stakes strategy. While managing directors express confidence in eventual approval, the companies are prepared to operate projects as wholly-owned subsidiaries, highlighting the critical balance between regulatory compliance and aggressive expansion in India's burgeoning electronics sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:30:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69892a98b81b2b81dcfdfe7a_1770597165740.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Interarch Building Solutions Bets Big on Future Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Interarch-Building-Solutions-Bets-Big-on-Future-Demand/69892a1eb81b2b81dcfdfd00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Interarch-Building-Solutions-Bets-Big-on-Future-Demand/69892a1eb81b2b81dcfdfd00</guid><description>Interarch Building Solutions reported a 43.7% year-on-year revenue surge to Rs 522.5 crore in Q3 FY26, alongside a 43.2% jump in operating profit to Rs 50.3 crore. The company has upwardly revised its FY26 revenue guidance to nearly Rs 1,900 crore and is accelerating capital expenditure, indicating a strategic conviction to build capacity well ahead of market saturation. This proactive stance, particularly targeting the burgeoning data center segment, positions Interarch to capture significant future market share, although execution risks remain.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:28:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69892a1eb81b2b81dcfdfcff_1770597019398.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Medi Assist Health Insurance Q3: Revenue Surges 30%, Debt Slashed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Medi-Assist-Health-Insurance-Q3-Revenue-Surges-30percent-Debt-Slashed/698925e4b81b2b81dcfdfac7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Medi-Assist-Health-Insurance-Q3-Revenue-Surges-30percent-Debt-Slashed/698925e4b81b2b81dcfdfac7</guid><description>Medi Assist Healthcare Services reported a robust Q3 FY26, with total income jumping 29.9% YoY to ₹247.2 Cr, boosted by the Paramount integration. Revenue from Contracts grew 28.9% YoY to ₹239.7 Cr. EBITDA rose 12.4% YoY to ₹44.6 Cr, though margins saw a 154 bps YoY dip to 18.6%. The company achieved a near debt-free status by December 2025, reducing debt from ₹243.4 Cr to ₹39.4 Cr, and boasts ₹200.1 Cr in free cash. Exceptional items, including a cyber-security incident and alleged claims provision, impacted 9M FY26 PAT by ₹14.2 Cr. Strategic advancements include the impending slump transfer of Paramount TPA and an 81.5% YoY surge in proprietary technology revenue, with AI identifying ~₹400 Cr in fraud. Market share gains were noted in the Group segment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:10:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698925e4b81b2b81dcfdfac6_1770595946546.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>