<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:18:08 +0000</pubDate><item><title>IndiGo's ₹10,000 Compensation: Your Guide to Claiming Vouchers or Cash After Flight Chaos!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-10000-Compensation-Your-Guide-to-Claiming-Vouchers-or-Cash-After-Flight-Chaos/6957dc394342f77179fc7bfa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-10000-Compensation-Your-Guide-to-Claiming-Vouchers-or-Cash-After-Flight-Chaos/6957dc394342f77179fc7bfa</guid><description>IndiGo has detailed its 'Gesture of Care' compensation for passengers severely impacted by flight cancellations and prolonged delays between December 3-5, 2025. Eligible customers can claim a ₹10,000 travel voucher, issued as two ₹5,000 vouchers per passenger. Alternatively, a bank transfer option is available. This offer is independent of and in addition to the compensation mandated by the Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA).</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:46:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957dc394342f77179fc7bf9_1767365900770.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>🇰🇷 Crypto Capital Flight: $110 Billion Flees South Korea as Strict Rules Drive Investors Overseas!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-Capital-Flight-110-Billion-Flees-South-Korea-as-Strict-Rules-Drive-Investors-Overseas/6957dc484342f77179fc7c99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-Capital-Flight-110-Billion-Flees-South-Korea-as-Strict-Rules-Drive-Investors-Overseas/6957dc484342f77179fc7c99</guid><description>South Koreans moved over $110 billion (160 trillion won) from local cryptocurrency exchanges to foreign platforms last year. This mass exodus is driven by strict domestic trading rules that limit offerings, pushing investors towards overseas platforms that provide access to more complex products like leverage and derivatives, ultimately stagnating growth in South Korea's digital asset market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:44:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957dc484342f77179fc7c98_1767365875684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Missed Global Rally? SEBI Curbs Kept Indian Investors From Huge Overseas Fund Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Missed-Global-Rally-SEBI-Curbs-Kept-Indian-Investors-From-Huge-Overseas-Fund-Gains/6957dbc04342f77179fc7992</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Missed-Global-Rally-SEBI-Curbs-Kept-Indian-Investors-From-Huge-Overseas-Fund-Gains/6957dbc04342f77179fc7992</guid><description>Indian mutual fund investors missed significant returns from booming international markets due to SEBI's restrictions on fresh overseas investments starting in 2022. Funds investing globally delivered exceptional gains, some exceeding 50% and even 169% in the past year, far surpassing domestic returns like Nifty's 9%. While existing investors benefited from market-to-market gains, new investors were locked out, forcing high-net-worth individuals to use alternative routes like LRS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:37:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957dbc04342f77179fc7991_1767365772465.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Drops Bombshell: 10-Year Tech Masterplan to Transform Indian Markets! Will Your Investments Soar?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Drops-Bombshell-10-Year-Tech-Masterplan-to-Transform-Indian-Markets-Will-Your-Investments-Soar/6957dad84342f77179fc74cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Drops-Bombshell-10-Year-Tech-Masterplan-to-Transform-Indian-Markets-Will-Your-Investments-Soar/6957dad84342f77179fc74cd</guid><description>India's market regulator, SEBI, is crafting a crucial five- and ten-year technology roadmap for its core market infrastructure institutions. This strategic vision aims to elevate the Indian securities market by prioritizing quality, sophistication, and trust over mere scale. The plan involves significant investments in technology, advanced risk management, and robust cyber resilience, with a central focus on strengthening investor protection and market integrity using emerging tools like AI.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:36:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957dad84342f77179fc74cc_1767365600179.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Deep Tech Reset: India VCs Ditch Hype for Manufacturing Powerhouses!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Deep-Tech-Reset-India-VCs-Ditch-Hype-for-Manufacturing-Powerhouses/6957db674342f77179fc7795</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Deep-Tech-Reset-India-VCs-Ditch-Hype-for-Manufacturing-Powerhouses/6957db674342f77179fc7795</guid><description>India's deep-tech investment is shifting. Venture capital firms, like Capital A, are moving from broad, experimental bets made during the 2021 funding euphoria to focusing on manufacturing-first startups. Investors now demand early commercial traction, clear scaling paths, and demonstrable returns, reflecting a move towards discipline and conviction-led investing in capital-intensive deep-tech sectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:36:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957db674342f77179fc7794_1767365655044.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC Stock CRASHES: $7 Billion EVAPORATED After Government Tax 'Shock' Sparks Fury &amp; Downgrades!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-CRASHES-7-Billion-EVAPORATED-After-Government-Tax-Shock-Sparks-Fury-and-Downgrades/6957da5e4342f77179fc72ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-CRASHES-7-Billion-EVAPORATED-After-Government-Tax-Shock-Sparks-Fury-and-Downgrades/6957da5e4342f77179fc72ae</guid><description>India's largest cigarette maker ITC Ltd. has lost over $7 billion in market value following a significant government tax increase on tobacco products. The tax hike, effective February 1st, has led to numerous brokerage downgrades, with analysts warning of potential price increases, reduced demand, and pressure on profitability. Shares have fallen sharply, reaching their lowest point since February 2023.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:30:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957da5e4342f77179fc72ad_1767365469951.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unlocks Rs 7,295 Cr Trade Finance Power-Up for MSME Exporters!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Unlocks-Rs-7295-Cr-Trade-Finance-Power-Up-for-MSME-Exporters/6957d8d34342f77179fc6bb4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Unlocks-Rs-7295-Cr-Trade-Finance-Power-Up-for-MSME-Exporters/6957d8d34342f77179fc6bb4</guid><description>The Indian government has launched two significant sub-schemes under the Export Promotion Mission, totaling ₹7,295 crore, to make trade financing faster and cheaper for MSME exporters. One scheme offers substantial interest subvention on export credit, aiming to reduce borrowing costs and ease working capital. The second initiative provides crucial collateral guarantee support, enhancing MSMEs' access to bank finance and addressing collateral constraints, thereby boosting India's export competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:29:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957d8d34342f77179fc6bb3_1767365097912.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LIC Policyholders Rejoice! Lapsed Policies Revived with Huge Fee Cuts – Don't Miss Out!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Policyholders-Rejoice-Lapsed-Policies-Revived-with-Huge-Fee-Cuts-Dont-Miss-Out/6957d57a4342f77179fc5cfe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Policyholders-Rejoice-Lapsed-Policies-Revived-with-Huge-Fee-Cuts-Dont-Miss-Out/6957d57a4342f77179fc5cfe</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has launched a special revival campaign from January 1 to March 2, 2026, allowing lapsed individual insurance policyholders to restore their coverage. The campaign offers significant late fee concessions, including up to 30% for non-linked plans (max ₹5,000) and 100% for micro insurance plans. Policies lapsed during the premium-paying term can be revived within five years, provided they meet policy conditions. This initiative aims to help policyholders regain financial protection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957d57a4342f77179fc5cfd_1767364146923.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New Year's Strike: Gig Workers Revolt Against 10-Minute Delivery Model, Demand Fair Pay!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/New-Years-Strike-Gig-Workers-Revolt-Against-10-Minute-Delivery-Model-Demand-Fair-Pay/6957d6154342f77179fc609b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/New-Years-Strike-Gig-Workers-Revolt-Against-10-Minute-Delivery-Model-Demand-Fair-Pay/6957d6154342f77179fc609b</guid><description>Thousands of app-based delivery workers across India staged a flash strike on New Year's Eve, protesting against unfair pay, lack of minimum wage, and safety concerns related to ultra-fast delivery targets. While platforms like Zomato claimed business was unaffected, unions reported significant order delays, highlighting deep issues in India's booming gig economy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:15:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957d6154342f77179fc609a_1767364479641.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Andhra Pradesh Stuns Nation: Now India's Top Investment Magnet!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Andhra-Pradesh-Stuns-Nation-Now-Indias-Top-Investment-Magnet/6957d5a74342f77179fc5de1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Andhra-Pradesh-Stuns-Nation-Now-Indias-Top-Investment-Magnet/6957d5a74342f77179fc5de1</guid><description>Andhra Pradesh has become India's premier investment destination, capturing 25.3% of proposed capital investments in the first nine months of FY26. This positions the state ahead of Odisha and Maharashtra, signaling a major shift towards eastern and southern industrial corridors. Total national investment proposals grew 11.5% to ₹26.6 lakh crore.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:15:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957d5a74342f77179fc5de0_1767364175187.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zappfresh Seals Food Deal: Acquires 51% of Avyom Foodtech for ₹7.5 Crore!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zappfresh-Seals-Food-Deal-Acquires-51percent-of-Avyom-Foodtech-for-75-Crore/6957d55a4342f77179fc5c24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zappfresh-Seals-Food-Deal-Acquires-51percent-of-Avyom-Foodtech-for-75-Crore/6957d55a4342f77179fc5c24</guid><description>DSM Fresh Foods, operating as Zappfresh, has acquired a 51% controlling stake in Avyom Foodtech for ₹7.5 crore cash. This strategic move allows Zappfresh to enter the ready food solutions segment, expand its processing capabilities, and tap into overseas export markets by integrating Avyom's land and processing facility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:15:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957d55a4342f77179fc5c23_1767364033375.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ex-Bank of India Exec Karthikeyan Manickam Takes Helm as ESAF Small Finance Bank Chairman! What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Ex-Bank-of-India-Exec-Karthikeyan-Manickam-Takes-Helm-as-ESAF-Small-Finance-Bank-Chairman-Whats-Next/6957d3564342f77179fc52e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Ex-Bank-of-India-Exec-Karthikeyan-Manickam-Takes-Helm-as-ESAF-Small-Finance-Bank-Chairman-Whats-Next/6957d3564342f77179fc52e4</guid><description>ESAF Small Finance Bank has appointed Karthikeyan Manickam, a former executive director of Bank of India, as its new Chairman. Manickam brings extensive expertise in banking operations, risk management, regulatory compliance, human resources, and credit recovery. In his new role, he will provide strategic guidance and independent oversight to the bank's board, aiming to steer its future growth and stability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:07:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957d3564342f77179fc52e3_1767363561520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Forex Reserves Surge $3.29 Billion to Record $696 Billion, Fueled by Gold Rush!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Surge-329-Billion-to-Record-696-Billion-Fueled-by-Gold-Rush/6957d1f74342f77179fc4d0e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Surge-329-Billion-to-Record-696-Billion-Fueled-by-Gold-Rush/6957d1f74342f77179fc4d0e</guid><description>India's foreign exchange reserves climbed by $3.293 billion to reach $696.61 billion in the week ending December 26. This significant increase, reported by the Reserve Bank of India, was primarily driven by a substantial jump in gold holdings, reinforcing the nation's external financial buffer. Foreign currency assets also saw a modest rise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:01:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957d1f74342f77179fc4d0d_1767363221239.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Q3: Metal Output Surges, But Lead Production Faces Setback! See The Numbers Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Zinc-Q3-Metal-Output-Surges-But-Lead-Production-Faces-Setback-See-The-Numbers-Now/6957ce774342f77179fc3f19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Zinc-Q3-Metal-Output-Surges-But-Lead-Production-Faces-Setback-See-The-Numbers-Now/6957ce774342f77179fc3f19</guid><description>Hindustan Zinc reported a strong third quarter for December 2025, with mined metal production up 4% year-on-year to 276 kilotonnes and saleable metal output also rising 4% to 270 kilotonnes. Refined zinc saw an 8% increase to 221 kilotonnes, driven by debottlenecking projects and improved plant availability. However, refined lead production declined 11% to 49 kilotonnes due to operational factors. The company achieved its highest-ever December quarter mined and refined metal production since transitioning to underground mining.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:43:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957ce774342f77179fc3f18_1767362431389.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Union Bank of India Posts Stellar Q3: Advances Soar 7.13%, Deposits Climb Amidst Strong Market Performance!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Union-Bank-of-India-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Advances-Soar-713percent-Deposits-Climb-Amidst-Strong-Market-Performance/6957ce144342f77179fc3cea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Union-Bank-of-India-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Advances-Soar-713percent-Deposits-Climb-Amidst-Strong-Market-Performance/6957ce144342f77179fc3cea</guid><description>Union Bank of India released its provisional Q3 update for the period ending December 31, 2025. The bank reported a significant 7.13% year-on-year increase in global gross advances, reaching ₹10,16,805 crore. Domestic advances grew 7.42%, with Retail, Agriculture, and MSME (RAM) advances showing a strong 11.49% rise. Global deposits also saw a healthy 3.36% year-on-year increase. Following this positive update, Union Bank of India's shares closed up 2.23% at ₹157 on January 2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:43:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957ce144342f77179fc3ce9_1767362224528.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>D-Mart's Q3 Triumph: Revenue Skyrockets to ₹17,613 Crore! 442 Stores Strong - What This Means for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/D-Marts-Q3-Triumph-Revenue-Skyrockets-to-17613-Crore-442-Stores-Strong-What-This-Means-for-Your-Investments/6957cdf34342f77179fc3c64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/D-Marts-Q3-Triumph-Revenue-Skyrockets-to-17613-Crore-442-Stores-Strong-What-This-Means-for-Your-Investments/6957cdf34342f77179fc3c64</guid><description>Avenue Supermarts, operator of D-Mart, announced robust Q3 FY25 results with revenue soaring to ₹17,613 crore, marking a significant 15.5% year-on-year growth. The company also expanded its retail footprint to 442 stores across India. Profit saw a 3.9% rise to ₹685 crore, while EBITDA grew 11% to ₹1,213.8 crore, slightly missing analyst expectations on margins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:43:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957cdf34342f77179fc3c63_1767362107941.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Fever: MCX Overtakes NSE in Historic Trading Volume Clash!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Fever-MCX-Overtakes-NSE-in-Historic-Trading-Volume-Clash/6957cca54342f77179fc369e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Fever-MCX-Overtakes-NSE-in-Historic-Trading-Volume-Clash/6957cca54342f77179fc369e</guid><description>For the first time, Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd (MCX) has surpassed National Stock Exchange of India Ltd (NSE) in average daily turnover (ADT) for futures contracts on a monthly basis. This historic shift in December was driven by a significant rally in silver (+31%) and gold (+8%), boosting MCX's ADT to ₹93,929 crore, well above NSE's stock futures ADT of ₹72,515 crore. Analysts anticipate this bullion turnover may moderate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:39:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957cca54342f77179fc369d_1767361788300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Textile PLI Scheme Extended to March 31, 2026! Massive Boost for MMF Apparel &amp; Technical Textiles!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indias-Textile-PLI-Scheme-Extended-to-March-31-2026-Massive-Boost-for-MMF-Apparel-and-Technical-Textiles/6957cc8f4342f77179fc3609</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indias-Textile-PLI-Scheme-Extended-to-March-31-2026-Massive-Boost-for-MMF-Apparel-and-Technical-Textiles/6957cc8f4342f77179fc3609</guid><description>India has extended the Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme deadline for the textile sector to March 31, 2026. This decision follows a strong response from companies, especially in Man-Made Fibre (MMF) Apparel, MMF Fabrics, and Technical Textiles. The scheme, approved in September 2021 with a ₹10,683 crore outlay, has already seen 91 companies selected, attracting significant investment and creating thousands of jobs. A National Textiles Ministers’ Conference is also planned to align strategies for making India a global textile hub, targeting a $350 billion industry and $100 billion exports by 2030.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:35:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957cc8f4342f77179fc3608_1767361752436.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Force Motors Sales Surge! December Growth Jumps 49% - See the Numbers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Force-Motors-Sales-Surge-December-Growth-Jumps-49percent-See-the-Numbers/6957cb404342f77179fc2f41</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Force-Motors-Sales-Surge-December-Growth-Jumps-49percent-See-the-Numbers/6957cb404342f77179fc2f41</guid><description>Force Motors reported a significant 49% year-on-year sales increase for December 2025, selling 2,952 units compared to 1,985 units in December 2024. The company also saw a 47% jump in the October-December quarter, selling 8,427 units. Managing Director Prasan Firodia highlighted the revival in the tour and travel segment and steady school mobility as key drivers for this strong performance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:34:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957cb404342f77179fc2f40_1767361582698.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Ultra-Rich Secret: India's Mega-Wealth Secret Is Exploding!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indias-Ultra-Rich-Secret-Indias-Mega-Wealth-Secret-Is-Exploding/6957cb9e4342f77179fc30dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indias-Ultra-Rich-Secret-Indias-Mega-Wealth-Secret-Is-Exploding/6957cb9e4342f77179fc30dc</guid><description>India is witnessing a dramatic surge in Family Offices, private entities managing ultra-high-net-worth individuals' wealth. These offices have grown from 45 in 2018 to 300 in 2024, managing an estimated $30 billion in assets. Driven by a desire for greater control, cost reduction, and dissatisfaction with traditional institutional investors, wealthy families are increasingly diversifying investments across various asset classes, including private markets and high-growth sectors, signaling a significant shift in the investment landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:32:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957cb9e4342f77179fc30db_1767361801365.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TANFAC Industries Eyes ₹500 Crore Fundraising &amp; Stock Split: What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/TANFAC-Industries-Eyes-500-Crore-Fundraising-and-Stock-Split-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6957cb184342f77179fc2e50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/TANFAC-Industries-Eyes-500-Crore-Fundraising-and-Stock-Split-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6957cb184342f77179fc2e50</guid><description>TANFAC Industries' Board of Directors will convene to consider a significant fundraising proposal of approximately ₹500 crore through methods like Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) or private placement. The company is also exploring a sub-division of its equity shares to potentially increase liquidity. This follows a recent ₹336 crore contract for solar-grade diluted hydrofluoric acid.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957cb184342f77179fc2e4f_1767361391412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Giant Nibe Secures Massive ₹292 Crore Indian Army Order! Stock Skyrockets 🚀</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Giant-Nibe-Secures-Massive-292-Crore-Indian-Army-Order-Stock-Skyrockets/6957c69a4342f77179fc1a49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Giant-Nibe-Secures-Massive-292-Crore-Indian-Army-Order-Stock-Skyrockets/6957c69a4342f77179fc1a49</guid><description>Nibe Limited has announced a significant order win worth ₹292.69 crore from the Indian Army. The contract is for manufacturing and supplying critical ground equipment, accessories, ESP, and ammunition for a universal rocket launcher system. This advanced system supports long-range variants with strike capabilities up to 300 km and will be executed within 12 months. The news led to a substantial surge in Nibe's stock price, closing 9.22% higher on NSE.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:11:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c69a4342f77179fc1a48_1767360350225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Surgical Giant G Surgiwear Eyes Rs 740 Cr IPO: Is This Your Next Big Investment?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Surgical-Giant-G-Surgiwear-Eyes-Rs-740-Cr-IPO-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Investment/6957c5944342f77179fc1517</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Surgical-Giant-G-Surgiwear-Eyes-Rs-740-Cr-IPO-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Investment/6957c5944342f77179fc1517</guid><description>Surgical products maker G Surgiwear has filed a draft document with SEBI to raise up to Rs 740 crore via Initial Public Offering (IPO). The fundraising includes Rs 370 crore from a fresh issue of shares and Rs 370 crore from promoter Ghanshyam Das Agarwal via offer-for-sale. The company plans to use proceeds for machinery purchase and debt repayment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:07:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c5944342f77179fc1516_1767360043457.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economy Diverges: Consumption Soars While Manufacturing Dips! What's Next for 2026?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-Diverges-Consumption-Soars-While-Manufacturing-Dips-Whats-Next-for-2026/6957c60a4342f77179fc1792</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-Diverges-Consumption-Soars-While-Manufacturing-Dips-Whats-Next-for-2026/6957c60a4342f77179fc1792</guid><description>India's economy ended 2025 with a stark split: strong consumer demand fueled by record GST collections (₹1.74 lakh crore in December) and UPI transactions (21.6 billion), contrasting with a manufacturing slowdown hitting its weakest pace in two years (PMI at 55.0). Softening export growth also dampened business optimism for 2026, despite robust auto sales from Maruti Suzuki and Mahindra.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:07:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c60a4342f77179fc1791_1767360377526.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Textile Powerhouse Unleashed! PM MITRA Parks Secure ₹27,000 Cr Investment, Set to Revolutionize Apparel Industry!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Textile-Powerhouse-Unleashed-PM-MITRA-Parks-Secure-27000-Cr-Investment-Set-to-Revolutionize-Apparel-Industry/6957c59d4342f77179fc154e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Textile-Powerhouse-Unleashed-PM-MITRA-Parks-Secure-27000-Cr-Investment-Set-to-Revolutionize-Apparel-Industry/6957c59d4342f77179fc154e</guid><description>India's textile sector is set for a major boost with the PM Mega Integrated Textile Region and Apparel (MITRA) Parks project. The Rs 13,040 crore initiative will establish seven large-scale, integrated parks across Tamil Nadu, Telangana, Gujarat, Karnataka, Madhya Pradesh, Uttar Pradesh, and Maharashtra. These parks aim to cut logistics costs, enhance global competitiveness, and have already attracted Memoranda of Understanding (MoUs) worth over Rs 27,434 crore, promising significant investment and job creation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:03:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c59d4342f77179fc154d_1767360316376.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Banks Go Digital: Personal Loans Revolutionized, Are You Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Banks-Go-Digital-Personal-Loans-Revolutionized-Are-You-Ready/6957c5934342f77179fc14e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Banks-Go-Digital-Personal-Loans-Revolutionized-Are-You-Ready/6957c5934342f77179fc14e8</guid><description>India's retail credit market is shifting structurally, with banks increasingly adopting digital pathways for personal loans. This evolution, moving beyond fintech disruption, emphasizes faster, paperless borrowing, enhanced customer trust, and flexible usage. IDFC FIRST Bank's FIRSTmoney exemplifies this trend by offering modular loan access, instant disbursal, and transparent pricing, reflecting a broader industry move towards self-managed, user-controlled credit experiences. The focus is now on financial clarity and responsible lending within digital ecosystems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:02:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c5934342f77179fc14e7_1767360272152.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Data Shockwave: Bank Credit to Industry Surges to 9.6%, Fueling Economic Optimism!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Data-Shockwave-Bank-Credit-to-Industry-Surges-to-96percent-Fueling-Economic-Optimism/6957c4e34342f77179fc119b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Data-Shockwave-Bank-Credit-to-Industry-Surges-to-96percent-Fueling-Economic-Optimism/6957c4e34342f77179fc119b</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India data for November 2025 shows bank credit to industry grew by 9.6%, accelerating from 8.3% last year. This robust growth, especially in micro, small, and medium enterprises, infrastructure, and textiles, indicates rising economic activity. Non-food credit and services sector lending also increased, signaling a positive economic trajectory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:02:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c4e34342f77179fc119a_1767359863252.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Suzuki Motorcycle India Shatters Records: 26% Sales Jump in December 2025 Ignites Investor Excitement!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Suzuki-Motorcycle-India-Shatters-Records-26percent-Sales-Jump-in-December-2025-Ignites-Investor-Excitement/6957c3f94342f77179fc0c39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Suzuki-Motorcycle-India-Shatters-Records-26percent-Sales-Jump-in-December-2025-Ignites-Investor-Excitement/6957c3f94342f77179fc0c39</guid><description>Suzuki Motorcycle India Pvt Ltd announced a significant 26% year-on-year increase in total sales for December 2025, reaching 1,22,366 units compared to 96,804 units in December 2024. Domestic sales climbed 24% to 97,823 units, while exports saw a substantial 37% surge to 24,543 units. The company's leadership expressed confidence in enhancing customer experience and expanding its network in the upcoming year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:02:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c3f94342f77179fc0c38_1767359598414.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>21 Years of Magic: Rs 10,000 SIP Explodes to ₹2.39 Crore! Nippon India Pharma Fund's Jaw-Dropping Wealth Creation Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/21-Years-of-Magic-Rs-10000-SIP-Explodes-to-239-Crore-Nippon-India-Pharma-Funds-Jaw-Dropping-Wealth-Creation-Revealed/6957c4264342f77179fc0d86</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/21-Years-of-Magic-Rs-10000-SIP-Explodes-to-239-Crore-Nippon-India-Pharma-Funds-Jaw-Dropping-Wealth-Creation-Revealed/6957c4264342f77179fc0d86</guid><description>Nippon India Pharma Fund, a healthcare-focused mutual fund, has demonstrated exceptional long-term wealth creation. Over 21 years, a ₹10,000 monthly SIP has grown to approximately ₹2.39 crore, yielding an 18.32% annual return. Lump sum investors also saw significant gains, with ₹1 lakh growing to ₹52 lakh, a 52x increase with a 20.18% CAGR. While outperforming its benchmark over the long term, the fund exhibits high volatility and has seen short-to-medium term underperformance, highlighting the risks of sectoral investing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:01:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c4264342f77179fc0d85_1767359796286.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Solar Powerhouse: Jakson Group Plans Major US &amp; Europe Exports with ₹8,000 Cr Investment!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Solar-Powerhouse-Jakson-Group-Plans-Major-US-and-Europe-Exports-with-8000-Cr-Investment/6957c41d4342f77179fc0cf8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Solar-Powerhouse-Jakson-Group-Plans-Major-US-and-Europe-Exports-with-8000-Cr-Investment/6957c41d4342f77179fc0cf8</guid><description>Jakson Group is investing ₹8,000 crore to build a massive 6GW integrated solar manufacturing facility in Madhya Pradesh. Starting fiscal year 2027, the company plans significant exports of solar modules to the United States, Europe, and West Asia, aiming to become a global player beyond its current 1.2 GW plant in Greater Noida.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:00:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c41d4342f77179fc0cf7_1767359587137.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Power Surge Incoming? Analysts Issue Bold 'Buy' Rating with Huge Target!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Surge-Incoming-Analysts-Issue-Bold-Buy-Rating-with-Huge-Target/6957c3744342f77179fc0948</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Surge-Incoming-Analysts-Issue-Bold-Buy-Rating-with-Huge-Target/6957c3744342f77179fc0948</guid><description>Analysts initiate coverage on Adani Power with a 'Buy' rating and a target price of ₹178. The company, India's largest private thermal power producer, plans to significantly expand its capacity to 41.9 GW by FY32, supported by strong operational metrics and projected EBITDA growth. While capital expenditure will increase debt temporarily, it's expected to moderate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:00:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c3744342f77179fc0947_1767359480388.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Cinemas Roar Back in 2025: Box Office Triumph Fuels Massive 2026 Growth Hopes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indian-Cinemas-Roar-Back-in-2025-Box-Office-Triumph-Fuels-Massive-2026-Growth-Hopes/6957c34a4342f77179fc0843</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indian-Cinemas-Roar-Back-in-2025-Box-Office-Triumph-Fuels-Massive-2026-Growth-Hopes/6957c34a4342f77179fc0843</guid><description>Indian cinemas have demonstrated remarkable resilience and vibrancy in 2025, with strong box office performance dispelling doubts about the impact of OTT. Kamal Gianchandani of the Multiplex Association of India highlighted this success, emphasizing that both big screens and OTT platforms are vital to the entertainment ecosystem. The industry is looking forward to an even stronger 2026, anticipating significant growth driven by a robust content pipeline, positive macro-economic conditions, and increasing disposable incomes. Exhibitors are also seeking government support through GST rationalization on tickets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:59:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c34a4342f77179fc0842_1767359976444.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Agitech Powerhouse Arya.ag Bags Rs 725 Cr! Farmers' Fortunes Set to Soar?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indian-Agitech-Powerhouse-Aryaag-Bags-Rs-725-Cr-Farmers-Fortunes-Set-to-Soar/6957c3254342f77179fc0784</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indian-Agitech-Powerhouse-Aryaag-Bags-Rs-725-Cr-Farmers-Fortunes-Set-to-Soar/6957c3254342f77179fc0784</guid><description>Indian integrated grain commerce platform Arya.ag has secured ₹725 crore ($80.58 million) in a Series D funding round led by GEF Capital Partners. The capital will bolster climate-smart agriculture practices, enhance farmer access to technology, and significantly reduce post-harvest losses. Arya.ag aims to boost farmer incomes through its comprehensive services spanning storage, finance, and market access, reinforcing its position as India's sole profitable agritech platform.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:58:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c3254342f77179fc0783_1767359396000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹1 Crore Dream: 5 Golden Rules Indians Break &amp; How to Fix Them Instantly!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/1-Crore-Dream-5-Golden-Rules-Indians-Break-and-How-to-Fix-Them-Instantly/6957c2244342f77179fc0372</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/1-Crore-Dream-5-Golden-Rules-Indians-Break-and-How-to-Fix-Them-Instantly/6957c2244342f77179fc0372</guid><description>Achieving a ₹1 crore savings goal is possible for many Indians, but common mistakes can derail plans. Key pitfalls include lifestyle inflation as income rises, delaying investments which misses out on compounding, investing in only one asset type, neglecting essential insurance and emergency funds, and making emotional decisions during market swings. Avoiding these issues is crucial for wealth creation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:53:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957c2244342f77179fc0371_1767359126624.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PNB Q3 Surprise: Loan Growth Outpaces Deposits! ₹29 Lakh Crore Business Milestone Revealed - Investor Alert!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PNB-Q3-Surprise-Loan-Growth-Outpaces-Deposits-29-Lakh-Crore-Business-Milestone-Revealed-Investor-Alert/6957bf284342f77179fbf7ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PNB-Q3-Surprise-Loan-Growth-Outpaces-Deposits-29-Lakh-Crore-Business-Milestone-Revealed-Investor-Alert/6957bf284342f77179fbf7ad</guid><description>Punjab National Bank (PNB) released strong Q3 results, showing significant growth. Its global business reached nearly ₹29 lakh crore, up 9.57% year-on-year. Loan growth was robust, with global advances increasing by 10.98%, outpacing the 8.54% growth in global deposits. This led to a higher credit-deposit ratio of 74.21%. These figures are provisional and subject to auditor review.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:37:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957bf284342f77179fbf7ac_1767358502819.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises Surges as Subsidiaries Win Key Electronics Scheme Approval! India's Manufacturing Boost?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-Surges-as-Subsidiaries-Win-Key-Electronics-Scheme-Approval-Indias-Manufacturing-Boost/6957be994342f77179fbf502</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-Surges-as-Subsidiaries-Win-Key-Electronics-Scheme-Approval-Indias-Manufacturing-Boost/6957be994342f77179fbf502</guid><description>Amber Enterprises India announced its subsidiaries, Ascent-K Circuit Private Limited and Shogini Technoarts Pvt Ltd, have secured approval under the government's Electronics Components Manufacturing Scheme. This development is a significant step towards bolstering India's domestic electronics manufacturing capabilities and reducing import reliance, aligning with the Atmanirbhar Bharat initiative. The shares saw a slight increase following the announcement.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:37:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957be994342f77179fbf501_1767358332982.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's IT Ministry Cracks Down on X's Grok AI for Obscene Image Generation! Swift Action Imminent!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-IT-Ministry-Cracks-Down-on-Xs-Grok-AI-for-Obscene-Image-Generation-Swift-Action-Imminent/6957be924342f77179fbf4b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-IT-Ministry-Cracks-Down-on-Xs-Grok-AI-for-Obscene-Image-Generation-Swift-Action-Imminent/6957be924342f77179fbf4b3</guid><description>India's Ministry of Electronics and Information Technology (MeitY) is investigating the misuse of X's AI tool Grok to create obscene images. Secretary S Krishnan indicated swift regulatory action is coming, emphasizing that technology platforms cannot escape accountability under the IT Act's Safe Harbour provisions. This follows reports of users generating non-consensual, explicit content.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:37:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957be924342f77179fbf4b2_1767358289586.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CSB Bank Q3 Shockwave: Deposits Surge 21%, Advances Leap 29%! Investors Cheer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CSB-Bank-Q3-Shockwave-Deposits-Surge-21percent-Advances-Leap-29percent-Investors-Cheer/6957be624342f77179fbf37b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CSB-Bank-Q3-Shockwave-Deposits-Surge-21percent-Advances-Leap-29percent-Investors-Cheer/6957be624342f77179fbf37b</guid><description>CSB Bank released its Q3 business update for the quarter ending December 31, 2025, reporting significant year-on-year growth. Total deposits rose 21% to ₹40,460 crore, while gross advances jumped 29% to ₹37,208 crore. Advances against gold and gold jewellery saw a substantial 46% increase. CASA deposits grew 3% year-on-year. The bank's shares closed slightly up on the BSE.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:37:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957be624342f77179fbf37a_1767358436894.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Govt Unlocks Rs 5,181 Crore Export Boost for MSMEs: 2.75% Interest Subsidy Now Available!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Govt-Unlocks-Rs-5181-Crore-Export-Boost-for-MSMEs-275percent-Interest-Subsidy-Now-Available/6957bdc24342f77179fbf096</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Govt-Unlocks-Rs-5181-Crore-Export-Boost-for-MSMEs-275percent-Interest-Subsidy-Now-Available/6957bdc24342f77179fbf096</guid><description>The Indian government has launched a new Interest Subvention Scheme for MSME exporters, allocating ₹5,181 crore over six years (2025-2031). Eligible businesses will receive a 2.75% floating interest subsidy on pre- and post-shipment export credit. This initiative aims to lower borrowing costs and enhance the global competitiveness of micro, small, and medium enterprises, enabling them to access export finance at rates below market levels.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:33:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957bdc24342f77179fbf095_1767358062856.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Secret Oil Move: Weekly Russian Data Request Sparks US Trade Deal Hopes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Secret-Oil-Move-Weekly-Russian-Data-Request-Sparks-US-Trade-Deal-Hopes/6957bd764342f77179fbef47</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Secret-Oil-Move-Weekly-Russian-Data-Request-Sparks-US-Trade-Deal-Hopes/6957bd764342f77179fbef47</guid><description>India is now demanding weekly reports from refiners on their Russian and U.S. oil purchases. This move comes as India aims to finalize a trade deal with the United States, which had previously imposed tariffs due to India's heavy reliance on Russian crude. The data request, prompted by Prime Minister Narendra Modi's office, aims to provide verified figures to Washington, potentially easing trade tensions and leading to a dip in Russian oil imports below one million barrels per day.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:30:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957bd764342f77179fbef46_1767357953769.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>