<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:59:58 +0000</pubDate><item><title>BSE Profit Surges on Derivatives; Valuation, STT Hike Raise Questions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/BSE-Profit-Surges-on-Derivatives-Valuation-STT-Hike-Raise-Questions/698ab813757d40c78184e391</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/BSE-Profit-Surges-on-Derivatives-Valuation-STT-Hike-Raise-Questions/698ab813757d40c78184e391</guid><description>BSE Ltd. delivered a robust Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit jumping 174% year-on-year to ₹602 crore on revenue growth of 62% to ₹1,244 crore. This surge was primarily fueled by increased transaction charges and strong performance in index options trading. Despite the impressive results, BSE's market capitalization of ₹1.21 trillion, coupled with a high P/E ratio of approximately 68.4x, raises valuation concerns. Furthermore, the recent increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives trading by the Union Budget 2026 presents a potential headwind. While Nuvama reiterated a 'Buy' rating and raised its target to ₹3,760, other analysts offer mixed views, and the exchange faces increased competition and regulatory scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:46:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ab813757d40c78184e390_1770698901641.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEPC Secures ₹314 Cr Smart Meter Project, Revenue Surges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEPC-Secures-314-Cr-Smart-Meter-Project-Revenue-Surges/698ab557757d40c78184dcee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEPC-Secures-314-Cr-Smart-Meter-Project-Revenue-Surges/698ab557757d40c78184dcee</guid><description>SEPC Limited has bagged a significant Letter of Intent (LOI) worth ₹313.96 crore from Telecommunications Consultants India Limited (TCIL) for a Smart Prepaid Metering project in Punjab. The company also reported robust financial performance for the nine months ended December 2025, with revenue exceeding the entire previous fiscal year by over 33%. The project, to be executed on a Design, Build, Finance, Own, Operate and Transfer (DBFOOT) basis, aligns with SEPC's strategy for long-term annuity revenue streams. However, a closer look reveals a notable compression in EBITDA margins compared to the previous fiscal year.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:34:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ab557757d40c78184dced.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Carysil's Q3 Profit Surge: Margin Gains Sustainable?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carysils-Q3-Profit-Surge-Margin-Gains-Sustainable/698ab541757d40c78184dc6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carysils-Q3-Profit-Surge-Margin-Gains-Sustainable/698ab541757d40c78184dc6d</guid><description>Carysil Ltd. delivered robust Q3 FY26 earnings, with profits significantly outpacing revenue growth. This performance was primarily fueled by a sharp decline in raw material costs, particularly MMA, and operational leverage, which expanded EBITDA margins to 18.9%. The company also anticipates benefiting from a US tariff reduction, expected to boost realisations from Q4 FY26. Quartz sink volumes surged 27% YoY, though revenue growth lagged due to prior US pricing discounts. Capacity expansions across key segments are underway to support future demand. However, the company's P/E ratio and increasing net debt warrant scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:34:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ab541757d40c78184dc6c_1770698153675.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Varroc Engineering Surges on EV Growth &amp; Record Wins, Eyes Market Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Varroc-Engineering-Surges-on-EV-Growth-and-Record-Wins-Eyes-Market-Share/698ab462757d40c78184d6ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Varroc-Engineering-Surges-on-EV-Growth-and-Record-Wins-Eyes-Market-Share/698ab462757d40c78184d6ba</guid><description>Varroc Engineering reported strong Q3 FY26 results with revenue up 10.2% YoY to ₹2290 Cr. The EV segment posted a remarkable 53% YoY growth, contributing 14.3% to revenues. The company achieved its highest-ever new business wins worth ₹2063.6 Cr in annualized potential, heavily skewed towards EVs. Profit Before Tax (PBT) before JV profits surged 53% YoY to ₹101 Cr, with PBT margins improving significantly. Despite challenges in overseas operations, management provided an aggressive growth outlook and is exploring strategic options for its non-core forging business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:30:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ab462757d40c78184d6b9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MTAR Tech Soars: Record Highs Mask Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/MTAR-Tech-Soars-Record-Highs-Mask-Valuation-Concerns/698ab455757d40c78184d5ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/MTAR-Tech-Soars-Record-Highs-Mask-Valuation-Concerns/698ab455757d40c78184d5ca</guid><description>MTAR Technologies' stock price surged to an all-time high, propelled by a stellar Q3 FY26 performance featuring a 117% year-on-year profit jump and a significant order book valued at over ₹2,394 crore. Analysts remain bullish, maintaining 'BUY' ratings and setting ambitious targets for FY26 and FY27 revenue growth. However, the rapid ascent has pushed the company's valuation metrics, notably its Price-to-Earnings ratio, to exceptionally high levels, raising questions about the sustainability of its current market momentum.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:30:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ab455757d40c78184d5c9_1770698011947.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Star Cement: Expansion Debt Threatens Q3 Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Star-Cement-Expansion-Debt-Threatens-Q3-Gains/698ab3f3757d40c78184d406</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Star-Cement-Expansion-Debt-Threatens-Q3-Gains/698ab3f3757d40c78184d406</guid><description>Star Cement reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue up 22.4% and net profit surging 723%. However, Investec downgraded the stock to 'Sell' with a price target of ₹179, below its 52-week low. The downgrade stems from concerns over the company's aggressive, debt-financed ₹4,800 crore expansion plan into North India, which the brokerage believes may not cover its cost of credit. Management's reduced full-year volume guidance and potential pressure from loss of GST incentives add to the bearish outlook, despite sector tailwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:28:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ab3f3757d40c78184d405.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NMDC Price Hike Amidst Soaring Costs Sparks Investor Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NMDC-Price-Hike-Amidst-Soaring-Costs-Sparks-Investor-Scrutiny/698ab3d9757d40c78184d329</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NMDC-Price-Hike-Amidst-Soaring-Costs-Sparks-Investor-Scrutiny/698ab3d9757d40c78184d329</guid><description>National Mineral Development Corporation (NMDC) has raised iron ore prices by ₹100 per tonne for lumps and fines, effective February 10, 2026. This move comes as the company battles a significant surge in operational expenses, which has led to a sharp contraction in EBITDA margins to 28.2% from 36.1% year-on-year, despite a 16% revenue increase to ₹7,610.8 crore in its December quarter results. The stock reacted with minor declines, reflecting investor concerns over the sustainability of profitability amidst these cost pressures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:28:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ab3d9757d40c78184d328_1770697814816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bata India's Q3 Rally Fueled by Margin Gains, Not Sales Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bata-Indias-Q3-Rally-Fueled-by-Margin-Gains-Not-Sales-Growth/698ab369757d40c78184d197</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bata-Indias-Q3-Rally-Fueled-by-Margin-Gains-Not-Sales-Growth/698ab369757d40c78184d197</guid><description>Bata India's shares saw an 8% jump after reporting December quarter earnings that showcased robust profit growth and margin expansion, even with soft revenue increases. Profit after tax climbed 12.8% to ₹66.1 crore, while EBITDA grew 6.5% to ₹211.9 crore, with margins improving to 22.4%. Management pointed to sustained demand and strong performance from key brands like Hush Puppies and Power, alongside the addition of 27 new franchise stores, signaling a strategic focus on profitability and market reach.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:26:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ab369757d40c78184d196_1770697685293.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bangladesh-US Trade Pact Sparks Indian Textile Export Worries</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Bangladesh-US-Trade-Pact-Sparks-Indian-Textile-Export-Worries/698ab30a757d40c78184cfd8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Bangladesh-US-Trade-Pact-Sparks-Indian-Textile-Export-Worries/698ab30a757d40c78184cfd8</guid><description>Bangladesh secured limited zero-duty US market access for garments made with US cotton/fibers. This development raises concerns for Indian cotton and yarn exporters, as Bangladesh is a major buyer of Indian raw materials. While experts predict a sentiment-driven reaction, integrated Indian textile players with strong cost controls are seen as better positioned to navigate potential shifts in the regional supply chain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:24:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ab30a757d40c78184cfd7_1770697620211.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GPIL Mines Expanded Capacity to 6 MTPA, Securing Key Raw Material Supply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GPIL-Mines-Expanded-Capacity-to-6-MTPA-Securing-Key-Raw-Material-Supply/698ab2ea757d40c78184cecc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GPIL-Mines-Expanded-Capacity-to-6-MTPA-Securing-Key-Raw-Material-Supply/698ab2ea757d40c78184cecc</guid><description>Godawari Power and Ispat Limited (GPIL) has secured the 'Consent to Operate' for its Ari Dongri Iron Ore Mines expansion, boosting capacity to 6 MTPA from 2.35 MTPA. This crucial approval, effective immediately from February 10, 2026, follows environmental clearance and significantly enhances GPIL's raw material supply chain. As an integrated player, this move is poised to improve cost efficiencies and bolster downstream production capabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:24:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ab2ea757d40c78184cecb_1770697570304.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sensex, Nifty Surge on Trade Deal; Capex Boom Fuels Growth Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Nifty-Surge-on-Trade-Deal-Capex-Boom-Fuels-Growth-Hopes/698ab019757d40c78184cc31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Nifty-Surge-on-Trade-Deal-Capex-Boom-Fuels-Growth-Hopes/698ab019757d40c78184cc31</guid><description>Indian benchmark indices, Nifty50 and BSE Sensex, opened higher Tuesday, extending gains post the India-US trade deal announcement. Nifty50 surpassed 25,900, while BSE Sensex climbed over 150 points. Experts cite strengthening tailwinds, improved economic growth prospects driven by a significant turnaround in private capital expenditure and rising bank credit, projecting GDP growth above 7% and corporate earnings growth exceeding 16%. This optimism, amplified by retail investor enthusiasm for smallcaps, supports market resilience.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:12:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ab019757d40c78184cc30_1770696838883.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Websol Energy Surges 77% Revenue, Plans ₹3000Cr Capex Amid Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Websol-Energy-Surges-77percent-Revenue-Plans-3000Cr-Capex-Amid-Margin-Squeeze/698aafa1757d40c78184cae1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Websol-Energy-Surges-77percent-Revenue-Plans-3000Cr-Capex-Amid-Margin-Squeeze/698aafa1757d40c78184cae1</guid><description>Websol Energy System Limited reported a robust Q3FY26, with revenue leaping 77.2% YoY to INR 261 Cr and PAT growing 56.2% YoY to INR 65 Cr. Despite a YoY margin compression in Q3, 9MFY26 saw EBITDA margins at 43.6% and PAT margins at 35.9%. The company outlined an aggressive expansion strategy, planning over 5.2 GW cell and 4.5 GW module capacity by 2028, including a 2 GW Topcon integrated line, backed by over ₹3,000 Cr in capex. Debt ratios significantly improved, with Debt-to-Equity at 0.29x.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:10:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aafa1757d40c78184cae0_1770696733910.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Citi Cautions Lenskart Valuation; Neutral Stance Dampens Rally Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Citi-Cautions-Lenskart-Valuation-Neutral-Stance-Dampens-Rally-Hopes/698aad4a757d40c78184c92b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Citi-Cautions-Lenskart-Valuation-Neutral-Stance-Dampens-Rally-Hopes/698aad4a757d40c78184c92b</guid><description>Brokerage firm Citi has initiated coverage on Lenskart Solutions with a 'Neutral' rating and a ₹500 price target, signaling a modest 8% upside potential from current levels. While acknowledging Lenskart's transformative impact on India's eyewear industry and its robust growth outlook, Citi believes the stock's current valuation already prices in significant medium-term gains. Key risks include supply chain dependencies, competitive pressures, and potential deterioration in store economics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:00:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aad4a757d40c78184c92a_1770696078266.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Modernizes Kisan Credit Card for Agri-Tech Era</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/RBI-Modernizes-Kisan-Credit-Card-for-Agri-Tech-Era/698aacd3757d40c78184c7cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/RBI-Modernizes-Kisan-Credit-Card-for-Agri-Tech-Era/698aacd3757d40c78184c7cb</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is implementing a significant upgrade to the Kisan Credit Card (KCC) scheme, moving towards a more robust framework for agricultural finance. Key revisions include extending the card's validity to six years, integrating expenses for modern agri-technology, and linking credit limits to official cultivation cost scales. These changes aim to enhance farmer coverage, streamline operations, and better align farm credit with contemporary agricultural practices and escalating input expenses. South Indian Bank's CFO indicated alignment with this strategy, highlighting the sector's focus on rural credit.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:58:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aacd3757d40c78184c7ca_1770696007408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lupin Buys US Certainty: $90M Settlement Secures Mirabegron Market Access</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Buys-US-Certainty-90M-Settlement-Secures-Mirabegron-Market-Access/698aab03757d40c78184c5b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Buys-US-Certainty-90M-Settlement-Secures-Mirabegron-Market-Access/698aab03757d40c78184c5b1</guid><description>Lupin Ltd. has concluded its patent dispute with Astellas Pharma, agreeing to a $90 million settlement. This payment resolves litigation and guarantees Lupin's continued marketing and sales of Mirabegron in the US market. The move provides significant strategic clarity, allowing Lupin to focus on growth rather than protracted legal battles. While substantial, the expenditure secures a key revenue stream in the competitive overactive bladder treatment market, where Mirabegron holds a significant share.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:50:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aab03757d40c78184c5b0_1770695596281.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Surges 22% From Lows, Gold Firm Above $5,070 Amid Fed Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-22percent-From-Lows-Gold-Firm-Above-5070-Amid-Fed-Jitters/698aaaef757d40c78184c49a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-22percent-From-Lows-Gold-Firm-Above-5070-Amid-Fed-Jitters/698aaaef757d40c78184c49a</guid><description>Spot silver has recovered nearly 22% from recent lows of $67 per ounce, trading near $82 as industrial demand props up prices. Gold remains steady above $5,070 per ounce, buoyed by central bank purchases and fiscal risk concerns. Market attention now shifts to crucial US jobs and inflation data, which could influence Federal Reserve policy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:50:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aaaef757d40c78184c499_1770695516640.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lupin Pays $90M for US Mirabegron Sales, Strains Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Pays-90M-for-US-Mirabegron-Sales-Strains-Margins/698aaa9e757d40c78184c2ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Pays-90M-for-US-Mirabegron-Sales-Strains-Margins/698aaa9e757d40c78184c2ef</guid><description>Lupin Ltd. has resolved a patent infringement dispute with Astellas Pharma, agreeing to a $90 million settlement to continue selling its generic Mirabegron in the United States. The payment includes a $75 million upfront sum and per-unit licensing fees through September 2027. This agreement averts further litigation, providing market certainty for the bladder disorder drug.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:48:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aaa9e757d40c78184c2ee_1770695509020.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market Eyes Consolidation; Specific Stocks Poised for Activity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Market-Eyes-Consolidation-Specific-Stocks-Poised-for-Activity/698aaa7c757d40c78184c20f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Market-Eyes-Consolidation-Specific-Stocks-Poised-for-Activity/698aaa7c757d40c78184c20f</guid><description>Indian equity markets are poised for a flat opening, expected to consolidate as investors await fresh catalysts following the Indo-US trade agreement. While foreign portfolio investor (FPI) inflows and a stable rupee provide a cautious optimistic undertone, derivatives data suggests a range-bound trading session with defined support and resistance levels. Specific stocks like TCS, CUB, Marico, GRSE, and HAL are anticipated to see increased activity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:48:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aaa7c757d40c78184c20e_1770695400221.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HUL Q3 Results: Demerger Shadow, GST Woes Cloud Modest Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Q3-Results-Demerger-Shadow-GST-Woes-Cloud-Modest-Growth/698aa650757d40c78184b75b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Q3-Results-Demerger-Shadow-GST-Woes-Cloud-Modest-Growth/698aa650757d40c78184b75b</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever is set to report its Q3FY26 results on February 12, 2026, with analysts anticipating a slight uptick in net profit and revenue. However, the performance is projected to be nuanced, reflecting the complexities of the recently demerged ice cream business and the residual effects of GST disruptions on October sales. Underlying volume growth is expected to remain subdued, while competitive pressures and evolving consumer preferences present ongoing challenges. Brokerage sentiment remains cautiously optimistic, with a 'Buy' consensus and an average price target suggesting modest upside potential.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:30:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aa650757d40c78184b75a_1770694375890.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Inflation Data Overshadowed by New CPI Series Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Inflation-Data-Overshadowed-by-New-CPI-Series-Uncertainty/698aa642757d40c78184b6c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Inflation-Data-Overshadowed-by-New-CPI-Series-Uncertainty/698aa642757d40c78184b6c1</guid><description>India's January inflation is projected at 2.4%, returning to the RBI's target band, but a new CPI series with a significantly lower food weight introduces opacity. The revised methodology, intended to reduce volatility, may mask underlying demand pressures, complicating the Reserve Bank of India's assessment of price stability and future policy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:30:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aa642757d40c78184b6c0_1770694317156.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NMDC Hikes Iron Ore Prices; Baila Lump at ₹4,700/Ton</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NMDC-Hikes-Iron-Ore-Prices-Baila-Lump-at-4700Ton/698aa54e757d40c78184b50d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NMDC-Hikes-Iron-Ore-Prices-Baila-Lump-at-4700Ton/698aa54e757d40c78184b50d</guid><description>State-owned miner NMDC Limited has announced revised prices for its iron ore products, effective February 10, 2026. Baila Lump (65.5%) is now priced at ₹4,700 per ton, and Baila Fines (64%) at ₹4,000 per ton. These FOR rates exclude a host of charges, including royalty, taxes, and GST, necessitating careful financial assessment by investors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:26:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aa54e757d40c78184b50c_1770694079765.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ACME Solar Secures 220 MW MP Project with Battery Storage</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ACME-Solar-Secures-220-MW-MP-Project-with-Battery-Storage/698aa4e4757d40c78184b36d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ACME-Solar-Secures-220-MW-MP-Project-with-Battery-Storage/698aa4e4757d40c78184b36d</guid><description>ACME Solar Holdings Limited announced receiving a Letter of Award (LOA) from Rewa Ultra Mega Solar Limited (RUMSL) for a 220 MW Solar with Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) project in Madhya Pradesh's Morena Solar Park. The project includes a 25-year Power Purchase Agreement (PPA) at Rs. 2.764 per unit, with a Scheduled Commercial Operation Date (SCOD) of December 31, 2027. This significant award enhances ACME Solar's extensive 8,071 MW renewable energy portfolio.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:24:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698aa4e4757d40c78184b36c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cipla's US Subsidiary Gets 2 Observations in FDA Inspection</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ciplas-US-Subsidiary-Gets-2-Observations-in-FDA-Inspection/698aa4d7757d40c78184b256</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ciplas-US-Subsidiary-Gets-2-Observations-in-FDA-Inspection/698aa4d7757d40c78184b256</guid><description>Cipla Limited's wholly owned US subsidiary, InvaGen Pharmaceuticals, Inc., located in Hauppauge, New York, received 2 inspectional observations in Form 483 following a USFDA Pre-Approval Inspection conducted between February 2nd and February 9th, 2026. The company has affirmed its commitment to working with the USFDA to address these observations promptly and comprehensively within the stipulated timeframe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:24:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aa4d7757d40c78184b255_1770693952692.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Tea Exports Hit Record ₹8,488 Cr Amidst Rupee Gain; Quality Scrutiny Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Tea-Exports-Hit-Record-8488-Cr-Amidst-Rupee-Gain-Quality-Scrutiny-Looms/698aa0a2757d40c78184afb8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Tea-Exports-Hit-Record-8488-Cr-Amidst-Rupee-Gain-Quality-Scrutiny-Looms/698aa0a2757d40c78184afb8</guid><description>Indian tea exports achieved a record value of ₹8,488.43 crore in 2025, a 18.4% increase year-on-year, propelled by a depreciating rupee and robust shipments. Exporters secured an average price exceeding ₹300 per kilogram for the first time. While North India saw significant volume growth, South India's exports declined. Simultaneously, the industry grapples with issues of inferior tea imports and the looming impact of stricter European Union pesticide regulations, prompting new import controls.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:06:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aa0a2757d40c78184afb7_1770692883540.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axis Bank Eyes MFI Acquisition: Synergies vs. Integration Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-Eyes-MFI-Acquisition-Synergies-vs-Integration-Risks/698a9fb4757d40c78184ae0f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-Eyes-MFI-Acquisition-Synergies-vs-Integration-Risks/698a9fb4757d40c78184ae0f</guid><description>Reports indicate Axis Bank is evaluating the acquisition of CreditAccess Grameen, a move lauded by CLSA for its strategic synergies. However, the deal faces scrutiny over CreditAccess Grameen's high valuation, the complexities of integrating an MFI business, and prevailing regulatory pressures within the microfinance sector. Axis Bank's prior acquisition of Citibank's retail operations offers a precedent for integration timelines and costs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:02:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a9fb4757d40c78184ae0e_1770692679197.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bandhan Multi-Asset Fund Hits ₹2.7K Cr AUM at 2-Year Mark</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Bandhan-Multi-Asset-Fund-Hits-27K-Cr-AUM-at-2-Year-Mark/698a9f4f757d40c78184ac4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Bandhan-Multi-Asset-Fund-Hits-27K-Cr-AUM-at-2-Year-Mark/698a9f4f757d40c78184ac4f</guid><description>Bandhan Multi Asset Allocation Fund celebrates its second anniversary, now managing over ₹2,700 crore in assets. An initial ₹10,000 investment has appreciated by 40%. The fund employs a diversified strategy with 50% equity, 15% precious metals, 15% arbitrage, 10% international equity, and 10% fixed income. While performance has been strong, analysts caution about potential underperformance in robust equity market rallies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:00:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a9f4f757d40c78184ac4e_1770692578253.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Engineered Addiction Trial Rocks Meta, Google; Section 230 Faces Unprecedented Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Engineered-Addiction-Trial-Rocks-Meta-Google-Section-230-Faces-Unprecedented-Test/698a9f3c757d40c78184ab81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Engineered-Addiction-Trial-Rocks-Meta-Google-Section-230-Faces-Unprecedented-Test/698a9f3c757d40c78184ab81</guid><description>Opening statements in Los Angeles have launched a pivotal trial against Meta and Google, alleging their social media platforms were intentionally engineered to addict children. Plaintiffs contend internal documents reveal a deliberate strategy to exploit user vulnerabilities for profit, bypassing crucial legal protections like Section 230. This case, a bellwether for thousands of similar suits, could force fundamental changes in how Big Tech operates and prioritizes user safety, with significant implications for their multi-trillion dollar market valuations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a9f3c757d40c78184ab80_1770692519114.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Earnings: Auto, FMCG, Healthcare Face Key Q3 Results</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Earnings-Auto-FMCG-Healthcare-Face-Key-Q3-Results/698a98b9757d40c781849ad0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Earnings-Auto-FMCG-Healthcare-Face-Key-Q3-Results/698a98b9757d40c781849ad0</guid><description>As India's third-quarter earnings season approaches, investors are keenly observing Eicher Motors, Britannia Industries, and Apollo Hospitals Enterprise. These companies, representing key sectors, will report financial results amid shifting market dynamics. Eicher Motors faces automotive sector compliance costs, Britannia grapples with input inflation in consumer staples, and Apollo Hospitals navigates valuation concerns within a growing healthcare industry. Past performance indicates margin pressures and varied market reactions, setting a cautious tone for the upcoming disclosures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 02:32:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a98b9757d40c781849acf_1770690882361.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC Balanced Advantage Fund: Long-Term SIPs Shine, But Volatility Rules</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/HDFC-Balanced-Advantage-Fund-Long-Term-SIPs-Shine-But-Volatility-Rules/698a98ab757d40c781849928</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/HDFC-Balanced-Advantage-Fund-Long-Term-SIPs-Shine-But-Volatility-Rules/698a98ab757d40c781849928</guid><description>A ₹10,000 monthly SIP in HDFC Balanced Advantage Fund since 1994 has grown to ₹15.89 crore, showcasing strong long-term potential. However, the fund's dynamic asset allocation strategy creates significant performance divergence across shorter timeframes and lump-sum investments, necessitating a careful assessment of its 'Very High' risk profile and market-dependent returns.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 02:32:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a98ab757d40c781849927_1770690863513.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India F&amp;B PE Frenzy: Quick Commerce Fuels $10B+ Deals, Analyst Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-FandB-PE-Frenzy-Quick-Commerce-Fuels-10B-Deals-Analyst-Caution/698a9655757d40c78184847e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-FandB-PE-Frenzy-Quick-Commerce-Fuels-10B-Deals-Analyst-Caution/698a9655757d40c78184847e</guid><description>Private equity investors are making significant bets on India's food and beverage sector, accelerating deal activity. Valuations are soaring, exemplified by Haldiram Snacks Food hitting $10 billion. The surge is fueled by a paradigm shift in scalability via quick commerce and evolving preferences of millennials and Gen Z. However, recent PE market data indicates a slowdown in deal volume for late 2025, and the sky-high valuations, particularly for publicly listed entities like Devyani International, are drawing scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 02:22:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a9655757d40c78184847d_1770690256875.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Auto Sector Surges: TVS, Maruti Lead Charge Amid Evolving Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Auto-Sector-Surges-TVS-Maruti-Lead-Charge-Amid-Evolving-Market/698a9295757d40c781848252</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Auto-Sector-Surges-TVS-Maruti-Lead-Charge-Amid-Evolving-Market/698a9295757d40c781848252</guid><description>India's automotive sector began 2026 with robust, broad-based momentum across PVs, 2Ws, CVs, and tractors. January wholesales reflected strong demand, aided by lean inventories. TVS Motor and Maruti Suzuki are key beneficiaries, though competitive pressures and input costs are rising. TVS Motor shows consistent market share gains and projected growth, while Maruti Suzuki maintains PV leadership. Analysts see sustained demand, but valuations and margin risks require careful monitoring.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 02:06:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a9295757d40c781848251_1770689315255.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSE Ltd.: Surge in Revenue Masks Margin Squeeze, Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BSE-Ltd-Surge-in-Revenue-Masks-Margin-Squeeze-Valuation-Concerns/698a9222757d40c7818480e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BSE-Ltd-Surge-in-Revenue-Masks-Margin-Squeeze-Valuation-Concerns/698a9222757d40c7818480e9</guid><description>BSE Ltd. posted robust Q3 FY26 results with revenue climbing 62% year-on-year to ₹1,244 crore and net profit surging 174% to ₹602 crore, largely due to a significant rise in transaction charges. However, operating margins narrowed to 62.5% from 64.7% in the prior quarter, influenced by rising employee expenses. Despite strong recent stock performance, BSE's market capitalization of ₹1.21 trillion is supported by a P/E ratio of approximately 68.4x, raising valuation concerns against its larger competitor, NSE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 02:04:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a9222757d40c7818480e8_1770689182966.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPFO's UPI Push: Convenience Meets Liquidity Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFOs-UPI-Push-Convenience-Meets-Liquidity-Risk/698a9053757d40c781847e69</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFOs-UPI-Push-Convenience-Meets-Liquidity-Risk/698a9053757d40c781847e69</guid><description>The Employees' Provident Fund Organisation (EPFO) is set to launch a mobile application by April enabling instant Provident Fund (PF) withdrawals via UPI. This digital upgrade, part of its EPFO 3.0 initiative, aims to streamline the historically cumbersome process for its over 7 crore members. While promising unprecedented speed and convenience, this shift raises critical questions about managing the ₹31 trillion corpus and balancing immediate liquidity needs against the fundamental mandate of long-term retirement savings growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:56:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a9053757d40c781847e68_1770688694259.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Surge Fuels Tech Rally; Silver Shines Amid Mixed Economic Signals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Surge-Fuels-Tech-Rally-Silver-Shines-Amid-Mixed-Economic-Signals/698a903e757d40c781847dce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Surge-Fuels-Tech-Rally-Silver-Shines-Amid-Mixed-Economic-Signals/698a903e757d40c781847dce</guid><description>Global markets extended gains on February 10, 2026, propelled by a significant recovery in technology stocks, particularly those focused on Artificial Intelligence. US indices, including the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq, climbed, with the Dow Jones setting a new record. Asian markets also posted gains, with Japan's Nikkei 225 reaching all-time highs following a landmark election victory. Indian markets are poised for a higher open, buoyed by a preliminary India-US trade agreement. Amidst this, silver prices experienced a substantial surge, while gold saw modest gains, and crude oil futures showed a slight uptick despite a bearish long-term forecast.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:56:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a903e757d40c781847dcd_1770688681365.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FMCG Firms Shift to Value: Premiumization Hits Affordability Wall</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Firms-Shift-to-Value-Premiumization-Hits-Affordability-Wall/698a8fc2757d40c781847c3c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Firms-Shift-to-Value-Premiumization-Hits-Affordability-Wall/698a8fc2757d40c781847c3c</guid><description>Fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) companies are recalibrating strategies, de-emphasizing premium pitches for value-driven sales. While premiumization remains a long-term goal, recent execution shows volume recovery powered by entry-level packs and promotions, not premium upselling. Companies like Marico, Tata Consumer Products, and Godrej Consumer Products are adapting, focusing on affordability to maintain volume. Analysts suggest this shift reflects current economic realities, where affordability, not aspirational buying, dictates consumer choices, posing challenges to historical margin expansion models.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:54:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a8fc2757d40c781847c3b_1770688565936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Q3 FY26: Europe Fuels 8.4% Revenue Growth, API Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Q3-FY26-Europe-Fuels-84percent-Revenue-Growth-API-Dips/698a8c77757d40c781847a05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Q3-FY26-Europe-Fuels-84percent-Revenue-Growth-API-Dips/698a8c77757d40c781847a05</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma reported Q3FY26 revenue of ₹8,646 Cr, up 8.4% YoY, propelled by strong European sales and ARV segment growth. EBITDA rose 9.0% to ₹1,773 Cr with margins at 20.5%. The US market remained stable, though the API business saw a 4.3% decline. The company highlighted progress in its biosimilars pipeline and US product approvals, eyeing future growth despite API challenges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:40:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a8c77757d40c781847a04_1770687803023.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Surges on Iran Tensions; Supply Surplus Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-Surges-on-Iran-Tensions-Supply-Surplus-Looms/698a8c22757d40c781847882</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-Surges-on-Iran-Tensions-Supply-Surplus-Looms/698a8c22757d40c781847882</guid><description>Oil prices ascended on heightened geopolitical tensions involving Iran and the Strait of Hormuz, pushing WTI above $64 and Brent near $69. However, global oil demand growth forecasts for 2026 remain subdued, with the IEA predicting a substantial market surplus that may cap upward price momentum. Major energy firms' valuations present a mixed picture, and the broader energy sector ETF indicates overbought conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:38:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698a8c22757d40c781847881.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ramco Cements: Asset Sales Mask Margin Squeeze Amid Cost Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ramco-Cements-Asset-Sales-Mask-Margin-Squeeze-Amid-Cost-Headwinds/698a8c07757d40c781847770</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ramco-Cements-Asset-Sales-Mask-Margin-Squeeze-Amid-Cost-Headwinds/698a8c07757d40c781847770</guid><description>Ramco Cements reported a significant Q3 FY26 profit jump, largely driven by ₹506 crore from non-core asset sales. However, this masks underlying operational pressures: cement prices fell 6% QoQ, steeper than anticipated, impacting revenue growth to a modest 6.2% YoY. EBITDA remained flat, and operating margins compressed to 13.3% from 14% year-on-year. Elevated fuel costs and a new ₹160/tonne limestone tax in Tamil Nadu further pressured raw material expenses, contributing to an 11% EBITDA miss against analyst estimates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:38:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a8c07757d40c78184776f_1770687633930.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Giant's Capex vs. Chemical's Soaring P/E: A Tale of Two Industries</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Steel-Giants-Capex-vs-Chemicals-Soaring-PE-A-Tale-of-Two-Industries/698a8765757d40c78184745d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Steel-Giants-Capex-vs-Chemicals-Soaring-PE-A-Tale-of-Two-Industries/698a8765757d40c78184745d</guid><description>JSW Steel's Q3 FY26 saw revenue climb and volumes increase, yet EBITDA margins faced sequential pressure. Aggressive capacity expansion plans requiring significant capital expenditure are underway, financed partly by stake monetization. Meanwhile, Acutaas Chemicals reported robust revenue and profit growth driven by its Contract Development and Manufacturing Organization (CDMO) segment, raising forward guidance. However, the company's valuation multiples stand exceptionally high compared to industry peers, and its nascent specialty chemical ventures carry inherent risks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:18:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698a8765757d40c78184745c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asia Hits Record Highs as Alphabet Eyes 100-Year Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Asia-Hits-Record-Highs-as-Alphabet-Eyes-100-Year-Debt/698a8752757d40c7818473a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Asia-Hits-Record-Highs-as-Alphabet-Eyes-100-Year-Debt/698a8752757d40c7818473a2</guid><description>Asian markets achieved record highs Tuesday, propelled by a U.S. tech stock recovery and easing AI trade concerns. Japan's Nikkei 225 index reached an all-time high, mirroring global optimism. Alphabet Inc. is making a significant move into long-dated debt with plans for a rare 100-year bond to finance its substantial AI infrastructure investments. Investors await crucial U.S. jobs and inflation data, which will heavily influence Federal Reserve rate policy expectations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:18:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a8752757d40c7818473a1_1770686407314.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>