<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:34:12 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Global Beer Giants Pivot to India Amidst European Contraction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Global-Beer-Giants-Pivot-to-India-Amidst-European-Contraction/69987c5f057e346edab45b93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Global-Beer-Giants-Pivot-to-India-Amidst-European-Contraction/69987c5f057e346edab45b93</guid><description>Soufflet Malt is investing €100 million in a new Indian production facility while closing European plants, mirroring a global shift as Europe's beer market stagnates due to demographic and health trends. India, with its rapidly growing young population, urbanization, and favorable policies including tax reforms and the EU-India FTA, presents a critical growth engine. Carlsberg is exploring an IPO in India, designating it its top growth market, while Heineken doubles down on its UBL subsidiary. This strategic rebalancing highlights India's emergence as the pivotal frontier for international brewers seeking volume and value.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:23:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69987c5f057e346edab45b92.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US GDP Slows Sharply; Sticky Inflation &amp; AI Boom Defy Downturn</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-GDP-Slows-Sharply-Sticky-Inflation-and-AI-Boom-Defy-Downturn/69987ac8057e346edab45a81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-GDP-Slows-Sharply-Sticky-Inflation-and-AI-Boom-Defy-Downturn/69987ac8057e346edab45a81</guid><description>The U.S. economy's expansion decelerated sharply to a 1.4% annualized rate in the fourth quarter of 2025, significantly underperforming expectations. This slowdown was primarily attributed to a record-length government shutdown, reduced government spending, and a cooling in consumer outlays. However, robust business investment in artificial intelligence and persistent core inflation above the Federal Reserve's target indicate underlying economic dynamics that complicate the growth narrative.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:16:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69987ac8057e346edab45a80_1771600760389.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Midwest Gold Plans ₹200 Cr Rare Earth Magnet Venture Amidst Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Midwest-Gold-Plans-200-Cr-Rare-Earth-Magnet-Venture-Amidst-Losses/69987996057e346edab45976</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Midwest-Gold-Plans-200-Cr-Rare-Earth-Magnet-Venture-Amidst-Losses/69987996057e346edab45976</guid><description>Midwest Gold Limited is raising ₹200 Crore via a preferential share issue at ₹2,000 per share to fund a new Rare Earth Magnet (REM) manufacturing facility. This marks a significant strategic pivot for the company, historically involved in granite and gold mining, as it seeks to enter the high-demand REM market, though it faces challenges with recent losses and a premium issue price.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:11:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69987996057e346edab45975_1771600450310.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHPC Approves ₹5,700 Crore for New J&amp;K Hydro Power Projects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NHPC-Approves-5700-Crore-for-New-JandK-Hydro-Power-Projects/6998798a057e346edab4595c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NHPC-Approves-5700-Crore-for-New-JandK-Hydro-Power-Projects/6998798a057e346edab4595c</guid><description>NHPC's Board of Directors has approved an investment of approximately ₹5,702.91 Crore for two new hydroelectric projects in Jammu &amp; Kashmir: Uri-I Stage-II (240 MW) and Dulhasti Stage-II (260 MW). These projects are set to boost the company's renewable energy capacity, subject to final agreements with the Jammu &amp; Kashmir government.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:11:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998798a057e346edab4595b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Rebound Brewing as Non-Ferrous Faces Price Puzzles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Rebound-Brewing-as-Non-Ferrous-Faces-Price-Puzzles/6998774d057e346edab45840</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Rebound-Brewing-as-Non-Ferrous-Faces-Price-Puzzles/6998774d057e346edab45840</guid><description>The Indian metals sector is experiencing a split outlook. Steel producers, challenged by weak Q3FY26 prices, are showing signs of a rebound driven by delayed safeguard duties on imports and firming domestic demand, with prices recovering significantly. In contrast, non-ferrous metals, while buoyed by global supply constraints and a weaker dollar, face headwinds from market surpluses in lead and zinc, alongside specific company challenges like restructuring and operational disruptions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:01:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998774d057e346edab4583f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fiscal Tightening: Growth vs. Debt Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Tightening-Growth-vs-Debt-Pressure/699876c4057e346edab457d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Tightening-Growth-vs-Debt-Pressure/699876c4057e346edab457d1</guid><description>India's Union government plans to significantly lower net market borrowings to 3% of GDP by FY27, a move intended to bolster private sector credit availability and ease financial market pressures. While this aligns with a post-pandemic fiscal consolidation strategy and follows S&amp;P's 'BBB' sovereign rating upgrade, persistent revenue shortfalls, escalating interest payment burdens, and ambitious disinvestment targets pose substantial risks to achieving these fiscal targets without compromising growth. Bond yields remain sensitive to borrowing fears, highlighting the delicate balancing act ahead.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:59:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699876c4057e346edab457d0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bloom Energy: AI Boom Fuels Valuation Surge, But Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bloom-Energy-AI-Boom-Fuels-Valuation-Surge-But-Risks-Loom/69987538057e346edab45660</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bloom-Energy-AI-Boom-Fuels-Valuation-Surge-But-Risks-Loom/69987538057e346edab45660</guid><description>Bloom Energy's stock has surged on demand for its on-site power solutions amid AI data center grid limitations. The company reports strong revenue growth and improving margins. However, its valuation appears stretched, with significant analyst skepticism about long-term projections and competitive threats. Investors face a stark choice between betting on sustained high growth or acknowledging potential overvaluation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:52:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69987538057e346edab4565f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>France's Tech Sovereignty Push Faces Structural Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Frances-Tech-Sovereignty-Push-Faces-Structural-Hurdles/6998751d057e346edab45649</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Frances-Tech-Sovereignty-Push-Faces-Structural-Hurdles/6998751d057e346edab45649</guid><description>French President Emmanuel Macron has articulated a strategy to elevate France and Europe's standing in global technology, aiming for leadership in AI and quantum computing. This vision seeks to counter US and Chinese dominance by fostering 'strategic autonomy.' However, the ambition is tempered by significant structural disadvantages including a persistent capital deficit compared to international rivals, a complex and often burdensome regulatory environment, and challenges in scaling homegrown technological champions like Mistral AI. The success of this sovereignty push hinges on overcoming these deep-seated impediments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:52:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998751d057e346edab45648_1771599304249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Disinvestment Sparks Hope, Faces Evolving Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PSU-Disinvestment-Sparks-Hope-Faces-Evolving-Challenges/699874a2057e346edab455de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PSU-Disinvestment-Sparks-Hope-Faces-Evolving-Challenges/699874a2057e346edab455de</guid><description>India aims to raise ₹80,000 crore through disinvestment and asset monetization, injecting optimism into public sector stocks following market volatility. While historical reforms like Hindustan Zinc and VSNL privatization yielded substantial value, current PSU divestment faces a more intricate landscape. Sustained gains will depend on deep operational reforms and navigating heightened competition, not just asset sales. The market watches for execution beyond ambitious targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:50:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699874a2057e346edab455dd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Investors Shift Capital to Global Assets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Investors-Shift-Capital-to-Global-Assets/69987191057e346edab45488</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Investors-Shift-Capital-to-Global-Assets/69987191057e346edab45488</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India data shows a marked shift in outward remittances, with total outflows moderating 4.12% to $21.36 billion in April-December FY26, driven by lower travel and education spending. Conversely, overseas investments in equity and debt surged 89.10%, alongside significant rises in property and deposit remittances. This indicates a strategic reallocation by Indian individuals towards global diversification and yield-seeking.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:37:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69987191057e346edab45487.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NRI Deposits Reallocate: FCNR(B) Slumps as NRIs Shift Funds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NRI-Deposits-Reallocate-FCNRB-Slumps-as-NRIs-Shift-Funds/699870a9057e346edab45308</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NRI-Deposits-Reallocate-FCNRB-Slumps-as-NRIs-Shift-Funds/699870a9057e346edab45308</guid><description>The flow of money from Non-Resident Indians (NRIs) into Indian deposit schemes fell by 15.97% to $11.20 billion between April–December 2025 compared to the previous year. This overall decline was significantly influenced by a steep drop in Foreign Currency Non-Resident (FCNR) deposits, which plunged to $2.04 billion from $6.46 billion. Conversely, Non-Resident External (NRE) and Non-Resident Ordinary (NRO) deposits demonstrated resilience, attracting $5.06 billion and $4.10 billion respectively, contributing to a total outstanding balance of $169.27 billion. This suggests a strategic reallocation of funds by NRIs rather than a complete withdrawal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:33:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699870a9057e346edab45307_1771598232059.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Retail Surge: Sebi Fortifies Defenses Amidst Investor Flood</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Indias-Retail-Surge-Sebi-Fortifies-Defenses-Amidst-Investor-Flood/699870a7057e346edab452f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Indias-Retail-Surge-Sebi-Fortifies-Defenses-Amidst-Investor-Flood/699870a7057e346edab452f1</guid><description>India's retail investor numbers have surged past 140 million, prompting the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) to intensify its efforts against fraud and mis-selling. Sebi Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey highlighted new verification tools like 'Sebi Check' and mandated UPI handle structures designed to combat escalating cyber frauds. Despite technological advancements, a significant gap persists between basic investor awareness and the understanding required for informed market participation. Sebi is also directing stock exchanges to maintain authorized broker lists and actively monitoring digital platforms for misleading content.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:33:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699870a7057e346edab452f0_1771598219060.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Probes UPI Autopay Flaws, Digital Trust at Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Probes-UPI-Autopay-Flaws-Digital-Trust-at-Stake/699870a6057e346edab452da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Probes-UPI-Autopay-Flaws-Digital-Trust-at-Stake/699870a6057e346edab452da</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is directing the National Payments Corporation of India to investigate a surge in UPI Autopay complaints, including unauthorized debits and difficulties canceling mandates, which began surfacing late 2025. NPCI convened stakeholder meetings in December to address potential design or flow gaps contributing to user frustration and potential erosion of trust in India's leading digital payment system. This probe arrives as UPI Autopay has seen exponential growth, now commanding a significant share of recurring transactions, and amidst broader regulatory efforts to bolster security and transparency in the fintech landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:33:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699870a6057e346edab452d9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Intervention Surges: Rupee Under Pressure, REER Weakens</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Intervention-Surges-Rupee-Under-Pressure-REER-Weakens/699870a6057e346edab452c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Intervention-Surges-Rupee-Under-Pressure-REER-Weakens/699870a6057e346edab452c3</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India intensified its foreign exchange market intervention in December, net selling $10 billion, a slight increase from November's $9.7 billion. This aggressive stance, characterized by buying $18.3 billion and selling $28.3 billion, aims to manage currency volatility. Despite these efforts, the net short dollar position in the rupee forward market narrowed to $62.35 billion by year-end. Concurrently, the Real Effective Exchange Rate (REER) of the rupee declined to 94.76 in January 2026, suggesting potential support for export competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:33:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699870a6057e346edab452c2_1771598116106.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Western Carriers Logs 14.5% Volume Jump; Margins Dip as DFC Nears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Western-Carriers-Logs-145percent-Volume-Jump-Margins-Dip-as-DFC-Nears/699870a1057e346edab452ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Western-Carriers-Logs-145percent-Volume-Jump-Margins-Dip-as-DFC-Nears/699870a1057e346edab452ac</guid><description>Western Carriers India Limited reported a strong 14.5% volume growth in Q3 FY26, reaching INR 478 crores in revenue. However, gross margins contracted by 200 basis points to 12%, and operating cash flow remained subdued due to higher working capital needs. Management sees the upcoming completion of the Western Dedicated Freight Corridor (DFC) by March 2026 as a key catalyst and aims to balance its revenue mix away from metals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:33:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699870a1057e346edab452ab.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Denta Water Grows 30%, But FY26 Revenue Target Now Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Denta-Water-Grows-30percent-But-FY26-Revenue-Target-Now-Looms/69986ebf057e346edab4510b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Denta-Water-Grows-30percent-But-FY26-Revenue-Target-Now-Looms/69986ebf057e346edab4510b</guid><description>Denta Water and Infra Solutions reported robust 30.8% year-on-year revenue growth for the first nine months of FY26, reaching Rs. 1,950.67 million. However, the company acknowledged it will likely miss its full-year revenue target of Rs. 300 crore, now projecting a 20-25% increase. Management cited project timing, delayed government payments, and monsoon disruptions for a Q3 slowdown. Investors are watching potential working capital stretches and collection cycles closely, even as the company maintains a healthy order book of over Rs. 8,400 million.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:25:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69986ebf057e346edab4510a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FDI Faces Capital Flight Pressure Amid Record Outflows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FDI-Faces-Capital-Flight-Pressure-Amid-Record-Outflows/69986e7b057e346edab45092</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FDI-Faces-Capital-Flight-Pressure-Amid-Record-Outflows/69986e7b057e346edab45092</guid><description>India witnessed a net outflow of Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) for the fourth consecutive month in December 2025, a trend driven by record repatriation by foreign investors and a substantial increase in overseas investments by Indian companies. This dual pressure has compressed net FDI inflows to under $4 billion for the fiscal year, significantly weakening the rupee and underscoring a shift from stable capital inflows to volatile capital flight. Despite robust gross inflows, the net figures reveal underlying economic pressures and a changing investment landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:23:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69986e7b057e346edab45091_1771597636039.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Starbucks Bets Big on India's Premium Coffee Segment Amidst Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Starbucks-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Premium-Coffee-Segment-Amidst-Caution/69986e1a057e346edab45030</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Starbucks-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Premium-Coffee-Segment-Amidst-Caution/69986e1a057e346edab45030</guid><description>Tata Starbucks is accelerating its expansion of premium Starbucks Reserve outlets across India, targeting Bengaluru, Hyderabad, and Kolkata. This strategic move aims to capitalize on India's rapidly growing coffee market and evolving consumer habits, positioning experiential formats at the forefront. However, this expansion occurs against a backdrop of persistent operational losses for Starbucks India, deeply entrenched tea consumption patterns, and a recent slowdown in Indian consumer discretionary spending, suggesting a high-stakes gambit for market leadership.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:22:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69986e1a057e346edab4502f_1771597502969.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SER Industries Renames to Desi Farms, Boosts Powers for Acquisitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/SER-Industries-Renames-to-Desi-Farms-Boosts-Powers-for-Acquisitions/69986dea057e346edab44fa4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/SER-Industries-Renames-to-Desi-Farms-Boosts-Powers-for-Acquisitions/69986dea057e346edab44fa4</guid><description>SER Industries Limited has taken a significant step by renaming itself 'Desi Farms India Limited' following an Extra-ordinary General Meeting (EGM). The company also secured approval for substantially increased borrowing and investment powers, alongside authorizing preferential share issuances. These moves are geared towards funding the acquisition of SNA Milk and Milk Products Limited and DFSU Farmer Connect Private Limited, signaling a strategic pivot for the company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:21:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69986dea057e346edab44fa3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Banks: Lower Small Loan Rates Mandated, Digital Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Lower-Small-Loan-Rates-Mandated-Digital-Focus/699869b6057e346edab44d14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Lower-Small-Loan-Rates-Mandated-Digital-Focus/699869b6057e346edab44d14</guid><description>DFS Secretary Nagaraju directed Indian banks to reduce interest rates on small business loans, citing disparity with corporate borrowing costs. Despite PSBs' strong capital and improving asset quality, the directive highlights challenges in operational costs and risk premiums for smaller borrowers. New digital platforms for consortium and co-lending aim to improve access and efficiency, reflecting a push for a more agile banking ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:03:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699869b6057e346edab44d13.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airtel, Zscaler Launch AI Cyber Defense Hub in India</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Airtel-Zscaler-Launch-AI-Cyber-Defense-Hub-in-India/699869ac057e346edab44cfb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Airtel-Zscaler-Launch-AI-Cyber-Defense-Hub-in-India/699869ac057e346edab44cfb</guid><description>Bharti Airtel and Zscaler have inaugurated the AI &amp; Cyber Threat Research Centre – India, a strategic initiative to fortify national cybersecurity defenses. This collaboration leverages Airtel's network intelligence and Zscaler's AI-driven security cloud to protect critical sectors, including telecommunications, banking, and energy, from sophisticated cyber threats. The center aims to foster industry-wide collaboration, advance AI-powered defenses, and strengthen India's cybersecurity talent pool.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:03:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699869ac057e346edab44cfa_1771596377397.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's $2.75B MSME Export Mission Targets Systemic Trade Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-275B-MSME-Export-Mission-Targets-Systemic-Trade-Hurdles/699869a6057e346edab44ce3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-275B-MSME-Export-Mission-Targets-Systemic-Trade-Hurdles/699869a6057e346edab44ce3</guid><description>The Indian government launched a ₹25,060 crore ($2.75 billion) Export Promotion Mission (EPM) to bolster Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs) in global markets. Ten of eleven planned interventions are now active, combining financial enablers and trade ecosystem support. These initiatives target critical challenges like high capital costs, limited trade finance, compliance burdens, and logistics disadvantages, aiming to enhance India's export competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:03:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699869a6057e346edab44ce2_1771596402325.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Elitecon Board to Decide on Acquisition Reversal Amid Funding Failure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Elitecon-Board-to-Decide-on-Acquisition-Reversal-Amid-Funding-Failure/6998699a057e346edab44cb9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Elitecon-Board-to-Decide-on-Acquisition-Reversal-Amid-Funding-Failure/6998699a057e346edab44cb9</guid><description>Elitecon International Limited has called a board meeting for February 27, 2026. The agenda includes considering the resignation of Executive Director Mr. Dayanand Ray and a critical proposal to reverse the acquisition of Sunbridge Agro Private Limited (SAPL). This proposed reversal stems from the company's failure to complete a planned Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP), resulting in non-receipt of funds needed to meet payment obligations for the acquisition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998699a057e346edab44cb8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shakti Press Board to Decide on Rights Issue Next Week</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shakti-Press-Board-to-Decide-on-Rights-Issue-Next-Week/6998691f057e346edab44bd1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shakti-Press-Board-to-Decide-on-Rights-Issue-Next-Week/6998691f057e346edab44bd1</guid><description>Shakti Press Limited will hold a Board of Directors meeting on February 25, 2026, to discuss and approve a Rights Issue. The company aims to finalize key details such as the number of shares, issue price, and record date. This move signals a need for capital, and existing shareholders should pay close attention to the terms of the offer, as it could impact their ownership stake and the company's future funding strategy. A trading window closure is in effect for company insiders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:01:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998691f057e346edab44bd0_1771596174195.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DFS Pressure on Indian Banks: Rate Cuts for Credit Growth Goals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/DFS-Pressure-on-Indian-Banks-Rate-Cuts-for-Credit-Growth-Goals/699868ed057e346edab44b85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/DFS-Pressure-on-Indian-Banks-Rate-Cuts-for-Credit-Growth-Goals/699868ed057e346edab44b85</guid><description>Department of Financial Services Secretary M. Nagaraju has mandated Indian banks to lower lending rates for small borrowers and businesses, aiming to expand credit penetration and bridge a significant gap in the country's credit-to-GDP ratio. This directive is framed as essential for realizing India's ambitious economic vision for 2047, even as banks are praised for resilience amid global instability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:00:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699868ed057e346edab44b84_1771596189262.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Readies Rs 94K Cr M&amp;A War Chest, Eyes Japanese Partnerships</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Readies-Rs-94K-Cr-MandA-War-Chest-Eyes-Japanese-Partnerships/6998684d057e346edab44aa5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Readies-Rs-94K-Cr-MandA-War-Chest-Eyes-Japanese-Partnerships/6998684d057e346edab44aa5</guid><description>State Bank of India is poised to enter the M&amp;A financing market, backed by new Reserve Bank of India regulations that allow for increased lending. The bank has identified a potential lending headroom of Rs 94,000 crore and is actively seeking partnerships with Japanese financial institutions. SBI plans a cautious, phased approach, focusing initially on smaller, less complex transactions and consortium-based deals. This move signals a significant shift in India's corporate finance landscape, historically dominated by non-bank lenders and offshore entities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:57:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998684d057e346edab44aa4_1771596064984.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSB EASE 9.0: Tech Ambitions Clash with Execution Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSB-EASE-90-Tech-Ambitions-Clash-with-Execution-Reality/699867e6057e346edab449dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSB-EASE-90-Tech-Ambitions-Clash-with-Execution-Reality/699867e6057e346edab449dd</guid><description>India's Public Sector Banks (PSBs) are launching EASE 9.0, a reform initiative heavily focused on AI, cloud, and GenAI integration. While aiming for global competitiveness, the agenda presents substantial execution challenges and requires significant capital investment. The ability of PSBs to adopt advanced technologies and attract talent will be critical in bridging the gap with more agile private sector institutions, as reflected in their current market valuations and analyst outlooks for FY27.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:55:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699867e6057e346edab449dc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Timken India: Upgrade Signals Growth, But Margin Hurdles Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Timken-India-Upgrade-Signals-Growth-But-Margin-Hurdles-Loom/699867b9057e346edab44995</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Timken-India-Upgrade-Signals-Growth-But-Margin-Hurdles-Loom/699867b9057e346edab44995</guid><description>Timken India reported a 14% year-over-year revenue increase to ₹764.3 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by strong performance across segments, especially Process (+24%). Analysts upgraded the stock to 'Accumulate' with a target price of ₹3,665, anticipating a 15% revenue CAGR through FY28. However, the company faces margin headwinds from its Bharuch plant's ramp-up and temporary cost pressures, leading to a sequential decline in profitability despite top-line gains. The stock trades at a premium valuation relative to sector peers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:55:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699867b9057e346edab44994_1771595884453.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oval Projects IPO Fund Use Okay, But Funds Mixed: Agency Flags Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oval-Projects-IPO-Fund-Use-Okay-But-Funds-Mixed-Agency-Flags-Concern/69986755057e346edab448cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oval-Projects-IPO-Fund-Use-Okay-But-Funds-Mixed-Agency-Flags-Concern/69986755057e346edab448cc</guid><description>Oval Projects Engineering Limited's IPO proceeds are being used as planned, according to a report by Infomerics Valuation and Rating. However, the report highlighted a significant governance concern: the company mixed IPO funds with other bank accounts, a practice known as 'commingling'. This practice led the monitoring agency to rely on management certificates to verify fund usage, raising questions about transparency and control over the Rs. 46.74 crore raised.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:53:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69986755057e346edab448cb_1771595700500.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nisus Finance Posts Strong Q3, Expands to UAE, Eyes New Products</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nisus-Finance-Posts-Strong-Q3-Expands-to-UAE-Eyes-New-Products/699866cd057e346edab4482b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nisus-Finance-Posts-Strong-Q3-Expands-to-UAE-Eyes-New-Products/699866cd057e346edab4482b</guid><description>Nisus Finance Services (NIFCO) reported robust Q3 and 9M FY26 results, with combined revenue hitting ₹365.27 crore and pre-consolidation revenue surpassing last year. The company is expanding into the UAE with a new asset acquisition and regulatory license, while its asset management segment now drives over half of its revenue. Its construction subsidiary, NCCCL, secured new mandates despite a one-time hit from labor law changes, and NIFCO plans AUM growth and new product launches like tokenization and SM REIT.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:51:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699866cd057e346edab4482a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Forex Reserves Hit Record, But Rupee Vulnerable to Geopolitics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Forex-Reserves-Hit-Record-But-Rupee-Vulnerable-to-Geopolitics/699863d3057e346edab44651</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Forex-Reserves-Hit-Record-But-Rupee-Vulnerable-to-Geopolitics/699863d3057e346edab44651</guid><description>India's foreign exchange reserves climbed to a record $725.7 billion as of February 13, 2026, buoyed by foreign currency assets and gold holdings. Despite this buffer, the Indian rupee depreciated 0.34% to 90.99 against the US dollar on Friday, February 20, 2026. The Reserve Bank of India's intervention capped losses, preventing a breach of the 91/$ mark, but escalating geopolitical tensions in the Middle East and sustained dollar strength continue to pressure the domestic currency. Benchmark bond yields also edged higher amid cautious sentiment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:38:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699863d3057e346edab44650_1771594861142.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Holds Rates: Growth Soars Amid Global Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Growth-Soars-Amid-Global-Uncertainty/69986355057e346edab4459a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Growth-Soars-Amid-Global-Uncertainty/69986355057e346edab4459a</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) unanimously decided to maintain the repo rate at 5.25%, affirming its neutral stance. Governor Sanjay Malhotra highlighted India's improving growth outlook, significantly brightened by trade agreements with the US and EU, while inflation remains contained. Despite this domestic optimism, global investor sentiment remains nervous, and financial markets volatile. The MPC's decision prioritizes policy stability amid external headwinds, signaling a cautious yet confident approach to navigating the complex economic environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:36:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69986355057e346edab44599.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Holds Rates Steady Amid Growth Surge, Inflation Watch Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Steady-Amid-Growth-Surge-Inflation-Watch-Intensifies/69986342057e346edab44573</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Steady-Amid-Growth-Surge-Inflation-Watch-Intensifies/69986342057e346edab44573</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee maintained the repo rate at 5.25%, keeping its neutral stance. Governor Sanjay Malhotra cited buoyant economic growth and benign inflation as justification, while Deputy Governor Poonam Gupta highlighted upward growth revisions and the impact of new trade deals. However, the central bank's explicit reliance on upcoming data series for GDP and inflation, alongside revised inflation projections for the next fiscal year, signals a cautious outlook, anticipating a gradual rise in price pressures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:36:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69986342057e346edab44572.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Marico's Record High: Growth Surge vs. Copra Cycle Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Maricos-Record-High-Growth-Surge-vs-Copra-Cycle-Risks/699862cb057e346edab44486</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Maricos-Record-High-Growth-Surge-vs-Copra-Cycle-Risks/699862cb057e346edab44486</guid><description>Marico's share price surged to an all-time high, fueled by a robust 27% revenue growth in Q3 FY26 and success in premium product categories. Investor optimism is high, with analysts at HSBC and Jefferies reiterating 'Buy' ratings and price targets of Rs 900. However, a cautious perspective from BNP Paribas highlights the looming threat of a Copra downcycle, historically a drag on the company's growth and margins, amidst a broadly tepid FMCG sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:34:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699862cb057e346edab44485_1771594588217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FTA Offensive: Strategic Push for Global Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indias-FTA-Offensive-Strategic-Push-for-Global-Dominance/699862c6057e346edab44421</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indias-FTA-Offensive-Strategic-Push-for-Global-Dominance/699862c6057e346edab44421</guid><description>India is accelerating its Free Trade Agreement (FTA) agenda, with key accords set for operationalization by April 2026, including with the UK and Oman, followed by New Zealand and the EU. This multi-front trade offensive aims to diversify export markets, attract investment, and embed Indian businesses into global value chains, signaling a decisive strategic push for future economic dominance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:33:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699862c6057e346edab44420.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Highway Infra Lands ₹154 Cr NHAI Toll Contract on Mega Expressway</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Highway-Infra-Lands-154-Cr-NHAI-Toll-Contract-on-Mega-Expressway/699862a0057e346edab443e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Highway-Infra-Lands-154-Cr-NHAI-Toll-Contract-on-Mega-Expressway/699862a0057e346edab443e8</guid><description>Highway Infrastructure Limited has secured a significant contract worth ₹154.60 Crores from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI). The agreement is for the operation and collection of user fees at toll plazas on the vital Vadodara-Mumbai Expressway. This move bolsters the company's position in the highway management sector amidst ongoing expressway development in India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:33:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699862a0057e346edab443e7_1771594524073.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's RBI Projects 7.4% Growth Amidst Geopolitical Crosswinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-RBI-Projects-74percent-Growth-Amidst-Geopolitical-Crosswinds/6998624b057e346edab44316</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-RBI-Projects-74percent-Growth-Amidst-Geopolitical-Crosswinds/6998624b057e346edab44316</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) anticipates a significant 7.4% GDP growth for fiscal year 2026, bolstered by recent trade agreements with the US and EU and supportive Union Budget measures. Despite projecting benign inflation, the central bank highlighted persistent geopolitical uncertainties and volatile energy prices as key external risks. The Monetary Policy Committee maintained a neutral stance, signaling a data-dependent approach to future policy adjustments, even as one member suggested a shift towards an accommodative posture.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:31:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998624b057e346edab44315.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GRP Ltd Tariff Relief Boosts Exports, New Projects Face Delays</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/GRP-Ltd-Tariff-Relief-Boosts-Exports-New-Projects-Face-Delays/69986218057e346edab442f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/GRP-Ltd-Tariff-Relief-Boosts-Exports-New-Projects-Face-Delays/69986218057e346edab442f1</guid><description>GRP Limited's Q3 FY26 earnings call revealed significant relief from U.S. tariffs, expected to revive its export business. While domestic reclaim rubber showed strong growth, the company faces challenges with new tyre pyrolysis and recovered carbon black projects facing commissioning delays and sub-optimal utilization. Management outlined plans for capex and expects mid-teen volume growth in FY27, but investors will be watching execution closely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69986218057e346edab442f0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Centum Electronics Pivots: Exits Losses to Target Defense Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Centum-Electronics-Pivots-Exits-Losses-to-Target-Defense-Boom/699861b8057e346edab4423a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Centum-Electronics-Pivots-Exits-Losses-to-Target-Defense-Boom/699861b8057e346edab4423a</guid><description>Centum Electronics is strategically exiting loss-making overseas operations in Canada and France, taking a significant INR 153.8 crore one-time impairment charge. The company is pivoting to capitalize on India's booming defense and space programs, with new opportunities in radar and air navigation systems, alongside a rapidly scaling semiconductor equipment business. Management targets high margins for these growth areas.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:29:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699861b8057e346edab44239.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fabtech Cleanrooms to Raise ₹3.98 Cr Via Preferential Issue, Plans Name Change</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Fabtech-Cleanrooms-to-Raise-398-Cr-Via-Preferential-Issue-Plans-Name-Change/69986129057e346edab4414a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Fabtech-Cleanrooms-to-Raise-398-Cr-Via-Preferential-Issue-Plans-Name-Change/69986129057e346edab4414a</guid><description>Fabtech Technologies Cleanrooms Limited has announced an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) on March 14, 2026, to seek shareholder approval for two key proposals. The company plans to raise approximately ₹3.98 Crores through a preferential issue of equity shares to Mr. Raveendra Shetty, a non-promoter and Director of its subsidiary Kelvin Air Conditioning. Additionally, shareholders will vote on changing the company's name from "Fabtech Technologies Cleanrooms Limited" to "Fabtech Cleanrooms Limited" or another approved name, aiming to distinguish itself from a group entity and better reflect its core business. The funds raised are earmarked for working capital and general corporate purposes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:27:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69986129057e346edab44149_1771594170888.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>