<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:25:20 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Private Bank Jobs Plummet in FY25! ICICI Bank Leads Exodus, PSU Banks See Slight Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Private-Bank-Jobs-Plummet-in-FY25-ICICI-Bank-Leads-Exodus-PSU-Banks-See-Slight-Rise/6952c6a84342f77179e48dd8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Private-Bank-Jobs-Plummet-in-FY25-ICICI-Bank-Leads-Exodus-PSU-Banks-See-Slight-Rise/6952c6a84342f77179e48dd8</guid><description>Indian private sector banks reduced their workforce in fiscal year 2025, primarily driven by a significant drop at ICICI Bank. In contrast, public sector banks reported a marginal increase in employees. Overall banking system employment grew, thanks to substantial hiring by Small Finance Banks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:11:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952c6a84342f77179e48dd7_1767032614356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSE's Shocking F&amp;O Turnover EXPLOSION: How They Toppled NSE Amidst Sebi's Tight Grip!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/BSEs-Shocking-FandO-Turnover-EXPLOSION-How-They-Toppled-NSE-Amidst-Sebis-Tight-Grip/6952c5df4342f77179e48bdb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/BSEs-Shocking-FandO-Turnover-EXPLOSION-How-They-Toppled-NSE-Amidst-Sebis-Tight-Grip/6952c5df4342f77179e48bdb</guid><description>The Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) has seen its futures and options average daily premium turnover skyrocket by 1,539% over the past two years, reaching ₹15,325 crore recently. This remarkable growth occurred even as the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) imposed several restrictive regulations. Experts attribute BSE's success to its Sensex contracts attracting traders and the addition of institutional clients, while the National Stock Exchange (NSE) experienced a significant fall in its turnover during the same period.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:10:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952c5df4342f77179e48bda_1767032461895.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OneCard's Revenue Skyrockets 32% to ₹1,878 Crore in FY25 as Losses Shrink Dramatically!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OneCards-Revenue-Skyrockets-32percent-to-1878-Crore-in-FY25-as-Losses-Shrink-Dramatically/6952c6234342f77179e48c46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OneCards-Revenue-Skyrockets-32percent-to-1878-Crore-in-FY25-as-Losses-Shrink-Dramatically/6952c6234342f77179e48c46</guid><description>Mobile-first credit card startup OneCard, operated by FPL Technologies, has reported a significant 32% jump in revenue for FY25, reaching ₹1,878 crore from ₹1,425.5 crore in FY24. Total revenue crossed ₹1,900 crore. The company also successfully narrowed its losses by 26% to ₹297.5 crore, down from ₹401 crore in the previous fiscal year. This growth was driven by its credit card operations and the OneScore app, even amidst increasing regulatory attention on co-branded cards.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:08:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952c6234342f77179e48c45_1767032717775.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Blockchain Boom: Aptos Sees Over Half Its 20 Million Wallets From India!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Blockchain-Boom-Aptos-Sees-Over-Half-Its-20-Million-Wallets-From-India/6952c5454342f77179e48ada</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Blockchain-Boom-Aptos-Sees-Over-Half-Its-20-Million-Wallets-From-India/6952c5454342f77179e48ada</guid><description>Blockchain platform Aptos has achieved over 20 million monthly active addresses, with a significant majority coming from India. Co-founder Avery Ching highlighted India's crucial role, citing partnerships with major players like Reliance Jio and a focus on developing real-world applications and decentralized trading infrastructure. The company is also involved in government blockchain pilots in states like Telangana.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:07:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952c5454342f77179e48ad9_1767032236486.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Revolution: Founders Leapfrog Silicon Valley's Decade-Long Lead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Revolution-Founders-Leapfrog-Silicon-Valleys-Decade-Long-Lead/6952c4f84342f77179e48a55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Revolution-Founders-Leapfrog-Silicon-Valleys-Decade-Long-Lead/6952c4f84342f77179e48a55</guid><description>Elevation Capital's AI partner Krishna Mehra states India has significantly narrowed the Artificial Intelligence gap with Silicon Valley, potentially only six months to a year behind. He urges Indian founders to build category-leading global companies, emphasizing the need for rapid product iteration and early validation with international customers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:07:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952c4f84342f77179e48a54_1767032130954.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Precious Metals Plunge: Gold, Silver Retreat From Peaks - What Investors MUST Know Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Plunge-Gold-Silver-Retreat-From-Peaks-What-Investors-MUST-Know-Now/6952c0974342f77179e4852a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Plunge-Gold-Silver-Retreat-From-Peaks-What-Investors-MUST-Know-Now/6952c0974342f77179e4852a</guid><description>Silver dropped from its record $80 per ounce peak, and gold eased from historic highs as investors took profits. Reduced geopolitical tensions, particularly concerning Ukraine peace talks, also curbed safe-haven demand. Platinum and palladium saw significant declines. Meanwhile, UBS raised its gold price outlook to $5,000 per ounce by 2026, citing factors like lower yields and economic concerns. Investors now await US Federal Reserve meeting minutes for interest rate clues.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:48:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952c0974342f77179e48529_1767031151244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Farming Future: Syngenta's AI App Connects Millions of Smallholders to Tech &amp; Markets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Farming-Future-Syngentas-AI-App-Connects-Millions-of-Smallholders-to-Tech-and-Markets/6952be374342f77179e481d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Farming-Future-Syngentas-AI-App-Connects-Millions-of-Smallholders-to-Tech-and-Markets/6952be374342f77179e481d0</guid><description>Syngenta Group is expanding its 'Cropwise Grower' digital platform for smallholder farmers in India. The app provides access to technology, market prices, and agronomist services in local languages, utilizing AI and satellite imagery for seed selection and pest detection. Currently serving 2.38 million farmers, Syngenta plans to integrate with the agriculture ministry's VISTAAR initiative, offering virtual classrooms and access to credit and digital marketplaces. The company also launched drone services via the app and is developing an AI chatbot.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:40:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952be374342f77179e481cf_1767030392019.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FMCG Giant HUL Faces Historic Reset: First Woman CEO Priya Nair Takes Charge Amidst Fierce Competition!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-FMCG-Giant-HUL-Faces-Historic-Reset-First-Woman-CEO-Priya-Nair-Takes-Charge-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/6952bef74342f77179e482f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-FMCG-Giant-HUL-Faces-Historic-Reset-First-Woman-CEO-Priya-Nair-Takes-Charge-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/6952bef74342f77179e482f6</guid><description>Priya Nair has become Hindustan Unilever's (HUL) first woman CEO and Managing Director, inheriting a legacy FMCG giant at a critical juncture. Facing sluggish growth, intense competition from niche and regional players, and evolving consumer habits, Nair's mandate is to restore growth and agility. Her strategy involves focusing on high-growth demand areas, reviving volume, and investing in emerging niche categories to navigate the challenging market landscape.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:40:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952bef74342f77179e482f5_1767030743110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Gears Up to Host Global AI Summit 2026: Will it Forge World's AI Rulebook?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Gears-Up-to-Host-Global-AI-Summit-2026-Will-it-Forge-Worlds-AI-Rulebook/6952b99a4342f77179e47b97</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Gears-Up-to-Host-Global-AI-Summit-2026-Will-it-Forge-Worlds-AI-Rulebook/6952b99a4342f77179e47b97</guid><description>India is set to host the AI Summit in February 2026, aiming to build a shared global understanding and consensus on artificial intelligence governance. Expected to draw over 100 countries, the summit will feature high-profile attendees including Bill Gates, CEOs from Anthropic and Adobe, and the French President, positioning India as a key convenor in global tech policy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:17:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952b99a4342f77179e47b96_1767029470923.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Next Tech Revolution Funded? IAN Group Closes $100 Million Alpha Fund for Deep Tech &amp; Defence Stars!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Next-Tech-Revolution-Funded-IAN-Group-Closes-100-Million-Alpha-Fund-for-Deep-Tech-and-Defence-Stars/6952b9574342f77179e47b11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Next-Tech-Revolution-Funded-IAN-Group-Closes-100-Million-Alpha-Fund-for-Deep-Tech-and-Defence-Stars/6952b9574342f77179e47b11</guid><description>IAN Group's second venture capital fund, the IAN Alpha Fund, has closed at $100 million. This fund will invest in deep technology startups and MSMEs crucial for India's strategic priorities, including semiconductors, defence tech, AI, biotech, and climate solutions. Despite cautious early-stage funding, the fund aims to back companies solving real problems with global scalability. IAN Group's track record and focus on commercial readiness are key to attracting investors. The fund typically invests $2 million per startup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:17:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952b9574342f77179e47b10_1767029159718.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jio SMOKES Competition in 5G! OpenSignal Reveals Shocking Speed &amp; Availability Lead - Are Others Left Behind?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Jio-SMOKES-Competition-in-5G-OpenSignal-Reveals-Shocking-Speed-and-Availability-Lead-Are-Others-Left-Behind/6952b86d4342f77179e478e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Jio-SMOKES-Competition-in-5G-OpenSignal-Reveals-Shocking-Speed-and-Availability-Lead-Are-Others-Left-Behind/6952b86d4342f77179e478e6</guid><description>Jio has emerged as the leader in 5G speed, signal availability, and subscriber utilization, according to a new report by broadband research firm Open Signal. The study, covering data from September 1 to November 30, 2025, shows Jio's 5G download speeds reaching 199.7 Mbps, significantly faster than competitors Bharti Airtel and Vodafone Idea. Jio's network consistently provides users with 5G connectivity for a majority of their usage time, highlighting the effectiveness of its Standalone architecture.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:12:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952b86d4342f77179e478e5_1767029242415.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Informatica CEO: India is Not Just a Market, It's Our AI Innovation Engine!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Informatica-CEO-India-is-Not-Just-a-Market-Its-Our-AI-Innovation-Engine/6952b87f4342f77179e47926</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Informatica-CEO-India-is-Not-Just-a-Market-Its-Our-AI-Innovation-Engine/6952b87f4342f77179e47926</guid><description>Informatica CEO Amit Walia highlights India's crucial role in the company's global strategy, emphasizing it as a core innovation hub. With over half its global workforce based in India, the company is leveraging its Bengaluru, Hyderabad, and Chennai centers, particularly iLabs, to drive advancements in AI-powered data management. Informatica's Intelligent Data Management Cloud (IDMC) platform is designed to help Indian enterprises navigate complex data challenges, ensure data reliability for AI adoption, and scale digital initiatives with confidence amidst rising regulatory demands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:09:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952b87f4342f77179e47925_1767028937986.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fog Chaos! Delhi Airport Grounds Flights; IndiGo, Air India Warn of Mass Cancellations - Are You Affected?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Fog-Chaos-Delhi-Airport-Grounds-Flights-IndiGo-Air-India-Warn-of-Mass-Cancellations-Are-You-Affected/6952b6bb4342f77179e4765a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Fog-Chaos-Delhi-Airport-Grounds-Flights-IndiGo-Air-India-Warn-of-Mass-Cancellations-Are-You-Affected/6952b6bb4342f77179e4765a</guid><description>Dense fog has enveloped Delhi and large parts of North, East, and Northeast India, leading to significant flight disruptions. Indira Gandhi International Airport has activated CAT-3 procedures due to visibility dropping to just 50 meters. Major airlines like IndiGo and Air India have issued advisories warning passengers of potential delays and cancellations, urging them to confirm flight status before heading to the airport. The aviation regulator, DGCA, has designated December 10, 2025, to February 10, 2026, as the official fog window.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:06:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952b6bb4342f77179e47659_1767028484460.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bandhan Bank Offloads Rs 6,872 Crore Bad Loans: What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bandhan-Bank-Offloads-Rs-6872-Crore-Bad-Loans-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6952b3224342f77179e156ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bandhan-Bank-Offloads-Rs-6872-Crore-Bad-Loans-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6952b3224342f77179e156ae</guid><description>Bandhan Bank has completed the sale of approximately ₹6,872 crore worth of identified unsecured non-performing asset (NPA) and written-off loan portfolios to Asset Reconstruction Companies (ARCs). The bank sold an NPA portfolio of ₹3,165.25 crore principal for ₹569.75 crore to ARCIL, and a written-off portfolio of ₹3,707.11 crore principal for ₹331.97 crore to Phoenix ARC, both on a security receipts basis. This move aims to clean up the bank's balance sheet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:46:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952b3224342f77179e156ad_1767027736340.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Shocker: CEO Amit Paithankar to Step Down in 2026! Who's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Waaree-Energies-Shocker-CEO-Amit-Paithankar-to-Step-Down-in-2026-Whos-Next/6952b2114342f77179e139e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Waaree-Energies-Shocker-CEO-Amit-Paithankar-to-Step-Down-in-2026-Whos-Next/6952b2114342f77179e139e8</guid><description>Waaree Energies announced that Whole-Time Director and CEO Amit Paithankar will resign effective May 15, 2026, to pursue external opportunities. The board has appointed Jignesh Rathod, currently Director-Operations, as CEO-Designate, ensuring leadership continuity. Rathod brings over 18 years of experience in operations and capacity expansion to the role.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:45:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952b2114342f77179e139e7_1767027312841.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fog Alert! Indian Railways Rolls Out Emergency Plan to Keep Vande Bharat &amp; Shatabdi on Time This Winter!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Fog-Alert-Indian-Railways-Rolls-Out-Emergency-Plan-to-Keep-Vande-Bharat-and-Shatabdi-on-Time-This-Winter/6952b1974342f77179e138b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Fog-Alert-Indian-Railways-Rolls-Out-Emergency-Plan-to-Keep-Vande-Bharat-and-Shatabdi-on-Time-This-Winter/6952b1974342f77179e138b8</guid><description>The Ministry of Railways is implementing real-time train checks and ensuring availability of spare rakes, including 20-car Vande Bharat sets, to maintain punctuality during the winter fog season. Measures cover catering and housekeeping services, with direct monitoring by the Railway Board via war rooms to prevent delays.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:40:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952b1974342f77179e138b7_1767027300587.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Finance Achieves Top-Tier AAA Credit Rating: What This Means for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Achieves-Top-Tier-AAA-Credit-Rating-What-This-Means-for-Investors/6952acf84342f77179df0899</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Achieves-Top-Tier-AAA-Credit-Rating-What-This-Means-for-Investors/6952acf84342f77179df0899</guid><description>Shriram Finance Ltd. announced a significant credit rating upgrade by CARE Ratings Limited. Its non-convertible debentures and subordinated debt have been elevated to 'CARE AAA; Stable,' the highest possible rating, from 'CARE AA+; Stable.' The company's commercial paper program also received a reaffirmation of 'CARE A1+,' indicating top-tier short-term credit quality. This upgrade reflects the agency's positive assessment of Shriram Finance's operational and financial performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:15:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952acf84342f77179df0898_1767026957992.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Energy Giant EESL Seeks $723M Sale of Smart Meter JV Amidst Debt Crisis!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Giant-EESL-Seeks-723M-Sale-of-Smart-Meter-JV-Amidst-Debt-Crisis/6952abfe4342f77179df00c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Giant-EESL-Seeks-723M-Sale-of-Smart-Meter-JV-Amidst-Debt-Crisis/6952abfe4342f77179df00c7</guid><description>Cash-strapped Energy Efficiency Services Ltd (EESL) and the National Investment and Infrastructure Fund (NIIF) are selling their IntelliSmart joint venture for an estimated $723 million. Advised by Deloitte, the sale aims to help EESL significantly reduce its ₹6,049 crore debt pile. This strategic move is vital for EESL's financial recovery and supports India's ambitious $30 billion smart metering program.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:11:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952abfe4342f77179df00c6_1767025855230.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Telecom Security Rules Extended! Govt Slashes Lab Fees, Speeds Up 5G &amp; Broadband Rollout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Telecom-Security-Rules-Extended-Govt-Slashes-Lab-Fees-Speeds-Up-5G-and-Broadband-Rollout/6952abfd4342f77179df009c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Telecom-Security-Rules-Extended-Govt-Slashes-Lab-Fees-Speeds-Up-5G-and-Broadband-Rollout/6952abfd4342f77179df009c</guid><description>India's Department of Telecommunications has extended the telecom equipment security certification scheme for one year, ensuring continuity for testing and certification. The government also reduced application fees for Telecom Security Testing Laboratories (TSTLs) and simplified security norms for Optical Network Terminator (ONT) devices. These measures aim to lower compliance costs, accelerate approvals, and boost the faster deployment of 5G and fibre broadband networks while supporting domestic manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:09:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952abfd4342f77179df009b_1767026638277.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Extends Oil &amp; Gas Block Bids: HUGE Opportunity for Investors?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Extends-Oil-and-Gas-Block-Bids-HUGE-Opportunity-for-Investors/6952aae54342f77179dee8bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Extends-Oil-and-Gas-Block-Bids-HUGE-Opportunity-for-Investors/6952aae54342f77179dee8bb</guid><description>India's Directorate General of Hydrocarbons (DGH) has extended the bid submission deadline for its latest oil and gas block auctions, including OALP-X, DSF, and CBM rounds, until February 18, 2026. This third extension, for up to six more weeks, aims to attract more investors and boost domestic energy production, potentially reducing the nation's significant oil import bill. The OALP-X round alone offers 25 blocks covering over 191,986 sq km.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:08:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952aae54342f77179dee8ba_1767026585128.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways' Fare Hike Puzzle: Small Changes, Big Financial Questions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Fare-Hike-Puzzle-Small-Changes-Big-Financial-Questions/6952aa744342f77179dee75d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Fare-Hike-Puzzle-Small-Changes-Big-Financial-Questions/6952aa744342f77179dee75d</guid><description>Indian Railways has implemented two passenger fare increases this fiscal year, but critics argue they are too small to address the core financial issues. The hikes, aimed at closing the revenue-expenditure gap and maintaining an operating ratio below 100%, are seen as populist and insufficient. The article questions the pricing of premium trains and suggests an independent tariff commission for rational fare revisions, highlighting the unsustainable reliance on freight revenue and the general budget.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:05:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952aa744342f77179dee75c_1767026008378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Pharma Giants Brace for Impact: Crucial GMP Deadline Sparks Industry Plea for More Time!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indian-Pharma-Giants-Brace-for-Impact-Crucial-GMP-Deadline-Sparks-Industry-Plea-for-More-Time/6952a96c4342f77179decd32</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indian-Pharma-Giants-Brace-for-Impact-Crucial-GMP-Deadline-Sparks-Industry-Plea-for-More-Time/6952a96c4342f77179decd32</guid><description>India's smaller drug manufacturers are scrambling to meet the revised Good Manufacturing Practices (GMP) deadline of December 31, 2025. Companies with annual turnover below ₹250 crore are seeking a 12-month extension, citing challenges in acquiring equipment and sourcing finance. Industry representatives are hopeful for a government reprieve, especially in light of recent cough syrup-related health concerns, as a significant portion of these units may be impacted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:05:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a96c4342f77179decd31_1767025334672.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Startup Funding Surge: VCs Bet Big on Fewer, Established Giants!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Funding-Surge-VCs-Bet-Big-on-Fewer-Established-Giants/6952a9cc4342f77179ded792</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Funding-Surge-VCs-Bet-Big-on-Fewer-Established-Giants/6952a9cc4342f77179ded792</guid><description>Late-stage startup funding in India showed resilience in 2025, raising $18 billion, up from $15 billion a year ago, despite fewer deals. Investors increasingly prefer scaled, revenue-generating companies with clear exit potential, while early-stage funding faces pressure. This trend reflects the maturity of India's venture ecosystem and a shift towards profitability and near-term liquidity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:04:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a9cc4342f77179ded791_1767025879963.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Shatters Clean Energy Records: 44.5 GW Added in 2025, Surpassing Global Goals!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/India-Shatters-Clean-Energy-Records-445-GW-Added-in-2025-Surpassing-Global-Goals/6952a7b34342f77179deb2f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/India-Shatters-Clean-Energy-Records-445-GW-Added-in-2025-Surpassing-Global-Goals/6952a7b34342f77179deb2f0</guid><description>India has achieved a landmark year for clean energy, adding a record 44.5 GW of renewable capacity by November 2025. This massive expansion brings the nation's total non-fossil fuel power capacity to 262.74 GW, now representing over 51% of its total installed capacity. Driven primarily by solar energy additions, this achievement helps India meet its Paris Agreement targets five years ahead of schedule and positions it as a global leader in renewable energy. This momentum supports the ambitious goal of reaching 500 GW non-fossil energy capacity by 2030.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:01:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a7b34342f77179deb2ef_1767025508417.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nabard Halts Huge ₹7,000 Crore Bond Issue: Is Your Money Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nabard-Halts-Huge-7000-Crore-Bond-Issue-Is-Your-Money-Safe/6952a5ce4342f77179deaeab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nabard-Halts-Huge-7000-Crore-Bond-Issue-Is-Your-Money-Safe/6952a5ce4342f77179deaeab</guid><description>State-owned Nabard has canceled its planned ₹7,000 crore bond issuance for the second time due to persistently high yields at the shorter end of the debt market. This indicates that the Reserve Bank of India's recent rate cuts are not effectively lowering borrowing costs, mirroring similar withdrawals by Power Finance Corporation and signaling potential market stress.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:44:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a5ce4342f77179deaeaa_1767024285820.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Approves Indian Overseas Bank's Global Leap: New Unit at GIFT City Set to Revolutionize Forex Operations!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Approves-Indian-Overseas-Banks-Global-Leap-New-Unit-at-GIFT-City-Set-to-Revolutionize-Forex-Operations/6952a5724342f77179dead8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Approves-Indian-Overseas-Banks-Global-Leap-New-Unit-at-GIFT-City-Set-to-Revolutionize-Forex-Operations/6952a5724342f77179dead8d</guid><description>Indian Overseas Bank has secured approval from the Reserve Bank of India to establish an International Financial Services Centre (IFSC) Banking Unit in Gujarat's GIFT City. This strategic move allows the public sector lender to expand its international financial services offerings and strengthen its presence in a key global financial hub, as detailed in a recent regulatory filing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:44:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a5724342f77179dead8c_1767024324156.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cantor Fitzgerald Forecasts Crypto Winter 2026: Is This the Calm Before Institutional Storm?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cantor-Fitzgerald-Forecasts-Crypto-Winter-2026-Is-This-the-Calm-Before-Institutional-Storm/6952a54e4342f77179dead12</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cantor-Fitzgerald-Forecasts-Crypto-Winter-2026-Is-This-the-Calm-Before-Institutional-Storm/6952a54e4342f77179dead12</guid><description>Cantor Fitzgerald analysts predict a 'crypto winter' starting in 2026, potentially pressuring Bitcoin prices. However, they see this downturn paving the way for a more stable, institutionally-driven crypto market. Key growth areas identified include Real-World Asset (RWA) tokenization, which could exceed $50 billion by 2026, and the increasing market share of Decentralized Exchanges (DEXs). The recent passage of the US CLARITY Act is expected to provide regulatory clarity, encouraging greater institutional involvement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:42:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a54e4342f77179dead11_1767024206633.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo's Pilot Pay Hike: A Fix for Mass Cancellations or Just More Costs?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-Pilot-Pay-Hike-A-Fix-for-Mass-Cancellations-or-Just-More-Costs/6952a4454342f77179deaab8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-Pilot-Pay-Hike-A-Fix-for-Mass-Cancellations-or-Just-More-Costs/6952a4454342f77179deaab8</guid><description>India's largest airline, IndiGo, is increasing pilot allowances and introducing new ones, effective January 1. This action follows weeks of mass flight cancellations attributed to poor roster planning, which stranded thousands of passengers. The move aims to boost pilot morale and combat competition from foreign carriers, while the airline faces regulatory scrutiny and warnings of financial damage from Moody's Ratings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:38:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a4454342f77179deaab7_1767023929737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Issues Stern Warning: Microlenders Must Monitor Mounting Stress!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Issues-Stern-Warning-Microlenders-Must-Monitor-Mounting-Stress/6952a4c64342f77179deaba6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Issues-Stern-Warning-Microlenders-Must-Monitor-Mounting-Stress/6952a4c64342f77179deaba6</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has directed microfinance institutions to closely monitor stress build-up in their loan portfolios. This directive comes as the RBI's Trend and Progress in Banking Report for FY25 notes lower disbursements in southern states, despite industry efforts and self-regulatory measures like guardrails to ensure steady growth. The central bank aims to foster systemic and sustainable growth while promoting financial inclusion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:37:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a4c64342f77179deaba5_1767024117241.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fertiliser Imports Skyrocket 60%: Winter Crops Boom or Subsidy Shock Looming?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Fertiliser-Imports-Skyrocket-60percent-Winter-Crops-Boom-or-Subsidy-Shock-Looming/6952a3df4342f77179dea9b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Fertiliser-Imports-Skyrocket-60percent-Winter-Crops-Boom-or-Subsidy-Shock-Looming/6952a3df4342f77179dea9b2</guid><description>India's fertiliser imports surged 60% to 17.37 million tonnes in April-November FY26, driven by strong winter crop sowing and robust monsoon rains. This trend ensures adequate supply but raises concerns over a potentially larger government subsidy bill. Imports of urea and DAP saw particularly sharp increases, highlighting domestic demand and import reliance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:36:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a3df4342f77179dea9b1_1767023752923.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys's Rs 21 Lakh Fresher Offer: Reality Check Amidst AI Hiring Blitz!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosyss-Rs-21-Lakh-Fresher-Offer-Reality-Check-Amidst-AI-Hiring-Blitz/6952a3724342f77179dea876</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosyss-Rs-21-Lakh-Fresher-Offer-Reality-Check-Amidst-AI-Hiring-Blitz/6952a3724342f77179dea876</guid><description>Infosys is reportedly offering freshers up to ₹21 lakh per annum for specialized AI roles, aiming to hire 20,000 new recruits. However, social media reactions suggest a significant gap between this advertised maximum and the actual offers received by most graduates, sparking debate about entry-level compensation realities in the IT sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:28:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a3724342f77179dea875_1767023562245.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haier India's Next Big Thing? Warburg Pincus Spots Massive Consumption Opportunity!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Haier-Indias-Next-Big-Thing-Warburg-Pincus-Spots-Massive-Consumption-Opportunity/6952a3634342f77179dea83c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Haier-Indias-Next-Big-Thing-Warburg-Pincus-Spots-Massive-Consumption-Opportunity/6952a3634342f77179dea83c</guid><description>Warburg Pincus views Haier India as a highly attractive investment, citing its strong global brand, manufacturing capabilities, and value proposition. The firm highlighted the underpenetrated Indian consumer market, where Haier's focus on quality, affordability, and local manufacturing aligns with the 'Make in India' initiative. Warburg Pincus sees significant long-term growth potential in India's consumption story, particularly in durable goods and home appliances.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:28:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a3634342f77179dea83b_1767023647742.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Pilots Get Major Pay Hike Post-Meltdown: Details Inside!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Pilots-Get-Major-Pay-Hike-Post-Meltdown-Details-Inside/6952a2404342f77179dea598</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Pilots-Get-Major-Pay-Hike-Post-Meltdown-Details-Inside/6952a2404342f77179dea598</guid><description>IndiGo has restructured pilot salaries, increasing allowances for domestic layovers, deadheading, and night hours, plus introducing a new tail-swap allowance. This move follows recent operational disruptions and is part of the airline's strategy to comply with Flight Duty Time Limit (FTDL) norms by February, aiming to stabilize its services and boost pilot morale.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:28:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a2404342f77179dea597_1767023515258.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's 2025 King Revealed: Larry Ellison's Shocking $89 Billion Leap!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-2025-King-Revealed-Larry-Ellisons-Shocking-89-Billion-Leap/6952a18d4342f77179dea3d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-2025-King-Revealed-Larry-Ellisons-Shocking-89-Billion-Leap/6952a18d4342f77179dea3d6</guid><description>Oracle co-founder Larry Ellison, not Elon Musk, is highlighted as defining AI in 2025. His wealth surged by $89 billion in a single day to $388 billion after Oracle's stock jumped 40% on strong AI cloud forecasts and a massive $300 billion deal with OpenAI for computing power. Ellison is also involved in the 'Stargate' initiative to build US AI data centers and has been expanding media interests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:28:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a18d4342f77179dea3d5_1767023255807.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra's Shock EV Bet: CEO Shah Ditches Hybrids, Calls Them 'Typewriters' in iPhone Era!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindras-Shock-EV-Bet-CEO-Shah-Ditches-Hybrids-Calls-Them-Typewriters-in-iPhone-Era/6952a0db4342f77179de6200</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindras-Shock-EV-Bet-CEO-Shah-Ditches-Hybrids-Calls-Them-Typewriters-in-iPhone-Era/6952a0db4342f77179de6200</guid><description>Mahindra Group CEO Anish Shah has declared the company's exclusive focus on 'born electric' vehicles, dismissing hybrid technology as a short-term solution akin to a typewriter in the age of iPhones. While competitors like Maruti Suzuki and Toyota Kirloskar Motors are pushing hybrids to address infrastructure concerns, Mahindra believes vehicles designed from the ground up for electric power are more efficient and offer superior performance. Shah's strategy prioritizes long-term EV advantages, even as other Indian automakers, like Tata Motors, maintain flexible approaches.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:25:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952a0db4342f77179de61ff_1767023126287.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Flags Major Risk: Microfinance Loans Deteriorate, NBFCs Urged to Monitor Closely!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Flags-Major-Risk-Microfinance-Loans-Deteriorate-NBFCs-Urged-to-Monitor-Closely/69529de74342f77179ddf2fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Flags-Major-Risk-Microfinance-Loans-Deteriorate-NBFCs-Urged-to-Monitor-Closely/69529de74342f77179ddf2fb</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has cautioned Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs) regarding the deteriorating performance of microfinance loans. While the overall NBFC sector's asset quality improved, NBFC-microfinance institutions (MFIs) saw their Gross Non-Performing Assets (GNPA) ratio rise to 4.1% and Net Non-Performing Assets (NNPA) ratio to 1.2% by March 2025. The RBI stressed the need for close monitoring, funding diversification, and vigilance against technological risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:08:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69529de74342f77179ddf2fa_1767022576814.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo GROUNDED! 118 Flights Cancelled as Fog Engulfs India - Are You Affected?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-GROUNDED-118-Flights-Cancelled-as-Fog-Engulfs-India-Are-You-Affected/69529d604342f77179ddf0fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-GROUNDED-118-Flights-Cancelled-as-Fog-Engulfs-India-Are-You-Affected/69529d604342f77179ddf0fe</guid><description>IndiGo has cancelled 118 flights on Monday due to severe fog and operational issues across northern India, impacting major airports like Delhi, Mumbai, and Bengaluru. The airline issued a travel advisory, warning of continued delays. This follows numerous earlier cancellations this month, highlighting the ongoing challenges faced by the aviation sector during the winter fog season. Passengers are advised to check their flight status.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:07:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69529d604342f77179ddf0fd_1767022312709.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Major Business Shake-Up: Lloyds Engineering Merges Arms for ₹6,150 Crore Order Book Boost!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Major-Business-Shake-Up-Lloyds-Engineering-Merges-Arms-for-6150-Crore-Order-Book-Boost/69529d3b4342f77179dde7a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Major-Business-Shake-Up-Lloyds-Engineering-Merges-Arms-for-6150-Crore-Order-Book-Boost/69529d3b4342f77179dde7a5</guid><description>Lloyds Engineering Works Limited's board has approved a significant merger plan, consolidating its infrastructure, engineering, and fabrication businesses. The amalgamation involves Lloyds Infrastructure &amp; Construction Ltd, Metalfab Hightech Pvt Ltd, and Techno Industries Ltd into the main entity. This strategic move aims to simplify the corporate structure, enhance operational efficiencies, and enable the unified company to bid for larger, multi-disciplinary projects. The combined entity will boast an order book of approximately ₹6,150 crore, positioning Lloyds Engineering for future growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:07:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69529d3b4342f77179dde7a4_1767022357786.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LG Electronics Ally Neolite ZKW Files Rs 600 Cr IPO Papers: Auto Lighting Giant Seeks Public Funding!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/LG-Electronics-Ally-Neolite-ZKW-Files-Rs-600-Cr-IPO-Papers-Auto-Lighting-Giant-Seeks-Public-Funding/69529bda4342f77179dde25e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/LG-Electronics-Ally-Neolite-ZKW-Files-Rs-600-Cr-IPO-Papers-Auto-Lighting-Giant-Seeks-Public-Funding/69529bda4342f77179dde25e</guid><description>Neolite ZKW Lightings, backed by LG Electronics subsidiary ZKW Group GmbH, has filed draft papers with SEBI to raise ₹600 crore through an Initial Public Offering (IPO). The IPO includes a fresh issuance of shares worth ₹400 crore and an offer-for-sale of ₹200 crore by existing shareholders. The company plans to use the funds for a new manufacturing facility, machinery purchase, debt repayment, and general corporate purposes. Neolite reported a significant profit jump of 177.2% in FY25.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:04:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69529bda4342f77179dde25d_1767022405276.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Grounds 118 Flights: Major India Travel Chaos As Fog Blinds Airports!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Grounds-118-Flights-Major-India-Travel-Chaos-As-Fog-Blinds-Airports/69529b364342f77179dde0cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Grounds-118-Flights-Major-India-Travel-Chaos-As-Fog-Blinds-Airports/69529b364342f77179dde0cf</guid><description>India's largest airline, IndiGo, cancelled 118 flights on Monday due to severe fog and operational issues, impacting major airports like Delhi, Mumbai, and Bengaluru. Passengers faced significant delays and disruptions. The airline cited ongoing foggy conditions in North India, with visibility yet to fully improve, extending flight impacts into the afternoon.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:02:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69529b364342f77179dde0ce_1767021660443.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>