<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:19:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Nuclear Leap: NTPC Ties Up with Russia &amp; France for Massive Power Projects!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Nuclear-Leap-NTPC-Ties-Up-with-Russia-and-France-for-Massive-Power-Projects/69571c664342f77179f906d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Nuclear-Leap-NTPC-Ties-Up-with-Russia-and-France-for-Massive-Power-Projects/69571c664342f77179f906d7</guid><description>NTPC, India's leading power generator, has signed non-disclosure agreements with Russia's Rosatom and France's EDF. These pacts aim to explore collaboration on large pressurized water reactor (PWR) nuclear power projects in India, covering the entire project lifecycle. This move follows India's recent law changes easing private sector entry and supplier liability, potentially accelerating the nation's nuclear energy expansion targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:07:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571c664342f77179f906d6_1767316710692.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Breakfast Boom: iD Fresh Food Secures Massive ₹1300 Crore Investment from Apax Partners!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Breakfast-Boom-iD-Fresh-Food-Secures-Massive-1300-Crore-Investment-from-Apax-Partners/69571c334342f77179f90618</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Breakfast-Boom-iD-Fresh-Food-Secures-Massive-1300-Crore-Investment-from-Apax-Partners/69571c334342f77179f90618</guid><description>British private equity firm Apax Partners is acquiring a quarter stake in Indian ready-to-cook breakfast maker iD Fresh Food for nearly Rs 1,300 crore, valuing the company at Rs 4,500 crore. This significant investment highlights the growing trend of premiumisation in India's fast-growing consumer sector, particularly in ready-to-cook breakfast staples. iD Fresh Food, known for its preservative-free products, aims for a public listing by 2027.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:07:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571c334342f77179f90617_1767316607305.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rs 25,000 Crore Infra Boost: Will This Fund Unlock Stalled Projects &amp; Skyrocket Stocks?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rs-25000-Crore-Infra-Boost-Will-This-Fund-Unlock-Stalled-Projects-and-Skyrocket-Stocks/69571c3d4342f77179f9064f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rs-25000-Crore-Infra-Boost-Will-This-Fund-Unlock-Stalled-Projects-and-Skyrocket-Stocks/69571c3d4342f77179f9064f</guid><description>The Indian government is reportedly planning a Rs 25,000 crore 'risk guarantee' fund to revive stalled infrastructure projects. This initiative aims to boost lender confidence and overcome financing bottlenecks, potentially accelerating projects in roads, rail, and metro sectors. Companies like KNR Constructions, PNC Infratech, and IRB Infrastructure Developers, focused on EPC and HAM models, could see improved execution and cash flows if the fund materializes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:05:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571c3d4342f77179f9064e_1767316698733.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shock Strike! Swiggy, Zomato Stocks Tumble as Delivery Workers Demand Fair Pay - Is India's Gig Economy at Risk?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Shock-Strike-Swiggy-Zomato-Stocks-Tumble-as-Delivery-Workers-Demand-Fair-Pay-Is-Indias-Gig-Economy-at-Risk/69571b414342f77179f9035c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Shock-Strike-Swiggy-Zomato-Stocks-Tumble-as-Delivery-Workers-Demand-Fair-Pay-Is-Indias-Gig-Economy-at-Risk/69571b414342f77179f9035c</guid><description>Delivery workers across India, employed by platforms like Swiggy and Zomato, staged nationwide strikes on December 25 and December 31, causing significant disruptions. The protests led to a drop in the shares of these companies, highlighting worker demands for predictable earnings and basic protections. While companies offered incentives, strike leaders indicated this was just the beginning, signalling a critical juncture for India's gig economy and platform business models.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:03:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571b414342f77179f9035b_1767316388852.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC Sell-Off Triggers Nifty Downturn: Can Indian Markets Rally Back Before Weekend Close?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/ITC-Sell-Off-Triggers-Nifty-Downturn-Can-Indian-Markets-Rally-Back-Before-Weekend-Close/695717774342f77179f8fa81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/ITC-Sell-Off-Triggers-Nifty-Downturn-Can-Indian-Markets-Rally-Back-Before-Weekend-Close/695717774342f77179f8fa81</guid><description>Indian stock markets, including the benchmark Sensex and Nifty, are facing pressure as a sell-off in ITC stock weighs on investor sentiment. The Nifty 50 index is currently aiming to recover from recent losses, with investors watching closely to see if a broader market recovery can materialize by the end of the trading week.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:46:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695717774342f77179f8fa80_1767315423595.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Giants Weigh Hybrid Future: JSW Motors, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Open to REEVs If Policy Shifts!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Giants-Weigh-Hybrid-Future-JSW-Motors-Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Open-to-REEVs-If-Policy-Shifts/695717644342f77179f8fa30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Giants-Weigh-Hybrid-Future-JSW-Motors-Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Open-to-REEVs-If-Policy-Shifts/695717644342f77179f8fa30</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra and JSW Motors are open to developing range-extended electric vehicles (REEVs) if India's policy framework expands incentives beyond pure electric cars. REEVs use an electric motor for driving, with a small internal combustion engine acting solely as a generator when the battery charge is low. While currently focused on pure EVs, automakers see REEVs as a transitional technology that could ease consumer adoption of electrification, provided policy and taxation support, mirroring trends seen in markets like China. Experts caution that REEVs still involve fossil fuel use, unlike pure EVs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695717644342f77179f8fa2f_1767315375356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Quick Commerce WAR: Billions Burned, Giants Clash – What 2026 Holds!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Quick-Commerce-WAR-Billions-Burned-Giants-Clash-What-2026-Holds/6957174f4342f77179f8f9ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Quick-Commerce-WAR-Billions-Burned-Giants-Clash-What-2026-Holds/6957174f4342f77179f8f9ce</guid><description>India's quick commerce sector is seeing explosive growth, with companies like Swiggy Instamart, Blinkit, and Zepto expanding rapidly and burning significant cash. This intense competition is expected to sharpen in 2026 as giants like Amazon and Flipkart enter the fray. While order volumes and revenue are surging, losses are widening, prompting a focus on profitable models, private labels, and deeper penetration into categories like pharmacy. The sector is already outperforming overall online retail, but 2026 will test execution and profitability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957174f4342f77179f8f9cd_1767315665429.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Sweet Tooth Suffers: Diabetes &amp; Health Trends Force Major Sugar Consumption Slowdown!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Sweet-Tooth-Suffers-Diabetes-and-Health-Trends-Force-Major-Sugar-Consumption-Slowdown/695717244342f77179f8f94d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Sweet-Tooth-Suffers-Diabetes-and-Health-Trends-Force-Major-Sugar-Consumption-Slowdown/695717244342f77179f8f94d</guid><description>India's legendary appetite for sugar is diminishing as a diabetes epidemic and evolving dietary habits lead to slowing consumption growth. Projections show growth at just 1.42% this fiscal year, with a decline anticipated next. This shift, driven by rising health consciousness and a younger generation's preference for healthier alternatives, poses significant challenges for the nation's sugar industry, including farmers and mills, though it is welcomed by healthcare professionals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695717244342f77179f8f94c_1767315321926.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Streaming Wars: Tiny Shows Rule, But Big Mergers Loom? Click to See What's Next!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Streaming-Wars-Tiny-Shows-Rule-But-Big-Mergers-Loom-Click-to-See-Whats-Next/6957171c4342f77179f8f8fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Streaming-Wars-Tiny-Shows-Rule-But-Big-Mergers-Loom-Click-to-See-Whats-Next/6957171c4342f77179f8f8fd</guid><description>India's streaming industry is embracing 'micro-dramas' in 2025-2026 due to tight budgets and slowing subscriptions. While creators and regional content rise, global media consolidation, including potential bids for Warner Bros. Discovery, could reduce space for independent makers. Monetization remains a challenge with fragmented markets and balancing ad-supported vs. subscription models, leading to selectivity and potential smaller OTT acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957171c4342f77179f8f8fc_1767315320156.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Real Estate 2026: Housing Slows, Office &amp; Logistics Set to Soar! Your Investment Guide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Real-Estate-2026-Housing-Slows-Office-and-Logistics-Set-to-Soar-Your-Investment-Guide/695716804342f77179f8f718</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Real-Estate-2026-Housing-Slows-Office-and-Logistics-Set-to-Soar-Your-Investment-Guide/695716804342f77179f8f718</guid><description>India's real estate market is set for healthy growth in 2026, with non-residential sectors like office and logistics expected to outperform housing. Residential sales slowed in 2025 due to high prices, but are predicted to stabilize moderately in 2026, driven by branded developers and potential RBI rate cuts. The office market shows global resilience with strong leasing momentum, while logistics demand from manufacturing and e-commerce is projected for significant growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695716804342f77179f8f717_1767315164857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Raja Venkatraman's Top 3 Stock Picks for January 2nd: HEG, AB Capital, UPL – Buy Now?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Raja-Venkatramans-Top-3-Stock-Picks-for-January-2nd-HEG-AB-Capital-UPL-Buy-Now/695716824342f77179f8f743</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Raja-Venkatramans-Top-3-Stock-Picks-for-January-2nd-HEG-AB-Capital-UPL-Buy-Now/695716824342f77179f8f743</guid><description>Indian equities closed mixed on the first trading day of 2026, with the Sensex down and Nifty 50 higher. Amid caution before Q3 earnings and trade talks, Raja Venkatraman of NeoTrader has recommended three stocks to buy: HEG, Aditya Birla Capital, and UPL, providing specific entry levels, stop losses, and target prices for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695716824342f77179f8f742_1767315181728.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Market Kick-off: MarketSmith India Unveils 2 Must-Buy Stocks for Big Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/2026-Market-Kick-off-MarketSmith-India-Unveils-2-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-Big-Gains/695716364342f77179f8f65b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/2026-Market-Kick-off-MarketSmith-India-Unveils-2-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-Big-Gains/695716364342f77179f8f65b</guid><description>Indian stock markets began 2026 with muted trading, as Nifty 50 and BSE Sensex showed little movement. While Auto, IT, and Realty sectors gained, FMCG stocks, led by ITC, fell sharply due to increased tobacco excise duties. Market breadth remained positive. MarketSmith India has recommended buying Fedbank Financial Services Ltd, citing strong parentage and growth in lending, and Adani Energy Solutions Ltd, highlighting its power sector presence and Adani Group backing. Key metrics and risks for both are detailed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695716364342f77179f8f65a_1767315077842.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Dealmakers Rejoice: Record $1.5 Billion Fees Propel Investment Bankers Towards Mega Bonuses!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Dealmakers-Rejoice-Record-15-Billion-Fees-Propel-Investment-Bankers-Towards-Mega-Bonuses/695710454342f77179f8eb34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Dealmakers-Rejoice-Record-15-Billion-Fees-Propel-Investment-Bankers-Towards-Mega-Bonuses/695710454342f77179f8eb34</guid><description>Investment bankers in India are set for significant bonuses following a record-breaking 2025, which saw total fees reach $1.5 billion. Equity capital markets and private dealmaking fueled this surge, with ECM contributing $651.8 million and M&amp;A $391.3 million. Bonuses for 2025 are projected to be 150-200% of base compensation, potentially exceeding ₹1,000-1,200 crore in aggregate. Top banks like Morgan Stanley, Jefferies, JP Morgan, Kotak Mahindra Bank, and Axis Bank earned substantial fees. The strong performance is expected to continue into 2026, driven by robust deal volumes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:13:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695710454342f77179f8eb33_1767313630372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Job Loss? India's New Labour Code Promises Fund Within 45 Days for Reskilling!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Job-Loss-Indias-New-Labour-Code-Promises-Fund-Within-45-Days-for-Reskilling/69570d984342f77179f8e681</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Job-Loss-Indias-New-Labour-Code-Promises-Fund-Within-45-Days-for-Reskilling/69570d984342f77179f8e681</guid><description>India's draft Industrial Relations Code, 2020, introduces a significant worker support measure. Retrenched employees will receive a reskilling fund, equivalent to 15 days of their last drawn wages, within 45 days of job loss. Employers must transfer funds to the government within 10 days. This move aims to institutionalize skilling and support workers transitioning to new roles. The rules also propose giving retrenched employees preference for re-employment in similar vacancies within one year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:03:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69570d984342f77179f8e680_1767312877771.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Highway Toll Cut! Big Relief for Commuters as Construction Tolls Halved, Expressway Fees Standardized</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Highway-Toll-Cut-Big-Relief-for-Commuters-as-Construction-Tolls-Halved-Expressway-Fees-Standardized/69570cff4342f77179f8e503</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Highway-Toll-Cut-Big-Relief-for-Commuters-as-Construction-Tolls-Halved-Expressway-Fees-Standardized/69570cff4342f77179f8e503</guid><description>In a significant move for highway commuters, the Finance Ministry has approved proposals to halve toll charges during the construction period for road stretches being expanded from two-lane to four-lane. Commuters will now pay reduced tolls as they experience reduced road width. Additionally, user fees on partially opened expressways, including routes like Delhi-Mumbai and Amritsar-Jamnagar, will be standardized to match other National Highways, ending the previous higher charges. The Ministry also emphasized strict penalties for contractors missing project timelines.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:03:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69570cff4342f77179f8e502_1767312704295.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Gig Worker Rules: 90 Days to Unlock Social Security Benefits!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Gig-Worker-Rules-90-Days-to-Unlock-Social-Security-Benefits/69570d724342f77179f8e609</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Gig-Worker-Rules-90-Days-to-Unlock-Social-Security-Benefits/69570d724342f77179f8e609</guid><description>India's government has proposed draft rules requiring gig and platform workers to complete at least 90 days of engagement with a single aggregator, or 120 days across multiple aggregators, within a financial year to qualify for social security benefits. These benefits include health, life, and personal accident insurance, with potential future pension eligibility. The rules also mandate Aadhaar-linked registration for workers over 16, aiming to create a universal account number and formalize the growing gig workforce.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:03:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69570d724342f77179f8e608_1767312941780.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>