<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:57:13 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Inflation Gauge Reset: New CPI Series Shows 2.75%, Eyes Policy Impact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Inflation-Gauge-Reset-New-CPI-Series-Shows-275percent-Eyes-Policy-Impact/698dcbade8013a522e7719de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Inflation-Gauge-Reset-New-CPI-Series-Shows-275percent-Eyes-Policy-Impact/698dcbade8013a522e7719de</guid><description>India's retail inflation registered 2.75% in January 2026, based on a newly released Consumer Price Index (CPI) series with a 2024 base year. This significant methodological overhaul by the National Statistics Office (NSO) expands the item basket to 358 from 299, incorporating digital services, rural housing, and updated transport costs. The revision aims to better reflect contemporary consumption patterns and refine monetary policy inputs, moving away from the previous 2012 base year metrics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GIFT City Fuels India's MF Maturity: Summit Eyes Global Leap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GIFT-City-Fuels-Indias-MF-Maturity-Summit-Eyes-Global-Leap/698dcb31e8013a522e7717d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GIFT-City-Fuels-Indias-MF-Maturity-Summit-Eyes-Global-Leap/698dcb31e8013a522e7717d1</guid><description>India's mutual fund industry is maturing beyond mere scale, with a projected reach of ₹100 trillion by 2030. The spotlight is shifting to sophisticated investment pathways and global integration, spearheaded by GIFT City. This International Financial Services Centre (IFSC) is emerging as a critical nexus for cross-border finance, attracting significant capital and entities. Discussions at the Moneycontrol Mutual Fund Summit 2026 will dissect GIFT City's role in enabling a 'local-plus-global' investment strategy for Indian investors and fund houses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:44:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedanta Hits Record Highs in Q3 FY26, Acquires Incab Industries</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedanta-Hits-Record-Highs-in-Q3-FY26-Acquires-Incab-Industries/698dcadfe8013a522e771656</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedanta-Hits-Record-Highs-in-Q3-FY26-Acquires-Incab-Industries/698dcadfe8013a522e771656</guid><description>Vedanta Limited delivered a record-breaking Q3 FY26, with revenue soaring to ₹45,899 Cr (19% YoY) and EBITDA reaching an all-time high of ₹15,171 Cr (34% YoY). PAT surged 60% YoY to ₹7,807 Cr. The company also strategically acquired Incab Industries, bolstering its downstream copper and aluminium operations. This move strengthens Vedanta's position in India's energy transition, though concerns about rising low-cost copper imports persist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ADF Foods Hits Record Revenue, Profit Surges 55% in Q3 FY'26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ADF-Foods-Hits-Record-Revenue-Profit-Surges-55percent-in-Q3-FY26/698dcad7e8013a522e77164f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ADF-Foods-Hits-Record-Revenue-Profit-Surges-55percent-in-Q3-FY26/698dcad7e8013a522e77164f</guid><description>ADF Foods reported a record Q3 FY'26 with consolidated revenues soaring 29.5% YoY to INR 191 Cr, and PAT (excl. exceptional items) jumping 55.7% to INR 29.2 Cr. Strong traction from the Ashoka and Truly Indian brands, especially in the US market, alongside volume growth, fueled this performance. The company is on track to operationalize its Surat greenfield facility by Q4 FY'26, enhancing capacity. ADF Foods guided for INR 925-1000 Cr revenue in FY'27, aiming for high-teen EBITDA margins.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Alexander Stamps &amp; Coins Faces Auditor's Disclaimer; Survival in Doubt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Alexander-Stamps-and-Coins-Faces-Auditors-Disclaimer-Survival-in-Doubt/698dcad6e8013a522e771647</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Alexander-Stamps-and-Coins-Faces-Auditors-Disclaimer-Survival-in-Doubt/698dcad6e8013a522e771647</guid><description>Alexander Stamps and Coin Limited has plunged into a financial crisis, reporting a 46.1% YoY revenue drop to ₹5.92 lakhs in Q3 FY26 and a net loss of ₹0.47 lakhs. The company's statutory auditors have issued a disclaimer of conclusion, unable to verify significant assets including ₹113.67 lakhs in non-current investments and ₹1,648.18 lakhs in inventories. A substantial ₹344.56 lakhs income tax demand further compounds the issues, leading auditors to raise material uncertainty about the company's ability to continue as a going concern.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Regency Ceramics Revenue Surges 190%, But Deep Losses &amp; Auditor Red Flags Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Regency-Ceramics-Revenue-Surges-190percent-But-Deep-Losses-and-Auditor-Red-Flags-Loom/698dcabee8013a522e771541</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Regency-Ceramics-Revenue-Surges-190percent-But-Deep-Losses-and-Auditor-Red-Flags-Loom/698dcabee8013a522e771541</guid><description>Regency Ceramics reported a dramatic 190.91% YoY revenue surge to ₹1,152.23 Lakhs in Q3 FY26, signaling operational revival. However, net losses widened by 34.62% YoY to ₹516.26 Lakhs, further eroding net worth. Compounding these issues, the independent auditor's report flagged significant qualifications regarding employee benefits, balance confirmations, loan interest, statutory dues, and inventory valuation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vraj Iron Profit Plummets 87% Despite Sales; Tax Anomaly Cited</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vraj-Iron-Profit-Plummets-87percent-Despite-Sales-Tax-Anomaly-Cited/698dca30e8013a522e77143b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vraj-Iron-Profit-Plummets-87percent-Despite-Sales-Tax-Anomaly-Cited/698dca30e8013a522e77143b</guid><description>Vraj Iron &amp; Steel's Q3 FY26 results reveal a stark profit collapse of 87% YoY, with PAT falling to ₹9.91 Cr despite a 22% revenue jump. Margins compressed severely, and a significant tax calculation anomaly raises concerns about financial reporting. The company also faces a low interest cover ratio as it plans debt-funded expansion for a solar plant.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AAI Commits ₹3,490 Cr to Modernize Air Navigation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/AAI-Commits-3490-Cr-to-Modernize-Air-Navigation/698dc9fae8013a522e771322</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/AAI-Commits-3490-Cr-to-Modernize-Air-Navigation/698dc9fae8013a522e771322</guid><description>Airports Authority of India is undertaking a significant ₹3,490 crore investment in its air navigation infrastructure from 2026-2028. The capital outlay prioritizes ₹1,532 crore for automating air traffic management systems and enhancing cybersecurity. This strategic push aims to accommodate India's rapidly growing air traffic demand, improve operational efficiency, and prevent disruptions by modernizing critical communication, navigation, and surveillance systems nationwide.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Biological E Secures WHO Phase II Nod for Novel Polio Vaccine Production</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biological-E-Secures-WHO-Phase-II-Nod-for-Novel-Polio-Vaccine-Production/698dc9f4e8013a522e7712e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biological-E-Secures-WHO-Phase-II-Nod-for-Novel-Polio-Vaccine-Production/698dc9f4e8013a522e7712e6</guid><description>Hyderabad-based Biological E Limited announced a significant achievement Thursday: the World Health Organization granted phase II pre-qualification for its Novel Oral Polio Vaccine type 2 (nOPV2). This approval validates the complete manufacturing chain for nOPV2 at a single, integrated site. The company has already supplied 700 million doses globally to combat circulating poliovirus outbreaks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RCF Bets ₹865 Cr on Phosphoric Acid Amidst Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/RCF-Bets-865-Cr-on-Phosphoric-Acid-Amidst-Mixed-Market-Signals/698dc8dbe8013a522e770da5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/RCF-Bets-865-Cr-on-Phosphoric-Acid-Amidst-Mixed-Market-Signals/698dc8dbe8013a522e770da5</guid><description>Rashtriya Chemicals and Fertilizers Ltd. is committing ₹865.25 crore to a new 300-TPD phosphoric acid plant in Maharashtra. This strategic move targets enhanced backward integration and production control. However, it occurs amid a competitive landscape, fluctuating market sentiment, and mixed analyst ratings, raising questions about optimal capital deployment versus strategic necessity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Rafale Deal Fuels Dassault Dominance, Strategic Industrial Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Rafale-Deal-Fuels-Dassault-Dominance-Strategic-Industrial-Pivot/698dc8a1e8013a522e770ca7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Rafale-Deal-Fuels-Dassault-Dominance-Strategic-Industrial-Pivot/698dc8a1e8013a522e770ca7</guid><description>India's Defence Acquisition Council has approved a ₹3.25 lakh crore deal for 114 Rafale fighter jets from France's Dassault Aviation. This significant acquisition aims to address the Indian Air Force's squadron deficit and substantially bolster India's domestic defense manufacturing capabilities through local assembly and production. The order reinforces Dassault's global market position and highlights a strategic industrial realignment for India.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SEBI Streamlines Rules: Balancing Cost Cuts with Infrastructure Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SEBI-Streamlines-Rules-Balancing-Cost-Cuts-with-Infrastructure-Risks/698dc86ce8013a522e770c5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SEBI-Streamlines-Rules-Balancing-Cost-Cuts-with-Infrastructure-Risks/698dc86ce8013a522e770c5b</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) is strategically reducing regulatory costs and simplifying compliance to enhance market competitiveness and attract capital. Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey emphasized this initiative's importance in lowering the cost of capital. Concurrently, a recent technical glitch at the National Securities Depository Ltd (NSDL) exposed operational vulnerabilities, raising concerns about market infrastructure robustness and potentially tempering investor enthusiasm despite cost-saving efforts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PFC-REC Merger: Performance Gap Casts Shadow Over Synergy Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFC-REC-Merger-Performance-Gap-Casts-Shadow-Over-Synergy-Hopes/698dc85ee8013a522e770be1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFC-REC-Merger-Performance-Gap-Casts-Shadow-Over-Synergy-Hopes/698dc85ee8013a522e770be1</guid><description>The proposed merger of Power Finance Corporation (PFC) and REC is drawing attention, yet Q3 FY26 results reveal a significant performance split. PFC demonstrates stronger loan growth and stable margins, outperforming REC, which grapples with slower expansion, margin compression, and elevated repayments. While analysts maintain 'Buy' ratings for both, the merger's success hinges on reconciling these divergent operational trajectories to achieve stated goals of scale and efficiency.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cohance Lifesciences Profits Plummet 87% Amid FDA Woes, Guides for Revenue Decline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Cohance-Lifesciences-Profits-Plummet-87percent-Amid-FDA-Woes-Guides-for-Revenue-Decline/698dc7e2e8013a522e770a66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Cohance-Lifesciences-Profits-Plummet-87percent-Amid-FDA-Woes-Guides-for-Revenue-Decline/698dc7e2e8013a522e770a66</guid><description>Cohance Lifesciences (formerly Suven Pharma) reported a brutal Q3 FY26, with Adjusted PAT plunging 87.3% YoY to ₹21.1 Cr and margins collapsing. Revenue fell 19.5% YoY. The company cited an FDA Warning Letter at its Nacham facility, causing ₹55 Cr shipment deferrals and disruptions. With FY26 declared a "transition year" and revised guidance predicting an "early-to-mid double-digit decline" in revenue, recovery is anticipated from FY27, driven by R&amp;D pipeline conversions and capacity expansions. Despite the downturn, the company maintained a net cash positive position and reduced borrowings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindalco Q3: Standalone PAT Soars, but Novelis Fires Drag Consolidated Profit Down</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindalco-Q3-Standalone-PAT-Soars-but-Novelis-Fires-Drag-Consolidated-Profit-Down/698dc757e8013a522e77091f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindalco-Q3-Standalone-PAT-Soars-but-Novelis-Fires-Drag-Consolidated-Profit-Down/698dc757e8013a522e77091f</guid><description>Hindalco Industries reported a starkly divided Q3 FY26 performance. Standalone PAT surged 106.2% YoY to ₹3,017 Crore, driven by significant tax benefits. However, consolidated PAT plummeted 45.1% YoY to ₹2,049 Crore, heavily impacted by exceptional expenses of ₹2,610 Crore due to fire incidents at its Novelis subsidiary's Oswego plant. The company also faces a CBI chargesheet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's New CPI: 2.75% Inflation Returns to Target Band</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-CPI-275percent-Inflation-Returns-to-Target-Band/698dc6f4e8013a522e770855</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-CPI-275percent-Inflation-Returns-to-Target-Band/698dc6f4e8013a522e770855</guid><description>India's retail inflation registered 2.75% in January, marking the first reading under a new Consumer Price Index (CPI) series using 2024 as its base year. This recalibration, derived from the 2023-24 Household Consumption Expenditure Survey, aims to better reflect contemporary spending patterns by adjusting item weights and expanding coverage. While this brings inflation back within the Reserve Bank of India's target range, economists suggest the methodological shifts may not immediately alter monetary policy, pointing towards a sustained pause in interest rate adjustments as the economy navigates evolving price dynamics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ingersoll Rand India's Q3 Surge: Revenue Jumps 19%, New Gujarat Plant Operational</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ingersoll-Rand-Indias-Q3-Surge-Revenue-Jumps-19percent-New-Gujarat-Plant-Operational/698dc603e8013a522e77049c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ingersoll-Rand-Indias-Q3-Surge-Revenue-Jumps-19percent-New-Gujarat-Plant-Operational/698dc603e8013a522e77049c</guid><description>Ingersoll Rand India reported a strong Q3 FY25-26, with revenue soaring 19% YoY to INR 455.48 crores and PBT growing 15% to INR 121.67 crores. The company commissioned its new Sanand, Gujarat manufacturing facility, boosting output by 1.5x. Despite a 9-month PAT dip attributed to exceptional costs, management eyes doubling growth via localization and strategic expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Moneyboxx Finance: Profit Crashes 92%, NCD Covenants Breached</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Moneyboxx-Finance-Profit-Crashes-92percent-NCD-Covenants-Breached/698dc5a2e8013a522e7702d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Moneyboxx-Finance-Profit-Crashes-92percent-NCD-Covenants-Breached/698dc5a2e8013a522e7702d0</guid><description>Moneyboxx Finance reported a sharp 92.29% year-on-year decline in Profit After Tax (PAT) for Q3 FY26, falling to ₹76.36 crore from ₹989.33 crore in Q3 FY25, despite a stated 10% rise in total income to ₹248.77 crore. This severe profitability hit was driven by a 67.5% surge in finance costs and increased impairment charges. A major red flag is the company's non-compliance with financial covenants for its listed Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs), with the PAR&gt;90 ratio exceeding the limit. The company is seeking a waiver from the Debenture Trustee.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Heliware Secures ₹4.5 Cr for Global Geospatial Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Heliware-Secures-45-Cr-for-Global-Geospatial-Dominance/698dc598e8013a522e770293</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Heliware-Secures-45-Cr-for-Global-Geospatial-Dominance/698dc598e8013a522e770293</guid><description>Heliware, a deeptech startup specializing in advanced geospatial intelligence and 3D analytics, has secured ₹4.5 crore (approximately $496,000 USD) in bridge funding, led by Inflection Point Ventures. The capital infusion will accelerate its international market expansion, focusing on strategic partnerships, talent acquisition, and global operational setup. Heliware's proprietary platform offers analysis five times faster and at half the cost of traditional methods, positioning it to capture significant share in the rapidly growing geospatial market, estimated to exceed $250 billion globally by 2032.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Neueon Corp Faces Auditor Qualifiers Post-CIRP Amid Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Neueon-Corp-Faces-Auditor-Qualifiers-Post-CIRP-Amid-Revenue-Surge/698dc530e8013a522e77005c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Neueon-Corp-Faces-Auditor-Qualifiers-Post-CIRP-Amid-Revenue-Surge/698dc530e8013a522e77005c</guid><description>Neueon Corporation, recently out of Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), reported a significant YoY revenue increase to ₹122.34 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, with net losses narrowing to ₹879.76 Lakhs. However, statutory auditors issued a qualified conclusion due to the company's failure to conduct impairment testing on key assets and uncertainty surrounding a substantial subsidiary investment. This casts a shadow on the financial health despite operational recovery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:18:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gayatri Highways Profit Masked by Grave Auditor Red Flags on Debt, Impairment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Gayatri-Highways-Profit-Masked-by-Grave-Auditor-Red-Flags-on-Debt-Impairment/698dc4a7e8013a522e76fe15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Gayatri-Highways-Profit-Masked-by-Grave-Auditor-Red-Flags-on-Debt-Impairment/698dc4a7e8013a522e76fe15</guid><description>Gayatri Highways announced Q3 FY26 results, showing a standalone profit for the nine months driven by 'Other Income'. However, a qualified auditor's report raises severe concerns, detailing debt defaults totalling ₹5,015.86 Lakhs, pending loan confirmations of ₹17,887.51 Lakhs, and potential impairments exceeding ₹6,000 Lakhs across subsidiaries. Consolidated results showed a comprehensive loss, impacted by joint venture performance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Suraksha Diagnostics Posts 30% Revenue Growth Amid Expansion, Margin Pressure Expected</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Suraksha-Diagnostics-Posts-30percent-Revenue-Growth-Amid-Expansion-Margin-Pressure-Expected/698dc4a4e8013a522e76fdb8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Suraksha-Diagnostics-Posts-30percent-Revenue-Growth-Amid-Expansion-Margin-Pressure-Expected/698dc4a4e8013a522e76fdb8</guid><description>Suraksha Diagnostics reported a robust 30.3% YoY revenue growth in Q3 FY'26, reaching INR 783.09 million, driven by a 23% increase in patients and 30.7% rise in tests. While PAT grew to INR 72.41 million, EBITDA margins compressed to 30.6% due to pre-operative costs from aggressive network expansion. Management forecasts ~32% EBITDA margins for FY'26, with recovery expected from Q3 FY'27 as new centers mature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Anmol India Q3 PAT Surges 674% YoY on Revenue Boost, Lacks Guidance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Anmol-India-Q3-PAT-Surges-674percent-YoY-on-Revenue-Boost-Lacks-Guidance/698dc469e8013a522e76fbd5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Anmol-India-Q3-PAT-Surges-674percent-YoY-on-Revenue-Boost-Lacks-Guidance/698dc469e8013a522e76fbd5</guid><description>Anmol India Limited reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with Net Profit soaring 673.68% year-on-year to ₹2.94 crore, fueled by a 20.57% revenue increase to ₹305.42 crore. Sequentially, Net Profit surged over 4100% from Q2 FY26. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, revenue grew 15.42%, but Profit Before Tax declined YoY. Net Profit for the nine-month period still rose 63.08% due to lower tax expenses. The company operates solely in coal and other items trading, and no future guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IHCL Posts Record Q3 Revenue; PAT Surges 55% on Landmark JV Sale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/IHCL-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-PAT-Surges-55percent-on-Landmark-JV-Sale/698dc458e8013a522e76fb53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/IHCL-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-PAT-Surges-55percent-on-Landmark-JV-Sale/698dc458e8013a522e76fb53</guid><description>Indian Hotels Company Limited (IHCL) reported a record-breaking fifteenth consecutive quarter of performance for Q3 FY2026. Consolidated revenue climbed 12% year-on-year to INR 2,900 Crores, with EBITDA growing 11% to INR 1,134 Crores. Profit After Tax (PAT) surged 55% YoY to INR 903 Crores, significantly boosted by a INR 327 Crores profit from a joint venture stake sale. The company also highlighted strong portfolio expansion, signing 239 hotels year-to-date.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Unimech Q3 PAT Plunges 77%, Secures Saudi JV Amid Tariff Woes.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Unimech-Q3-PAT-Plunges-77percent-Secures-Saudi-JV-Amid-Tariff-Woes/698dc3bde8013a522e76f655</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Unimech-Q3-PAT-Plunges-77percent-Secures-Saudi-JV-Amid-Tariff-Woes/698dc3bde8013a522e76f655</guid><description>Unimech Aerospace reported a steep 77% year-on-year fall in consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) for the third quarter of FY26, with revenue declining 45.6%. This stark downturn contrasts with a robust 45.5% PAT growth in standalone nine-month results. The company is navigating challenges from US tariffs impacting its export markets. Strategically, Unimech approved a new renewable energy subsidiary and a 51% stake in a Saudi Arabian joint venture for precision machining, signaling diversification and expansion efforts. Unutilized IPO funds also saw reallocation approvals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamdhenu Ventures Profit Halved Amid Sales Slump; Plans ₹20 Crore Fundraise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kamdhenu-Ventures-Profit-Halved-Amid-Sales-Slump-Plans-20-Crore-Fundraise/698dc361eb56cdd490ff4cbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kamdhenu-Ventures-Profit-Halved-Amid-Sales-Slump-Plans-20-Crore-Fundraise/698dc361eb56cdd490ff4cbb</guid><description>Kamdhenu Ventures Limited reported a challenging Q3 and nine-month period ended December 31, 2025. Consolidated revenue declined 15% YoY to ₹63.2 crore in Q3 and 7% YoY to ₹170.3 crore for the nine months. Profit After Tax (PAT) halved to ₹1.0 crore in Q3 and fell 40% YoY to ₹2.9 crore for nine months. The company attributes the dip to a tough market and plans a ₹20 crore preferential issue to fund growth in new categories.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:11:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dc361eb56cdd490ff4cba.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ingersoll-Rand India Q3 Profit Soars 78%, EPS Jumps 80%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ingersoll-Rand-India-Q3-Profit-Soars-78percent-EPS-Jumps-80percent/698dc359eb56cdd490ff4cb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ingersoll-Rand-India-Q3-Profit-Soars-78percent-EPS-Jumps-80percent/698dc359eb56cdd490ff4cb2</guid><description>Ingersoll-Rand (India) Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26 with total income rising 12.0% YoY to ₹9.63 Cr. Profit After Tax (PAT) surged 78.0% YoY to ₹0.76 Cr, and Earnings Per Share (EPS) grew 80.5% YoY to ₹0.74. For the nine-month period, PAT increased 49.1% YoY to ₹2.30 Cr. The company maintains a strong balance sheet with net cash of ₹89.58 Cr and a minimal Debt-to-Equity ratio of 0.04.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajasthan Petro Synthetics Q3 Loss, But 9-Month Profit Skyrockets 863%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Rajasthan-Petro-Synthetics-Q3-Loss-But-9-Month-Profit-Skyrockets-863percent/698dc31ceb56cdd490ff4b4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Rajasthan-Petro-Synthetics-Q3-Loss-But-9-Month-Profit-Skyrockets-863percent/698dc31ceb56cdd490ff4b4f</guid><description>Rajasthan Petro Synthetics Limited reported a sharp Q3 FY26 net loss of ₹4 Lakhs on revenues of ₹57 Lakhs, an 89.6% drop YoY. However, for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, revenue surged 65% to ₹1650 Lakhs, with net profit skyrocketing 863% to ₹1445 Lakhs. This signals significant volatility but underlying nine-month strength, with an unmodified auditor's report.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:10:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dc31ceb56cdd490ff4b4e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kamdhenu Ventures Logs Revenue Dip, PAT Halved Amid Rising Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kamdhenu-Ventures-Logs-Revenue-Dip-PAT-Halved-Amid-Rising-Debt/698dc2d3eb56cdd490ff49c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kamdhenu-Ventures-Logs-Revenue-Dip-PAT-Halved-Amid-Rising-Debt/698dc2d3eb56cdd490ff49c0</guid><description>Kamdhenu Ventures reported a challenging Q3 FY26 with revenue down 15% YoY to ₹63.2 Cr and PAT plummeting 50% to ₹1.0 Cr. Nine-month performance also saw declines. While EBITDA margins held steady, PAT margins contracted. The company is bolstering its strategy around product premiumization, aiming for a 42% ASP increase and expanding its dealer network, yet faces rising borrowings and a significant drop in operating cash flow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:08:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dc2d3eb56cdd490ff49bf.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hariom Pipe Logs 21% Revenue Growth, Eyes Expansion Via Solar and Trading</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hariom-Pipe-Logs-21percent-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-Expansion-Via-Solar-and-Trading/698dc2a8eb56cdd490ff4983</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hariom-Pipe-Logs-21percent-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-Expansion-Via-Solar-and-Trading/698dc2a8eb56cdd490ff4983</guid><description>Hariom Pipe Industries reported a robust 21% year-on-year revenue growth for both Q3 and nine months of FY26, reaching INR 1,159.7 crores for the nine months. The company maintained stable EBITDA margins around 12.5% and highlighted increasing contributions from value-added products and B2B sales. Strategic initiatives include the near-completion of a 60 MW solar project and the launch of a new steel trading subsidiary, Metal Mart, aiming to expand market reach and diversify revenue. Management projects around 30% volume growth for FY27.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:08:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698dc2a8eb56cdd490ff4982_1770898782992.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Engineers India Q3 Profit Surges 242% On Project Adjustments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Engineers-India-Q3-Profit-Surges-242percent-On-Project-Adjustments/698dc253eb56cdd490ff4896</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Engineers-India-Q3-Profit-Surges-242percent-On-Project-Adjustments/698dc253eb56cdd490ff4896</guid><description>Engineers India Limited (EIL) has reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with standalone PAT surging 242.5% YoY to ₹301.74 Cr. Consolidated PAT grew 225.9% YoY to ₹305.55 Cr. This remarkable growth was significantly bolstered by substantial accounting adjustments, including an increase in revenue and profit from a turnkey project due to mechanical completion and a write-back of contractual obligations. Revenue from operations saw robust YoY growth of 59.1% standalone and 58.3% consolidated.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:06:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IHCL Q3 Profit Soars 96% on Taj GVK Stake Sale; Acquisitions Boost Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/IHCL-Q3-Profit-Soars-96percent-on-Taj-GVK-Stake-Sale-Acquisitions-Boost-Growth/698dc197eb56cdd490ff4352</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/IHCL-Q3-Profit-Soars-96percent-on-Taj-GVK-Stake-Sale-Acquisitions-Boost-Growth/698dc197eb56cdd490ff4352</guid><description>The Indian Hotels Company Limited (IHCL) reported robust financial results for Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue rising 12.17% YoY to ₹2841.96 Cr and consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 50.8% YoY to ₹954.24 Cr. Standalone PAT saw a dramatic 96.4% jump to ₹920.60 Cr, primarily driven by the sale of its entire stake in Taj GVK Hotels &amp; Resorts Limited. Additionally, its subsidiary, Roots Corporation, acquired 51% stakes in ANK Hotels and Pride Hospitality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:03:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dc197eb56cdd490ff4351.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IHCL Posts 96% PAT Surge on Asset Sale, Buys Stakes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/IHCL-Posts-96percent-PAT-Surge-on-Asset-Sale-Buys-Stakes/698dc18beb56cdd490ff4332</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/IHCL-Posts-96percent-PAT-Surge-on-Asset-Sale-Buys-Stakes/698dc18beb56cdd490ff4332</guid><description>The Indian Hotels Company Limited (IHCL) reported a robust Q3 FY26, with standalone revenue up 9.51% YoY to ₹161,384 lakhs. PAT surged 96.38% to ₹92,060 lakhs, significantly boosted by a ₹43,346 lakh profit from divesting its stake in Taj GVK Hotels &amp; Resorts. Consolidated revenue grew 12.19% YoY. IHCL also completed strategic acquisitions, with Roots Corporation Limited buying majority stakes in ANK Hotels and Pride Hospitality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:03:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dc18beb56cdd490ff4331.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Williamson Magor Auditors Warn of Going Concern Risk Amidst Massive Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Williamson-Magor-Auditors-Warn-of-Going-Concern-Risk-Amidst-Massive-Losses/698dc13ceb56cdd490ff431d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Williamson-Magor-Auditors-Warn-of-Going-Concern-Risk-Amidst-Massive-Losses/698dc13ceb56cdd490ff431d</guid><description>Williamson Magor &amp; Co. Limited's latest unaudited financials for Q3 FY26 have unveiled a precarious financial situation. Auditors have raised a "material uncertainty related to Going Concern," citing the company's net worth being fully eroded. The report details significant non-compliance with RBI norms, loan defaults, and a staggering understatement of finance costs due to non-recognition of substantial interest expenses, casting serious doubt on the company's ability to continue operations. Consolidated net loss for nine months reached ₹1,96,700 thousand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:02:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dc13ceb56cdd490ff431c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GDL, Snowman Hit By Tax Storm; Snowman Margins Plunge Below 3%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/GDL-Snowman-Hit-By-Tax-Storm-Snowman-Margins-Plunge-Below-3percent/698dc112eb56cdd490ff4294</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/GDL-Snowman-Hit-By-Tax-Storm-Snowman-Margins-Plunge-Below-3percent/698dc112eb56cdd490ff4294</guid><description>Gateway Distriparks and Snowman Logistics faced tough questions on numerous tax disputes and Snowman's steep drop in warehousing EBIT margins to below 3%. Management detailed efforts to resolve tax issues and explained margin compression due to business mix shift. GDL announced fleet upgrades and an Indore ICD project, while Snowman plans capacity expansion despite reinvesting profits for growth. Guidance remained general, focusing on adapting to volume mix changes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:01:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dc112eb56cdd490ff4293.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Hosts Landmark AI Summit, Prioritizing Human Impact Over Pure Tech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Hosts-Landmark-AI-Summit-Prioritizing-Human-Impact-Over-Pure-Tech/698dc033eb56cdd490ff3e77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Hosts-Landmark-AI-Summit-Prioritizing-Human-Impact-Over-Pure-Tech/698dc033eb56cdd490ff3e77</guid><description>India hosted the inaugural India AI Impact Summit 2026, a landmark event in the Global South focusing on AI's human impact. Indian Institute of Management Bodh Gaya is championing a 'mindful AI' approach, integrating AI and Sustainability into its curriculum. The institute is pioneering multi-modal, multilingual AI solutions, particularly voice recognition, to bridge the digital literacy gap for grassroots leaders in rural Bihar. This 'applied AI' philosophy aims to strengthen governance and public service delivery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:57:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dc033eb56cdd490ff3e76.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tier-II Housing Market Bifurcates: Volume Drops, Premium Segment Drives Value</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Tier-II-Housing-Market-Bifurcates-Volume-Drops-Premium-Segment-Drives-Value/698dc01feb56cdd490ff3e3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Tier-II-Housing-Market-Bifurcates-Volume-Drops-Premium-Segment-Drives-Value/698dc01feb56cdd490ff3e3d</guid><description>Housing sales volume in 15 tier-II Indian cities fell 10% to 1.56 lakh units in 2025, with value holding at ₹1.48 lakh crore. Rising construction costs are shrinking the sub-₹1 crore segment, pushing demand and sales into properties priced above ₹1 crore, mirroring trends in tier-I cities. Homes below ₹1 crore saw a 15% volume decline, while those above ₹1 crore experienced 9% sales growth, increasing their market share.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:57:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698dc01feb56cdd490ff3e3c_1770898301550.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kalpa Commercial Turns Profitable, Revenue Skyrockets Past Previous Year</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Kalpa-Commercial-Turns-Profitable-Revenue-Skyrockets-Past-Previous-Year/698dbefaeb56cdd490ff3658</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Kalpa-Commercial-Turns-Profitable-Revenue-Skyrockets-Past-Previous-Year/698dbefaeb56cdd490ff3658</guid><description>Kalpa Commercial Limited has reported a significant turnaround, swinging to a net profit of ₹57.33 Lakh in Q3 FY26 from a loss in the prior year. Revenue from operations surged to ₹878.82 Lakh, a 25.50% quarter-on-quarter increase, and already surpassing the entire FY25 audited revenue. The company is assessing the impact of new Labour Codes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:52:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dbefaeb56cdd490ff3657.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Real Touch Finance Q3 Profit Plunges 50% Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Real-Touch-Finance-Q3-Profit-Plunges-50percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth/698dbea4eb56cdd490ff348a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Real-Touch-Finance-Q3-Profit-Plunges-50percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth/698dbea4eb56cdd490ff348a</guid><description>Real Touch Finance Limited reported a stark divergence in its Q3 FY26 results, with total income rising 14.77% year-on-year to ₹878.70 Lakhs. However, profitability was severely hit, with Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeting 50.11% to ₹85.75 Lakhs due to increased finance costs and impairments. Basic EPS fell 50% to ₹0.68. For the nine months, revenue grew 35.26% but PAT saw a modest 7.52% increase.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dbea4eb56cdd490ff3489.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GST Ruling Clarifies 'Fixed Establishment', Easing Service Provider Compliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GST-Ruling-Clarifies-Fixed-Establishment-Easing-Service-Provider-Compliance/698dbe82eb56cdd490ff33dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GST-Ruling-Clarifies-Fixed-Establishment-Easing-Service-Provider-Compliance/698dbe82eb56cdd490ff33dc</guid><description>The Odisha Appellate Authority for Advance Ruling (AAAR) has ruled that Annual Maintenance Contract (AMC) services executed by deputed engineers do not mandate separate GST registration if they don't constitute a 'fixed establishment'. This decision prioritizes the supplier's head office as the nexus for tax liability, significantly easing compliance burdens for companies operating across multiple states.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:50:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698dbe82eb56cdd490ff33db_1770897984128.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>