<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:40 +0000</pubDate><item><title>OYO Parent Prism Files Massive ₹6,650 Crore IPO! Next Big Startup Listing Amidst Profit Turnaround?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/OYO-Parent-Prism-Files-Massive-6650-Crore-IPO-Next-Big-Startup-Listing-Amidst-Profit-Turnaround/69558a7a4342f77179ef7983</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/OYO-Parent-Prism-Files-Massive-6650-Crore-IPO-Next-Big-Startup-Listing-Amidst-Profit-Turnaround/69558a7a4342f77179ef7983</guid><description>Prism, the parent company of hospitality firm OYO, has confidentially filed draft papers for a Rs 6,650 crore Initial Public Offering (IPO) with SEBI. Aiming for a valuation between $7-8 billion, this move follows Prism's achievement of its first full year of net profitability in FY24 and robust growth in gross booking value and revenue. This marks Prism's second attempt at listing after shelving plans in 2021.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:34:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69558a7a4342f77179ef7982_1767214036444.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Billionaire Ranks Shrink! Midcaps Tank, Rupee Dives - See Who's Out!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Billionaire-Ranks-Shrink-Midcaps-Tank-Rupee-Dives-See-Whos-Out/6955785d4342f77179ef6c90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Billionaire-Ranks-Shrink-Midcaps-Tank-Rupee-Dives-See-Whos-Out/6955785d4342f77179ef6c90</guid><description>India's elite club of dollar billionaire promoters saw its numbers fall in 2025 for the first time in three years. A significant selloff in mid and smallcap stocks eroded market values, while a weaker rupee reduced the dollar-denominated wealth of existing billionaires. The total number of such promoters dropped 13.7% to 176, with combined net worth declining 5% to $984.2 billion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:11:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955785d4342f77179ef6c8f_1767209212380.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Concert Boom: How Live Entertainment Became a Massive Money Machine!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Concert-Boom-How-Live-Entertainment-Became-a-Massive-Money-Machine/695569474342f77179ef5150</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Concert-Boom-How-Live-Entertainment-Became-a-Massive-Money-Machine/695569474342f77179ef5150</guid><description>India's live entertainment and concert industry is experiencing exponential growth, transforming from a niche activity into a significant economic engine. Driven by increased ticket sales, professional production, and brand investments, the sector is expanding beyond major cities into tier-two and tier-three markets. This boom is generating substantial economic impact, creating jobs, boosting tourism, and increasing tax revenues, signaling a new era for India's experience-driven economy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:09:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695569474342f77179ef514f_1767205299062.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Soars: 123 Million Passengers Targeted by 2025 Amidst Operational Push!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Soars-123-Million-Passengers-Targeted-by-2025-Amidst-Operational-Push/6955673c4342f77179ef4d3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Soars-123-Million-Passengers-Targeted-by-2025-Amidst-Operational-Push/6955673c4342f77179ef4d3f</guid><description>IndiGo expects to carry over 123 million passengers in 2025, an increase of more than 10 million from 2024. The airline is enhancing operational resilience after recent disruptions and is fully cooperating with the DGCA's investigation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:04:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955673c4342f77179ef4d3e_1767204749467.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Dollar Plunges 10% in Shocking 2025 Fall: Global Economy and Indian Rupee in Turmoil!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Dollar-Plunges-10percent-in-Shocking-2025-Fall-Global-Economy-and-Indian-Rupee-in-Turmoil/695567784342f77179ef4ded</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Dollar-Plunges-10percent-in-Shocking-2025-Fall-Global-Economy-and-Indian-Rupee-in-Turmoil/695567784342f77179ef4ded</guid><description>The US Dollar Index saw its worst performance in over 50 years, falling nearly 10% in 2025. This was driven by uncertainty from President Donald Trump's trade policies and Federal Reserve interest rate cuts. While US exports benefited, consumers faced rising prices ('sneakflation'), and jobs were impacted. Notably, the Indian Rupee weakened significantly against the dollar, falling from Rs.85.56 to Rs.89.87, its sharpest decline in three years, raising questions about the dollar's global safe-haven status.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:01:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695567784342f77179ef4dec_1767204939441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sensex@40: Unlocking 4 Decades of 13.4% Annual Returns! India's Epic Economic Journey Revealed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Sensex40-Unlocking-4-Decades-of-134percent-Annual-Returns-Indias-Epic-Economic-Journey-Revealed/695567614342f77179ef4d7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Sensex40-Unlocking-4-Decades-of-134percent-Annual-Returns-Indias-Epic-Economic-Journey-Revealed/695567614342f77179ef4d7a</guid><description>As India's benchmark Sensex index turns 40 in January 2026, it marks four decades of remarkable growth, delivering a Compound Annual Growth Rate (CAGR) of 13.4%. This journey mirrors India's economic rise, with its nominal GDP growing 12.62% over the same period. The article delves into key historical periods, including the post-liberalization boom, the dot-com bust, the mid-2000s rally, the 2008 crisis, and the more moderate returns of the 2010s and recent years. It also highlights the evolution of the index's constituent companies and sectoral composition, showcasing India's dynamic corporate landscape.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:01:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695567604342f77179ef4d79_1767204967440.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRFC's Massive Infrastructure Push: Rs 5,000 Crore Loan Sanctioned to MAHAGENCO for Power Sector Boost!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IRFCs-Massive-Infrastructure-Push-Rs-5000-Crore-Loan-Sanctioned-to-MAHAGENCO-for-Power-Sector-Boost/695562214342f77179ef45b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IRFCs-Massive-Infrastructure-Push-Rs-5000-Crore-Loan-Sanctioned-to-MAHAGENCO-for-Power-Sector-Boost/695562214342f77179ef45b7</guid><description>Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd (IRFC) has executed a significant Rupee Term Loan Agreement with Maharashtra State Power Generation Company Ltd (MAHAGENCO), sanctioning ₹5,000 crore. A substantial portion, ₹3,000 crore, was disbursed immediately. This financing strengthens IRFC's commitment to supporting critical public sector utilities and infrastructure development beyond its core railway mandate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:40:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695562214342f77179ef45b6_1767203438329.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive Tax Shock! India Rolls Out New Health Cess on Pan Masala &amp; Steeper Duties on Cigarettes from Feb 1!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Massive-Tax-Shock-India-Rolls-Out-New-Health-Cess-on-Pan-Masala-and-Steeper-Duties-on-Cigarettes-from-Feb-1/6955600c4342f77179ef41c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Massive-Tax-Shock-India-Rolls-Out-New-Health-Cess-on-Pan-Masala-and-Steeper-Duties-on-Cigarettes-from-Feb-1/6955600c4342f77179ef41c9</guid><description>India's Finance Ministry has announced new levies on pan masala and tobacco products, including cigarettes, effective February 1. The Health Security Cess Act will impose a cess on pan masala, while the Central Excise (Amendment) Act introduces additional excise duty on cigarettes and other tobacco items. These measures aim to maintain the existing tax burden on these 'sin goods' by replacing the compensation cess, with revenues earmarked for public health, national security, and funding public health initiatives.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:29:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955600c4342f77179ef41c8_1767202992048.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sammaan Capital Board Approves NBFC Merger, Clearing Path for $1 Billion IHC Investment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sammaan-Capital-Board-Approves-NBFC-Merger-Clearing-Path-for-1-Billion-IHC-Investment/69555c704342f77179ef3bca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sammaan-Capital-Board-Approves-NBFC-Merger-Clearing-Path-for-1-Billion-IHC-Investment/69555c704342f77179ef3bca</guid><description>Sammaan Capital's board has approved a scheme to merge its subsidiary, Samman Finserv's non-banking financial company (NBFC) business, into the parent entity. This move involves surrendering the NBFC license to consolidate lending operations and meet regulatory requirements for a significant $1 billion investment from Abu Dhabi's International Holding Company (IHC). The consolidation aims to enhance governance, operational clarity, and prepare Sammaan Capital for expansion into multi-product lending, fintech, and alternative investment funds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:10:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69555c704342f77179ef3bc9_1767202036172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Extends Key Steel Input Import Ban: What This Means for Prices!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Extends-Key-Steel-Input-Import-Ban-What-This-Means-for-Prices/69555b594342f77179ef39cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Extends-Key-Steel-Input-Import-Ban-What-This-Means-for-Prices/69555b594342f77179ef39cb</guid><description>India has extended import restrictions on low-ash metallurgical coke, a critical component for steelmaking, until June 30, 2026. The ban, effective from January 1, 2026, specifically targets coke with less than 18% ash content. Imports of high-ash metallurgical coke (above 18% ash) will continue to be permitted freely. This move aims to manage domestic supply and potentially impact raw material costs for the steel industry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:09:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69555b594342f77179ef39ca_1767201799268.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's EV Two-Wheeler Boom: TVS Motor Races Ahead as Millions Register! What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Two-Wheeler-Boom-TVS-Motor-Races-Ahead-as-Millions-Register-Whats-Next/69555a454342f77179ef3782</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Two-Wheeler-Boom-TVS-Motor-Races-Ahead-as-Millions-Register-Whats-Next/69555a454342f77179ef3782</guid><description>India's electric two-wheeler market surged in 2025, surpassing 1.27 million registrations. TVS Motor emerged as the leader with a 23.5% market share, driven by its iQube range. Bajaj Auto secured the second position with 24.9%, while Ola Electric followed at 18.8%, and Ather Energy at 14.2%. The market is set for intensified competition in 2026, with price adjustments and new model launches anticipated due to rising component costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:07:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69555a454342f77179ef3781_1767201443090.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Governor's Bold Year-End Message: Stability, Growth, and Simplified Rules Navigate Global Chaos!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Governors-Bold-Year-End-Message-Stability-Growth-and-Simplified-Rules-Navigate-Global-Chaos/695559084342f77179ef3494</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Governors-Bold-Year-End-Message-Stability-Growth-and-Simplified-Rules-Navigate-Global-Chaos/695559084342f77179ef3494</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India Governor Sanjay Malhotra's year-end letter revealed calibrated policy actions in 2025 balanced economic stability with growth amidst global uncertainties. The central bank institutionalized a structured framework for simplified regulations, consolidating thousands of circulars. Key economic indicators showed progress, with retail inflation averaging 2.3% and GDP growth at 7.8% in the reported periods. The RBI remains focused on strengthening monetary policy, supervision, and financial markets for 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695559084342f77179ef3493_1767201432255.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Issues Stark Warning: Stablecoins Threaten India's Monetary Sovereignty &amp; Financial Stability!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Issues-Stark-Warning-Stablecoins-Threaten-Indias-Monetary-Sovereignty-and-Financial-Stability/695559444342f77179ef3538</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Issues-Stark-Warning-Stablecoins-Threaten-Indias-Monetary-Sovereignty-and-Financial-Stability/695559444342f77179ef3538</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has cautioned that widespread adoption of stablecoins poses significant risks to India's monetary sovereignty and financial stability. The central bank highlighted vulnerabilities in stablecoins that could undermine monetary policy control and introduce new financial stability risks, especially during market stress. The RBI strongly advocates for prioritizing Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) over privately issued stablecoins to maintain trust and security in the financial system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695559444342f77179ef3537_1767201378536.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Sector Skyrockets: PLI Scheme Fuels ₹35,657 Cr Investment &amp; 48,974 Jobs – But Firms Face Govt Crackdown!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Sector-Skyrockets-PLI-Scheme-Fuels-35657-Cr-Investment-and-48974-Jobs-But-Firms-Face-Govt-Crackdown/6955579e4342f77179ef31b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Sector-Skyrockets-PLI-Scheme-Fuels-35657-Cr-Investment-and-48974-Jobs-But-Firms-Face-Govt-Crackdown/6955579e4342f77179ef31b5</guid><description>India's Production-Linked Incentive (PLI) Auto scheme has attracted a significant ₹35,657 crore in cumulative investment and generated ₹32,879 crore in sales up to September 30, 2025, creating 48,974 jobs by September this year. The Heavy Industries Ministry is now set to invoke bank guarantees for 10 firms that have made zero investment, signaling a strict approach to compliance for the program running until 2027-28. Incentives totaling ₹1,999.94 crore have already been disbursed to five major auto players for the 2024-25 performance year.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:54:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955579e4342f77179ef31b4_1767200848777.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2025 Wrap: Indian Markets End Green But Lag Global Peers! Rupee Woes, RBI Confidence &amp; Vodafone Idea Drama Unpacked!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2025-Wrap-Indian-Markets-End-Green-But-Lag-Global-Peers-Rupee-Woes-RBI-Confidence-and-Vodafone-Idea-Drama-Unpacked/695554bb4342f77179ef2be6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2025-Wrap-Indian-Markets-End-Green-But-Lag-Global-Peers-Rupee-Woes-RBI-Confidence-and-Vodafone-Idea-Drama-Unpacked/695554bb4342f77179ef2be6</guid><description>Indian equity markets concluded 2025 positively for the tenth consecutive year but underperformed global peers amid domestic and global headwinds. The Indian Rupee faced significant volatility, depreciating nearly 5% against the US dollar. The Reserve Bank of India affirmed the financial system's resilience, while Vodafone Idea shares fell due to AGR dues. Bharat Forge secured a defence contract, and India imposed steel import tariffs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:39:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695554bb4342f77179ef2be5_1767200156877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Global Trade Forecast: Trump's Strategy, AI Race &amp; India's Strategic Pivot!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-Global-Trade-Forecast-Trumps-Strategy-AI-Race-and-Indias-Strategic-Pivot/6955520a4342f77179ef26bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-Global-Trade-Forecast-Trumps-Strategy-AI-Race-and-Indias-Strategic-Pivot/6955520a4342f77179ef26bd</guid><description>As 2026 dawns, the global landscape faces major shifts in trade and geopolitics. Expect continued influence from US President Donald Trump's trade tactics, alongside the burgeoning AI race and critical mineral competition between the US and China. India is navigating these changes by diversifying exports away from the US and focusing on 'near-shoring' and new trade pacts, though rupee volatility remains a concern.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:30:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955520a4342f77179ef26bc_1767199523639.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver's Record Year Ends With a Bang! Best Gains Since the 70s, But What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silvers-Record-Year-Ends-With-a-Bang-Best-Gains-Since-the-70s-But-Whats-Next/695550294342f77179ef22f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silvers-Record-Year-Ends-With-a-Bang-Best-Gains-Since-the-70s-But-Whats-Next/695550294342f77179ef22f2</guid><description>Gold and silver concluded 2025 on a shaky note, falling on the last trading day. However, they are set to achieve their most significant annual gains since the 1970s. This remarkable performance was fueled by strong demand for safe-haven assets amidst geopolitical tensions and interest rate cuts by the US Federal Reserve. Gold prices surged approximately 64%, while silver prices climbed nearly 150%. Extreme volatility prompted CME Group to increase margin requirements multiple times, impacting traders.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:24:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695550294342f77179ef22f1_1767199178799.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dollar's Worst Year in 8 Years! Is Fed Uncertainty About to Sink It Further?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dollars-Worst-Year-in-8-Years-Is-Fed-Uncertainty-About-to-Sink-It-Further/69554fe84342f77179ef2272</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dollars-Worst-Year-in-8-Years-Is-Fed-Uncertainty-About-to-Sink-It-Further/69554fe84342f77179ef2272</guid><description>The U.S. Dollar is set for its steepest annual decline since 2017, down around 8%. This is largely driven by expectations of future interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve and uncertainty over President Trump's nominee for the Fed Chair position. This policy divergence from other major economies, which are not cutting rates or are considering hikes, is dimming the dollar's appeal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:24:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69554fe84342f77179ef2271_1767198770073.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Investment Secrets: 2 Top Experts Reveal Their Game-Changing Portfolio Strategies!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/2026-Investment-Secrets-2-Top-Experts-Reveal-Their-Game-Changing-Portfolio-Strategies/69554da54342f77179ef1d61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/2026-Investment-Secrets-2-Top-Experts-Reveal-Their-Game-Changing-Portfolio-Strategies/69554da54342f77179ef1d61</guid><description>Following a year of modest returns, Indian equity investors are questioning how to position portfolios for 2026 amid global uncertainty. Two leading market experts, Feroze Azeez of Anand Rathi Wealth and Mohit Gang of Moneyfront, emphasize disciplined asset allocation and diversification over aggressive stock picking. Their advice includes a strong focus on equities, strategic shifts towards gold over traditional debt, and the importance of global diversification for medium-risk investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:10:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69554da54342f77179ef1d60_1767198279359.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Sounds Alarm: NBFCs' Foreign Debt Makes Them Risky Bets on Rupee Swings!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Sounds-Alarm-NBFCs-Foreign-Debt-Makes-Them-Risky-Bets-on-Rupee-Swings/695548204342f77179ef134e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Sounds-Alarm-NBFCs-Foreign-Debt-Makes-Them-Risky-Bets-on-Rupee-Swings/695548204342f77179ef134e</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has warned that Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs) are becoming more vulnerable to currency fluctuations due to their increasing reliance on external borrowings. While most foreign currency debt is hedged, potential exchange rate volatility could still impact profitability, even as the sector shows improved headline asset quality alongside rising stress in loan portfolios.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695548204342f77179ef134d_1767196893371.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea DENIES Govt Relief Reports Amidst Rs 87,695 Cr AGR Dues Freeze!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-DENIES-Govt-Relief-Reports-Amidst-Rs-87695-Cr-AGR-Dues-Freeze/695546be4342f77179ef1016</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-DENIES-Govt-Relief-Reports-Amidst-Rs-87695-Cr-AGR-Dues-Freeze/695546be4342f77179ef1016</guid><description>Vodafone Idea has clarified it has not received any official communication from the government regarding a reported relief package for its Rs 87,695 crore AGR dues. Media speculation about Union Cabinet approval for freezing these dues with a moratorium caused share price volatility. The company awaits official developments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:40:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695546be4342f77179ef1015_1767196572431.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSNL Mega Deal: Pace Digitek Secures ₹94 Crore Lithium-Ion Battery Order – Investors Buzzing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/BSNL-Mega-Deal-Pace-Digitek-Secures-94-Crore-Lithium-Ion-Battery-Order-Investors-Buzzing/6955463b4342f77179ef0e3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/BSNL-Mega-Deal-Pace-Digitek-Secures-94-Crore-Lithium-Ion-Battery-Order-Investors-Buzzing/6955463b4342f77179ef0e3e</guid><description>Pace Digitek's subsidiary, Lineage Power Private Limited, has secured a substantial ₹94.35 crore order from Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited (BSNL) for lithium-ion battery solutions. The order includes supplying 25,000 battery modules and 2,500 racks, along with a five-year maintenance contract post-warranty. This significant win boosts the company's energy storage segment and was reflected in its stock performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:40:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955463b4342f77179ef0e3d_1767196406700.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HUDCO's Q3 Loan Sanctions Skyrocket to ₹46,167 Cr, Fueling Investor Excitement!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HUDCOs-Q3-Loan-Sanctions-Skyrocket-to-46167-Cr-Fueling-Investor-Excitement/695545b24342f77179ef0ca3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HUDCOs-Q3-Loan-Sanctions-Skyrocket-to-46167-Cr-Fueling-Investor-Excitement/695545b24342f77179ef0ca3</guid><description>Housing and Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO) reported robust business performance for the first nine months of FY26. Loan sanctions reached a provisional ₹1.39 lakh crore, with ₹46,167.32 crore sanctioned in the third quarter alone. Disbursements for the nine-month period stood at ₹41,346.70 crore, including ₹15,508.25 crore in Q3 FY26. The company also signed an MoU with the National Institute of Urban Affairs (NIUA) to enhance cooperation in urban infrastructure development. HUDCO shares closed 1.57% higher on December 31, 2025, at ₹227.50.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:40:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695545b24342f77179ef0ca2_1767196434046.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Buzz: SBI MF Buys Big in Privi Speciality, Promoters Exit Vishnu Prakash R Punglia – What It Means!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Buzz-SBI-MF-Buys-Big-in-Privi-Speciality-Promoters-Exit-Vishnu-Prakash-R-Punglia-What-It-Means/695545f54342f77179ef0d3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Buzz-SBI-MF-Buys-Big-in-Privi-Speciality-Promoters-Exit-Vishnu-Prakash-R-Punglia-What-It-Means/695545f54342f77179ef0d3d</guid><description>On December 31, SBI Mutual Fund significantly increased its stake in Privi Speciality Chemicals by acquiring nearly 6% equity for ₹634.8 crore. This comes as promoter entity Vivira Investment and Trading offloaded over 9% of its stake in the aroma and fragrance chemicals manufacturer. Meanwhile, promoters also sold 4.01% in infrastructure firm Vishnu Prakash R Punglia, leading to stock price declines for both companies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:37:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695545f54342f77179ef0d3c_1767196390326.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Millions to Keep Earning Same Returns: India's Small Savings Rates Unchanged for Jan-Mar 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Millions-to-Keep-Earning-Same-Returns-Indias-Small-Savings-Rates-Unchanged-for-Jan-Mar-2026/695544404342f77179ef091d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Millions-to-Keep-Earning-Same-Returns-Indias-Small-Savings-Rates-Unchanged-for-Jan-Mar-2026/695544404342f77179ef091d</guid><description>India's Finance Ministry has announced that interest rates on popular small savings schemes, including Public Provident Fund (PPF), Sukanya Samriddhi Scheme, and National Savings Certificate (NSC), will remain unchanged for the January to March 2026 quarter. This marks the seventh consecutive quarter where the government has maintained the status quo, offering millions of household savers predictable returns on these low-risk investment options. Rates for schemes like Sukanya Samriddhi (8.2%) and PPF (7.1%) will continue as before.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:32:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695544404342f77179ef091c_1767195801688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Gig Economy Set for Explosive Growth: 2 Million New Jobs Expected in 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Gig-Economy-Set-for-Explosive-Growth-2-Million-New-Jobs-Expected-in-2026/695544444342f77179ef0948</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Gig-Economy-Set-for-Explosive-Growth-2-Million-New-Jobs-Expected-in-2026/695544444342f77179ef0948</guid><description>Demand for gig and contract workers in India is projected to surge in 2026, with firms expecting a need for approximately 20 lakh additional workers. This expansion is fueled by quick commerce companies broadening their reach into tier-2 cities beyond major metros. While growth is strong, gig worker unions are escalating protests demanding better pay, safety, and social security, even threatening strikes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:31:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695544444342f77179ef0947_1767195815834.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Bombshell: Insurers &amp; Pension Funds Abandon Bonds, Yield Curve Skyrockets! What Investors MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Bombshell-Insurers-and-Pension-Funds-Abandon-Bonds-Yield-Curve-Skyrockets-What-Investors-MUST-Know/695540a24342f77179eefff5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Bombshell-Insurers-and-Pension-Funds-Abandon-Bonds-Yield-Curve-Skyrockets-What-Investors-MUST-Know/695540a24342f77179eefff5</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Financial Stability Report reveals a significant shift as insurance companies and pension funds reduce their holdings of government securities, despite rising issuance. This has led to a steepening yield curve, with short-term rates falling while long-term yields rise due to persistent supply. Foreign investor inflows remain robust, but the Indian rupee has weakened against the US dollar amid trade concerns and moderating capital flows, increasing market volatility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:11:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695540a24342f77179eefff4_1767194986507.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC Stock Hits First Annual Loss Since 2020: Expert Reveals Buy Signal or Sell Warning?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-Hits-First-Annual-Loss-Since-2020-Expert-Reveals-Buy-Signal-or-Sell-Warning/695540924342f77179eeffa5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-Hits-First-Annual-Loss-Since-2020-Expert-Reveals-Buy-Signal-or-Sell-Warning/695540924342f77179eeffa5</guid><description>ITC Limited experienced its first negative annual return in 2025 since 2020, ending the year down 12%. Despite this, analysts remain bullish long-term, citing the company's strong fundamentals, steady FMCG growth, and demerger of its hotels business as positive catalysts. The current stock price around ₹400 is viewed as a buying opportunity for patient investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:10:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695540924342f77179eeffa4_1767195055969.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2025's Mega Splits: ITC, Tata Motors, HUL Lead Massive Corporate Demergers Unlocking Hidden Value!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2025s-Mega-Splits-ITC-Tata-Motors-HUL-Lead-Massive-Corporate-Demergers-Unlocking-Hidden-Value/695541044342f77179ef0100</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2025s-Mega-Splits-ITC-Tata-Motors-HUL-Lead-Massive-Corporate-Demergers-Unlocking-Hidden-Value/695541044342f77179ef0100</guid><description>2025 has been a pivotal year for corporate restructuring in India, marked by a surge in demergers. Major companies including ITC, Tata Motors, Hindustan Unilever, Siemens Energy, Aditya Birla Fashion and Retail, and Dalmia Bharat Sugar have strategically separated key business units. These moves are designed to unlock shareholder value, improve operational focus, and enhance market positioning, fundamentally reshaping ownership and operational landscapes across various sectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:10:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695541044342f77179ef00ff_1767195111709.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Surges 190 Points, Ends 2025 High! Can it Break 26,250 in 2026? Investors Watch Closely!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Surges-190-Points-Ends-2025-High-Can-it-Break-26250-in-2026-Investors-Watch-Closely/69553fb54342f77179eefc42</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Surges-190-Points-Ends-2025-High-Can-it-Break-26250-in-2026-Investors-Watch-Closely/69553fb54342f77179eefc42</guid><description>Indian equities concluded 2025 on a high, with the Nifty surging nearly 190 points to 26,129, driven by broad-based buying. Key drivers included Reliance Industries and banking stocks, while steel shares rallied sharply due to government safeguard duties. The Nifty achieved a 10.5% gain for the year. Experts are cautiously optimistic for 2026, anticipating steady growth supported by earnings recovery and policy measures. Technical levels suggest the Nifty is eyeing resistance around 26,250-26,350.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:10:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553fb54342f77179eefc41_1767194838239.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India &amp; IndiGo Reveal HUGE 2026 Fleet Plans: New Planes, Global Expansion &amp; More!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-and-IndiGo-Reveal-HUGE-2026-Fleet-Plans-New-Planes-Global-Expansion-and-More/69553fd84342f77179eefcb7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-and-IndiGo-Reveal-HUGE-2026-Fleet-Plans-New-Planes-Global-Expansion-and-More/69553fd84342f77179eefcb7</guid><description>Air India and IndiGo have announced ambitious plans for 2026. Air India will reintroduce two retrofitted Boeing 787-8 aircraft in February, with more to follow monthly, alongside new A350s and refits for its 777 fleet. IndiGo will induct its first Airbus A321XLR, expand international services to Athens, and expects to carry over 123 million passengers in 2025, aiming to enhance operational reliability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:10:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553fd84342f77179eefcb6_1767194848814.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India Faces DGCA Probe Over Risky Dreamliner Flights Amid Safety Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Faces-DGCA-Probe-Over-Risky-Dreamliner-Flights-Amid-Safety-Concerns/69553f8f4342f77179eefbcc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Faces-DGCA-Probe-Over-Risky-Dreamliner-Flights-Amid-Safety-Concerns/69553f8f4342f77179eefbcc</guid><description>Aviation regulator DGCA has issued a show-cause notice to Air India demanding an explanation for operating a Boeing 787-8 Dreamliner (VT-ANI) despite repeated technical snags. The notice highlights safety concerns related to Minimum Equipment List (MEL) non-compliance and flight crew decisions during operations on flights AI 258 and AI 357, potentially affecting the Delhi-Tokyo route.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:10:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553f8f4342f77179eefbcb_1767194726926.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump Media's Bold Crypto Move: Shareholders Set for FREE Digital Tokens!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Trump-Medias-Bold-Crypto-Move-Shareholders-Set-for-FREE-Digital-Tokens/695540004342f77179eefd21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Trump-Medias-Bold-Crypto-Move-Shareholders-Set-for-FREE-Digital-Tokens/695540004342f77179eefd21</guid><description>Trump Media and Technology Group (DJT) plans to distribute a new digital token to shareholders via a partnership with Crypto.com. Each shareholder will receive one token per DJT share, with potential rewards and benefits linked to Truth Social products. The announcement saw DJT shares rise in pre-market trading.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:08:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695540004342f77179eefd20_1767194741782.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India in Hot Water: DGCA Slams Airline Over Repeated Dreamliner Snags, Demands Answers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-in-Hot-Water-DGCA-Slams-Airline-Over-Repeated-Dreamliner-Snags-Demands-Answers/69553e344342f77179eef817</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-in-Hot-Water-DGCA-Slams-Airline-Over-Repeated-Dreamliner-Snags-Demands-Answers/69553e344342f77179eef817</guid><description>India's aviation regulator, the DGCA, has issued a show-cause notice to Air India demanding an explanation for operating a Boeing 787-8 Dreamliner (VT-ANI) despite recurring technical issues. The notice highlights safety concerns, including non-compliance with the Minimum Equipment List (MEL) during flights on the Delhi-Tokyo route.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:05:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553e344342f77179eef816_1767194360077.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fiscal Tightrope: Deficit Hits ₹9.76 Lakh Crore! Are Investors Watching?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Tightrope-Deficit-Hits-976-Lakh-Crore-Are-Investors-Watching/69553de04342f77179eef6f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Tightrope-Deficit-Hits-976-Lakh-Crore-Are-Investors-Watching/69553de04342f77179eef6f0</guid><description>India's fiscal deficit for April-November reached ₹9.76 lakh crore, accounting for 63% of the full fiscal year's budget estimate. This is a significant increase compared to the same period last year, which stood at 53% of the budget estimate. Government receipts are at 55.7% of the estimate, with tax revenues showing mixed performance, while expenditure is at 57.8%, driven by interest payments and subsidies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:02:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553de04342f77179eef6ef_1767194393534.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EU Carbon Tax Looming: Will India's Crucial FTA Talks Collapse or Secure Lifeline for Exporters?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EU-Carbon-Tax-Looming-Will-Indias-Crucial-FTA-Talks-Collapse-or-Secure-Lifeline-for-Exporters/69553df84342f77179eef74a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EU-Carbon-Tax-Looming-Will-Indias-Crucial-FTA-Talks-Collapse-or-Secure-Lifeline-for-Exporters/69553df84342f77179eef74a</guid><description>India is seeking critical exemptions from the European Union's Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (CBAM), set to take effect January 1, 2026. These EU carbon taxes could force Indian steel and aluminium exporters to cut prices by up to 22%, impacting competitiveness. Negotiations for a Free Trade Agreement (FTA) between India and the EU are in their final stages, with India pushing for flexibility on CBAM and other regulations to protect its carbon-intensive industries and ensure market access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553df84342f77179eef749_1767194359352.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mutual Funds Skyrocket: India's AUM Hits Astounding ₹81 Lakh Crore Milestone!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Mutual-Funds-Skyrocket-Indias-AUM-Hits-Astounding-81-Lakh-Crore-Milestone/69553d3e4342f77179eef495</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Mutual-Funds-Skyrocket-Indias-AUM-Hits-Astounding-81-Lakh-Crore-Milestone/69553d3e4342f77179eef495</guid><description>India's mutual fund industry has achieved a significant milestone, with assets under management (AUM) surging 19% year-on-year to reach ₹81 lakh crore by the end of November. Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) played a crucial role, contributing ₹1 lakh crore with a 63% increase year-on-year. Equity schemes hold ₹36 lakh crore, while non-equity schemes manage ₹45 lakh crore, reflecting strong retail investor demand for equity exposure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553d3e4342f77179eef494_1767193997160.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Jobless Claims Plunge to 2024 Lows Amid Holiday Season Volatility!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Jobless-Claims-Plunge-to-2024-Lows-Amid-Holiday-Season-Volatility/69553ab64342f77179eeee0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Jobless-Claims-Plunge-to-2024-Lows-Amid-Holiday-Season-Volatility/69553ab64342f77179eeee0a</guid><description>US unemployment benefit applications dropped significantly to 199,000 during the Christmas week, reaching one of the lowest points this year. Despite typical holiday data volatility, this figure undershot economist expectations and signals a resilient labor market, though overall hiring has been sluggish.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:54:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553ab64342f77179eeee09_1767193347984.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Sounds Alarm: Are Bank-NBFC Loan Deals Posing Hidden Risks to Your Investments?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Sounds-Alarm-Are-Bank-NBFC-Loan-Deals-Posing-Hidden-Risks-to-Your-Investments/6955382f4342f77179eee656</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Sounds-Alarm-Are-Bank-NBFC-Loan-Deals-Posing-Hidden-Risks-to-Your-Investments/6955382f4342f77179eee656</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Financial Stability Report highlights concerns over banks aggressively buying loans from non-banking finance companies (NBFCs) to boost retail portfolios. The report warns of concentration risks, as banks source nearly 80% of these assets from a few NBFCs, potentially amplifying financial stress and leading to weaker credit performance compared to banks' own loan originations, particularly for public sector lenders.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955382f4342f77179eee655_1767192988084.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Boosts Dollar Bets: Is Rupee Stability at Risk?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Boosts-Dollar-Bets-Is-Rupee-Stability-at-Risk/695538214342f77179eee609</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Boosts-Dollar-Bets-Is-Rupee-Stability-at-Risk/695538214342f77179eee609</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's net short dollar position in the rupee forward market rose to $66.04 billion by end-November, up from $63.6 billion in October. This indicates increased intervention to manage currency volatility. Meanwhile, the Real Effective Exchange Rate (REER) remained stable at 97.51, suggesting potential challenges for export competitiveness if the rupee strengthens significantly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:40:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695538214342f77179eee608_1767192801189.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>