<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:24:30 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Rent vs. Buy Debate: Wealth Shift Amidst Rising Prices</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Rent-vs-Buy-Debate-Wealth-Shift-Amidst-Rising-Prices/69992e21730b6847a51737ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Rent-vs-Buy-Debate-Wealth-Shift-Amidst-Rising-Prices/69992e21730b6847a51737ad</guid><description>In India's 2026 property market, soaring home prices are increasingly outpacing salary growth, intensifying the rent versus buy dilemma. Changes in tax laws and robust returns from alternative investments are compelling a pragmatic re-evaluation, positioning renting not just as a lifestyle choice but a financially astute strategy for many. While property values climb, compressed rental yields and affordability concerns are reshaping wealth-building narratives beyond traditional homeownership.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:01:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69992e21730b6847a51737ac_1771646598000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Industrial Giants Secure Major Global Orders</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Industrial-Giants-Secure-Major-Global-Orders/699925a0730b6847a51735c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Industrial-Giants-Secure-Major-Global-Orders/699925a0730b6847a51735c9</guid><description>Indian companies across energy, infrastructure, and engineering sectors have secured substantial orders this week. Cochin Shipyard's ₹3,267 crore deal with CMA CGM for LNG vessels marks a turning point in global shipbuilding sourcing. BHEL secured a ₹1,200-1,500 crore power project from SAIL, while Power Mech Projects won ₹1,000 crore from Adani Power. These wins underscore India's growing industrial prowess and its increasing role in international projects, driven by government support and evolving global dynamics.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 03:25:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699925a0730b6847a51735c8_1771644493716.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Banks Monitor West Asia Risk Amid Resilience Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Banks-Monitor-West-Asia-Risk-Amid-Resilience-Drive/69992481730b6847a51734fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Banks-Monitor-West-Asia-Risk-Amid-Resilience-Drive/69992481730b6847a51734fb</guid><description>Finance Secretary M. Nagaraju stated that the Indian government is closely monitoring geopolitical developments in West Asia and assessing the nation's financial exposure to the region. Despite rising global uncertainties, including potential conflict stemming from US-Iran tensions, the Indian banking system and economy are deemed resilient. The government is also focused on the long-term evolution of banking, emphasizing credit provision remaining bank-dominated and guiding the sector's transformation over the next two to three decades.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 03:20:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69992481730b6847a51734fa_1771644187019.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OpenAI's $850B Valuation Bets on $280B Revenue Amid Spending Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAIs-850B-Valuation-Bets-on-280B-Revenue-Amid-Spending-Shift/69991bbb730b6847a517325c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAIs-850B-Valuation-Bets-on-280B-Revenue-Amid-Spending-Shift/69991bbb730b6847a517325c</guid><description>OpenAI is projecting revenues to exceed $280 billion by 2030, buoyed by a potential $100 billion+ funding round that could push its valuation past $850 billion. This ambitious outlook is tempered by a significant recalibration of its infrastructure spending, now targeting $600 billion by 2030, down from a previous $1.4 trillion projection. This adjustment reflects growing investor scrutiny on the immense capital required to fuel AI advancements, even as competitors like Anthropic also secure substantial funding.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 02:43:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69991bbb730b6847a517325b_1771641912690.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Embraer's India FAL Gambit: 200 Orders as High Bar</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Embraers-India-FAL-Gambit-200-Orders-as-High-Bar/69991529730b6847a5171850</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Embraers-India-FAL-Gambit-200-Orders-as-High-Bar/69991529730b6847a5171850</guid><description>Embraer is pushing for a commercial fixed-wing aircraft final assembly line (FAL) in India, contingent on firm orders exceeding 200 jets. President and CEO Francisco Gomes Neto indicated this threshold is crucial for viability, with a potential 2028 rollout if orders materialize this year. This move comes as India's aviation market is projected to require at least 500 regional jets, driven by rapid growth and government initiatives like UDAN. Embraer also eyes a 'completion center' as an interim step, while facing competition and a cautious stance from global giants like Boeing and Airbus on establishing similar manufacturing hubs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 02:15:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69991529730b6847a517184f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerage Bets: AI, Silver Drive 10 Stocks Amid Mixed Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokerage-Bets-AI-Silver-Drive-10-Stocks-Amid-Mixed-Valuations/69990fa3730b6847a5171674</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokerage-Bets-AI-Silver-Drive-10-Stocks-Amid-Mixed-Valuations/69990fa3730b6847a5171674</guid><description>Indian equities saw a wave of positive brokerage recommendations this week, spotlighting ten stocks across diverse sectors. Analysts are betting on AI-driven growth for IT giants like Infosys, sustained demand for metals from Tata Steel, and a persistent silver deficit supporting Hindustan Zinc. Pharmaceutical firms such as Lupin are favored for their complex generics, while packaging solutions from EPL Limited and paint demand for Indigo Paints also feature. Go Digit's unique underwriting model and IHCL's hospitality strength draw 'Buy' ratings, alongside LG Electronics India and Lenskart for their market positions. Despite optimism, several counters face scrutiny over elevated valuations and past performance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:51:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69990fa3730b6847a5171673.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LTI Mindtree Navigates AI Shift: Diamond Workforce &amp; Brownfield Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/LTI-Mindtree-Navigates-AI-Shift-Diamond-Workforce-and-Brownfield-Hurdles/69990fa2730b6847a517165d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/LTI-Mindtree-Navigates-AI-Shift-Diamond-Workforce-and-Brownfield-Hurdles/69990fa2730b6847a517165d</guid><description>LTI Mindtree's Chief Delivery Officer Gururaj Deshpande predicts a 'diamond' workforce, with fewer entry-level roles due to AI automation. The firm focuses on simplifying AI for enterprises overwhelmed by options, acting as a structure and governance enabler rather than a foundational model builder. This strategy addresses the significant challenges of scaling AI in complex, legacy brownfield environments, where operating models must be rethought for consistency and scalability, not just tool deployment. Amidst broader sector concerns over AI disruption and recent stock declines, LTI Mindtree's approach positions it to manage margin pressures and talent evolution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:51:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69990fa2730b6847a517165c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defense Electronics Boom: Valuation Premiums Face Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defense-Electronics-Boom-Valuation-Premiums-Face-Scrutiny/69990f28730b6847a5171598</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defense-Electronics-Boom-Valuation-Premiums-Face-Scrutiny/69990f28730b6847a5171598</guid><description>India's defense sector is pivoting from traditional hardware to sophisticated electronics, with Kaynes Technology and Avalon Technologies leading the charge as key component suppliers. While revenue and order books show strong growth, the companies trade at substantial valuation premiums. This report analyzes their market position, competitive landscape, and the critical risks that could challenge their sky-high valuations, contrasting them with sector peers and broader industry trends.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:49:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69990f28730b6847a5171597_1771638683872.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Smart Meter Boom: Genus, Techno, HPL Face Execution Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Smart-Meter-Boom-Genus-Techno-HPL-Face-Execution-Test/69990f11730b6847a5171581</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Smart-Meter-Boom-Genus-Techno-HPL-Face-Execution-Test/69990f11730b6847a5171581</guid><description>India's ambitious smart meter program, targeting 250-300 million installations, presents a substantial ₹60,000-90,000 crore market opportunity. Genus Power leads in scale and market share, Techno Electric excels in high-speed execution and annuity revenue, and HPL Electric diversifies into water metering. However, sustained growth hinges on operational efficiency, balance sheet strength, and navigating competitive pressures as the sector matures.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69990f11730b6847a5171580.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI: IMF Flags Tsunami Risk, Growth Duality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-IMF-Flags-Tsunami-Risk-Growth-Duality/69990df9730b6847a51714c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-IMF-Flags-Tsunami-Risk-Growth-Duality/69990df9730b6847a51714c3</guid><description>The IMF warns AI's labor market impact is a "tsunami," potentially displacing 40% of jobs globally and widening inequality. While projecting a 0.8% global growth boost, the fund highlights severe financial stability risks, including market volatility and increased systemic vulnerabilities. Investors and policymakers face the critical challenge of managing these dualities.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:44:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69990df9730b6847a51714c2_1771638369220.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kyndryl's India AI Push Faces Scrutiny Amid Reporting Issues</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kyndryls-India-AI-Push-Faces-Scrutiny-Amid-Reporting-Issues/6999062a730b6847a51712aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kyndryls-India-AI-Push-Faces-Scrutiny-Amid-Reporting-Issues/6999062a730b6847a51712aa</guid><description>Kyndryl is aggressively expanding its AI and digital transformation services in India, with a new AI Innovation Lab in Bengaluru and plans to train 50,000 students in AI literacy. This strategic push aims to bolster governance and cybersecurity initiatives. However, the company is currently under heightened investor scrutiny following a significant stock price drop in early February 2026, triggered by a delayed Q4 fiscal 2025 earnings report, disclosures of material internal control weaknesses, and the departure of key finance executives. A securities class-action lawsuit is also pending, compounding concerns about financial transparency and reporting integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:11:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999062a730b6847a51712a9_1771636386396.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Muni Bonds Gain Scale, Eye Institutional Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Muni-Bonds-Gain-Scale-Eye-Institutional-Capital/699900ad730b6847a5171146</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Muni-Bonds-Gain-Scale-Eye-Institutional-Capital/699900ad730b6847a5171146</guid><description>India's municipal bond market is undergoing a structural transformation. The Union Budget 2026-27 introduced a ₹100 crore incentive for issuances exceeding ₹1,000 crore, aiming to attract institutional capital by promoting scale, corporate-like financial discipline, and advanced credit mechanisms such as escrow accounts. This initiative moves the market beyond its historically fragmented and illiquid state, potentially enhancing its depth and tradability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:47:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699900ad730b6847a5171145_1771634960446.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nitin Castings Proposes BSE Voluntary Delisting at ₹273.36 Floor Price</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nitin-Castings-Proposes-BSE-Voluntary-Delisting-at-27336-Floor-Price/6998f6b0730b6847a5170f6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nitin-Castings-Proposes-BSE-Voluntary-Delisting-at-27336-Floor-Price/6998f6b0730b6847a5170f6e</guid><description>Nitin Castings Limited's Board has approved a proposal to voluntarily delist its equity shares from the BSE. The offer, initiated by promoters, sets a floor price of ₹273.36 per share and requires shareholder approval. This move aims to acquire all publicly held shares.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:05:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998f6b0730b6847a5170f6d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>