<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:25:18 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's 2026 'Goldilocks Moment': 5 Portfolio Checks to Unlock Massive Wealth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-2026-Goldilocks-Moment-5-Portfolio-Checks-to-Unlock-Massive-Wealth/6955ccd34342f77179f37bc2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-2026-Goldilocks-Moment-5-Portfolio-Checks-to-Unlock-Massive-Wealth/6955ccd34342f77179f37bc2</guid><description>Indian investors should prepare for India's 2026 'Goldilocks moment' characterized by high growth and low inflation, according to RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra. With Nifty 50 targeting 30,000 and SIP flows nearing ₹40,000 crore monthly, five key portfolio checks are vital: assess small-cap allocation with an 86% rebound probability, evaluate exposure to domestic-focused sectors benefiting from the ₹2 lakh crore 8th Pay Commission, ensure large caps have a 15% earnings growth path, lock in yields around 5.25% in debt funds, and explore AI infrastructure opportunities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Massive ₹44,700 Cr Shipbuilding Push: 3 Indian Defence Giants Set to Soar!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-44700-Cr-Shipbuilding-Push-3-Indian-Defence-Giants-Set-to-Soar/6955ccbd4342f77179f37b8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-44700-Cr-Shipbuilding-Push-3-Indian-Defence-Giants-Set-to-Soar/6955ccbd4342f77179f37b8d</guid><description>India's Ministry of Ports, Shipping, and Waterways has launched two shipbuilding programs worth ₹44,700 crore to boost domestic capacity and global competitiveness through FY36. The schemes offer 15-25% financial assistance for ship construction and fund infrastructure development. Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders, Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers, and Cochin Shipyard are the primary beneficiaries, benefiting from substantial order books and future project pipelines in both defence and commercial sectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Global Trade War: India's Export Lifeline Under Threat Amid US Tariffs &amp; Geopolitical Shifts!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Trade-War-Indias-Export-Lifeline-Under-Threat-Amid-US-Tariffs-and-Geopolitical-Shifts/6955cbc14342f77179f37995</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Trade-War-Indias-Export-Lifeline-Under-Threat-Amid-US-Tariffs-and-Geopolitical-Shifts/6955cbc14342f77179f37995</guid><description>India faces a challenging trade environment in 2026, with merchandise exports expected to remain flat around $438 billion due to weak global demand and US tariffs. Services exports may reach $400 billion, falling short of the $1 trillion target. Exporters are diversifying markets away from the US, while the EU's Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism, new deforestation rules, and China's growing trade surplus pose further risks. Navigating these geopolitical and regulatory hurdles is crucial for India's competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:11:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955cbc14342f77179f37994_1767230675098.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Energy Revolution: Storage &amp; Nuclear Power Set to Dominate Post-2025!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Revolution-Storage-and-Nuclear-Power-Set-to-Dominate-Post-2025/6955c8624342f77179f3741f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Revolution-Storage-and-Nuclear-Power-Set-to-Dominate-Post-2025/6955c8624342f77179f3741f</guid><description>India is shifting its energy transition focus from just adding solar and wind capacity to building crucial energy storage and diversifying into nuclear power. Despite reaching 50% non-fossil fuel generation, erratic renewable sources limit output. Policymakers are targeting 2026 for significant progress in grid integration, storage solutions, and opening nuclear power to private investment to ensure reliable, round-the-clock clean energy supply and meet ambitious national goals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:52:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c8624342f77179f3741e_1767229615615.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Year-End Rally Ignites Indian Markets! Discover 2 Must-Buy Stocks from MarketSmith India</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Year-End-Rally-Ignites-Indian-Markets-Discover-2-Must-Buy-Stocks-from-MarketSmith-India/6955c8884342f77179f374af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Year-End-Rally-Ignites-Indian-Markets-Discover-2-Must-Buy-Stocks-from-MarketSmith-India/6955c8884342f77179f374af</guid><description>Indian stock markets closed 2025 on a high note, with Nifty 50 and Sensex advancing. The metal sector surged on government import tariffs, boosting JSW Steel and Tata Steel. MarketSmith India has recommended two stocks: Hindalco Industries Ltd and Fertilizers and Chemicals Travancore Ltd, citing strong fundamentals and growth potential. Investors are now looking towards Q3 earnings and auto sales data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:52:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c8884342f77179f374ae_1767229763227.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sebi's New Rules Cool SME IPO Frenzy: What Investors MUST Know About This Major Market Shift!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sebis-New-Rules-Cool-SME-IPO-Frenzy-What-Investors-MUST-Know-About-This-Major-Market-Shift/6955c8084342f77179f373b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sebis-New-Rules-Cool-SME-IPO-Frenzy-What-Investors-MUST-Know-About-This-Major-Market-Shift/6955c8084342f77179f373b7</guid><description>The pace of small and medium enterprise (SME) Initial Public Offerings (IPOs) has slowed down significantly this year, moving from 31% growth in 2024 to just 12.5% in the current period. This slowdown is largely due to stringent new regulations introduced by the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) aimed at curbing speculation and ensuring better governance. Alongside these policy changes, unfavorable macroeconomic conditions also played a role in dampening investor enthusiasm for new listings. Despite the slower growth, experts suggest these measures are improving the quality of companies listing on SME platforms, leading to larger average issue sizes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:52:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c8084342f77179f373b6_1767229614586.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCS Explores Gig Work for AI Talent: Is This the Future of IT Jobs in India?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Explores-Gig-Work-for-AI-Talent-Is-This-the-Future-of-IT-Jobs-in-India/6955c77e4342f77179f372ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Explores-Gig-Work-for-AI-Talent-Is-This-the-Future-of-IT-Jobs-in-India/6955c77e4342f77179f372ca</guid><description>Tata Consultancy Services is considering a new hiring model, offering gig-like arrangements for hard-to-retain AI specialists such as data architects and scientists. This move aims to address the talent crunch in India's $283 billion IT sector, allowing these experts to work flexible hours and potentially elsewhere, a significant shift from traditional full-time employment. The plan, still under development, aims to boost efficiency and manage costs while navigating data privacy concerns and margin pressures faced by the company.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:52:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c77e4342f77179f372c9_1767229640301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haier India Deal: Chinese Giant Cedes Control in $1.5B Transaction, Signaling Key Global Trend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Haier-India-Deal-Chinese-Giant-Cedes-Control-in-15B-Transaction-Signaling-Key-Global-Trend/6955c56c4342f77179f36fda</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Haier-India-Deal-Chinese-Giant-Cedes-Control-in-15B-Transaction-Signaling-Key-Global-Trend/6955c56c4342f77179f36fda</guid><description>Chinese appliance maker Haier has sold a 49% stake in its Indian subsidiary, Haier India, to a Bharti-Warburg Pincus consortium for $1.5 billion. Haier now holds a minority stake, reflecting a growing trend where Chinese firms relinquish control for market access. The deal, involving two manufacturing plants and a significant market share in appliances, underscores the ambition of Chinese companies in India despite geopolitical challenges and highlights the role of private equity as a buffer in international deal-making.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c56c4342f77179f36fd9_1767228874488.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Minimum Wage Hike Looms? India Unveils Draft Labour Rules, Set to Reshape Worker Pay!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Minimum-Wage-Hike-Looms-India-Unveils-Draft-Labour-Rules-Set-to-Reshape-Worker-Pay/6955c4804342f77179f36ed5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Minimum-Wage-Hike-Looms-India-Unveils-Draft-Labour-Rules-Set-to-Reshape-Worker-Pay/6955c4804342f77179f36ed5</guid><description>India's government has released draft rules for its four new labour codes, proposing significant changes to minimum wage calculations, working hours, and worker welfare. Minimum daily wages will be determined by family needs, including specific calorie intake, housing costs, and other essentials, signalling a potential upward revision. Weekly working hours are capped at 48. Gratuity provisions will also see changes, becoming prospective from November 21, 2025, with fixed-term employees gaining eligibility after just one year of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:42:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c4804342f77179f36ed4_1767228616145.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IREDA Skyrockets on Stellar Q3: Loan Book Nears ₹90,000 Cr as Disbursements Surge 44%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Skyrockets-on-Stellar-Q3-Loan-Book-Nears-90000-Cr-as-Disbursements-Surge-44percent/6955c2234342f77179f36c96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Skyrockets-on-Stellar-Q3-Loan-Book-Nears-90000-Cr-as-Disbursements-Surge-44percent/6955c2234342f77179f36c96</guid><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd. (IREDA) reported a strong Q3, with loan sanctions up 29% to ₹40,100 crore and disbursements soaring 44% to ₹24,903 crore year-on-year. The outstanding loan book expanded 28% to ₹87,975 crore, signaling robust growth in India's renewable energy financing sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:32:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c2234342f77179f36c95_1767228004903.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Warren Buffett's Secret Weapon: The Skill That Outlasts Him &amp; Why You Need It Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Warren-Buffetts-Secret-Weapon-The-Skill-That-Outlasts-Him-and-Why-You-Need-It-Now/6955c0784342f77179f36ae0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Warren-Buffetts-Secret-Weapon-The-Skill-That-Outlasts-Him-and-Why-You-Need-It-Now/6955c0784342f77179f36ae0</guid><description>Warren Buffett's enduring success wasn't built on innovation but on unparalleled patience. He consistently bought quality businesses at fair prices, holding them for decades to let compounding work its magic. This article reveals why patience, often seen as a weakness today, was Buffett's strategic advantage. It explores how this disciplined approach, despite market speed and technological shifts, remains the most powerful, yet overlooked, edge for investors seeking long-term wealth creation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:23:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c0784342f77179f36adf_1767227578438.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>