<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:38 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Bumper Year Ahead for Indian Real Estate? Nomura Names Top Developers Defying Market Woes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bumper-Year-Ahead-for-Indian-Real-Estate-Nomura-Names-Top-Developers-Defying-Market-Woes/695740c34342f77179f9bbec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bumper-Year-Ahead-for-Indian-Real-Estate-Nomura-Names-Top-Developers-Defying-Market-Woes/695740c34342f77179f9bbec</guid><description>Nomura forecasts a strong performance for India's listed real estate developers, expecting a third consecutive quarter of resilient pre-sales in Q3FY26. Despite broader market pressures, demand for branded residential projects remains healthy, with supply and regulatory approvals cited as key bottlenecks rather than buyer appetite. Nomura reiterates Prestige Estates as its top pick and also favors Lodha Developers and Aditya Birla Real Estate, anticipating many leading developers will meet their FY26 sales targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:43:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695740c34342f77179f9bbeb_1767325993953.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LAST CHANCE: Modern Diagnostic IPO Closes Today with Massive 28x Subscription &amp; ₹14 GMP!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/LAST-CHANCE-Modern-Diagnostic-IPO-Closes-Today-with-Massive-28x-Subscription-and-14-GMP/695740b74342f77179f9bb9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/LAST-CHANCE-Modern-Diagnostic-IPO-Closes-Today-with-Massive-28x-Subscription-and-14-GMP/695740b74342f77179f9bb9b</guid><description>Modern Diagnostic IPO is closing today, January 2, 2026, after opening on December 31, 2025. The public issue has seen overwhelming investor demand, reaching over 28.77 times subscription, largely driven by Non-Institutional Investors and retail investors. The Grey Market Premium (GMP) stands strong at ₹14 (15.56%) over the upper price band of ₹90. The ₹36.89 crore IPO aims to fund medical equipment, working capital, and debt repayment. Listing is expected on BSE SME on January 7, 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:43:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695740b74342f77179f9bb9a_1767325953532.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Government's Rs 3.84 Lakh Crore T-Bill Plan: Your Guide to Safe Investing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Governments-Rs-384-Lakh-Crore-T-Bill-Plan-Your-Guide-to-Safe-Investing/69573fe34342f77179f9b8b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Governments-Rs-384-Lakh-Crore-T-Bill-Plan-Your-Guide-to-Safe-Investing/69573fe34342f77179f9b8b7</guid><description>The Finance Ministry has announced the auction calendar for Government of India Treasury Bills, aiming to raise Rs 3.84 lakh crore by March 2026. These T-bills, available in 91, 182, and 364-day terms with a minimum investment of Rs 25,000, offer assured returns and are suitable for risk-averse investors. Profits are taxed as short-term capital gains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:38:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69573fe34342f77179f9b8b6_1767325739027.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Smartworks Stock Set for 19% Surge? Analysts Say BUY as Vikhroli Campus Nears World Record!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Smartworks-Stock-Set-for-19percent-Surge-Analysts-Say-BUY-as-Vikhroli-Campus-Nears-World-Record/695739634342f77179f99948</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Smartworks-Stock-Set-for-19percent-Surge-Analysts-Say-BUY-as-Vikhroli-Campus-Nears-World-Record/695739634342f77179f99948</guid><description>Kotak Institutional Equities initiated coverage on Smartworks Coworking Spaces Ltd. with a 'Buy' rating and ₹600 price target, expecting a 19% upside. The firm cited Smartworks' leading position in India's flexible workspace market, projecting 38% EBITDA CAGR and significant area expansion. All five analysts tracking the stock have a 'Buy' rating. The company is also developing the world's largest managed office campus in Vikhroli.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:09:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695739634342f77179f99947_1767324176826.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Fed's Shocking Concern: December Minutes Reveal Hidden Risk of Short-Term Funding Seizing Up!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Feds-Shocking-Concern-December-Minutes-Reveal-Hidden-Risk-of-Short-Term-Funding-Seizing-Up/695737a54342f77179f99133</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Feds-Shocking-Concern-December-Minutes-Reveal-Hidden-Risk-of-Short-Term-Funding-Seizing-Up/695737a54342f77179f99133</guid><description>Minutes from the Federal Reserve's December 2025 policy meeting reveal officials are closely monitoring a significant risk: the potential for short-term funding markets to experience a cash shortage. Despite comfort with the economic outlook and expected rate cuts, signs indicate tighter conditions in overnight borrowing markets. The Fed is considering purchasing approximately $220 billion in short-term Treasury securities to maintain adequate bank reserves and ensure smooth market functioning.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:05:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695737a54342f77179f99132_1767323620353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chemical Stocks in Freefall: 4 Giants Down Nearly 50%! China's Shadow or Market Glitch?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Chemical-Stocks-in-Freefall-4-Giants-Down-Nearly-50percent-Chinas-Shadow-or-Market-Glitch/6957374a4342f77179f98f00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Chemical-Stocks-in-Freefall-4-Giants-Down-Nearly-50percent-Chinas-Shadow-or-Market-Glitch/6957374a4342f77179f98f00</guid><description>Four prominent Indian chemical companies — Neogen Chemicals, Clean Science and Technology, Balaji Amines, and Sudarshan Chemical Industries — have seen their stock prices fall by up to 49% from their 52-week highs. This decline is attributed to factors including intensified competition from Chinese manufacturers flooding the market with cheaper alternatives, a global demand slowdown, rising input costs, and company-specific challenges like plant incidents and inventory pressures. Investors are advised to exercise caution and conduct thorough research.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957374a4342f77179f98eff_1767323530444.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DRDO Unveils Rs 1.30 Lakh Crore Defence Arsenal: India's Self-Reliance Takes 'Quantum Leap'!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DRDO-Unveils-Rs-130-Lakh-Crore-Defence-Arsenal-Indias-Self-Reliance-Takes-Quantum-Leap/695736294342f77179f98937</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DRDO-Unveils-Rs-130-Lakh-Crore-Defence-Arsenal-Indias-Self-Reliance-Takes-Quantum-Leap/695736294342f77179f98937</guid><description>India's defence self-reliance has achieved a 'quantum jump' with the government approving 22 Acceptance of Necessity (AoN) for defence systems worth approximately Rs 1.30 lakh crore. DRDO Chairman Samir V Kamat stated these systems will be manufactured by Indian industries, marking the highest value of AoNs in history and significantly boosting the 'Aatmanirbhar Bharat' vision. Key approvals include advanced missile systems and drone interdiction technology.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:57:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695736294342f77179f98936_1767323338262.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Indian Startups: Profit Surge or Bust? AI, Fintech IPOs &amp; Gaming Shake-up!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/2026-Indian-Startups-Profit-Surge-or-Bust-AI-Fintech-IPOs-and-Gaming-Shake-up/695735994342f77179f9863b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/2026-Indian-Startups-Profit-Surge-or-Bust-AI-Fintech-IPOs-and-Gaming-Shake-up/695735994342f77179f9863b</guid><description>Indian startups in 2026 will prioritize discipline, profitability, and sustainable unit economics over rapid expansion. Expect a shift towards AI integration, heightened scrutiny of the EV sector, and a surge in lending tech IPOs from companies like Kreditbee, Fibe, and Moneyview. The real money gaming sector is rebuilding post-ban, while e-commerce focuses on owned channels and quick commerce intensifies competition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:56:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695735994342f77179f9863a_1767323103092.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Soar: Tech Stocks Hit New Highs, Gold &amp; Silver Rebound as New Year Begins!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-Markets-Soar-Tech-Stocks-Hit-New-Highs-Gold-and-Silver-Rebound-as-New-Year-Begins/6957340c4342f77179f97f4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-Markets-Soar-Tech-Stocks-Hit-New-Highs-Gold-and-Silver-Rebound-as-New-Year-Begins/6957340c4342f77179f97f4d</guid><description>Global stocks and US equity futures climbed at the start of the new year, led by technology shares like Samsung Electronics. Precious metals, including gold and silver, also rebounded. Despite optimism around artificial intelligence and strong 2025 performance, risks from US monetary policy and high tech valuations persist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:49:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957340c4342f77179f97f4c_1767322701122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supreme Court Declares: Corporate Duty Extends to Nature, Profit Not Paramount!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Supreme-Court-Declares-Corporate-Duty-Extends-to-Nature-Profit-Not-Paramount/695731dc4342f77179f975a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Supreme-Court-Declares-Corporate-Duty-Extends-to-Nature-Profit-Not-Paramount/695731dc4342f77179f975a0</guid><description>India's Supreme Court has ruled that corporations must prioritize environmental and wildlife protection, expanding Corporate Social Responsibility beyond shareholder interests. The court invoked the 'polluter pays' principle, mandating companies to fund conservation efforts if their operations threaten endangered species' habitats. This landmark observation calls for a critical reevaluation of development policies and judicial intervention against state actions that harm ecosystems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:34:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695731dc4342f77179f9759f_1767322383282.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fuel Price Mystery: IOCL Chairman Unpacks 2026 Pricing 'Jigsaw Puzzle' Amidst Shifting Margins!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Fuel-Price-Mystery-IOCL-Chairman-Unpacks-2026-Pricing-Jigsaw-Puzzle-Amidst-Shifting-Margins/695731554342f77179f97310</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Fuel-Price-Mystery-IOCL-Chairman-Unpacks-2026-Pricing-Jigsaw-Puzzle-Amidst-Shifting-Margins/695731554342f77179f97310</guid><description>Indian Oil Corporation (IOCL) Chairman A. S. Sahney described domestic petrol and diesel pricing as a "complex jigsaw puzzle," clarifying there's no direct link to falling global crude oil prices. He explained that profitability for Oil Marketing Companies (OMCs) relies on balancing refining margins, which are currently strong, against marketing margins, which are weaker. Factors like increasing fuel demand and the need for significant capital expenditure (capex) for infrastructure and sustainable energy also influence pricing decisions, making an immediate price cut unlikely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:33:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695731554342f77179f9730f_1767322001260.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Chip IPO EXPLODES in Hong Kong: Stock Doubles on Listing Day Amidst 2,300x Retail Frenzy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Chip-IPO-EXPLODES-in-Hong-Kong-Stock-Doubles-on-Listing-Day-Amidst-2300x-Retail-Frenzy/695730d34342f77179f970cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Chip-IPO-EXPLODES-in-Hong-Kong-Stock-Doubles-on-Listing-Day-Amidst-2300x-Retail-Frenzy/695730d34342f77179f970cf</guid><description>Shanghai Biren Technology, an AI chip designer, saw its shares surge 82% on its Hong Kong listing day after raising $717 million. The IPO was met with massive demand, with retail investors subscribing 2,300 times the shares offered. This explosive debut is fueled by the global AI boom and investor appetite for semiconductor stocks, especially those benefiting from China's focus on homegrown technology.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:33:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695730d34342f77179f970ce_1767321902243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Volatility Fears? Why Smart Investors Are Rushing to Hybrid Funds for Safer Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Volatility-Fears-Why-Smart-Investors-Are-Rushing-to-Hybrid-Funds-for-Safer-Growth/695730614342f77179f96ea6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Volatility-Fears-Why-Smart-Investors-Are-Rushing-to-Hybrid-Funds-for-Safer-Growth/695730614342f77179f96ea6</guid><description>Hybrid mutual funds are gaining traction among investors seeking to balance market-linked growth with downside protection. By diversifying investments across equity, debt, and other assets like commodities, these funds help manage market volatility, making them appealing for those wanting to stay invested in growth opportunities while mitigating risks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:33:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695730614342f77179f96ea5_1767322035455.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor's Q3 Sales EXPLODE: Record Quarter &amp; 50% December Surge Rocks Market!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motors-Q3-Sales-EXPLODE-Record-Quarter-and-50percent-December-Surge-Rocks-Market/69572fc34342f77179f96bf6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motors-Q3-Sales-EXPLODE-Record-Quarter-and-50percent-December-Surge-Rocks-Market/69572fc34342f77179f96bf6</guid><description>TVS Motor Company has posted its highest-ever quarterly sales in Q3 FY26, delivering 15.44 lakh units. This was driven by a 25% surge in two-wheeler sales and a massive 106% jump in three-wheeler sales. December alone saw a 50% increase to 481,389 units, with strong performance from its EV segment and international business growing 40%. The company's stock is expected to be in focus following these robust figures, especially after touching a 52-week high.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:28:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69572fc34342f77179f96bf5_1767321637557.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Retail Investors Ditch Stocks for IPOs: Record Rs 34,840 Cr Poured into Primary Market!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Retail-Investors-Ditch-Stocks-for-IPOs-Record-Rs-34840-Cr-Poured-into-Primary-Market/69572f614342f77179f96a90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Retail-Investors-Ditch-Stocks-for-IPOs-Record-Rs-34840-Cr-Poured-into-Primary-Market/69572f614342f77179f96a90</guid><description>Indian retail investors are pouring record funds into the primary market, investing Rs 34,840 crore in FY26 so far, seeking higher returns. This surge coincides with significant outflows of Rs 13,000 crore from the volatile secondary market, where many listings have seen muted debuts. Analysts suggest this shift is driven by dissatisfaction with secondary market performance and a pursuit of potential gains in new issues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:28:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69572f614342f77179f96a8f_1767321509792.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BIG GAINS AHEAD? India Stocks Set for Positive Start as GST Data &amp; FPIs Spark Hope!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/BIG-GAINS-AHEAD-India-Stocks-Set-for-Positive-Start-as-GST-Data-and-FPIs-Spark-Hope/69572e284342f77179f958b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/BIG-GAINS-AHEAD-India-Stocks-Set-for-Positive-Start-as-GST-Data-and-FPIs-Spark-Hope/69572e284342f77179f958b2</guid><description>Indian markets are expected to open higher on Friday, with Gift Nifty signalling a 40-point gap-up. December GST collections reached ₹1.75 lakh crore, a 6.1% year-on-year rise, though net domestic collections dipped due to increased refunds. Analysts anticipate Foreign Portfolio Investors (FPIs) returning soon, citing India's economic stability. Stocks like Devyani International and Sunteck Realty are in focus ahead of the Q3 earnings season.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:22:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69572e284342f77179f958b1_1767321428823.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EV Shock: Petrol Cars Surge as GST Cuts Hit Electric Vehicle Dominance in India!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/EV-Shock-Petrol-Cars-Surge-as-GST-Cuts-Hit-Electric-Vehicle-Dominance-in-India/69572d0a4342f77179f944b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/EV-Shock-Petrol-Cars-Surge-as-GST-Cuts-Hit-Electric-Vehicle-Dominance-in-India/69572d0a4342f77179f944b4</guid><description>India's electric vehicle (EV) market share in two-wheelers and passenger cars has slipped in late 2025. This comes after GST rate reductions for petrol and diesel vehicles made them more competitive against EVs. While overall EV sales volume saw healthy growth, the price gap narrowing significantly impacted EV penetration in these segments. The three-wheeler EV segment, however, bucked the trend with improved penetration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:17:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69572d0a4342f77179f944b3_1767320906754.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>January 2, 2026: Bajaj Broking Reveals Top Stock Buys for HUGE Returns! 🚀 Nifty &amp; Bank Nifty Outlook Included!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/January-2-2026-Bajaj-Broking-Reveals-Top-Stock-Buys-for-HUGE-Returns-Nifty-and-Bank-Nifty-Outlook-Included/69572d834342f77179f9473a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/January-2-2026-Bajaj-Broking-Reveals-Top-Stock-Buys-for-HUGE-Returns-Nifty-and-Bank-Nifty-Outlook-Included/69572d834342f77179f9473a</guid><description>Bajaj Broking Research has unveiled its top stock recommendations for January 2, 2026, identifying Canara Bank and Nykaa as prime 'buy' opportunities. Canara Bank is targeted at ₹175 for a 13% return in three months, while Nykaa is set for ₹292, expecting an 11% gain. The firm also provided an outlook for Nifty, anticipating a range-bound movement within 25,700–26,300 with an upward bias, and noted Bank Nifty's outperformance, suggesting continued strength within its 58,500–60,100 band.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:17:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69572d834342f77179f94739_1767321029503.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Tech Stocks Explode: Funds Skyrocket Over 100%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Chinas-Tech-Stocks-Explode-Funds-Skyrocket-Over-100percent/69572bca4342f77179f93f28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Chinas-Tech-Stocks-Explode-Funds-Skyrocket-Over-100percent/69572bca4342f77179f93f28</guid><description>Chinese multi-asset funds dominated global rankings last year, securing 13 of the top 20 spots. Seven funds delivered over 100% returns by heavily investing in technology and artificial intelligence stocks. Eoptolink Technology Inc. and Zhongji Innolight Co. were top holdings, highlighting the immense profitability of AI bets despite global market jitters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:14:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69572bca4342f77179f93f27_1767320736932.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver EXPLODE in 2026: Best Gains Since 1979! What's Next? 🚀</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-EXPLODE-in-2026-Best-Gains-Since-1979-Whats-Next/69572bb54342f77179f93ecb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-EXPLODE-in-2026-Best-Gains-Since-1979-Whats-Next/69572bb54342f77179f93ecb</guid><description>Gold and silver have surged at the start of 2026, extending their best annual performance since 1979. While potential US interest-rate cuts and dollar weakness offer upside, near-term concerns arise from index rebalancing which could pressure prices. Analysts predict significant selling in silver futures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:13:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69572bb54342f77179f93eca_1767320578276.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock January Profits: Experts Reveal 7 Must-Buy Stocks for Early Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Unlock-January-Profits-Experts-Reveal-7-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-Early-Gains/695726194342f77179f928a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Unlock-January-Profits-Experts-Reveal-7-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-Early-Gains/695726194342f77179f928a1</guid><description>Indian market experts have identified seven stocks for potential gains on January 2. Amidst market consolidation, these 'buy' recommendations are based on strong technical indicators, offering short-term trading opportunities for investors keen on capitalizing on specific stock movements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:48:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695726194342f77179f928a0_1767319167343.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sunteck Realty Stock Surges 8%! Buy Signal at ₹429? Expert Predicts ₹475 Target - Don't Miss Out!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Sunteck-Realty-Stock-Surges-8percent-Buy-Signal-at-429-Expert-Predicts-475-Target-Dont-Miss-Out/695722bd4342f77179f91cda</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Sunteck-Realty-Stock-Surges-8percent-Buy-Signal-at-429-Expert-Predicts-475-Target-Dont-Miss-Out/695722bd4342f77179f91cda</guid><description>Sunteck Realty shares surged over 8% on Thursday, closing strongly and surpassing the ₹410-₹420 resistance zone, now expected to act as support. Analysts are bullish, recommending a buy at ₹429 with a short-term target of ₹470-₹475. A detailed strategy includes accumulating on dips around ₹416 and managing risk with a trailing stop-loss, starting at ₹395.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:34:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695722bd4342f77179f91cd9_1767318300332.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Blazing GDP: Growth Fakery or Real Rally? Expert Warns of Hidden Dangers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Blazing-GDP-Growth-Fakery-or-Real-Rally-Expert-Warns-of-Hidden-Dangers/695722344342f77179f91acb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Blazing-GDP-Growth-Fakery-or-Real-Rally-Expert-Warns-of-Hidden-Dangers/695722344342f77179f91acb</guid><description>India's 8.2% GDP growth in July-September 2025 leads globally, but masks concerns. Nominal GDP growth has slowed, with a sharp drop in price deflators suggesting 'optical' gains rather than broad production increases. Weak nominal growth impacts corporate results and tax collections, while consumption-heavy demand and moderating investment raise questions about sustainability. Experts urge focus on reviving private investment and exports, not just headline figures, for long-term expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:33:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695722344342f77179f91aca_1767318131233.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Policy Focuses on Using AI, Not Building It – Is the Nation Falling Behind?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Policy-Focuses-on-Using-AI-Not-Building-It-Is-the-Nation-Falling-Behind/695722054342f77179f91a2e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Policy-Focuses-on-Using-AI-Not-Building-It-Is-the-Nation-Falling-Behind/695722054342f77179f91a2e</guid><description>India's AI governance strategy emphasizes digital public infrastructure and voluntary guardrails, excelling at AI deployment. However, concerns exist about a policy imbalance hindering foundational AI creation. Lack of clarity on data usage for training, unresolved liability issues, and underleveraged research infrastructure could limit India's global AI capability. Targeted policy interventions are needed to foster AI development and ensure national competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:33:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695722054342f77179f91a2d_1767318091189.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Loans Explode 125% in India, Outpacing Bank Credit 10x!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Loans-Explode-125percent-in-India-Outpacing-Bank-Credit-10x/695721964342f77179f9187c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Loans-Explode-125percent-in-India-Outpacing-Bank-Credit-10x/695721964342f77179f9187c</guid><description>Gold loans in India have surged by an astounding 125% year-on-year as of November 2025, significantly dwarfing the 11.5% growth in overall bank credit. This boom, driven by rising gold prices, lender preference for secured lending, and RBI reclassifications, saw outstanding gold loans reach ₹3.6 lakh crore. This marks a substantial shift, with banks increasingly focusing on small-ticket, priority-sector lending and consumers over large corporate borrowing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:30:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695721964342f77179f9187b_1767317973251.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Market Soars: See How Reforms Under Different PMs Fueled Sensex Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Market-Soars-See-How-Reforms-Under-Different-PMs-Fueled-Sensex-Growth/69571fa14342f77179f911f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Market-Soars-See-How-Reforms-Under-Different-PMs-Fueled-Sensex-Growth/69571fa14342f77179f911f2</guid><description>The Indian stock market's benchmark index, Sensex, has historically mirrored the nation's economic journey. This analysis reveals how market returns have significantly correlated with government stability and the implementation of economic reforms across various Prime Ministers' tenures. Periods of strong reforms and stable governance have consistently led to market gains, showcasing the crucial link between policy and investor confidence in India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:17:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571fa14342f77179f911f1_1767317608212.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sensex 40-Year Makeover: Legacy Firms Out, Tech &amp; PSUs IN! India's Market Revolution Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-40-Year-Makeover-Legacy-Firms-Out-Tech-and-PSUs-IN-Indias-Market-Revolution-Revealed/69571f494342f77179f91098</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-40-Year-Makeover-Legacy-Firms-Out-Tech-and-PSUs-IN-Indias-Market-Revolution-Revealed/69571f494342f77179f91098</guid><description>India's premier stock index, the Sensex, has undergone a dramatic 40-year transformation. Family-owned businesses, once dominant, have significantly reduced their representation, making way for Central Public Sector Undertakings (CPSUs) and companies owned by independent institutions. The shift also reflects a sectoral evolution from manufacturing to booming financial services (BFSI) and information technology (IT), mirroring India's changing economic landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:17:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571f494342f77179f91097_1767317492083.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sensex Shake-Up: Over 60 Top Indian Firms Vanish Since 1985 – What's Driving the Massive Corporate Churn?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Shake-Up-Over-60-Top-Indian-Firms-Vanish-Since-1985-Whats-Driving-the-Massive-Corporate-Churn/69571ed34342f77179f90edb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Shake-Up-Over-60-Top-Indian-Firms-Vanish-Since-1985-Whats-Driving-the-Massive-Corporate-Churn/69571ed34342f77179f90edb</guid><description>An analysis of BSE data reveals that since 1985, 93 companies have been part of the Sensex, with 63 exiting due to business downturns, mergers, or falling valuations. This significant churn highlights India's economic transformation, marked by the decline of manufacturing's dominance and the rise of the services sector. Experts predict the pace of index changes may accelerate with digitization and new-age listings, signaling a dynamic future for India's top companies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:17:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571ed34342f77179f90eda_1767317304946.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>40 Years of Dominance: BSE Sensex Outshines Gold, Global Stocks, and Savings!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/40-Years-of-Dominance-BSE-Sensex-Outshines-Gold-Global-Stocks-and-Savings/69571ea24342f77179f90e26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/40-Years-of-Dominance-BSE-Sensex-Outshines-Gold-Global-Stocks-and-Savings/69571ea24342f77179f90e26</guid><description>Over the past 40 years, the BSE Sensex has significantly outperformed global equities, gold, and fixed-income investments, delivering consistent double-digit annual returns in rupee terms. While its dollar returns have been moderated by rupee depreciation, it still represents a powerful wealth creation tool for long-term Indian investors, marking a decade-long winning streak. The index has grown over 160 times since 1985, dwarfing other asset classes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:17:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571ea24342f77179f90e25_1767317219399.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Prices Hold Steady as 2026 Begins: OPEC+ Meeting and Venezuela Sanctions Steer Market Direction!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Hold-Steady-as-2026-Begins-OPEC-Meeting-and-Venezuela-Sanctions-Steer-Market-Direction/69571e074342f77179f90c67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Hold-Steady-as-2026-Begins-OPEC-Meeting-and-Venezuela-Sanctions-Steer-Market-Direction/69571e074342f77179f90c67</guid><description>Oil prices stabilized on the first trading day of 2026 after a significant 2025 decline. Traders are focused on an upcoming OPEC+ meeting expected to maintain supply cuts and U.S. sanctions targeting Venezuela's oil exports. Geopolitical tensions, including damage to Black Sea ports, add to market uncertainty, while a global oil glut is forecast for the year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:15:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571e074342f77179f90c66_1767317065888.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Nuclear Leap: NTPC Ties Up with Russia &amp; France for Massive Power Projects!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Nuclear-Leap-NTPC-Ties-Up-with-Russia-and-France-for-Massive-Power-Projects/69571c664342f77179f906d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Nuclear-Leap-NTPC-Ties-Up-with-Russia-and-France-for-Massive-Power-Projects/69571c664342f77179f906d7</guid><description>NTPC, India's leading power generator, has signed non-disclosure agreements with Russia's Rosatom and France's EDF. These pacts aim to explore collaboration on large pressurized water reactor (PWR) nuclear power projects in India, covering the entire project lifecycle. This move follows India's recent law changes easing private sector entry and supplier liability, potentially accelerating the nation's nuclear energy expansion targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:07:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571c664342f77179f906d6_1767316710692.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Breakfast Boom: iD Fresh Food Secures Massive ₹1300 Crore Investment from Apax Partners!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Breakfast-Boom-iD-Fresh-Food-Secures-Massive-1300-Crore-Investment-from-Apax-Partners/69571c334342f77179f90618</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Breakfast-Boom-iD-Fresh-Food-Secures-Massive-1300-Crore-Investment-from-Apax-Partners/69571c334342f77179f90618</guid><description>British private equity firm Apax Partners is acquiring a quarter stake in Indian ready-to-cook breakfast maker iD Fresh Food for nearly Rs 1,300 crore, valuing the company at Rs 4,500 crore. This significant investment highlights the growing trend of premiumisation in India's fast-growing consumer sector, particularly in ready-to-cook breakfast staples. iD Fresh Food, known for its preservative-free products, aims for a public listing by 2027.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:07:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571c334342f77179f90617_1767316607305.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rs 25,000 Crore Infra Boost: Will This Fund Unlock Stalled Projects &amp; Skyrocket Stocks?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rs-25000-Crore-Infra-Boost-Will-This-Fund-Unlock-Stalled-Projects-and-Skyrocket-Stocks/69571c3d4342f77179f9064f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rs-25000-Crore-Infra-Boost-Will-This-Fund-Unlock-Stalled-Projects-and-Skyrocket-Stocks/69571c3d4342f77179f9064f</guid><description>The Indian government is reportedly planning a Rs 25,000 crore 'risk guarantee' fund to revive stalled infrastructure projects. This initiative aims to boost lender confidence and overcome financing bottlenecks, potentially accelerating projects in roads, rail, and metro sectors. Companies like KNR Constructions, PNC Infratech, and IRB Infrastructure Developers, focused on EPC and HAM models, could see improved execution and cash flows if the fund materializes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:05:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571c3d4342f77179f9064e_1767316698733.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shock Strike! Swiggy, Zomato Stocks Tumble as Delivery Workers Demand Fair Pay - Is India's Gig Economy at Risk?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Shock-Strike-Swiggy-Zomato-Stocks-Tumble-as-Delivery-Workers-Demand-Fair-Pay-Is-Indias-Gig-Economy-at-Risk/69571b414342f77179f9035c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Shock-Strike-Swiggy-Zomato-Stocks-Tumble-as-Delivery-Workers-Demand-Fair-Pay-Is-Indias-Gig-Economy-at-Risk/69571b414342f77179f9035c</guid><description>Delivery workers across India, employed by platforms like Swiggy and Zomato, staged nationwide strikes on December 25 and December 31, causing significant disruptions. The protests led to a drop in the shares of these companies, highlighting worker demands for predictable earnings and basic protections. While companies offered incentives, strike leaders indicated this was just the beginning, signalling a critical juncture for India's gig economy and platform business models.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:03:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69571b414342f77179f9035b_1767316388852.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC Sell-Off Triggers Nifty Downturn: Can Indian Markets Rally Back Before Weekend Close?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/ITC-Sell-Off-Triggers-Nifty-Downturn-Can-Indian-Markets-Rally-Back-Before-Weekend-Close/695717774342f77179f8fa81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/ITC-Sell-Off-Triggers-Nifty-Downturn-Can-Indian-Markets-Rally-Back-Before-Weekend-Close/695717774342f77179f8fa81</guid><description>Indian stock markets, including the benchmark Sensex and Nifty, are facing pressure as a sell-off in ITC stock weighs on investor sentiment. The Nifty 50 index is currently aiming to recover from recent losses, with investors watching closely to see if a broader market recovery can materialize by the end of the trading week.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:46:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695717774342f77179f8fa80_1767315423595.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Giants Weigh Hybrid Future: JSW Motors, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Open to REEVs If Policy Shifts!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Giants-Weigh-Hybrid-Future-JSW-Motors-Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Open-to-REEVs-If-Policy-Shifts/695717644342f77179f8fa30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Giants-Weigh-Hybrid-Future-JSW-Motors-Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Open-to-REEVs-If-Policy-Shifts/695717644342f77179f8fa30</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra and JSW Motors are open to developing range-extended electric vehicles (REEVs) if India's policy framework expands incentives beyond pure electric cars. REEVs use an electric motor for driving, with a small internal combustion engine acting solely as a generator when the battery charge is low. While currently focused on pure EVs, automakers see REEVs as a transitional technology that could ease consumer adoption of electrification, provided policy and taxation support, mirroring trends seen in markets like China. Experts caution that REEVs still involve fossil fuel use, unlike pure EVs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695717644342f77179f8fa2f_1767315375356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Quick Commerce WAR: Billions Burned, Giants Clash – What 2026 Holds!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Quick-Commerce-WAR-Billions-Burned-Giants-Clash-What-2026-Holds/6957174f4342f77179f8f9ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Quick-Commerce-WAR-Billions-Burned-Giants-Clash-What-2026-Holds/6957174f4342f77179f8f9ce</guid><description>India's quick commerce sector is seeing explosive growth, with companies like Swiggy Instamart, Blinkit, and Zepto expanding rapidly and burning significant cash. This intense competition is expected to sharpen in 2026 as giants like Amazon and Flipkart enter the fray. While order volumes and revenue are surging, losses are widening, prompting a focus on profitable models, private labels, and deeper penetration into categories like pharmacy. The sector is already outperforming overall online retail, but 2026 will test execution and profitability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957174f4342f77179f8f9cd_1767315665429.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Sweet Tooth Suffers: Diabetes &amp; Health Trends Force Major Sugar Consumption Slowdown!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Sweet-Tooth-Suffers-Diabetes-and-Health-Trends-Force-Major-Sugar-Consumption-Slowdown/695717244342f77179f8f94d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Sweet-Tooth-Suffers-Diabetes-and-Health-Trends-Force-Major-Sugar-Consumption-Slowdown/695717244342f77179f8f94d</guid><description>India's legendary appetite for sugar is diminishing as a diabetes epidemic and evolving dietary habits lead to slowing consumption growth. Projections show growth at just 1.42% this fiscal year, with a decline anticipated next. This shift, driven by rising health consciousness and a younger generation's preference for healthier alternatives, poses significant challenges for the nation's sugar industry, including farmers and mills, though it is welcomed by healthcare professionals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695717244342f77179f8f94c_1767315321926.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Streaming Wars: Tiny Shows Rule, But Big Mergers Loom? Click to See What's Next!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Streaming-Wars-Tiny-Shows-Rule-But-Big-Mergers-Loom-Click-to-See-Whats-Next/6957171c4342f77179f8f8fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Streaming-Wars-Tiny-Shows-Rule-But-Big-Mergers-Loom-Click-to-See-Whats-Next/6957171c4342f77179f8f8fd</guid><description>India's streaming industry is embracing 'micro-dramas' in 2025-2026 due to tight budgets and slowing subscriptions. While creators and regional content rise, global media consolidation, including potential bids for Warner Bros. Discovery, could reduce space for independent makers. Monetization remains a challenge with fragmented markets and balancing ad-supported vs. subscription models, leading to selectivity and potential smaller OTT acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957171c4342f77179f8f8fc_1767315320156.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Real Estate 2026: Housing Slows, Office &amp; Logistics Set to Soar! Your Investment Guide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Real-Estate-2026-Housing-Slows-Office-and-Logistics-Set-to-Soar-Your-Investment-Guide/695716804342f77179f8f718</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Real-Estate-2026-Housing-Slows-Office-and-Logistics-Set-to-Soar-Your-Investment-Guide/695716804342f77179f8f718</guid><description>India's real estate market is set for healthy growth in 2026, with non-residential sectors like office and logistics expected to outperform housing. Residential sales slowed in 2025 due to high prices, but are predicted to stabilize moderately in 2026, driven by branded developers and potential RBI rate cuts. The office market shows global resilience with strong leasing momentum, while logistics demand from manufacturing and e-commerce is projected for significant growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:40:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695716804342f77179f8f717_1767315164857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>