<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:46:37 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India-Europe Air Travel Set for HUGE Boost! Air India Resumes Rome Flights, IndiGo Launches London Service – Is Your Next Trip Easier?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Europe-Air-Travel-Set-for-HUGE-Boost-Air-India-Resumes-Rome-Flights-IndiGo-Launches-London-Service-Is-Your-Next-Trip-Easier/694bdc6ee10c98d0787b30aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Europe-Air-Travel-Set-for-HUGE-Boost-Air-India-Resumes-Rome-Flights-IndiGo-Launches-London-Service-Is-Your-Next-Trip-Easier/694bdc6ee10c98d0787b30aa</guid><description>Air India will resume flights to Rome from Delhi four times weekly starting March 25, 2026, using Boeing 787-8 aircraft. Simultaneously, IndiGo will launch direct flights from Delhi to London Heathrow five times a week from February 2, 2026, using leased Boeing 787s. These expansions aim to enhance India-Europe connectivity for business and leisure travellers, bolstering both airlines' international networks and reflecting growing demand.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:13:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdc6ee10c98d0787b30a9_1766579402698.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Stocks Hit Brakes, Metals Rally: Expert Rohit Srivastava's Crucial Market Forecast!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/IT-Stocks-Hit-Brakes-Metals-Rally-Expert-Rohit-Srivastavas-Crucial-Market-Forecast/694bdbb8e10c98d0787b2f1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/IT-Stocks-Hit-Brakes-Metals-Rally-Expert-Rohit-Srivastavas-Crucial-Market-Forecast/694bdbb8e10c98d0787b2f1e</guid><description>Market expert Rohit Srivastava, founder of Strike Money Analytics and Indiacharts, forecasts the Nifty may reach 26,500 before December expiry. He expresses long-term caution on the IT sector despite short-term trading potential, while advocating for metals like Hindalco and National Aluminium as top picks for the Santa Rally, driven by a weakening dollar and rising commodity prices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:13:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdbb8e10c98d0787b2f1d_1766579582094.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Premier Energies Strikes Major Deal: Acquires Significant Stake in Transcon Ind for ₹250 Crore!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premier-Energies-Strikes-Major-Deal-Acquires-Significant-Stake-in-Transcon-Ind-for-250-Crore/694bdb3ae10c98d0787b2e30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premier-Energies-Strikes-Major-Deal-Acquires-Significant-Stake-in-Transcon-Ind-for-250-Crore/694bdb3ae10c98d0787b2e30</guid><description>Premier Energies Limited has successfully acquired a 34.21% equity stake in Transcon Ind Ltd for ₹250 crore. This marks the first phase of their planned acquisition, aiming for a total 51% stake. The deal, structured in tranches linked to Transcon Ind's capital expenditure, is expected to see its remaining stages completed by February 20, 2026. This strategic move positions Premier Energies to increase its control over Transcon Ind.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:13:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdb3ae10c98d0787b2e2f_1766579252588.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CESC Subsidiary Lands Massive 180 MW Renewable Deal! 25-Year Contract Ignites Investor Interest</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/CESC-Subsidiary-Lands-Massive-180-MW-Renewable-Deal-25-Year-Contract-Ignites-Investor-Interest/694bdbfee10c98d0787b2fed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/CESC-Subsidiary-Lands-Massive-180-MW-Renewable-Deal-25-Year-Contract-Ignites-Investor-Interest/694bdbfee10c98d0787b2fed</guid><description>CESC Limited's subsidiary, Purvah Green Power Private Limited, has been awarded a significant 180 MW round-the-clock (RTC) renewable energy project by REMC Limited. This 25-year contract, secured through competitive bidding, marks a substantial step for CESC in the expanding renewable energy sector, complementing its recent strong financial performance which saw a 20.4% rise in net profit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdbfee10c98d0787b2fec_1766580110378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manba Finance Powers TVS Electric 3-Wheelers: New Pan-India Funding Deal to Accelerate EV Adoption!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manba-Finance-Powers-TVS-Electric-3-Wheelers-New-Pan-India-Funding-Deal-to-Accelerate-EV-Adoption/694bdb62e10c98d0787b2e8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manba-Finance-Powers-TVS-Electric-3-Wheelers-New-Pan-India-Funding-Deal-to-Accelerate-EV-Adoption/694bdb62e10c98d0787b2e8f</guid><description>Manba Finance Limited has partnered with TVS Motor Company Limited through a new Memorandum of Understanding. This collaboration designates Manba Finance as the preferred financier for all TVS three-wheelers across India, with a strategic emphasis on electric models. The phased, pan-India rollout aims to boost EV financing and reduce ownership barriers for entrepreneurs and fleet operators, supporting India's sustainable mobility goals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:12:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdb62e10c98d0787b2e8e_1766579727547.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SFIO Launches Shock Probe into IndusInd Bank: Accounting Red Flags Uncovered!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SFIO-Launches-Shock-Probe-into-IndusInd-Bank-Accounting-Red-Flags-Uncovered/694bdaa7e10c98d0787b2da7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SFIO-Launches-Shock-Probe-into-IndusInd-Bank-Accounting-Red-Flags-Uncovered/694bdaa7e10c98d0787b2da7</guid><description>The Serious Fraud Investigation Office (SFIO) has started a formal investigation into IndusInd Bank's accounting practices under Section 212 of the Companies Act, 2013. This probe follows concerns raised by auditors regarding derivative trades, unsubstantiated balances, and microfinance interest income. IndusInd Bank has stated it is cooperating fully with the authorities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:12:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdaa7e10c98d0787b2da6_1766579139147.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2025 Travel Surge: Faith, Festivals &amp; Spontaneous Trips Dominate Bookings!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-2025-Travel-Surge-Faith-Festivals-and-Spontaneous-Trips-Dominate-Bookings/694bd967e10c98d0787b2c1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-2025-Travel-Surge-Faith-Festivals-and-Spontaneous-Trips-Dominate-Bookings/694bd967e10c98d0787b2c1c</guid><description>Paytm Travel's 2025 recap reveals faith-based journeys, particularly the Kumbh Mela in Prayagraj, drove significant growth, with bookings tripling. Festival travel, like Chhath Puja flights to Patna, also saw spikes. Decisions increasingly align with salary cycles, favoring spontaneous short breaks. Entertainment events are spurring travel, while leisure spots like Srinagar and Goa remain popular. Tier-2 cities like Indore and Kochi are showing steady inbound growth, reflecting evolving Indian travel preferences.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:03:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bd967e10c98d0787b2c1b_1766578640709.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Premji Invest's ₹754 Crore Infrastructure Power Play: Big Bet on India's Highways!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premji-Invests-754-Crore-Infrastructure-Power-Play-Big-Bet-on-Indias-Highways/694bd8cce10c98d0787b2ac9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premji-Invests-754-Crore-Infrastructure-Power-Play-Big-Bet-on-Indias-Highways/694bd8cce10c98d0787b2ac9</guid><description>Premji Invest, the family office of Azim Premji, has invested ₹754 crore to acquire a 2.61% stake in National Highways Infra Trust (NHIT). This strategic move through Prazim Trading signals strong investor confidence in India's infrastructure development and the government's asset monetization initiatives. NHIT, sponsored by NHAI, offers exposure to operational highway assets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:03:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bd8cce10c98d0787b2ac8_1766578620968.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Wedding Season Fuels Jewellery Boom: Diamonds Steal the Show as Spending Soars!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Wedding-Season-Fuels-Jewellery-Boom-Diamonds-Steal-the-Show-as-Spending-Soars/694bd34ae10c98d0787b25ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Wedding-Season-Fuels-Jewellery-Boom-Diamonds-Steal-the-Show-as-Spending-Soars/694bd34ae10c98d0787b25ba</guid><description>Jewellery demand is strong this wedding season, driven by higher spending and a noticeable shift towards diamond products, according to C Krishniah Chetty Group. India's overall wedding spending is nearing ₹6.5 lakh crore, with jewellery capturing a significant share. Consumers are increasingly opting for premium diamond bridal sets and solitaires, influenced by moderating diamond prices and a desire for contemporary designs. Traditional gold items and coins also see steady demand for wealth preservation, though gold price volatility prompts flexible buying strategies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:39:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bd34ae10c98d0787b25b9_1766577096045.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's REIT Market Set to Explode: Experts Reveal Massive Growth Potential!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-REIT-Market-Set-to-Explode-Experts-Reveal-Massive-Growth-Potential/694bd2b0e10c98d0787b2515</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-REIT-Market-Set-to-Explode-Experts-Reveal-Massive-Growth-Potential/694bd2b0e10c98d0787b2515</guid><description>India's Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT) market is poised for significant expansion, with less than 20% of Grade A office stock currently housed under REITs. Experts see substantial room for growth and new listings across offices, retail, hospitality, and warehousing. With market capitalization reaching $18 billion, REITs are increasingly recognized as equity instruments offering dividends and long-term capital appreciation, driven by strong demand for income-generating commercial assets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:39:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bd2b0e10c98d0787b2514_1766577918404.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Whisky Secret: How Surrinder Kumar Created Global Single Malt Stars and Skyrocketed Stocks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Whisky-Secret-How-Surrinder-Kumar-Created-Global-Single-Malt-Stars-and-Skyrocketed-Stocks/694bd32de10c98d0787b258b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Whisky-Secret-How-Surrinder-Kumar-Created-Global-Single-Malt-Stars-and-Skyrocketed-Stocks/694bd32de10c98d0787b258b</guid><description>Surrinder Kumar, a former agriculture officer, is revolutionizing the Indian single malt whisky industry. He played a pivotal role in developing Amrut Classic and later transformed Indri into India's best-selling single malt. His expertise in distillation, maturation, and flavour profiles has put Indian whiskies on the global map, with sales now surpassing imports and boosting companies like Piccadily Agro Industries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:35:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bd32de10c98d0787b258a_1766577249746.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's STQC Norms Unleash Surge in Domestic Surveillance Tech! Is Your Portfolio Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-STQC-Norms-Unleash-Surge-in-Domestic-Surveillance-Tech-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/694bcdf0e10c98d0787b20a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-STQC-Norms-Unleash-Surge-in-Domestic-Surveillance-Tech-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/694bcdf0e10c98d0787b20a8</guid><description>New government Standardisation Testing and Quality Certification (STQC) norms have significantly boosted India's security and surveillance market. According to Aditya Khemka, founder of Aditya Infotech, these regulations enhance trust and compliance, allowing domestic players to expand capacity and capture more market share. Global firms also see entry opportunities, driven by stricter audits covering supply-chain security and data protection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:07:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bcdf0e10c98d0787b20a7_1766575988021.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trading Halts! NSE, BSE Closed December 25th – Know Your Holiday Schedule NOW!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trading-Halts-NSE-BSE-Closed-December-25th-Know-Your-Holiday-Schedule-NOW/694bcd48e10c98d0787b1f7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trading-Halts-NSE-BSE-Closed-December-25th-Know-Your-Holiday-Schedule-NOW/694bcd48e10c98d0787b1f7c</guid><description>Indian stock markets, including the National Stock Exchange (NSE) and Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE), will be closed on December 25th for Christmas. This break affects equity, derivative, and currency trades. Additionally, the exchanges have released the full list of 15 trading holidays for 2026, covering national and religious observances. Investors should plan their trading strategies around these scheduled closures to avoid disruptions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:07:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bcd48e10c98d0787b1f7b_1766575518573.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Small Caps See Cash Flood Despite Losses! India's Retail Investors Double Down – What's Driving This Paradox?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Small-Caps-See-Cash-Flood-Despite-Losses-Indias-Retail-Investors-Double-Down-Whats-Driving-This-Paradox/694bcd9ce10c98d0787b2005</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Small-Caps-See-Cash-Flood-Despite-Losses-Indias-Retail-Investors-Double-Down-Whats-Driving-This-Paradox/694bcd9ce10c98d0787b2005</guid><description>Indian retail investors are pouring money into small-cap mutual funds, with November inflows jumping 27% to ₹4,406 crore. This surge continues despite the segment averaging a nearly 5% decline in 2025. Experts attribute this confidence to a disciplined long-term investment approach, easing valuation pressures, and potential earnings bottoming out, urging a focus on SIPs and diversification.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:07:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bcd9ce10c98d0787b2004_1766575755281.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cupid Shares Skyrocket 10X in Two Years: Promoter Slashes Pledge - Investor Confidence Soars!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Cupid-Shares-Skyrocket-10X-in-Two-Years-Promoter-Slashes-Pledge-Investor-Confidence-Soars/694bcd27e10c98d0787b1f2f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Cupid-Shares-Skyrocket-10X-in-Two-Years-Promoter-Slashes-Pledge-Investor-Confidence-Soars/694bcd27e10c98d0787b1f2f</guid><description>Cupid Limited's stock has surged dramatically, jumping 10 times in two years and over 500% this year, closing at ₹474.65. Promoters have significantly reduced their pledged shareholding from 36.13% to 20%, signaling improved financial strength and strong confidence in the company's long-term growth. Cupid manufactures condoms, lubricant jelly, and IVD kits, holding WHO/UNFPA pre-qualification status for condoms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:03:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bcd27e10c98d0787b1f2e_1766575489378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Miners Strike Gold in AI Data Centers as Crypto Mining Cools Down</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Miners-Strike-Gold-in-AI-Data-Centers-as-Crypto-Mining-Cools-Down/694bcc74e10c98d0787b1da5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Miners-Strike-Gold-in-AI-Data-Centers-as-Crypto-Mining-Cools-Down/694bcc74e10c98d0787b1da5</guid><description>Bitcoin miners are increasingly repurposing their data centers for the booming artificial intelligence industry. Facing declining profitability in crypto mining due to competition and events like the 'halving', miners are leveraging their existing infrastructure, including land, power contracts, and cooling systems, to serve AI giants like Alphabet, Amazon, Meta, and Microsoft. This strategic pivot is boosting miner stocks and providing AI companies with faster, cheaper expansion options, though it requires significant upgrades to specialized AI hardware and cooling.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:02:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bcc74e10c98d0787b1da4_1766575633211.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Energy Boom: Why This 'Everyone Wins' Stock Rally Faces a Reckoning!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/AI-Energy-Boom-Why-This-Everyone-Wins-Stock-Rally-Faces-a-Reckoning/694bcc0ce10c98d0787b1ce4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/AI-Energy-Boom-Why-This-Everyone-Wins-Stock-Rally-Faces-a-Reckoning/694bcc0ce10c98d0787b1ce4</guid><description>The power sector, from green renewables to traditional nuclear and fossil fuels, has seen a broad rally driven by surging electricity demand from Artificial Intelligence. Companies like Constellation Energy, GE Vernova, and Bloom Energy have soared. However, analysts warn this 'everyone's a winner' trend may not last, as high stock valuations require tangible AI deal execution, especially in 2026. Renewable stocks like NextEra Energy and First Solar show less dramatic price gains.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:02:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bcc0ce10c98d0787b1ce3_1766575414271.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Power Unleashes Rs 2 Lakh Crore Mega-Plan: India's Energy Future Set for Massive Overhaul!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Unleashes-Rs-2-Lakh-Crore-Mega-Plan-Indias-Energy-Future-Set-for-Massive-Overhaul/694bcb87e10c98d0787b1c1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Unleashes-Rs-2-Lakh-Crore-Mega-Plan-Indias-Energy-Future-Set-for-Massive-Overhaul/694bcb87e10c98d0787b1c1a</guid><description>Adani Power plans a Rs 2 lakh crore capital expenditure by FY32, aiming to increase installed capacity to 41.87 gigawatt. This aggressive expansion is designed to meet India's projected surge in electricity demand, reinforcing the critical role of thermal power in the nation's energy security. The company has secured land and key equipment orders for its significant project pipeline.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:58:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bcb87e10c98d0787b1c19_1766575233120.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gratuity Promise Delayed: New Labour Laws Spark Confusion, Employees Wait as States Hold Back Rules</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Gratuity-Promise-Delayed-New-Labour-Laws-Spark-Confusion-Employees-Wait-as-States-Hold-Back-Rules/694bcab3e10c98d0787b1ac3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Gratuity-Promise-Delayed-New-Labour-Laws-Spark-Confusion-Employees-Wait-as-States-Hold-Back-Rules/694bcab3e10c98d0787b1ac3</guid><description>New labour codes promised gratuity for fixed-term employees after just one year, down from five. However, despite central notification, states have not yet issued their own rules. This delay leaves companies hesitant to implement the change due to compliance risks, meaning employees continue under the old five-year rule, creating uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:58:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bcab3e10c98d0787b1ac2_1766575151928.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Juniper Green Energy Ignites India's Energy Storage Race with Landmark Rajasthan BESS Project!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Juniper-Green-Energy-Ignites-Indias-Energy-Storage-Race-with-Landmark-Rajasthan-BESS-Project/694bc9eae10c98d0787b1962</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Juniper-Green-Energy-Ignites-Indias-Energy-Storage-Race-with-Landmark-Rajasthan-BESS-Project/694bc9eae10c98d0787b1962</guid><description>Juniper Green Energy has commissioned 60 MWh of its 100 MWh merchant Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) project in Bikaner, Rajasthan. This milestone marks the company's first operational merchant BESS, positioning it as an early leader in India's energy storage market. Commercial operations began on December 24, 2025, with the remaining capacity expected soon. A further 400 MWh BESS is planned by Q1 2026, bolstering India's energy transition by enhancing grid stability and renewable integration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:57:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc9eae10c98d0787b1961_1766574654270.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Green Hydrogen Breakthrough: KPI Green Energy Lands ₹128 Crore NTPC Order!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Green-Hydrogen-Breakthrough-KPI-Green-Energy-Lands-128-Crore-NTPC-Order/694bc9c8e10c98d0787b191d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Green-Hydrogen-Breakthrough-KPI-Green-Energy-Lands-128-Crore-NTPC-Order/694bc9c8e10c98d0787b191d</guid><description>KPI Green Energy announced a significant ₹128.49 crore order from state-owned NTPC to establish a green hydrogen generation project. Utilizing advanced plasma gasification technology, the project will convert waste materials into hydrogen, supporting NTPC's initiative for a 1 tonne/day plant in Greater Noida. This move marks a key development for KPI Green Energy in the rapidly expanding renewable energy sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:57:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc9c8e10c98d0787b191c_1766574602379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Power Unlocks $22 Billion Powerhouse Plan: India's Energy Future Set for Massive Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Unlocks-22-Billion-Powerhouse-Plan-Indias-Energy-Future-Set-for-Massive-Surge/694bca7ce10c98d0787b1a64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Unlocks-22-Billion-Powerhouse-Plan-Indias-Energy-Future-Set-for-Massive-Surge/694bca7ce10c98d0787b1a64</guid><description>Adani Power Ltd has unveiled an ambitious expansion, targeting 41.87 GW of installed capacity by FY32, backed by a staggering ₹2 lakh crore capital expenditure. This represents India's largest private-sector thermal power investment, aiming to secure the nation's growing electricity demand amidst rising industrial and urban needs. The company has a secured pipeline of 23.72 GW, including multiple greenfield projects and a recent entry into hydropower.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:57:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bca7ce10c98d0787b1a63_1766574792657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Northern Arc Capital: Buy Signal Ignites as Retail Pivot Unlocks Hidden Growth Potential!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Northern-Arc-Capital-Buy-Signal-Ignites-as-Retail-Pivot-Unlocks-Hidden-Growth-Potential/694bc954e10c98d0787b1810</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Northern-Arc-Capital-Buy-Signal-Ignites-as-Retail-Pivot-Unlocks-Hidden-Growth-Potential/694bc954e10c98d0787b1810</guid><description>Northern Arc Capital Ltd is recommended a 'Buy' as analysts believe the market is overlooking its improving Net Interest Margin (NIM) and Return on Equity (ROE) prospects due to a strategic shift to direct-to-consumer (D2C) retail lending since FY22. This transition is expected to boost ROE to 15.7% by FY28. Fee income from finance placement and fund management will also contribute, helping absorb higher credit costs. The company is poised for strong EPS growth, with potential for further expansion in vehicle and affordable home finance. A current valuation discount to peers makes it attractive.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:57:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc954e10c98d0787b180f_1766575044406.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mark Your Calendars! India's 2026 Stock Market Holidays Announced - What Traders Need to Know NOW!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Mark-Your-Calendars-Indias-2026-Stock-Market-Holidays-Announced-What-Traders-Need-to-Know-NOW/694bc8ffe10c98d0787b1774</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Mark-Your-Calendars-Indias-2026-Stock-Market-Holidays-Announced-What-Traders-Need-to-Know-NOW/694bc8ffe10c98d0787b1774</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange (NSE) and Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) have released their trading holiday schedule for 2026, announcing 15 days when markets will be closed. This reduction in working days compared to previous years, coupled with potential extra holidays due to local elections and the Union Budget presentation, requires careful planning from investors and traders. The schedule also clarifies rules for options expiry falling on holidays and details the auspicious Muhurat Trading session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:57:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc8ffe10c98d0787b1773_1766574791740.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Mutual Fund Sells Delhivery Shares: What This Means for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SBI-Mutual-Fund-Sells-Delhivery-Shares-What-This-Means-for-Your-Investments/694bc8f1e10c98d0787b1729</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SBI-Mutual-Fund-Sells-Delhivery-Shares-What-This-Means-for-Your-Investments/694bc8f1e10c98d0787b1729</guid><description>SBI Mutual Fund significantly reduced its stake in Delhivery, the logistics giant, selling 18.18 lakh shares on December 22nd, bringing its holding down to 5.69%. This stake trimming, valued at INR 74.45 Cr, follows a trend over the past two years. The move comes amidst Delhivery reporting a net loss of INR 50.5 Cr in Q2 FY26, largely due to the integration costs of its rival Ecom Express, which are expected to add further financial pressure. Despite these challenges, Delhivery is diversifying with a new fintech subsidiary and international expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:54:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc8f1e10c98d0787b1728_1766574904211.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Drops Bombshell: Forewarned is Forearmed! New Rules Force Banks to Reveal ALL Hidden Forex Charges!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Drops-Bombshell-Forewarned-is-Forearmed-New-Rules-Force-Banks-to-Reveal-ALL-Hidden-Forex-Charges/694bc7cfe10c98d0787b1593</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Drops-Bombshell-Forewarned-is-Forearmed-New-Rules-Force-Banks-to-Reveal-ALL-Hidden-Forex-Charges/694bc7cfe10c98d0787b1593</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has proposed new draft rules to increase transparency in foreign exchange transactions. These regulations mandate banks and authorized dealers to disclose the complete cost of forex deals upfront, including exchange rates, conversion fees, and intermediary charges. This aims to empower retail customers with clear pricing information for better decision-making. Public comments are being accepted until January 9, 2026, before final guidelines are issued.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:51:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc7cfe10c98d0787b1592_1766574312897.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godavari Biorefineries Soars 11% on US Biotech Expansion News!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Godavari-Biorefineries-Soars-11percent-on-US-Biotech-Expansion-News/694bc44ce10c98d0787b116e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Godavari-Biorefineries-Soars-11percent-on-US-Biotech-Expansion-News/694bc44ce10c98d0787b116e</guid><description>Godavari Biorefineries shares surged over 11% to ₹300 intraday on Wednesday following the incorporation of a new US subsidiary, Sathgen Therapeutics LLC, in New Jersey. This strategic move aims to bolster the company's clinical-stage biotechnology presence, focusing on global intellectual property out-licensing and accelerating drug development programs. The stock closed 8% higher at ₹290.5, significantly outperforming the BSE Sensex.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:34:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc44ce10c98d0787b116d_1766573196602.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Top Stocks Today: Who Soared, Who Sank? Trent, Shriram Finance Lead Gains; Interglobe Aviation, Dr Reddys Face Losses!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Top-Stocks-Today-Who-Soared-Who-Sank-Trent-Shriram-Finance-Lead-Gains-Interglobe-Aviation-Dr-Reddys-Face-Losses/694bc3f3e10c98d0787b10ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Top-Stocks-Today-Who-Soared-Who-Sank-Trent-Shriram-Finance-Lead-Gains-Interglobe-Aviation-Dr-Reddys-Face-Losses/694bc3f3e10c98d0787b10ce</guid><description>On December 24, 2025, Trent Ltd and Shriram Finance Ltd emerged as top gainers, while Interglobe Aviation Ltd and Dr Reddys Laboratories Ltd were among the top losers in the Indian stock market. Major indices like the Sensex, Nifty 50, and Nifty Bank experienced slight downturns during the trading session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:33:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc3f3e10c98d0787b10cd_1766573827521.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Guru Dipan Mehta Reveals 2026 'Must-Watch' Sectors &amp; Top Stock Picks That Could Soar!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Guru-Dipan-Mehta-Reveals-2026-Must-Watch-Sectors-and-Top-Stock-Picks-That-Could-Soar/694bc432e10c98d0787b1127</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Guru-Dipan-Mehta-Reveals-2026-Must-Watch-Sectors-and-Top-Stock-Picks-That-Could-Soar/694bc432e10c98d0787b1127</guid><description>Veteran market expert Dipan Mehta is bullish on Indian equities for 2026, anticipating a return to leadership for small and mid-cap stocks as earnings catch up with valuations. He favors the auto sector, highlighting Ashok Leyland, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, Eicher Motors, and TVS Motor. For metals, Vedanta is his top long-term pick, while Adani Ports is seen as a strategic global play. Coal India is viewed as a short-term trading stock. Cholamandalam Finance remains a core holding despite recent scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:33:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc432e10c98d0787b1126_1766574065806.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BREAKING: India Splits Trade &amp; Investment Talks with GCC Bloc – Faster Deals Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/BREAKING-India-Splits-Trade-and-Investment-Talks-with-GCC-Bloc-Faster-Deals-Ahead/694bc349e10c98d0787b0f4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/BREAKING-India-Splits-Trade-and-Investment-Talks-with-GCC-Bloc-Faster-Deals-Ahead/694bc349e10c98d0787b0f4c</guid><description>India and the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) have agreed to separate negotiations for a Bilateral Investment Treaty (BIT) from Free Trade Agreement (FTA) discussions. This decoupling aims to accelerate the FTA process, potentially leading to quicker trade deals with the bloc or individual members like Qatar and Bahrain if BIT talks face delays. India's trade with the GCC stood at $161.59 billion in FY24.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:33:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc349e10c98d0787b0f4b_1766573696556.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking Truth: India's Deadly PM2.5 Pollution is Made, Not Just Emitted! Coal Plants Caught in Crosshairs.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Shocking-Truth-Indias-Deadly-PM25-Pollution-is-Made-Not-Just-Emitted-Coal-Plants-Caught-in-Crosshairs/694bc3a1e10c98d0787b0ffe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Shocking-Truth-Indias-Deadly-PM25-Pollution-is-Made-Not-Just-Emitted-Coal-Plants-Caught-in-Crosshairs/694bc3a1e10c98d0787b0ffe</guid><description>A new study by the Centre for Research on Energy and Clean Air (CREA) reveals that up to 42% of India's PM2.5 air pollution isn't directly emitted but forms chemically in the atmosphere. Sulphur dioxide (SO2) from coal-fired power plants is a primary source, yet most plants lack crucial pollution control systems. This points to regulatory gaps and highlights the need to control precursor gases for effective air quality improvement, especially in states like Chhattisgarh, Odisha, and Delhi.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:29:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc3a1e10c98d0787b0ffd_1766573060758.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Telecom Boom! Govt Receipts Skyrocket 47% as Tariff Hikes Fuel Massive Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Telecom-Boom-Govt-Receipts-Skyrocket-47percent-as-Tariff-Hikes-Fuel-Massive-Revenue-Surge/694bc36ae10c98d0787b0f92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Telecom-Boom-Govt-Receipts-Skyrocket-47percent-as-Tariff-Hikes-Fuel-Massive-Revenue-Surge/694bc36ae10c98d0787b0f92</guid><description>The Department of Telecommunications (DoT) collected ₹79,121 crore from telecom operators between April and November, a 47% increase year-on-year. This surge is attributed to telecom firms raising tariffs, leading to higher revenue share for the government, and steady payments for licence fees. Concurrently, capital expenditure on telecom infrastructure, especially BharatNet fiber rollouts, more than tripled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:27:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc36ae10c98d0787b0f91_1766572994973.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shankh Air Gets Green Light: New Airline Set to Take Off in India by Early 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Shankh-Air-Gets-Green-Light-New-Airline-Set-to-Take-Off-in-India-by-Early-2026/694bc25ee10c98d0787b0dec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Shankh-Air-Gets-Green-Light-New-Airline-Set-to-Take-Off-in-India-by-Early-2026/694bc25ee10c98d0787b0dec</guid><description>Shankh Air has received a no-objection certificate from India's civil aviation ministry and plans to launch flight services in the first quarter of 2026. The Uttar Pradesh-based airline, operated by Shankh Aviation, aims to build a fleet of 20-25 aircraft within two to three years. This move comes as India's aviation market is experiencing rapid growth, with the ministry assuring support for a smooth operational launch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:27:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc25ee10c98d0787b0deb_1766572712733.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samsonite Bets Big on India: Nashik Plant Triples Capacity, Becomes Global Manufacturing Hub!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Samsonite-Bets-Big-on-India-Nashik-Plant-Triples-Capacity-Becomes-Global-Manufacturing-Hub/694bc26ee10c98d0787b0e1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Samsonite-Bets-Big-on-India-Nashik-Plant-Triples-Capacity-Becomes-Global-Manufacturing-Hub/694bc26ee10c98d0787b0e1c</guid><description>Samsonite has significantly expanded its Nashik, India plant, tripling its capacity to 7 lakh units per month with a Rs 250 crore investment, making India its largest global manufacturing base. The company anticipates strong demand driven by domestic travel, weddings, and rising disposable incomes, and is planning further expansion within India while also increasing exports.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:25:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc26ee10c98d0787b0e1b_1766573506725.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock 2026 Wealth: 5 Top SBI Mutual Funds With 5-Star Ratings &amp; Lowest Costs Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Unlock-2026-Wealth-5-Top-SBI-Mutual-Funds-With-5-Star-Ratings-and-Lowest-Costs-Revealed/694bc1a2e10c98d0787b0c46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Unlock-2026-Wealth-5-Top-SBI-Mutual-Funds-With-5-Star-Ratings-and-Lowest-Costs-Revealed/694bc1a2e10c98d0787b0c46</guid><description>Discover five top-rated SBI Mutual Funds for 2026 investment, focusing on 5-star ratings from Value Research and low expense ratios. These growth-oriented equity and hybrid funds cater to diverse investor needs, from aggressive growth to conservative planning and tax saving, ensuring more returns stay with you.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:24:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc1a2e10c98d0787b0c45_1766572890999.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Startup Surge: VC Funding Jumps 17% Defying Global Slump!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Surge-VC-Funding-Jumps-17percent-Defying-Global-Slump/694bc1a9e10c98d0787b0c71</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Surge-VC-Funding-Jumps-17percent-Defying-Global-Slump/694bc1a9e10c98d0787b0c71</guid><description>India's venture capital market showed remarkable resilience in 2025, achieving double-digit growth. From January to November, deal volumes rose by approximately 11% and deal values by 17% year-on-year. This strong performance contrasts sharply with contractions seen in major markets like the US and UK, and declines in China. India continues to solidify its position as a top global player in venture capital, with future growth expected to focus on high-quality, scalable startups.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:23:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bc1a9e10c98d0787b0c70_1766573353727.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Music Giants Rewrite the Rules: Beyond Rights to Artist Powerhouse!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Music-Giants-Rewrite-the-Rules-Beyond-Rights-to-Artist-Powerhouse/694bbcf0e10c98d0787b067d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Music-Giants-Rewrite-the-Rules-Beyond-Rights-to-Artist-Powerhouse/694bbcf0e10c98d0787b067d</guid><description>Indian music labels like Saregama and Universal Music Group are transforming from mere rights owners into comprehensive artist managers. They are increasingly focusing on the booming independent music scene, offering artists a full spectrum of services beyond recorded music to build deeper fan engagement and unlock diverse revenue streams like brand deals and live shows amidst fierce competition and gradual streaming growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:05:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bbcf0e10c98d0787b067c_1766572387589.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Set for Historic Surge? Expert Forecasts Astonishing $5000 Gold, $100 Silver by 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Set-for-Historic-Surge-Expert-Forecasts-Astonishing-5000-Gold-100-Silver-by-2026/694bbc65e10c98d0787b05ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Set-for-Historic-Surge-Expert-Forecasts-Astonishing-5000-Gold-100-Silver-by-2026/694bbc65e10c98d0787b05ba</guid><description>Surendra Mehta, Secretary of the India Bullion and Jewellers Association, predicts a significant surge in precious metal prices. By 2026, silver could reach $95-$100 per ounce, and gold may climb to $4,900-$5,100 per ounce. This forecast is driven by structural market changes, including high lease rates and a notable shift from paper silver to physical holdings. Despite expected short-term corrections, Mehta suggests a strong long-term outlook for both gold and silver.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:59:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bbc65e10c98d0787b05b9_1766572157321.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Delhi High Court DEMANDS GST Cut on Air Purifiers Amidst Pollution Crisis!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Delhi-High-Court-DEMANDS-GST-Cut-on-Air-Purifiers-Amidst-Pollution-Crisis/694bba8ae10c98d0787b03f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Delhi-High-Court-DEMANDS-GST-Cut-on-Air-Purifiers-Amidst-Pollution-Crisis/694bba8ae10c98d0787b03f9</guid><description>The Delhi High Court has strongly urged the Goods and Services Tax Council to convene an urgent meeting to consider significantly reducing the Goods and Services Tax (GST) on air purifiers. The court suggested lowering the tax from the current 18% to 5%, citing the critical air pollution levels in Delhi and surrounding areas. This directive follows a plea arguing that air purifiers are essential for health, not luxury items, and should be more accessible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:54:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bba8ae10c98d0787b03f8_1766570743752.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Delhi Metro Expansion Approved! Rs 12,015 Cr Project to Add 13 Stations &amp; 16 Km, Boosting City Connectivity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Delhi-Metro-Expansion-Approved-Rs-12015-Cr-Project-to-Add-13-Stations-and-16-Km-Boosting-City-Connectivity/694bba0fe10c98d0787b02ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Delhi-Metro-Expansion-Approved-Rs-12015-Cr-Project-to-Add-13-Stations-and-16-Km-Boosting-City-Connectivity/694bba0fe10c98d0787b02ee</guid><description>The Union Cabinet has approved ₹12,015 crore for Delhi Metro Phase V, adding 16 kilometers and 13 new stations across three corridors. This expansion will extend the metro network beyond 400 kilometers within three years, improving last-mile connectivity and reducing congestion. The project is expected to save approximately 33,000 tonnes of CO2 emissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:52:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bba0fe10c98d0787b02ed_1766571192018.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>