<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:59:23 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Maharashtra Power Plant Units Ordered Closed Over Pollution Violations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Maharashtra-Power-Plant-Units-Ordered-Closed-Over-Pollution-Violations/698c0a010c9da38e2e764bdc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Maharashtra-Power-Plant-Units-Ordered-Closed-Over-Pollution-Violations/698c0a010c9da38e2e764bdc</guid><description>The Central Pollution Control Board (CPCB) has directed the immediate cessation of operations for units 6 and 8 at the Parli Thermal Power Station (PTPS) in Maharashtra. This directive, issued on February 5, 2026, stems from a pattern of environmental non-compliance, including excessively high particulate matter emissions and expired operating consents, highlighting significant regulatory breaches by the state-owned facility. The Maharashtra Pollution Control Board (MPCB) is tasked with enforcing the closure, underscoring the seriousness of the environmental infractions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India VC: Growth in Deals, Value Share Slips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-VC-Growth-in-Deals-Value-Share-Slips/698c09240c9da38e2e764b1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-VC-Growth-in-Deals-Value-Share-Slips/698c09240c9da38e2e764b1f</guid><description>India's venture capital sector demonstrated notable resilience in 2025, with deal volume increasing approximately 11% year-on-year. This growth occurred even as global deal volumes contracted by about 3%. However, India's share of global funding value saw a dip, falling to around 3.5% from 4.2%, primarily because the market did not witness any billion-dollar funding rounds, a trend contrasting sharply with capital concentration in markets like the United States.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>US-India Trade Deal: Concessions for Energy, Softer Promises Elsewhere</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-India-Trade-Deal-Concessions-for-Energy-Softer-Promises-Elsewhere/698c08260c9da38e2e764a20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-India-Trade-Deal-Concessions-for-Energy-Softer-Promises-Elsewhere/698c08260c9da38e2e764a20</guid><description>The White House has updated its factsheet on the US-India trade framework, signaling a recalibration of commitments. While India secured the removal of a punitive 25% tariff by agreeing to curtail Russian oil imports, the revised document now states India 'intends' to purchase American products, down from a prior 'commitment.' Specific agricultural products like 'certain pulses' were omitted from tariff reduction lists, and the claim of India removing digital services taxes was dropped. These adjustments suggest persistent complexities in finalizing broader trade liberalization, particularly for US agricultural and technology exporters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Quadrant Future Tek Bags ₹181 Cr KAVACH Order from BLW</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quadrant-Future-Tek-Bags-181-Cr-KAVACH-Order-from-BLW/698c06bc0c9da38e2e764474</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quadrant-Future-Tek-Bags-181-Cr-KAVACH-Order-from-BLW/698c06bc0c9da38e2e764474</guid><description>Quadrant Future Tek has accepted a significant ₹181.57 crore order from Banaras Locomotive Works (BLW) for the supply, installation, testing, and commissioning of 223 Onboard KAVACH Loco Equipment Ver- 4.0. The order, to be executed within 12 months, is a domestic win for the company, reinforcing its role in critical railway safety technology. This substantial order is poised to positively impact Quadrant Future Tek's financial performance in the upcoming fiscal year.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jobs Report Test: JPMorgan Offers Scenarios for Market Rebound</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jobs-Report-Test-JPMorgan-Offers-Scenarios-for-Market-Rebound/698c04ce0c9da38e2e763d9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jobs-Report-Test-JPMorgan-Offers-Scenarios-for-Market-Rebound/698c04ce0c9da38e2e763d9c</guid><description>The stock market's resurgence faces its most significant test this week with the upcoming January jobs report. JPMorgan Chase's trading desk has outlined several scenarios detailing how the data could influence market dynamics, from potentially boosting the rally to triggering a sell-off. The report is critical for understanding Federal Reserve policy and its implications for interest rates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Legal Win Against Journalist Signals Firm Stance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Adani-Enterprises-Legal-Win-Against-Journalist-Signals-Firm-Stance/698c045a0c9da38e2e763d74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Adani-Enterprises-Legal-Win-Against-Journalist-Signals-Firm-Stance/698c045a0c9da38e2e763d74</guid><description>Adani Enterprises secured a one-year jail sentence for journalist Ravi Nair following a criminal defamation case. The ruling, stemming from tweets and articles accusing the Adani Group of corruption and malpractices, underscores the company's aggressive strategy to protect its reputation against perceived misinformation. This legal victory, while specific to one journalist, aligns with Adani's broader approach to managing its public image amidst increased global scrutiny and ongoing regulatory investigations. The company is leveraging legal recourse to reinforce brand integrity and deter critical reporting, aiming to maintain investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Britannia Profit Jumps 17%, But High Valuation &amp; Labor Costs Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannia-Profit-Jumps-17percent-But-High-Valuation-and-Labor-Costs-Loom/698c02870c9da38e2e763ae6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannia-Profit-Jumps-17percent-But-High-Valuation-and-Labor-Costs-Loom/698c02870c9da38e2e763ae6</guid><description>Britannia Industries posted a 17% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹682 crore for Q3 FY26, fueled by a 9.5% revenue rise and better-than-expected volume growth of 4.5%. However, the company also recorded a ₹48.56 crore one-time expense linked to new labor codes. Despite margin expansion, the market's high valuation of Britannia, trading at a P/E of approximately 61x, prompts analysis into the sustainability of its growth amidst evolving competitive dynamics and rising operational costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Laxmi Finance Surges on Profit Growth, Asset Quality Concerns Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Laxmi-Finance-Surges-on-Profit-Growth-Asset-Quality-Concerns-Emerge/698c020e0c9da38e2e763aca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Laxmi-Finance-Surges-on-Profit-Growth-Asset-Quality-Concerns-Emerge/698c020e0c9da38e2e763aca</guid><description>Laxmi India Finance posted a strong Q3 FY26, with PAT soaring 63.59% YoY to ₹10.06 Cr on 46.21% income growth. Nine-month PAT climbed 36%, and AUM hit ₹1,451 Cr. Despite a reduced Debt Equity Ratio to 2.69 post-IPO, GNPA rose to 2.40% due to a DSA partner's stress. Management targets 30% AUM CAGR and improved ROE/ROA.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CLSA Favors Muthoot Finance, Flags Manappuram Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CLSA-Favors-Muthoot-Finance-Flags-Manappuram-Divergence/698bfe4b0c9da38e2e7637ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CLSA-Favors-Muthoot-Finance-Flags-Manappuram-Divergence/698bfe4b0c9da38e2e7637ff</guid><description>Global brokerage CLSA has upgraded Muthoot Finance to 'Outperform' with a higher price target, highlighting strong profit growth catalysts including rising gold prices, LTV expansion, and operating leverage. Conversely, CLSA maintained a 'Hold' on Manappuram Finance. This divergence reflects differing outlooks on loan growth, margins, and competitive positioning within the gold financing sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 03:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NIIF Divests Ather Energy Stake Amid EBITDA Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NIIF-Divests-Ather-Energy-Stake-Amid-EBITDA-Dip/698bfdd60c9da38e2e7637dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NIIF-Divests-Ather-Energy-Stake-Amid-EBITDA-Dip/698bfdd60c9da38e2e7637dd</guid><description>The National Investment and Infrastructure Fund (NIIF) has divested a stake in Ather Energy Ltd. for ₹233 crore, coinciding with the electric scooter manufacturer's reported third-quarter results. While Ather Energy announced a 50% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹953.6 crore and a narrowed net loss, its earnings before interest, tax, depreciation, and amortisation (EBITDA) decreased to ₹72 crore from ₹140 crore in the same period last year. This decline in operational profitability, coupled with a significant fund exit, presents a critical divergence for investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 03:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trimex Foods Eyes ₹800 Cr Stake Sale Amidst F&amp;B Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trimex-Foods-Eyes-800-Cr-Stake-Sale-Amidst-FandB-Boom/698bfcd80c9da38e2e763662</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trimex-Foods-Eyes-800-Cr-Stake-Sale-Amidst-FandB-Boom/698bfcd80c9da38e2e763662</guid><description>Trimex Foods, operator of Chili's, Cinnabon, and Paul Bakery in India, is divesting a minority stake, aiming for a ₹700-800 crore valuation to fuel aggressive expansion. The company reported ₹206 crore revenue in FY24 with a significant EBITDA CAGR, capitalizing on India's robust food services market growth. Discussions are ongoing with private equity firms and family offices, highlighting investor interest in the sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 03:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HBL Engineering Lands ₹800 Cr KAVACH Order from BLW</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HBL-Engineering-Lands-800-Cr-KAVACH-Order-from-BLW/698bfb7b0c9da38e2e763515</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HBL-Engineering-Lands-800-Cr-KAVACH-Order-from-BLW/698bfb7b0c9da38e2e763515</guid><description>HBL Engineering Limited has been awarded a significant Letter of Acceptance (LoA) from Banaras Locomotive Works (BLW) for ₹800.36 Crores. The contract, inclusive of GST, is for the supply, testing, and commissioning of On-board KAVACH equipment (Ver. 4.0) and is to be completed within 12 months, providing substantial revenue visibility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 03:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Titan's Q3 Surge: Premium Valuation Tested by Gold Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titans-Q3-Surge-Premium-Valuation-Tested-by-Gold-Volatility/698bf5670c9da38e2e762a6c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titans-Q3-Surge-Premium-Valuation-Tested-by-Gold-Volatility/698bf5670c9da38e2e762a6c</guid><description>Titan Company reported robust Q3 FY26 earnings, driven by a substantial 61% net profit increase to Rs 1,684 crore and a 40% revenue jump to Rs 25,400 crore, largely fueled by its jewellery segment. The stock reached a fresh 52-week high, reflecting strong investor confidence. However, a premium valuation, coupled with the impact of rising gold prices on margins and intensifying market competition, presents key challenges for sustained growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 03:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Q3 Earnings Surge, MSCI Rejig Fuel Indian Markets; Risks Remain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Q3-Earnings-Surge-MSCI-Rejig-Fuel-Indian-Markets-Risks-Remain/698bf1fd0c9da38e2e7627c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Q3-Earnings-Surge-MSCI-Rejig-Fuel-Indian-Markets-Risks-Remain/698bf1fd0c9da38e2e7627c7</guid><description>Indian equity markets are poised for a strong open on Wednesday, February 11, 2026, with GIFT Nifty futures signaling gains. This optimism is bolstered by a robust wave of Q3 financial results from major corporations and the upcoming MSCI Global Standard Index rejig, which will see additions and weightage increases for several Indian companies. However, beneath the surface of positive earnings, potential headwinds from global economic pressures and company-specific challenges warrant investor scrutiny. Several large-cap companies reported significant year-on-year profit and revenue growth, indicating resilience in consumer spending and industrial demand, despite a mixed global market performance overnight.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 03:05:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698bf1fd0c9da38e2e7627c6_1770779383335.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SFBs Face Profitability Squeeze Amidst Growth Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SFBs-Face-Profitability-Squeeze-Amidst-Growth-Push/698bf1370c9da38e2e76273c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SFBs-Face-Profitability-Squeeze-Amidst-Growth-Push/698bf1370c9da38e2e76273c</guid><description>Small Finance Banks (SFBs), initially focused on financial inclusion since 2015, have expanded significantly with large loan books and branch networks. This aggressive growth trajectory now presents systemic risks, increased operating costs from technology investments, and potential asset quality stress. As SFBs aim for universal banking and potential stock listings, intense competition from fintechs and legacy banks, coupled with margin pressures, is intensifying scrutiny on their profitability and risk management capabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 03:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>OneSource, Hikma Get SFDA nod for Generic Ozempic in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/OneSource-Hikma-Get-SFDA-nod-for-Generic-Ozempic-in-Saudi-Arabia/698bf0970c9da38e2e762648</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/OneSource-Hikma-Get-SFDA-nod-for-Generic-Ozempic-in-Saudi-Arabia/698bf0970c9da38e2e762648</guid><description>OneSource Specialty Pharma and Hikma Pharmaceuticals have secured SFDA approval to market a generic version of Ozempic (semaglutide) in Saudi Arabia. OneSource will manufacture the drug in India, while Hikma will handle distribution across Saudi Arabia and the MENA region. This move capitalizes on Saudi Arabia's significant market for GLP-1 therapies and aims to improve patient access to affordable alternatives.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Markets Eye Flat Open as Derivatives Data Signals Range-Bound Trade</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Eye-Flat-Open-as-Derivatives-Data-Signals-Range-Bound-Trade/698bee6c0c9da38e2e76249a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Eye-Flat-Open-as-Derivatives-Data-Signals-Range-Bound-Trade/698bee6c0c9da38e2e76249a</guid><description>Indian markets are expected to open flat on Wednesday amid mixed global signals. Derivative data indicates call writers are capping immediate upside around the 26,000 Nifty strike, while put writers establish support at 25,500, suggesting a range-bound trading environment. Despite this, foreign institutional investor (FII) flows have turned decisively positive, and domestic institutional investors (DIIs) continue their accumulation strategy, bolstering market sentiment and reducing volatility as India VIX eased. Several key stocks, including BHEL, Tata Motors, L&amp;T Finance, IRCTC, and Alok Industries, are under focus due to Q3 earnings season activity and sector-specific developments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Alphabet Raises $32 Billion for AI, Sells Rare 100-Year Bond</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Raises-32-Billion-for-AI-Sells-Rare-100-Year-Bond/698beaab0c9da38e2e7619c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Raises-32-Billion-for-AI-Sells-Rare-100-Year-Bond/698beaab0c9da38e2e7619c9</guid><description>Alphabet Inc. has secured nearly $32 billion in debt financing, including a landmark 100-year sterling bond. The massive issuance fuels the company's aggressive artificial intelligence expansion plans. Robust investor demand underscored the market's strong appetite for funding the tech sector's AI ambitions, despite rising concerns over debt scale.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jubilant Foodworks: Margin Nuance Amidst Growth Optimism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Jubilant-Foodworks-Margin-Nuance-Amidst-Growth-Optimism/698bea9e0c9da38e2e7618eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Jubilant-Foodworks-Margin-Nuance-Amidst-Growth-Optimism/698bea9e0c9da38e2e7618eb</guid><description>Jubilant Foodworks reported a strong third quarter with a 31.7% profit increase and 11.8% revenue growth, driven by robust EBITDA performance. Dominos India and Popeyes brands showed consistent like-for-like growth. Despite an expanding EBITDA margin to 20.5%, gross margins saw a marginal dip to 74.9%. Analyst sentiment is largely positive, with multiple 'buy' ratings and targets indicating significant upside potential, though the stock's recent six-month decline suggests underlying investor caution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>₹10,000 SIP Breeds ₹1 Crore: Baroda Fund's 20-Year Milestone</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/10000-SIP-Breeds-1-Crore-Baroda-Funds-20-Year-Milestone/698bea250c9da38e2e76115c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/10000-SIP-Breeds-1-Crore-Baroda-Funds-20-Year-Milestone/698bea250c9da38e2e76115c</guid><description>Baroda BNP Paribas ELSS Tax Saver Fund marks 20 years, turning a ₹10,000 monthly SIP into over ₹1.03 crore with 12.90% annualized SIP returns. Managed by Sanjay Chawla, the fund achieved an 11.65% CAGR since inception by focusing on predictable earnings and stable businesses. This ELSS scheme offers tax benefits under Section 80C but includes a mandatory three-year lock-in period per investment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Parveen Satija Eyes Ortin Global, Launches ₹31 Cr Open Offer at ₹14.65</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Parveen-Satija-Eyes-Ortin-Global-Launches-31-Cr-Open-Offer-at-1465/698be8ba0c9da38e2e75fd9d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Parveen-Satija-Eyes-Ortin-Global-Launches-31-Cr-Open-Offer-at-1465/698be8ba0c9da38e2e75fd9d</guid><description>Mr. Parveen Satija, via Rarever Financial Advisors, has launched a public open offer for Ortin Global Limited, seeking to acquire up to 26% of the company's voting share capital at ₹14.65 per share. The offer, valued at approximately ₹3.1 crore, is triggered by Mr. Satija's acquisition of 1.23% from existing promoters. This move positions Mr. Satija to become the new promoter and gain control of the BSE/NSE-listed entity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Shah Foods Open Offer: New Promoters Emerge, Minority Shareholders Get Exit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shah-Foods-Open-Offer-New-Promoters-Emerge-Minority-Shareholders-Get-Exit/698be7540c9da38e2e75fb63</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shah-Foods-Open-Offer-New-Promoters-Emerge-Minority-Shareholders-Get-Exit/698be7540c9da38e2e75fb63</guid><description>Shah Foods Limited announced an open offer to acquire up to 60,61,900 equity shares, representing 26% of its capital, at ₹62.50 per share. The offer is triggered by a preferential issue of shares to acquirers (Mr. Ankit Jalan and Mr. Anuj Jalan) and PACs for acquiring a stake in Tandhan Power Technologies Private Limited, and a share purchase agreement for existing shares. Upon completion, the acquirers and PACs will collectively hold 69.39%, becoming the new promoter group.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Anand Rathi Expert: IFCI, Swiggy, Fortis Top Buy Picks for Feb 11</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Anand-Rathi-Expert-IFCI-Swiggy-Fortis-Top-Buy-Picks-for-Feb-11/698be7540c9da38e2e75fb5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Anand-Rathi-Expert-IFCI-Swiggy-Fortis-Top-Buy-Picks-for-Feb-11/698be7540c9da38e2e75fb5c</guid><description>Mehul Kothari of Anand Rathi Shares and Stock Brokers identifies IFCI, Swiggy, and Fortis as top stock picks for February 11, 2026. The recommendations are based on technical analysis, citing bullish momentum for IFCI, trend reversal for Swiggy, and range breakout for Fortis, complete with specific buy zones, stop losses, and price targets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Climbs on Rate Cut Hopes, But Fed Caution Lingers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Climbs-on-Rate-Cut-Hopes-But-Fed-Caution-Lingers/698be41b0c9da38e2e75f6c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Climbs-on-Rate-Cut-Hopes-But-Fed-Caution-Lingers/698be41b0c9da38e2e75f6c6</guid><description>Precious metals saw gains as softer US retail sales data bolstered expectations for Federal Reserve rate cuts, driving down Treasury yields. Spot gold approached $5,040 per ounce, and silver rebounded. In India, gold ETFs attracted record inflows in January, signaling a flight to safety amidst geopolitical tensions and portfolio diversification, with inflows nearly matching equity funds. However, Fed officials signal no urgency to cut rates, highlighting persistent inflation concerns and an uncertain policy path ahead.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:06:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AU Small Finance Surges on MSCI Inflow; L&amp;T, AB Capital Added to Global Index</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AU-Small-Finance-Surges-on-MSCI-Inflow-LandT-AB-Capital-Added-to-Global-Index/698be3bd0c9da38e2e75f699</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AU-Small-Finance-Surges-on-MSCI-Inflow-LandT-AB-Capital-Added-to-Global-Index/698be3bd0c9da38e2e75f699</guid><description>AU Small Finance Bank shares are drawing attention after its weight is set to increase in the MSCI Global Standard Index. Analysts predict around $172 million in foreign inflows for the lender following this adjustment. L&amp;T Finance Holdings and Aditya Birla Capital have been added to the index, while IRCTC faces exclusion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:04:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698be3bd0c9da38e2e75f698_1770775801075.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE &amp; India Post Forge Rural MF Access</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/NSE-and-India-Post-Forge-Rural-MF-Access/698be39a0c9da38e2e75f690</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/NSE-and-India-Post-Forge-Rural-MF-Access/698be39a0c9da38e2e75f690</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange (NSE) and India Post (DoP) have inked an agreement to distribute mutual fund products through India Post's extensive network of over 1.64 lakh offices, aiming to boost penetration in rural and semi-urban areas. The collaboration leverages the NSE MF Invest platform, offering end-to-end investor services, and includes training for 2,500 India Post personnel. This initiative seeks to channel untapped household savings into productive financial instruments, addressing the current low mutual fund penetration of approximately 10% in Indian households.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:04:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Britannia's Margin Gains Clash With High Valuation Amidst Sector Optimism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannias-Margin-Gains-Clash-With-High-Valuation-Amidst-Sector-Optimism/698be3960c9da38e2e75f688</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannias-Margin-Gains-Clash-With-High-Valuation-Amidst-Sector-Optimism/698be3960c9da38e2e75f688</guid><description>Britannia Industries delivered robust third-quarter results, driven by a significant 450 basis point expansion in gross margins to 42.7%, fueled by stable input costs. Despite this operational strength and an 8.2% revenue growth, the company trades at a substantial P/E ratio of approximately 60-62x, significantly above the FMCG industry average. Analysts maintain a 'Buy' consensus with an average price target suggesting moderate upside, but the stock's flat year-to-date performance indicates investor scrutiny on sustained growth at such premium valuations. The recent appointment of Puneet Das as Chief Marketing Officer signals a strategic push to energize brand strategy and future expansion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 02:04:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698be3960c9da38e2e75f687_1770775793697.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Retiree Payout Peril: Timing Risk Trumps Returns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Retiree-Payout-Peril-Timing-Risk-Trumps-Returns/698be22b0c9da38e2e75f3fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Retiree-Payout-Peril-Timing-Risk-Trumps-Returns/698be22b0c9da38e2e75f3fc</guid><description>Indian retirees often receive large, one-time payouts that expose them to significant timing risk if invested all at once. This approach magnifies losses during market downturns, depletes retirement savings prematurely, and lacks the flexibility needed for unpredictable life events. Phased investing and dynamic withdrawal strategies are emerging as crucial tools to mitigate these risks, offering greater stability and longevity for retirement portfolios.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Global Markets Diverge: US Sales Wobble, Asia Rallies, Dow Hits Record</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Diverge-US-Sales-Wobble-Asia-Rallies-Dow-Hits-Record/698be2180c9da38e2e75f3e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Diverge-US-Sales-Wobble-Asia-Rallies-Dow-Hits-Record/698be2180c9da38e2e75f3e3</guid><description>Global markets displayed a fractured sentiment on February 11, 2025, as investors grappled with conflicting economic signals. In the US, disappointing retail sales data led to a dip in the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq, although the Dow Jones closed at a record high. Conversely, Asian markets opened higher, bucking the trend. Commodities experienced volatility, with gold prices declining and oil edging up. Domestic institutional investors continued their strong buying spree, injecting ₹1,174.21 crore into the market, while foreign institutions also posted net purchases.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Spending Fuels Market Hopes Amidst Economic Crosswinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/AI-Spending-Fuels-Market-Hopes-Amidst-Economic-Crosswinds/698bde240c9da38e2e75f1ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/AI-Spending-Fuels-Market-Hopes-Amidst-Economic-Crosswinds/698bde240c9da38e2e75f1ba</guid><description>Asian shares hover near record peaks as weak U.S. retail sales reinforce expectations of Federal Reserve rate cuts. However, substantial technology sector investment in artificial intelligence may mask underlying margin pressures and unsustainable growth, while central bank officials signal a data-dependent, cautious approach to monetary policy, creating a bifurcated market sentiment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Titan Beats Q3 Estimates; Valuation Scrutiny Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Beats-Q3-Estimates-Valuation-Scrutiny-Mounts/698bdd070c9da38e2e75efba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Beats-Q3-Estimates-Valuation-Scrutiny-Mounts/698bdd070c9da38e2e75efba</guid><description>Titan Company Ltd. posted robust third-quarter earnings, exceeding expectations with a 40% revenue jump and 55% EBITDA growth. Operating margins expanded, driven by the jewellery segment and CaratLane's performance. However, the company's premium valuation, coupled with increasing competition and a slight dip in its high-margin studded ratio, warrants investor caution. Analysts maintain positive ratings but highlight valuation risks amidst sector growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:36:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698bdd070c9da38e2e75efb9_1770774119031.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paramount Bid Sputters as WBD Leans Toward Netflix Amid Regulatory Storm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Paramount-Bid-Sputters-as-WBD-Leans-Toward-Netflix-Amid-Regulatory-Storm/698bdd050c9da38e2e75efb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Paramount-Bid-Sputters-as-WBD-Leans-Toward-Netflix-Amid-Regulatory-Storm/698bdd050c9da38e2e75efb2</guid><description>Paramount Global has again sweetened its hostile takeover bid for Warner Bros. Discovery (WBD), introducing a quarterly "ticking fee" and agreeing to cover WBD's $2.8 billion termination payout to Netflix. Despite these concessions, shareholder support has drastically declined, with tendered shares falling from over 168 million to just over 42 million. WBD's board remains committed to its preferred $82.7 billion merger with Netflix, leaving Paramount facing significant hurdles, including intensifying global antitrust reviews that scrutinize both potential transactions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs Bets Big: India Pivot Aims to Overtake Rivals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Goldman-Sachs-Bets-Big-India-Pivot-Aims-to-Overtake-Rivals/698bdb230c9da38e2e75edff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Goldman-Sachs-Bets-Big-India-Pivot-Aims-to-Overtake-Rivals/698bdb230c9da38e2e75edff</guid><description>Goldman Sachs has injected $500 million into its India operations over three years, abandoning a 'future growth story' approach for a current growth engine strategy. This pivot has improved its deal-making rankings, but faces stiff competition from global giants like JPMorgan and local powerhouses like Kotak Mahindra. The firm is building scale across multiple financial services, accepting narrower margins to gain a foothold in India's rapidly expanding capital markets. This move reflects a broader trend of global banks increasing their focus on India's robust economic growth and dynamic financial sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Fear Triggers Wealth Management Sell-Off: Overreaction?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Fear-Triggers-Wealth-Management-Sell-Off-Overreaction/698bd7dc0c9da38e2e75ec39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Fear-Triggers-Wealth-Management-Sell-Off-Overreaction/698bd7dc0c9da38e2e75ec39</guid><description>A new AI tool from Altruist Corp. sparked a significant sell-off across wealth management stocks on February 10, 2026. Raymond James Financial Inc. dropped 8.8%, Charles Schwab Corp. fell 7.4%, and LPL Financial Holdings Inc. declined 8.3%. This reaction mirrors prior AI-induced market jitters in other sectors, raising questions about whether the market is overestimating the immediate threat of automation and underestimating the enduring value of human advisory services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Polaris Smart Metering Bets Big on India's Energy Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Polaris-Smart-Metering-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Energy-Overhaul/698bd65a0c9da38e2e75e89f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Polaris-Smart-Metering-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Energy-Overhaul/698bd65a0c9da38e2e75e89f</guid><description>Polaris Smart Metering is injecting Rs 4,500 crore by 2027 to significantly expand its smart meter manufacturing capacity to 10 million units annually and enter the battery energy storage business. Backed by I Squared Capital, the company is also exploring an Initial Public Offering (IPO) to fuel its growth ambitions. This strategic move aims to capture a larger share of India's burgeoning smart metering market, driven by government schemes, while diversifying into the critical energy storage sector. The company targets doubling its current 10% market share within five years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:07:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698bd65a0c9da38e2e75e89e_1770772307026.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BHEL Stake Sale, Titan, Britannia Q3 Surge: Stocks to Watch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/BHEL-Stake-Sale-Titan-Britannia-Q3-Surge-Stocks-to-Watch/698bd5fd0c9da38e2e75e891</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/BHEL-Stake-Sale-Titan-Britannia-Q3-Surge-Stocks-to-Watch/698bd5fd0c9da38e2e75e891</guid><description>Indian markets are poised for a higher open as GIFT Nifty signals gains. Investors eye Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) as the government plans to divest a 5% stake, potentially raising over ₹4,400 crore. Meanwhile, strong third-quarter earnings are boosting sentiment, with Titan Company reporting a 61% profit jump and Britannia Industries seeing a 17% net profit rise. Eicher Motors and Grasim Industries also posted solid results. Telecom stocks are in focus as Bharti Airtel surpasses Reliance Jio in net subscriber additions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:06:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: DPI Powerhouse Meets Compute Divide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-DPI-Powerhouse-Meets-Compute-Divide/698bd5840c9da38e2e75e86b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-DPI-Powerhouse-Meets-Compute-Divide/698bd5840c9da38e2e75e86b</guid><description>India's AI development path, distinct through its public-led Digital Public Infrastructure (DPI) playbook, faces critical headwinds. While initiatives like common GPU access, sovereign LLMs (Sarvam AI), and vernacular language integration aim for broad inclusion, the nation grapples with a stark global 'Compute North vs. South' divide. The immense energy demands of AI data centers further strain India's power grid, posing significant scalability and geopolitical risks that could temper its innovation ecosystem's momentum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nifty Nears 26K: Auto Strength Meets Retail Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nifty-Nears-26K-Auto-Strength-Meets-Retail-Valuations/698bd4090c9da38e2e75e6e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nifty-Nears-26K-Auto-Strength-Meets-Retail-Valuations/698bd4090c9da38e2e75e6e9</guid><description>The Nifty 50 approaches the significant 26,000 mark, driven by corporate earnings and positive sectorial trends. Eicher Motors demonstrates robust performance, buoyed by strong automotive retail sales and expansion plans. Conversely, Titan Company faces higher valuation scrutiny despite positive revenue outlooks. Investors weigh the index rally against component-specific opportunities and challenges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JM Financial's 10 Growth Picks: Value or Volatility?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/JM-Financials-10-Growth-Picks-Value-or-Volatility/698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e37d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/JM-Financials-10-Growth-Picks-Value-or-Volatility/698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e37d</guid><description>JM Financial has spotlighted ten Indian companies poised for significant returns through fiscal years 2026-2028, citing robust earnings visibility, balance sheet health, and expansion plans. These selections span diverse sectors from retail to manufacturing. While the brokerage anticipates substantial upside, a deeper look reveals elevated valuations and potential execution hurdles for several names, particularly those undertaking aggressive capacity expansions. Competitor analysis shows many of these firms trade at a premium, suggesting growth is already priced in.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:48:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e37c_1770771241019.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Solar Push: GIPCL vs. Orient Green Power</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Solar-Push-GIPCL-vs-Orient-Green-Power/698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e375</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Solar-Push-GIPCL-vs-Orient-Green-Power/698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e375</guid><description>India's 2026 budget prioritizes clean energy, creating investment opportunities in renewables. Two small-caps, GIPCL and Orient Green Power, offer distinct plays. GIPCL, a state-backed utility, is pivoting from thermal to solar with significant projects, offering a defensive infrastructure play. Orient Green Power is a speculative turnaround, aggressively cleaning debt for solar expansion but facing promoter risk. Investors must choose between stability and high-risk/high-reward.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:48:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e374_1770771233204.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>