<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:45 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Dilip Buildcon Wins Gujarat Project Amidst Operational Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dilip-Buildcon-Wins-Gujarat-Project-Amidst-Operational-Headwinds/699460fdcffb93b3e9282d7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dilip-Buildcon-Wins-Gujarat-Project-Amidst-Operational-Headwinds/699460fdcffb93b3e9282d7d</guid><description>Dilip Buildcon has secured the lowest bid for a ₹668.02 crore flood protection embankment project in Gujarat, adding to its record order book of approximately ₹29,372 crore. While new order wins are positive, the company's recent financial results highlight operational pressures and reliance on exceptional gains for profit growth. Analysts maintain a neutral stance, pointing to concerns about revenue projections and core operating performance despite sector tailwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:37:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699460fdcffb93b3e9282d7c_1771332035911.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Long-Term Vision Sparks Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Long-Term-Vision-Sparks-Mixed-Market-Signals/699460f8cffb93b3e9282d65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Long-Term-Vision-Sparks-Mixed-Market-Signals/699460f8cffb93b3e9282d65</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 prioritizes long-term structural growth through increased capital expenditure and manufacturing incentives, eschewing short-term stimulus. While this strategy aims to bolster India's economic resilience against global uncertainties, it has led to a mixed market response. Initial declines due to derivative tax hikes were tempered by optimism over infrastructure spending, though concerns linger about immediate demand drivers and fiscal prudence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:37:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699460f8cffb93b3e9282d64.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hexaware Bets on AI Dev Speed, Faces Profit Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexaware-Bets-on-AI-Dev-Speed-Faces-Profit-Squeeze/699460f1cffb93b3e9282d4e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexaware-Bets-on-AI-Dev-Speed-Faces-Profit-Squeeze/699460f1cffb93b3e9282d4e</guid><description>Hexaware Technologies has unveiled an open version of its agentic AI platform, RapidX®, featuring native integration with Replit. The move aims to accelerate enterprise software engineering by enabling natural language-to-code conversion and empowering non-technical staff. Despite its strategic push into AI-native development and the establishment of a dedicated Centre of Excellence in Chennai, the company faces notable headwinds from declining quarterly profits and increasing operational expenses. The integration promises faster prototyping and scaled deployments, but the long-term success hinges on managing AI-driven code governance and demonstrating tangible ROI.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:37:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699460f1cffb93b3e9282d4d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Heat Crisis: Financial Sector Faces Material Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Heat-Crisis-Financial-Sector-Faces-Material-Risk/699460dacffb93b3e9282ce6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Heat-Crisis-Financial-Sector-Faces-Material-Risk/699460dacffb93b3e9282ce6</guid><description>India's economy confronts a significant threat from escalating urban heat, projected to cause substantial GDP losses and job reductions. Financial institutions are now integrating heat as a material financial risk, prompting portfolio reviews and a push for climate resilience investments. These proactive measures offer considerable returns against escalating climate-induced losses, although regulatory shifts and implementation challenges present systemic risks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:36:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699460dacffb93b3e9282ce5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai Luxury Flat Outperforms Stocks: A Tale of Scarcity, Not Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mumbai-Luxury-Flat-Outperforms-Stocks-A-Tale-of-Scarcity-Not-Strategy/6994607acffb93b3e9282c43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mumbai-Luxury-Flat-Outperforms-Stocks-A-Tale-of-Scarcity-Not-Strategy/6994607acffb93b3e9282c43</guid><description>A luxury apartment in Mumbai's Samudra Mahal complex has allegedly delivered a 19% CAGR over 40 years, purportedly outperforming Indian stock markets which averaged 17.5% CAGR over 30 years. Motilal Oswal Financial Services Chairman Raamdeo Agrawal cited the property's appreciation from ₹125 to ₹1.25 lakh per square foot. Agrawal's family acquired a duplex in the building for ₹46.29 crore in 2021. However, this exceptional performance is attributed to the hyper-prime location and scarcity, rather than a broad real estate market trend that universally beats equities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:35:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994607acffb93b3e9282c42_1771331860622.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RPP Infra Projects Under ROC Scanner for Data Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RPP-Infra-Projects-Under-ROC-Scanner-for-Data-Probe/69946078cffb93b3e9282c2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RPP-Infra-Projects-Under-ROC-Scanner-for-Data-Probe/69946078cffb93b3e9282c2c</guid><description>RPP Infra Projects Limited has received a formal notice from the Registrar of Companies (ROC) to provide data and documents for examination. This investigation by the ROC, a key regulatory body for corporate compliance in India, casts a shadow over the company's operations and investor confidence. Investors are watching closely for further developments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:35:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69946078cffb93b3e9282c2b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India, Lufthansa Forge EU-India Travel Pact Amid Trade Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Lufthansa-Forge-EU-India-Travel-Pact-Amid-Trade-Boom/6994600bcffb93b3e9282b43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Lufthansa-Forge-EU-India-Travel-Pact-Amid-Trade-Boom/6994600bcffb93b3e9282b43</guid><description>Air India and the Lufthansa Group have formalized a significant memorandum of understanding to establish a joint business agreement, aiming to boost connectivity between India and Europe. This strategic alliance leverages the recent EU-India Free Trade Agreement, which includes the elimination of tariffs on aircraft and parts, and enhances offerings for passengers across key routes. The pact signifies a deeper integration within the Star Alliance, positioning both carriers to capture growth in the high-potential India-Europe travel market while intensifying competition with other global players.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:33:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994600bcffb93b3e9282b42.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mobavenue AI Tech Soars 67% Revenue as AI Platforms Drive Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mobavenue-AI-Tech-Soars-67percent-Revenue-as-AI-Platforms-Drive-Growth/69945f89cffb93b3e9282a9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mobavenue-AI-Tech-Soars-67percent-Revenue-as-AI-Platforms-Drive-Growth/69945f89cffb93b3e9282a9c</guid><description>Mobavenue AI Tech reported a strong Q3 FY26, with revenue surging 67.2% year-over-year to ₹55.12 crore. EBITDA and PAT also doubled, driven by AI-powered platforms and growth in premium inventory like CTV. The company outlined plans for continued growth, focusing on global expansion and AI-driven automation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945f89cffb93b3e9282a9b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Corporates Unleash Dividend Spree; Focus Shifts to Payout Impact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Corporates-Unleash-Dividend-Spree-Focus-Shifts-to-Payout-Impact/69945f28cffb93b3e9282a10</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Corporates-Unleash-Dividend-Spree-Focus-Shifts-to-Payout-Impact/69945f28cffb93b3e9282a10</guid><description>A wave of Indian corporations, spanning sectors from mining and defence to pharmaceuticals and energy, are distributing significant interim dividends. Companies like Coal India, Hindustan Aeronautics, ONGC, and Torrent Pharmaceuticals are rewarding shareholders following strong financial results. This proactive shareholder return strategy highlights robust profitability, yet market participants are evaluating the balance between dividend payouts and strategic reinvestment for future growth amid evolving sector dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:29:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945f28cffb93b3e9282a0f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Baazar Style Retail Gets ₹331 Cr Boost from Cupid for Store Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Baazar-Style-Retail-Gets-331-Cr-Boost-from-Cupid-for-Store-Expansion/69945e98cffb93b3e9282963</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Baazar-Style-Retail-Gets-331-Cr-Boost-from-Cupid-for-Store-Expansion/69945e98cffb93b3e9282963</guid><description>Baazar Style Retail Limited secured a significant INR 331.53 crore investment from Cupid Limited via warrants. This strategic funding will fuel aggressive store expansion to over 500 outlets and help reduce debt. The company reported a robust 38% YoY revenue growth for 9M FY26, driven by increased store count and a higher private label contribution, signalling a strong growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:27:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945e98cffb93b3e9282962.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Grid Corp Lands Kenyan Grid Project Amidst Adani Deal Fallout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Corp-Lands-Kenyan-Grid-Project-Amidst-Adani-Deal-Fallout/69945daecffb93b3e928285d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Corp-Lands-Kenyan-Grid-Project-Amidst-Adani-Deal-Fallout/69945daecffb93b3e928285d</guid><description>Power Grid Corporation of India (PGCIL), in a joint venture with Africa50, has secured a $311 million public-private partnership (PPP) contract to expand and modernize Kenya's electricity transmission network. The project involves designing, constructing, operating, and maintaining critical high-voltage transmission lines to enhance power reliability across western and northern Kenya. This development follows Kenya's earlier cancellation of significant infrastructure deals with India's Adani Group, signaling a shift in how the nation approaches large-scale development projects and highlighting opportunities for experienced Indian state-owned enterprises.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:23:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945daecffb93b3e928285c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CMS Info Systems Votes on Board Changes, CEO Pay, ₹250 Cr Borrowing Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/CMS-Info-Systems-Votes-on-Board-Changes-CEO-Pay-250-Cr-Borrowing-Hike/69945da8cffb93b3e9282836</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/CMS-Info-Systems-Votes-on-Board-Changes-CEO-Pay-250-Cr-Borrowing-Hike/69945da8cffb93b3e9282836</guid><description>CMS Info Systems has initiated a postal ballot for shareholders to vote on crucial resolutions. These include appointing new directors, approving the remuneration for MD &amp; CEO Dr. Hardik Joshipura, and significantly increasing the company's borrowing limit to ₹250 Crore. The company's recent Q3 FY26 results showed a sharp 38.41% year-on-year decline in net profit, despite modest revenue growth, primarily due to rising operational costs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:23:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945da8cffb93b3e9282835.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NTPC Credit Rating Afﬁrmed 'AAA' By India Ratings, Stable Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Credit-Rating-Afﬁrmed-AAA-By-India-Ratings-Stable-Outlook/69945cbccffb93b3e928273c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Credit-Rating-Afﬁrmed-AAA-By-India-Ratings-Stable-Outlook/69945cbccffb93b3e928273c</guid><description>India Ratings has affirmed NTPC's 'IND AAA' credit rating with a 'Stable' outlook, signaling strong financial health. The rating covers various debt instruments including proposed and outstanding non-convertible debentures and bank loan facilities, reflecting the company's robust financial standing and stability in the Indian power sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:19:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945cbccffb93b3e928273b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fredun Pharma Surges on Q3 Results, But SEBI Scrutiny Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Fredun-Pharma-Surges-on-Q3-Results-But-SEBI-Scrutiny-Looms/69945cb7cffb93b3e9282716</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Fredun-Pharma-Surges-on-Q3-Results-But-SEBI-Scrutiny-Looms/69945cb7cffb93b3e9282716</guid><description>Fredun Pharmaceuticals has reported a robust Q3 FY26 with a 57% year-on-year revenue jump and a 99% surge in EBITDA, thanks to its expanding new-age business segments like pet care and mobility. The company also highlighted a significant reduction in trade receivables. However, a recent SEBI Adjudication Order flagged past compliance and corporate governance lapses, although no monetary penalty was imposed. Management remains confident about future growth, targeting higher contributions from new segments and a shift towards an asset-light manufacturing model.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:19:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945cb7cffb93b3e9282715.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exicom Standalone Soars, But EV Unit Tritium Drains Consolidated Profits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Exicom-Standalone-Soars-But-EV-Unit-Tritium-Drains-Consolidated-Profits/69945bc9cffb93b3e9282637</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Exicom-Standalone-Soars-But-EV-Unit-Tritium-Drains-Consolidated-Profits/69945bc9cffb93b3e9282637</guid><description>Exicom Tele-Systems reported a strong Q3 FY26 for its standalone business, with revenue jumping 58% YoY to ₹233 Crores, driven by Critical Power segment. However, consolidated profits were "pretty much flat" QoQ, primarily due to the ongoing financial stress of its EV charging subsidiary, Tritium. Management is focused on a turnaround for Tritium, targeting EBITDA breakeven by Q4 FY27.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:15:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945bc9cffb93b3e9282636.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ADAG's Regulatory Woes Expose Deep Financial Fault Lines</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/ADAGs-Regulatory-Woes-Expose-Deep-Financial-Fault-Lines/69945ad9cffb93b3e928256b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/ADAGs-Regulatory-Woes-Expose-Deep-Financial-Fault-Lines/69945ad9cffb93b3e928256b</guid><description>Tina Ambani has again failed to appear before the Enforcement Directorate (ED) in a money laundering probe, signaling continued regulatory pressure on the Anil Dhirubhai Ambani Group (ADAG). These escalating legal actions underscore the group's profound financial fragility, marked by substantial debt, historical mismanagement, and a stark contrast to the robust performance of industry peers. While the broader infrastructure and power sectors show growth, ADAG's persistent entanglement in investigations and its weak financial metrics suggest limited prospects for sustainable recovery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:11:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945ad9cffb93b3e928256a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Bets on OpenAI: AI Integration Amidst Valuation Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eternal-Ltd-Bets-on-OpenAI-AI-Integration-Amidst-Valuation-Risks/69945ad8cffb93b3e9282554</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eternal-Ltd-Bets-on-OpenAI-AI-Integration-Amidst-Valuation-Risks/69945ad8cffb93b3e9282554</guid><description>Eternal Ltd is integrating OpenAI's advanced AI capabilities across its consumer and enterprise platforms, including Zomato and Blinkit, and its AI-native venture Nugget. This strategic move aims to enhance customer interactions and internal automation. However, the company faces scrutiny over its extremely high P/E ratio, intense competition from players like Swiggy, and potential execution risks, despite a generally positive analyst consensus.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:11:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945ad8cffb93b3e9282553.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Binny Ltd Profit Plunges 78%, Auditor Flags Major Accounting Red Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Binny-Ltd-Profit-Plunges-78percent-Auditor-Flags-Major-Accounting-Red-Flags/699459e8cffb93b3e9282474</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Binny-Ltd-Profit-Plunges-78percent-Auditor-Flags-Major-Accounting-Red-Flags/699459e8cffb93b3e9282474</guid><description>Binny Limited reported a stark 78.21% year-on-year drop in net profit to ₹4.25 Cr for the quarter ended June 30, 2024. The company's revenue also fell sharply by 62.04%. Adding to investor worries, the auditor issued a 'Qualified Conclusion,' highlighting serious concerns about the recoverability of significant advances, improper accounting for land parcels, and issues with revenue recognition for key agreements. The Company Secretary has also resigned.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:07:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699459e8cffb93b3e9282473.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Verifiable Trust Fuels India's Food Traceability Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Verifiable-Trust-Fuels-Indias-Food-Traceability-Boom/6994588ccffb93b3e9282235</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Verifiable-Trust-Fuels-Indias-Food-Traceability-Boom/6994588ccffb93b3e9282235</guid><description>India's food sector is undergoing a seismic shift towards digital traceability, driven by escalating consumer demand for verifiable safety and origin. This transformation is moving transparency from a mere marketing claim to a critical operational system. Leveraging technologies like QR codes, IoT, and blockchain, companies are de-risking supply chains, enhancing efficiency, and unlocking new market opportunities, including lucrative export markets. The market is projected for substantial growth, indicating a fundamental recalibration of trust and value in the food business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:01:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994588ccffb93b3e9282234_1771329873339.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Labour Codes Trigger Actuarial Shockwaves, IT Margins Squeezed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Labour-Codes-Trigger-Actuarial-Shockwaves-IT-Margins-Squeezed/69945885cffb93b3e928221d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Labour-Codes-Trigger-Actuarial-Shockwaves-IT-Margins-Squeezed/69945885cffb93b3e928221d</guid><description>The recent implementation of India's four new labour codes, effective November 21, 2025, has fundamentally altered corporate compensation structures. A mandate requiring basic pay to constitute at least 50% of total remuneration has triggered significant increases in statutory liabilities, particularly for gratuity. This necessitates immediate accounting recognition of past service costs, leading to P&amp;L impacts and creating pronounced financial pressures for margin-sensitive sectors like IT, potentially moderating salary increments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:01:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945885cffb93b3e928221c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VVIP Infratech Projects ₹750 Cr Sales, Posts ₹36 Cr Profit in FY25</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/VVIP-Infratech-Projects-750-Cr-Sales-Posts-36-Cr-Profit-in-FY25/6994587fcffb93b3e92821f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/VVIP-Infratech-Projects-750-Cr-Sales-Posts-36-Cr-Profit-in-FY25/6994587fcffb93b3e92821f6</guid><description>VVIP Infratech Limited's step-down subsidiary has secured RERA registration for its "VVIP-YAMUNA" housing project in Uttar Pradesh, estimated at ₹750 Crores gross sales value. For the Financial Year 2025, the company reported consolidated revenues of ₹370.66 Crores and a Profit After Tax (PAT) of ₹36.11 Crores, signaling positive future prospects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:01:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994587fcffb93b3e92821f5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHC Foods Seeks Green Light for $27M Fundraise and 5X Borrowing Limit Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/NHC-Foods-Seeks-Green-Light-for-27M-Fundraise-and-5X-Borrowing-Limit-Hike/6994587fcffb93b3e92821e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/NHC-Foods-Seeks-Green-Light-for-27M-Fundraise-and-5X-Borrowing-Limit-Hike/6994587fcffb93b3e92821e3</guid><description>NHC Foods Limited is asking shareholders to approve raising up to USD 27 Million and increasing its borrowing limit from ₹100 Crores to ₹500 Crores. This move aims to fund expansion and strategic opportunities in the global food market. Shareholders can vote via postal ballot from February 18 to March 19, 2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:01:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994587fcffb93b3e92821e2.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Commerce Pilot: Choice of Empowerment or Inequality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Commerce-Pilot-Choice-of-Empowerment-or-Inequality/69945824cffb93b3e9282125</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Commerce-Pilot-Choice-of-Empowerment-or-Inequality/69945824cffb93b3e9282125</guid><description>India is pioneering agentic commerce, where AI agents autonomously handle consumer purchases, leveraging its advanced UPI infrastructure and digitally native Gen Z. This AI-driven retail evolution promises efficiency and personalization but introduces significant governance, data privacy, and market equity risks that policymakers and businesses must address. The initiative represents a pivotal socio-economic choice for the future of digital transactions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:59:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69945824cffb93b3e9282124_1771329716021.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's $1B AI Fund: Execution, Not Just Capital, Will Drive Deep Tech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-1B-AI-Fund-Execution-Not-Just-Capital-Will-Drive-Deep-Tech/6994581ecffb93b3e928210b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-1B-AI-Fund-Execution-Not-Just-Capital-Will-Drive-Deep-Tech/6994581ecffb93b3e928210b</guid><description>The India Deep Tech Alliance (IDTA) has committed $1 billion over three years to Indian AI startups, part of a larger $2.5 billion deep tech investment. This initiative aims to move beyond capital infusion by integrating strategic corporate expertise for scaling and global competitiveness. The move signals a critical juncture for India's AI sector, which saw a 58% funding jump in 2025, now representing 15% of the nation's VC-PE activity. Success hinges on decisive execution to bridge research to commercialization, especially as global AI funding continues its strong upward trajectory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:59:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994581ecffb93b3e928210a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Diamond Power Profit Soars, But Valuation Looms Large</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diamond-Power-Profit-Soars-But-Valuation-Looms-Large/69945793cffb93b3e928207c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diamond-Power-Profit-Soars-But-Valuation-Looms-Large/69945793cffb93b3e928207c</guid><description>Diamond Power Infrastructure posted an eight-fold increase in net profit to ₹50 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by enhanced execution and premium product sales. Revenue climbed 54% to ₹474 crore, supported by a substantial ₹3,300 crore order book. However, the company's market valuation, with a P/E ratio exceeding 126x and a negative book value, raises significant concerns for investors, even as sector tailwinds offer growth potential.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:57:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945793cffb93b3e928207b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Biocon Surges on Merger Completion, Profit Zooms 64%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biocon-Surges-on-Merger-Completion-Profit-Zooms-64percent/6994562ecffb93b3e9281f39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biocon-Surges-on-Merger-Completion-Profit-Zooms-64percent/6994562ecffb93b3e9281f39</guid><description>Biocon Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with operating revenues up 9% year-on-year to INR 4,173 Crores. Net profit soared 64% to INR 226 Crores (before exceptionals), driven by strong performance in Biosimilars and Generics. The company highlighted progress on its merger with Biocon Biologics, focusing on balance sheet strengthening and debt reduction, aiming for sustainable growth. Capex is set to moderate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:51:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994562ecffb93b3e9281f38_1771329232423.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGrid Revenue Up 11.7%, Buys Projects Worth INR 2.9K Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IndiGrid-Revenue-Up-117percent-Buys-Projects-Worth-INR-29K-Cr/69945629cffb93b3e9281f21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IndiGrid-Revenue-Up-117percent-Buys-Projects-Worth-INR-29K-Cr/69945629cffb93b3e9281f21</guid><description>IndiGrid Infrastructure Trust reported a solid Q3FY26 with revenue climbing 11.7% year-on-year to INR 862 Cr and EBITDA rising 13% to INR 784.3 Cr. The trust maintained its Distribution Per Unit (DPU) at INR 4, reaffirming its full-year guidance of INR 16, while strengthening its asset pipeline with acquisitions totalling approximately INR 2,900 Cr, including Gadag Transmission and two under-construction projects via EnerGrid. However, a dip in transmission asset collections to 90% and muted Net Cash Flow from Distribution warrant attention.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945629cffb93b3e9281f20.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KRBL Flags Basmati Volume Recovery Amid Governance Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/KRBL-Flags-Basmati-Volume-Recovery-Amid-Governance-Probe/69945627cffb93b3e9281f0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/KRBL-Flags-Basmati-Volume-Recovery-Amid-Governance-Probe/69945627cffb93b3e9281f0b</guid><description>Rice exporter KRBL's Q3 FY26 investor call discussion pointed to a strong recovery in Basmati rice sales volumes in key export markets and improved pricing power, alongside a reiterated FY26 revenue target of INR 1,500 crore. The company also noted reduced US tariffs and plans for new products. However, this positive outlook comes against a backdrop of significant past corporate governance concerns, including an ongoing Enforcement Directorate (ED) investigation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:51:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945627cffb93b3e9281f0a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Glycols Hits Record Revenue, Slashes Debt Amid Segment Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Glycols-Hits-Record-Revenue-Slashes-Debt-Amid-Segment-Concerns/69945448cffb93b3e9281d8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Glycols-Hits-Record-Revenue-Slashes-Debt-Amid-Segment-Concerns/69945448cffb93b3e9281d8f</guid><description>India Glycols Limited (IGL) announced record revenue and EBITDA for Q3 FY26, driven by strong performance in its Potable Spirits and Chemicals segments. The company also made significant strides in debt reduction, prepaying INR 582 Cr. However, challenges persist in its Joint Venture margins and Ennature Biopharma segment due to feedstock costs and market volatility. The credit rating is currently under watch due to an ongoing demerger.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:43:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69945448cffb93b3e9281d8e_1771328717973.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prince Pipes Posts Q3 Loss on Inventory Costs, Eyes Q4 Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Prince-Pipes-Posts-Q3-Loss-on-Inventory-Costs-Eyes-Q4-Recovery/69945447cffb93b3e9281d79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Prince-Pipes-Posts-Q3-Loss-on-Inventory-Costs-Eyes-Q4-Recovery/69945447cffb93b3e9281d79</guid><description>Prince Pipes and Fittings reported a net loss of ₹2 crore in Q3 FY26, heavily impacted by an ₹18-20 crore inventory loss. Despite this, the company achieved a 3% YoY volume growth for the quarter and posted a ₹17 crore PAT for the first nine months of FY26. Management remains optimistic for Q4 FY26 and targets double-digit volume growth in FY27, driven by capacity expansion and product innovation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:43:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69945447cffb93b3e9281d78_1771328733025.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bazel International Approves 1:1 Bonus Shares for Shareholders</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bazel-International-Approves-11-Bonus-Shares-for-Shareholders/699453d1cffb93b3e9281cb9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bazel-International-Approves-11-Bonus-Shares-for-Shareholders/699453d1cffb93b3e9281cb9</guid><description>Bazel International Limited's Board of Directors will meet on February 20, 2026, to approve a 1:1 bonus equity share issuance. Shareholders will receive one new share for each held, with a record date of February 19, 2026. This move aims to reward investors and enhance market liquidity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:41:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699453d1cffb93b3e9281cb8_1771328594368.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pesticides Sees 31% Revenue Jump, Eyes ₹3000 Cr Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Pesticides-Sees-31percent-Revenue-Jump-Eyes-3000-Cr-Target/699453cecffb93b3e9281ca1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Pesticides-Sees-31percent-Revenue-Jump-Eyes-3000-Cr-Target/699453cecffb93b3e9281ca1</guid><description>India Pesticides Limited posted a strong Q3 FY26 with revenue up 31% year-on-year to ₹229 crore, driven by robust domestic and export sales. EBITDA rose nearly 40%, and net profit jumped 41%. The company highlighted progress in capacity expansions, including the Shalvis facility, and reaffirmed its ambitious long-term vision to reach ₹3,000 crore in revenue by FY31, targeting steady EBITDA margins of 18-20%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:41:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699453cecffb93b3e9281ca0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shringar Mangalsutra Profit Jumps 134% on Strong Sales, Expansion Plans</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shringar-Mangalsutra-Profit-Jumps-134percent-on-Strong-Sales-Expansion-Plans/6994531dcffb93b3e9281b98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shringar-Mangalsutra-Profit-Jumps-134percent-on-Strong-Sales-Expansion-Plans/6994531dcffb93b3e9281b98</guid><description>Shringar House of Mangalsutra Limited reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with net profit soaring 134.2% year-on-year to ₹30.1 crore. This impressive growth was driven by a 68.4% surge in revenue to ₹658.9 crore, supported by a significant increase in gross profit margins. The company is aggressively expanding its manufacturing capacity and geographic reach, aiming for sustained growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:38:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994531dcffb93b3e9281b97.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tax Crackdown: Families Face Heat, Small Taxpayers Get Amnesty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Crackdown-Families-Face-Heat-Small-Taxpayers-Get-Amnesty/699452efcffb93b3e9281b4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Crackdown-Families-Face-Heat-Small-Taxpayers-Get-Amnesty/699452efcffb93b3e9281b4f</guid><description>The Indian Income Tax Department is launching a concerted effort to uncover undisclosed foreign assets held by major business families across key cities, leveraging international data exchange frameworks like AEOI and CRS. Concurrently, a special disclosure scheme introduced in Union Budget 2026 offers a leniency window for small taxpayers with undeclared foreign holdings. This dual approach signals a calibrated strategy to enhance tax compliance, targeting substantial undeclared wealth from the affluent while providing an avenue for minor disclosures from the less affluent, albeit excluding business families from the amnesty. Penalties for non-compliance remain severe, including substantial taxes and potential prosecution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:37:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699452efcffb93b3e9281b4e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GCC Boom: From Cost Hub to Innovation Powerhouse</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-GCC-Boom-From-Cost-Hub-to-Innovation-Powerhouse/6994527ccffb93b3e9281ac2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-GCC-Boom-From-Cost-Hub-to-Innovation-Powerhouse/6994527ccffb93b3e9281ac2</guid><description>Global Capability Centers (GCCs) are fueling unprecedented office leasing in India, surpassing 31 million sq ft in 2025 and pushing the total footprint towards 350 million sq ft. This expansion reflects India's evolution into a strategic hub for innovation and R&amp;D, moving beyond cost arbitrage. While metros like Bengaluru and Hyderabad lead with specialized offerings, Tier II cities are rapidly emerging as crucial growth frontiers, attracting investment with cost savings and talent access. This dynamic real estate shift underscores India's indispensable role in global corporate strategies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:35:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994527ccffb93b3e9281ac1_1771328283697.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shanti Gold Soars 110% Revenue; Eyes Major Expansion &amp; Export Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shanti-Gold-Soars-110percent-Revenue-Eyes-Major-Expansion-and-Export-Growth/69945267cffb93b3e9281aa7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shanti-Gold-Soars-110percent-Revenue-Eyes-Major-Expansion-and-Export-Growth/69945267cffb93b3e9281aa7</guid><description>Shanti Gold International posted a stellar Q3 FY26 with revenue surging 110% year-on-year to ₹637 Cr. Profits also more than doubled. The company is embarking on significant capacity expansions, targeting 7,900 kg annual capacity by May 2026, entering the Mangalsutra segment, and aiming to boost exports to 10%. Management is optimistic about sustained growth driven by industry formalization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:35:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69945267cffb93b3e9281aa6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eros Innovation Launches 'Large Cultural Model' AI Amidst Financial Distress</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eros-Innovation-Launches-Large-Cultural-Model-AI-Amidst-Financial-Distress/6994511bcffb93b3e92818a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eros-Innovation-Launches-Large-Cultural-Model-AI-Amidst-Financial-Distress/6994511bcffb93b3e92818a6</guid><description>Eros Innovation has launched Eros Universe, an AI-powered creator economy application leveraging its novel Large Cultural Models (LCMs), designed to embed cultural context into AI for Indian storytelling. This initiative, supported by a $5 million acceleration program, aims to foster India's AI ambitions and creator economy. However, the launch is overshadowed by Eros Media World PLC's critical financial state, marked by an extremely low market capitalization and near-zero stock valuation, raising significant questions about the project's viability and execution capabilities in a competitive global AI market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:29:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994511bcffb93b3e92818a5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>$53 Billion Unlock: High-Percentage Expiries Pose Valuation Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/53-Billion-Unlock-High-Percentage-Expiries-Pose-Valuation-Risk/69945100cffb93b3e928188a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/53-Billion-Unlock-High-Percentage-Expiries-Pose-Valuation-Risk/69945100cffb93b3e928188a</guid><description>A significant inflow of $53 billion (approx. ₹53,000 crore) in pre-listing shareholder holdings is set to become tradable between February 18 and March 30, 2026, according to Nuvama Alternative &amp; Quantitative Research. This concentrated release of shares, with several companies facing over 50% of their equity exiting lock-in, introduces substantial liquidity risk and potential valuation recalibrations for affected entities and the broader IPO market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:29:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69945100cffb93b3e9281889_1771327912471.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Data Centers: Grid Strain Threatens Digital Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Data-Centers-Grid-Strain-Threatens-Digital-Growth/699450ffcffb93b3e9281873</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Data-Centers-Grid-Strain-Threatens-Digital-Growth/699450ffcffb93b3e9281873</guid><description>India's data center industry is on an exponential growth trajectory, fueled by hyperscaler investments. However, this expansion is increasingly constrained by power delivery challenges. While renewable energy adoption is growing, the primary bottleneck is the inadequate transmission and distribution (T&amp;D) infrastructure, especially in major metropolitan areas where over 90% of facilities are concentrated. This geographic over-reliance on a few hubs is straining the national grid, creating a risk of power deficits and operational disruptions, demanding a strategic shift towards decentralization despite existing infrastructure gaps.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:29:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699450ffcffb93b3e9281872.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Partnership Sparks IT Rally Amidst Sectoral Anxiety</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AI-Partnership-Sparks-IT-Rally-Amidst-Sectoral-Anxiety/6994509ccffb93b3e928179a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AI-Partnership-Sparks-IT-Rally-Amidst-Sectoral-Anxiety/6994509ccffb93b3e928179a</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks edged higher on February 17, 2026, primarily powered by a significant rebound in IT stocks and sustained strength in PSU banks. This rally, led by Infosys's strategic AI partnership with Anthropic, contrasts sharply with prior sector-wide declines driven by artificial intelligence disruption fears. While IT gains offered a much-needed boost, broader market sentiment remained cautious, underscored by mixed sectoral performance and ongoing concerns about AI's long-term impact on technology services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:27:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994509ccffb93b3e9281799_1771327791830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>