<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:20:48 +0000</pubDate><item><title>MPS Infotecnics Plunges into Losses, Faces Imminent Delisting as Auditors Raise Alarms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MPS-Infotecnics-Plunges-into-Losses-Faces-Imminent-Delisting-as-Auditors-Raise-Alarms/698755d4b81b2b81dcfcb3bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MPS-Infotecnics-Plunges-into-Losses-Faces-Imminent-Delisting-as-Auditors-Raise-Alarms/698755d4b81b2b81dcfcb3bd</guid><description>MPS Infotecnics' Q3 FY26 results show widening losses and minimal revenue. Auditors issued a qualified conclusion citing significant asset impairment concerns, disputed bank balances, and uncertain loans. Both NSE and BSE have initiated delisting proceedings due to severe non-compliance and outstanding dues, with strict deadlines to avert delisting. The outlook is extremely bleak.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698755d4b81b2b81dcfcb3bc_1770477122506.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Spirits Industry Faces Imports Amid Tariff Cuts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Spirits-Industry-Faces-Imports-Amid-Tariff-Cuts/6987555cb81b2b81dcfcb295</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Spirits-Industry-Faces-Imports-Amid-Tariff-Cuts/6987555cb81b2b81dcfcb295</guid><description>Confederation of Indian Alcoholic Beverage Companies (CIABC) is urging the Indian government to ensure a level playing field as new trade agreements with the US, EU, and UK lead to significant import duty reductions on alcoholic beverages. While welcoming phased reductions, CIABC highlights that high domestic operational costs, complex licensing regimes, and state-level tax disparities already place Indian manufacturers at a disadvantage, raising concerns that these structural issues will be amplified by increased foreign competition. Major players like Sula Vineyards and Radico Khaitan face a complex market environment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:08:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987555cb81b2b81dcfcb294_1770476988311.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SNL Bearings Revenue Up 14%, But Profits Sink Amid Margin Compression</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SNL-Bearings-Revenue-Up-14percent-But-Profits-Sink-Amid-Margin-Compression/6987537cb81b2b81dcfcb0b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SNL-Bearings-Revenue-Up-14percent-But-Profits-Sink-Amid-Margin-Compression/6987537cb81b2b81dcfcb0b7</guid><description>SNL Bearings Limited has reported its Q3 FY26 results, with revenue from operations climbing 14.26% year-on-year to ₹1,426 Lakhs. However, this top-line growth was overshadowed by a 8.93% decline in Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹265 Lakhs and a significant compression in PAT margins from 23.32% to 18.58%. On a nine-month basis, revenue grew 10.75%, but PAT saw a modest 3.47% rise. The company also approved an ₹8 Crore capacity enhancement plan financed by internal accruals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987537cb81b2b81dcfcb0b6_1770476499971.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KDJ Holidayscapes Faces Auditor's Disclaimer Amid IBC Proceedings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/KDJ-Holidayscapes-Faces-Auditors-Disclaimer-Amid-IBC-Proceedings/6987521ab81b2b81dcfcaeb0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/KDJ-Holidayscapes-Faces-Auditors-Disclaimer-Amid-IBC-Proceedings/6987521ab81b2b81dcfcaeb0</guid><description>KDJ Holidayscapes &amp; Resorts has refiled its financial results for Q3 FY25 due to a typo. However, auditors have issued a disclaimer of conclusion on the standalone and consolidated statements, citing inability to obtain sufficient audit evidence amid ongoing Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code proceedings. Consolidated revenue plunged 66.6% YoY to ₹7.88 Cr, though net loss narrowed to ₹(7.88) Cr. The company's future hinges on the IBC resolution plan's execution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:54:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987521ab81b2b81dcfcaeaf_1770476402258.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Pact Faces Geopolitical Test Amid Russian Oil Mandate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Faces-Geopolitical-Test-Amid-Russian-Oil-Mandate/69874fbdb81b2b81dcfcab8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Faces-Geopolitical-Test-Amid-Russian-Oil-Mandate/69874fbdb81b2b81dcfcab8e</guid><description>The United States and India have finalized a trade agreement framework, reducing tariffs on Indian goods to 18% and committing India to substantial US product purchases. However, a critical condition requiring India to cease Russian oil imports introduces significant geopolitical friction and economic challenges, testing the nation's commitment to strategic autonomy. While India has not confirmed an outright ban, the move highlights the US leveraging trade policy to influence India's foreign energy sourcing and geopolitical alignments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:44:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874fbdb81b2b81dcfcab8d_1770476088936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KSH International Posts 58% Revenue Surge in Q3, But Profits Slip; Expands Capacity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Posts-58percent-Revenue-Surge-in-Q3-But-Profits-Slip-Expands-Capacity/69874ee3b81b2b81dcfca953</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Posts-58percent-Revenue-Surge-in-Q3-But-Profits-Slip-Expands-Capacity/69874ee3b81b2b81dcfca953</guid><description>KSH International reported a robust 58.52% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹8,177.69 Mn in Q3 FY2026, fueled by volume increases and a favorable product mix. Despite the top-line performance, Profit After Tax (PAT) declined 9.33% YoY to ₹233.26 Mn, impacted by non-recurring and exceptional items, along with higher finance costs. The company bolstered its operational capacity by adding 2,400 MTPA of specialized winding wire capacity and significantly reduced debt by repaying ₹226 Crore.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:40:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69874ee3b81b2b81dcfca952.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KSH International Posts Record Q3 Revenue, Eyes Growth Fueled by New Capacity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-Eyes-Growth-Fueled-by-New-Capacity/69874ecbb81b2b81dcfca8ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-Eyes-Growth-Fueled-by-New-Capacity/69874ecbb81b2b81dcfca8ec</guid><description>KSH International Limited achieved record-breaking Q3 FY2026 results, with revenue soaring 58.5% YoY to ₹8,177.7 million and EBITDA climbing 22.8% to ₹493.7 million. Sales volumes increased 23.6% YoY. The company significantly reduced debt by ₹2,259.77 million, bringing its debt-to-equity ratio to 0.42x. Management anticipates sustained growth driven by structural demand in renewables, data centers, EVs, and railways, supported by new operational capacity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:40:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69874ecbb81b2b81dcfca8eb.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tax Overhaul: Simplification Fuels Digital Push, Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Overhaul-Simplification-Fuels-Digital-Push-Risks-Loom/69874d68b81b2b81dcfca688</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Overhaul-Simplification-Fuels-Digital-Push-Risks-Loom/69874d68b81b2b81dcfca688</guid><description>India is poised to enact a sweeping overhaul of its Income Tax Act and rules, effective April 1, 2026. The Central Board of Direct Taxes (CBDT) proposes to slash the number of rules by nearly 35% and forms by over half, simplifying compliance for taxpayers. This significant recalibration emphasizes technological integration and streamlined processes, aiming to create a more efficient and intuitive tax administration. However, the transition introduces new digital dependencies and potential implementation risks that warrant scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874d68b81b2b81dcfca687_1770475567923.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Leverages Data, AI for Indian Capital Market Stability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Leverages-Data-AI-for-Indian-Capital-Market-Stability/69874cecb81b2b81dcfca52d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Leverages-Data-AI-for-Indian-Capital-Market-Stability/69874cecb81b2b81dcfca52d</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey has underscored the indispensable role of data infrastructure, cybersecurity, and standardized reporting in fortifying India's rapidly growing capital markets. The regulator is actively transforming oversight mechanisms, shifting towards a proactive, data-driven approach that leverages artificial intelligence and advanced analytics to preemptively manage risks and ensure market integrity. Initiatives like XBRL filings and Unified Distilled File Formats (UDiFF) are streamlining operations and enhancing transparency for intermediaries and investors alike.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:32:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874cecb81b2b81dcfca52c_1770475403479.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Suraj Industries Buys VRV Foods, Expands Liquor Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Suraj-Industries-Buys-VRV-Foods-Expands-Liquor-Business/69874bf8b81b2b81dcfca30e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Suraj-Industries-Buys-VRV-Foods-Expands-Liquor-Business/69874bf8b81b2b81dcfca30e</guid><description>Suraj Industries Limited announced its Board's approval to acquire 56.25 lakh equity shares of VRV Foods Limited for Rs. 37.13 crore, making VRV Foods a subsidiary. VRV Foods, with a 32% market share in Himachal Pradesh's country liquor segment, reported FY25 turnover of Rs. 122.90 crore and PAT of Rs. 3.16 crore. The acquisition aims to bolster Suraj Industries' liquor operations. Several other corporate actions, including a land lease agreement and revised inter-corporate loan limits, were also approved, pending shareholder nod.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:28:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69874bf8b81b2b81dcfca30d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Suraj Industries Buys VRV Foods for ₹37 Cr, Bolsters Liquor Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Suraj-Industries-Buys-VRV-Foods-for-37-Cr-Bolsters-Liquor-Business/69874b88b81b2b81dcfca1b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Suraj-Industries-Buys-VRV-Foods-for-37-Cr-Bolsters-Liquor-Business/69874b88b81b2b81dcfca1b8</guid><description>Suraj Industries is acquiring VRV Foods for ₹37.13 Crore, a move that will make the Himachal Pradesh-based country liquor manufacturer a subsidiary. VRV Foods holds an estimated 32% market share in its segment and reported a turnover of ₹122.90 Crore in FY25. This acquisition significantly enhances Suraj Industries' scale and profitability in the liquor business. The Board also approved a 15-year rent agreement with subsidiary Carya Chemicals and Fertilizers and increased inter-corporate finance limits to ₹500 Crore. Shareholder approval is required for the VRV Foods acquisition and alterations to the rights issue object.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:26:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874b88b81b2b81dcfca1b7_1770475263724.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Medi Assist Healthcare Posts 24% Revenue Growth, Becomes Debt-Free</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Medi-Assist-Healthcare-Posts-24percent-Revenue-Growth-Becomes-Debt-Free/6987492cb81b2b81dcfc9e82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Medi-Assist-Healthcare-Posts-24percent-Revenue-Growth-Becomes-Debt-Free/6987492cb81b2b81dcfc9e82</guid><description>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Limited posted robust Q3 FY26 results, achieving 24.0% YoY operating revenue growth for the nine-month period. Margins improved by 154 bps QoQ overall, with a significant 557 bps QoQ jump in the Paramount TPA segment. The company holds INR 200.1 Cr in free cash and is set to become debt-free from January 2026, supported by an 81.5% YoY surge in technology revenue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:16:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6987492cb81b2b81dcfc9e81.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KSH International IPO Success Marred by Q3 Profit Dip; Revenue Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-IPO-Success-Marred-by-Q3-Profit-Dip-Revenue-Soars/698748b7b81b2b81dcfc9d14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-IPO-Success-Marred-by-Q3-Profit-Dip-Revenue-Soars/698748b7b81b2b81dcfc9d14</guid><description>KSH International Limited reported a strong nine-month performance for FY26, with revenue up 47% YoY to INR 20,886.29 million and PAT rising 52.6% YoY to INR 755.99 million. However, Q3 FY26 saw a mixed trend: revenue surged 58.9% YoY to INR 8,177.69 million, but PAT declined 9.0% YoY to INR 233.26 million due to an exceptional item. PAT margins compressed in Q3. The company recently completed its IPO, significantly increasing equity share capital.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:14:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698748b7b81b2b81dcfc9d13_1770475111633.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ganesha Ecosphere Q3 Profit Plummets 81%, Standalone Unit Roars Back</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Ganesha-Ecosphere-Q3-Profit-Plummets-81percent-Standalone-Unit-Roars-Back/6987456bb81b2b81dcfc9908</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Ganesha-Ecosphere-Q3-Profit-Plummets-81percent-Standalone-Unit-Roars-Back/6987456bb81b2b81dcfc9908</guid><description>Ganesha Ecosphere's consolidated net profit plunged 81.1% YoY to ₹4.8 Crore in Q3FY26, hit by weak rPET demand linked to regulatory ambiguity. Revenue fell 10.2% to ₹357.2 Crore. In contrast, its standalone business surged QoQ, with PAT up 103.8% and EBITDA up 125.6%, as the company strategically targets higher-margin products amid a positive PET market outlook.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:00:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987456bb81b2b81dcfc9907_1770474854905.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Max Estates Q3 Margins Crash 80%, Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-Q3-Margins-Crash-80percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth/6987447cb81b2b81dcfc972a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-Q3-Margins-Crash-80percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth/6987447cb81b2b81dcfc972a</guid><description>Max Estates reported a 24% YoY revenue jump to ₹150 crore for 9M FY26, driven by a 38% surge in lease rentals. However, Q3 FY26 saw a dramatic 80% year-on-year drop in EBITDA margins to a mere 5.9% from 29.3%, despite revenue of ₹49.8 crore. The company holds robust liquidity with ₹1,284 crore cash against ₹414 crore net debt and boasts a ₹14,500-₹15,000 crore project pipeline, including launches in Noida.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:56:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987447cb81b2b81dcfc9729_1770474693470.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ganesha Ecosphere Q3 PAT Plunges 84% on Consolidated Basis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ganesha-Ecosphere-Q3-PAT-Plunges-84percent-on-Consolidated-Basis/69874310b81b2b81dcfc9498</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ganesha-Ecosphere-Q3-PAT-Plunges-84percent-on-Consolidated-Basis/69874310b81b2b81dcfc9498</guid><description>Ganesha Ecosphere Limited reported challenging Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeting 84.01% year-on-year to ₹474.84 Lakhs. Standalone revenue grew 1.84% to ₹27,294.53 Lakhs, but standalone PAT fell 18.55%. The company also reported a significant 81.08% drop in consolidated PAT for the nine-month period. Increased expenses and recognition of incremental impact from new Labour Codes contributed to the profit erosion. No management guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:50:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874310b81b2b81dcfc9497_1770474547762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bella Casa Fashion Revenue Surges 17%, Now Net Debt-Free</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Bella-Casa-Fashion-Revenue-Surges-17percent-Now-Net-Debt-Free/69874225b81b2b81dcfc927a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Bella-Casa-Fashion-Revenue-Surges-17percent-Now-Net-Debt-Free/69874225b81b2b81dcfc927a</guid><description>Bella Casa Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd. reported robust financial results for 9M FY26, with revenue up 17% YoY and PAT soaring 36% to ₹15.6 crore. The company achieved a significant milestone by becoming net debt-free in Q3 FY26. Management highlighted strong revenue visibility, driven by order commitments and a strategic push into export markets, supported by investments aimed at doubling production capacity and land acquisition for future growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:46:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874225b81b2b81dcfc9279_1770474384940.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Megastar Foods Q3 Profit Surges 680%, But Debt and Inventory Rise Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Megastar-Foods-Q3-Profit-Surges-680percent-But-Debt-and-Inventory-Rise-Sharply/69874131b81b2b81dcfc9094</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Megastar-Foods-Q3-Profit-Surges-680percent-But-Debt-and-Inventory-Rise-Sharply/69874131b81b2b81dcfc9094</guid><description>Megastar Foods reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with PAT soaring 680% YoY to ₹306 lakhs on 52.3% revenue growth. The nine-month period also saw robust performance. However, the balance sheet shows a significant increase in borrowings, current liabilities, and inventory, alongside a sharp drop in the current ratio, flagging potential financial risks. Full-year FY25 PAT saw a 40% decline.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:42:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874131b81b2b81dcfc9093_1770474192167.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Max Estates Surges on Strong Pre-Sales and Commercial Leasing Momentum</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-Surges-on-Strong-Pre-Sales-and-Commercial-Leasing-Momentum/698740bcb81b2b81dcfc8f24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-Surges-on-Strong-Pre-Sales-and-Commercial-Leasing-Momentum/698740bcb81b2b81dcfc8f24</guid><description>Max Estates Limited (MEL) reported strong financial performance for 9M FY26, driven by robust residential pre-sales exceeding INR 1,900 crore in Gurugram and significant commercial leasing momentum, including a major LOI for Max District, Gurugram. The company secured over INR 270 crore in gross rentals from this pre-leasing deal, three years ahead of project completion, at a substantial premium. With INR 150 crore in revenue and INR 20 crore PAT for the period, MEL maintains a healthy net debt position of INR 414 crore against INR 1,284 crore cash.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:40:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698740bcb81b2b81dcfc8f23.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIC Re Posts 36% Profit Surge, Eyes Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-Posts-36percent-Profit-Surge-Eyes-Global-Expansion/69874047b81b2b81dcfc8df4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-Posts-36percent-Profit-Surge-Eyes-Global-Expansion/69874047b81b2b81dcfc8df4</guid><description>GIC Re reported robust Nine Months FY26 results, with Profit After Tax soaring 35.84% YoY to ₹6,137.94 crore. Gross Premium grew 7.11% to ₹32,976.26 crore, supported by an improved Incurred Claims Ratio of 86.93% and a reduced Combined Ratio of 106.88%. The company is actively scaling its international business, aiming for a 60:40 domestic:international risk portfolio, and enhancing its solvency ratio to 3.87.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:38:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69874047b81b2b81dcfc8df3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIC Re Q3 PAT Dips Standalone, Surges Consolidated Amid Premium Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-Q3-PAT-Dips-Standalone-Surges-Consolidated-Amid-Premium-Growth/69873fccb81b2b81dcfc8c9a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-Q3-PAT-Dips-Standalone-Surges-Consolidated-Amid-Premium-Growth/69873fccb81b2b81dcfc8c9a</guid><description>General Insurance Corporation of India (GIC Re) posted a mixed performance for Q3 FY26. While consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) surged 7.9% year-on-year to ₹1,75,139 Lakhs, standalone PAT saw a 6.3% decline to ₹1,51,892 Lakhs. Gross Written Premiums (GWP) showed robust YoY growth, with consolidated GWP rising 9.7% and standalone GWP up 10.2%. The company also reported an improved combined ratio and stronger solvency ratios, alongside a final dividend of ₹10.00 per share.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:36:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69873fccb81b2b81dcfc8c99.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Housing Finance: AUM Surges 23%, PAT Rises 21% on Loan Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Housing-Finance-AUM-Surges-23percent-PAT-Rises-21percent-on-Loan-Growth/69873c0cb81b2b81dcfc87dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Housing-Finance-AUM-Surges-23percent-PAT-Rises-21percent-on-Loan-Growth/69873c0cb81b2b81dcfc87dc</guid><description>Bajaj Housing Finance reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with Assets Under Management (AUM) jumping 23% year-on-year to ₹1.33 lakh crore, driven by a 32% surge in disbursements. Profit After Tax (PAT) climbed 21% YoY to ₹665 crore. The company is aggressively expanding its 'Sambhav Loans' segment, targeting double disbursements within 15 months. However, Tier-1 capital saw a decline due to provisioning, and competitive pressures persist, impacting gross spreads.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:20:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69873c0cb81b2b81dcfc87db_1770473745879.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gravity India Posts 7814% Revenue Surge Amid Severe Auditor Qualifications</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gravity-India-Posts-7814percent-Revenue-Surge-Amid-Severe-Auditor-Qualifications/69873b1bb81b2b81dcfc862b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gravity-India-Posts-7814percent-Revenue-Surge-Amid-Severe-Auditor-Qualifications/69873b1bb81b2b81dcfc862b</guid><description>Gravity India Limited reported a staggering 7814% year-on-year revenue growth for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹5,950.97 Lakhs. Net profit also surged 1254% to ₹450.46 Lakhs. However, the celebratory mood is dampened by a qualified auditor's report citing serious issues with gratuity provision, lease accounting, TDS compliance, and fixed asset verification, stating the results do not present a 'true and fair view'.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:16:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69873b1bb81b2b81dcfc862a_1770473586854.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prozone Realty Soars: Q3 Profit Jumps 152% on Robust Real Estate and Rental Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Prozone-Realty-Soars-Q3-Profit-Jumps-152percent-on-Robust-Real-Estate-and-Rental-Growth/69873aa7b81b2b81dcfc84d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Prozone-Realty-Soars-Q3-Profit-Jumps-152percent-on-Robust-Real-Estate-and-Rental-Growth/69873aa7b81b2b81dcfc84d7</guid><description>Prozone Realty Limited posted a robust Q3 FY26, with Profit Before Tax (PBT) surging 152% year-on-year to Rs 108.4 million. EBITDA rose 28% YoY to Rs 254.8 million. Total income grew 30% to Rs 582.3 million, fueled by a 66% jump in real estate project revenue and a 13% rise in lease rentals. Profit After Tax (PAT) increased 75% YoY to Rs 67.8 million. The nine-month period also showed significant growth, with EBITDA up 50% YoY. Mall occupancy remained high, and consumption/footfall saw positive trends.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:14:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69873aa7b81b2b81dcfc84d6_1770473416623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oswal Pumps Posts Strong Revenue Growth, But Margins Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oswal-Pumps-Posts-Strong-Revenue-Growth-But-Margins-Squeeze/69873a31b81b2b81dcfc83a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oswal-Pumps-Posts-Strong-Revenue-Growth-But-Margins-Squeeze/69873a31b81b2b81dcfc83a9</guid><description>Oswal Pumps Limited reported a robust 31.07% YoY revenue growth to ₹4,477.17 million for Q3 FY26 on a standalone basis. However, profitability margins contracted, with PBT margin falling to 20.8% and net profit margin to 15.4% due to higher expense growth. Consolidated revenue also grew 31.94% YoY to ₹5,010.70 million, though margins saw similar pressure. The company has utilized ₹5,018.85 million of its IPO proceeds. An exceptional item of ₹18.52 million was booked due to new Labour Codes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:12:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69873a31b81b2b81dcfc83a8_1770473250817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sanghvi Movers Revenue Jumps, But Q3 Profit Dips Amid Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sanghvi-Movers-Revenue-Jumps-But-Q3-Profit-Dips-Amid-Expansion/698739d0b81b2b81dcfc8253</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sanghvi-Movers-Revenue-Jumps-But-Q3-Profit-Dips-Amid-Expansion/698739d0b81b2b81dcfc8253</guid><description>Sanghvi Movers reported a 39.7% YoY revenue jump in 9M FY26 to ₹719 Cr, driven by robust demand. However, Q3 FY26 saw a 12.4% YoY decline in Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹29 Cr, alongside margin compression. The company is investing ₹629 Cr in CAPEX for FY25-26, with significant deployment in India and Saudi Arabia, aiming for global expansion and diversification.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:10:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698739d0b81b2b81dcfc8252_1770473245133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TARC Surges on Q3 Growth, Eyes Net Debt Zero with ₹8,000 Crore Project Pipeline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/TARC-Surges-on-Q3-Growth-Eyes-Net-Debt-Zero-with-8000-Crore-Project-Pipeline/698739b3b81b2b81dcfc8164</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/TARC-Surges-on-Q3-Growth-Eyes-Net-Debt-Zero-with-8000-Crore-Project-Pipeline/698739b3b81b2b81dcfc8164</guid><description>TARC Limited's Q3 FY26 investor update reveals significant operational momentum, with 9MFY26 cash flows exceeding the previous fiscal year and pre-sales reaching ₹977 crore. The company turned profitable in 9MFY26 with a net profit of ₹17.42 lakhs, a substantial improvement from a prior year loss, and saw Q3 revenue surge 308.8% YoY. With a strong land bank and a clear strategy to achieve Net Debt Zero from over ₹1,900 crore gross debt, TARC anticipates over ₹1,000 crore and ₹8,000 crore in revenue recognition from its Tripundra and Kailasa/Ishva projects respectively in upcoming years.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:10:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698739b3b81b2b81dcfc8163_1770473081416.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sarda Energy: Q3 Margins Squeeze Amidst Acquisition Cloud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sarda-Energy-Q3-Margins-Squeeze-Amidst-Acquisition-Cloud/6987393eb81b2b81dcfc8023</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sarda-Energy-Q3-Margins-Squeeze-Amidst-Acquisition-Cloud/6987393eb81b2b81dcfc8023</guid><description>Sarda Energy &amp; Minerals posted a weaker operating performance for Q3 FY26, with revenue declining 3.3% year-on-year and EBITDA margins compressing to 24.36% from 27.95%. Despite a strong nine-month consolidated profit surge of 60.2% driven by the SKS Power acquisition, the company faces significant risk as this acquisition is under challenge in the Supreme Court. The stock, however, has gained 13.67% over the past year, reflecting investor optimism tempered by operational headwinds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:08:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987393eb81b2b81dcfc8022_1770472956682.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Auto Parts Win Quota Relief</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-US-Trade-Deal-Auto-Parts-Win-Quota-Relief/698737d6b81b2b81dcfc7dc1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-US-Trade-Deal-Auto-Parts-Win-Quota-Relief/698737d6b81b2b81dcfc7dc1</guid><description>The recently established India-US Interim Trade Agreement framework provides significant benefits for India's automotive component sector. Key provisions include preferential tariff-rate quotas (TRQs) for automotive parts and the removal of certain Section 232 tariffs, aiming to enhance export competitiveness. This accord, welcomed by the Automotive Component Manufacturers Association of India (ACMA), signals a strategic intent to deepen bilateral trade and manufacturing ties. While offering relief from previous high tariffs, the agreement's full impact hinges on further clarification and integration into the final bilateral trade agreement.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:02:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698737d6b81b2b81dcfc7dc0_1770472781254.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Viyash Scientific: Merger Synergies Drive Revenue, Valuation Strains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Viyash-Scientific-Merger-Synergies-Drive-Revenue-Valuation-Strains/6987377eb81b2b81dcfc7c63</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Viyash-Scientific-Merger-Synergies-Drive-Revenue-Valuation-Strains/6987377eb81b2b81dcfc7c63</guid><description>Viyash Scientific's inaugural Q3 results highlight an 11% revenue jump to ₹858 Cr and a 64% EBITDA surge to ₹185 Cr, validating merger synergies. However, profit metrics show volatility and a sharp valuation premium persists, leading to a stock price dip post-announcement amidst mixed analyst sentiment and a challenging regulatory environment for some segments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:00:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987377eb81b2b81dcfc7c62_1770472629972.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Q3 PAT Jumps 24.5% on Strong Operations, Divestment Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Q3-PAT-Jumps-245percent-on-Strong-Operations-Divestment-Gains/6987375cb81b2b81dcfc7b48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Q3-PAT-Jumps-245percent-on-Strong-Operations-Divestment-Gains/6987375cb81b2b81dcfc7b48</guid><description>State Bank of India reported a robust Q3 FY26, with standalone net profit soaring 24.5% YoY to ₹21,028 Crore. The bank also booked significant one-off gains, including ₹3,026.57 Crore from its Yes Bank stake sale and ₹25.46 Crore from Jio Payments Bank divestment, alongside ₹7,288.81 Crore from asset revaluation. A ₹25,000 Crore QIP further bolstered its capital base.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987375cb81b2b81dcfc7b47_1770472485161.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tejnaksh Healthcare Q3 Profit Plunges 48% on Revenue Drop, Margins Collapse</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Tejnaksh-Healthcare-Q3-Profit-Plunges-48percent-on-Revenue-Drop-Margins-Collapse/698736e7b81b2b81dcfc79f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Tejnaksh-Healthcare-Q3-Profit-Plunges-48percent-on-Revenue-Drop-Margins-Collapse/698736e7b81b2b81dcfc79f8</guid><description>Tejnaksh Healthcare reported a grim Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue down 18.01% year-on-year to ₹261.62 Cr and Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeting 48.11% to ₹28.82 Cr. Profit Before Tax (PBT) margins compressed significantly to 13.27% from 28.72% in Q3 FY25. Standalone PAT saw a steeper fall of 68.34% YoY. The company provided no forward-looking guidance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:58:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698736e7b81b2b81dcfc79f7_1770472393428.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HBL Engineering Q3: Revenue Up 90%, Profit Soars 254% on Strong Growth; Plans JV, Startup Bets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HBL-Engineering-Q3-Revenue-Up-90percent-Profit-Soars-254percent-on-Strong-Growth-Plans-JV-Startup-Bets/6987366bb81b2b81dcfc7891</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HBL-Engineering-Q3-Revenue-Up-90percent-Profit-Soars-254percent-on-Strong-Growth-Plans-JV-Startup-Bets/6987366bb81b2b81dcfc7891</guid><description>HBL Engineering reported exceptional Q3 FY26 financial results with a 90.0% year-over-year revenue increase to ₹863.65 Cr and a 254.4% surge in net profit to ₹217.69 Cr on a standalone basis. Consolidated figures also showed robust growth. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹2 per share and approved strategic initiatives including a joint venture with Cochin Shipyard Limited and equity investments in two startups, signaling aggressive expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:56:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6987366bb81b2b81dcfc7890.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tejnaksh Healthcare Revenue Plunges 18%, Profit Dips 48% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Tejnaksh-Healthcare-Revenue-Plunges-18percent-Profit-Dips-48percent-YoY/6987339cb81b2b81dcfc744d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Tejnaksh-Healthcare-Revenue-Plunges-18percent-Profit-Dips-48percent-YoY/6987339cb81b2b81dcfc744d</guid><description>Tejnaksh Healthcare Limited reported a steep 17.98% year-over-year decline in consolidated revenue to ₹261.62 Cr for Q3 FY26. Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeted 48.12% YoY to ₹28.82 Cr, with margins shrinking. Standalone results mirrored this trend, showing significant drops in revenue, PAT, and margins. The company provided no management commentary or forward-looking guidance, leaving investors uncertain.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:44:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987339cb81b2b81dcfc744c_1770472176319.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Pet Insurance Boom: High Costs Fuel Growth, But Gaps Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Pet-Insurance-Boom-High-Costs-Fuel-Growth-But-Gaps-Loom/698732acb81b2b81dcfc7289</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Pet-Insurance-Boom-High-Costs-Fuel-Growth-But-Gaps-Loom/698732acb81b2b81dcfc7289</guid><description>The Indian pet insurance sector is experiencing robust growth, driven by pets being viewed as family and escalating veterinary expenses. Despite market expansion, a significant gap persists between rising medical costs and comprehensive coverage, compounded by low consumer awareness and an evolving regulatory framework. Key players are introducing tailored policies, but potential policy limitations and underwriting challenges present a complex outlook for both insurers and pet parents.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698732acb81b2b81dcfc7288_1770472035702.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Life Insurers Face Stagnant Unclaimed Funds Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Life-Insurers-Face-Stagnant-Unclaimed-Funds-Issue/69873238b81b2b81dcfc7134</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Life-Insurers-Face-Stagnant-Unclaimed-Funds-Issue/69873238b81b2b81dcfc7134</guid><description>Life insurers in India are contending with over ₹20,000 crore in unclaimed benefits, a persistent issue highlighting awareness gaps and operational inefficiencies. Despite industry-led initiatives and regulatory drives, the accumulation of these funds suggests deeper systemic challenges. Policyholders and beneficiaries face hurdles in reclaiming their entitlements due to outdated data, procedural complexities, and communication breakdowns within the sector. The substantial sum, which doesn't represent lost funds but rather unaccessed rightful claims, underscores a critical need for enhanced data management and simplified claim processes across the life insurance industry.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:38:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69873238b81b2b81dcfc7133_1770471829236.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Tax Safe Harbour Boosts Manufacturing Hub Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-New-Tax-Safe-Harbour-Boosts-Manufacturing-Hub-Ambition/698731deb81b2b81dcfc6fce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-New-Tax-Safe-Harbour-Boosts-Manufacturing-Hub-Ambition/698731deb81b2b81dcfc6fce</guid><description>India is bolstering its manufacturing and supply chain ambitions with a new component warehousing tax framework, featuring a 2% safe harbour margin. This translates to an approximate 0.7% effective tax rate, providing multinational corporations with critical predictability in taxation and transfer pricing. The initiative, part of the Union Budget 2026-27, aims to reduce litigation and enhance ease of doing business, positioning India as a stable, competitive global hub.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:36:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698731deb81b2b81dcfc6fcd_1770471640561.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KRN Heat Exchanger Logs 65% PAT Jump; Acquisition Boosts Growth Prospects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KRN-Heat-Exchanger-Logs-65percent-PAT-Jump-Acquisition-Boosts-Growth-Prospects/698731c1b81b2b81dcfc6eed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KRN-Heat-Exchanger-Logs-65percent-PAT-Jump-Acquisition-Boosts-Growth-Prospects/698731c1b81b2b81dcfc6eed</guid><description>KRN Heat Exchanger reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated net profit soaring 65.09% YoY to ₹22.66 Cr on 37.46% revenue growth. EBITDA surged 96.54% YoY. The company also strengthened its transport cooling segment via acquisition and commenced subsidiary production. However, standalone margins contracted, and FY25 ROE fell significantly to 10.60% from 30.23%, signaling a mixed operational picture despite aggressive expansion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:36:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698731c1b81b2b81dcfc6eec.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L.G. Balakrishnan Posts 18% Revenue Growth, Profitability Trails Amidst Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LG-Balakrishnan-Posts-18percent-Revenue-Growth-Profitability-Trails-Amidst-Costs/698730ceb81b2b81dcfc6cc2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LG-Balakrishnan-Posts-18percent-Revenue-Growth-Profitability-Trails-Amidst-Costs/698730ceb81b2b81dcfc6cc2</guid><description>L.G. Balakrishnan &amp; Bros Limited reported a strong 18.38% YoY revenue growth for 9M FY26 to ₹2,26,062.72 Lakhs. However, net profit saw a more modest 4.26% rise to ₹29,066.21 Lakhs, indicating margin pressures. Q3 FY26 also showed robust revenue growth of 20.63%. The company also announced the re-appointment of an independent director.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:32:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698730ceb81b2b81dcfc6cc1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance MET City Bets Big on Haryana: Self-Funded Township Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Reliance-MET-City-Bets-Big-on-Haryana-Self-Funded-Township-Expansion/698730a1b81b2b81dcfc6bba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Reliance-MET-City-Bets-Big-on-Haryana-Self-Funded-Township-Expansion/698730a1b81b2b81dcfc6bba</guid><description>Reliance MET City, a subsidiary of Reliance Industries, is significantly expanding its integrated township in Jhajjar, Haryana, by launching a 140-acre plotted development phase. This initiative includes residential plots, industrial zones, and future group housing, emphasizing a 'walk-to-work' philosophy. The project is entirely self-funded, highlighting Reliance's robust financial capacity and long-term strategic vision for creating self-sustaining economic and residential ecosystems.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:31:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698730a1b81b2b81dcfc6bb9_1770471210721.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>