<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:56 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Gold Loan Surge: NBFCs Lead Amidst Banking Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Gold-Loan-Surge-NBFCs-Lead-Amidst-Banking-Push/69955fa0d25eafd9cdfd224e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Gold-Loan-Surge-NBFCs-Lead-Amidst-Banking-Push/69955fa0d25eafd9cdfd224e</guid><description>India's gold loan market is experiencing unprecedented expansion, with new loan sourcing value up 91% in FY26 Q3. While NBFCs are gaining traction in new business acquisition, leveraging regulatory tailwinds and changing social perceptions, banks are aggressively increasing their overall market share. Elevated gold prices and stringent rules on unsecured lending continue to fuel demand, but a complex competitive dynamic is emerging between lenders with varying funding costs and market strategies. The market's potential remains vast, with only a fraction of household gold in the organized pledge market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:43:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69955fa0d25eafd9cdfd224d_1771397183751.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Globe Civil Projects Posts Stable Profits Amid Cautious Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Globe-Civil-Projects-Posts-Stable-Profits-Amid-Cautious-Outlook/69955f7bd25eafd9cdfd2237</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Globe-Civil-Projects-Posts-Stable-Profits-Amid-Cautious-Outlook/69955f7bd25eafd9cdfd2237</guid><description>Globe Civil Projects Limited has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company maintained stable revenues and profitability, citing disciplined execution and cost management. The Managing Director expressed cautious optimism for future growth, driven by an improving project pipeline. However, an anomaly in consolidated Q3 revenue figures warrants attention.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:43:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69955f7bd25eafd9cdfd2236_1771397090584.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Marico Bets Big on Digital: Aims for 15x Foods Growth by FY30</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Marico-Bets-Big-on-Digital-Aims-for-15x-Foods-Growth-by-FY30/69955f7ad25eafd9cdfd2221</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Marico-Bets-Big-on-Digital-Aims-for-15x-Foods-Growth-by-FY30/69955f7ad25eafd9cdfd2221</guid><description>Marico Limited is aggressively transforming into a digital-first consumer powerhouse, setting ambitious targets for its Foods and Personal Care segments. The company plans to grow its Foods business 15 times by FY30 and significantly expand its digital personal care brands, leveraging acquisitions and its established strengths for sustainable growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:43:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69955f7ad25eafd9cdfd2220_1771397091849.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unimech Aerospace Revenue Drops 37% Amid Headwinds, Eyes Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Unimech-Aerospace-Revenue-Drops-37percent-Amid-Headwinds-Eyes-Recovery/69955f79d25eafd9cdfd220b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Unimech-Aerospace-Revenue-Drops-37percent-Amid-Headwinds-Eyes-Recovery/69955f79d25eafd9cdfd220b</guid><description>Unimech Aerospace reported a challenging Q3 FY2026 with revenue falling 37% year-on-year to ₹33.7 crore, mainly due to high U.S. tariffs and seasonal factors. Profitability also saw a sharp decline. However, the company secured record orders, formed a strategic joint venture in Saudi Arabia, and anticipates recovery driven by tariff reductions and its upcoming Free Trade Warehousing Zone. Management has revised its FY2026 revenue target downwards but remains optimistic for FY2027.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:43:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69955f79d25eafd9cdfd220a_1771397099957.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Platinum Industries Expands into Pharma, Eyes Big Growth; Egypt Plant Faces Delay</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Platinum-Industries-Expands-into-Pharma-Eyes-Big-Growth-Egypt-Plant-Faces-Delay/69955e89d25eafd9cdfd2149</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Platinum-Industries-Expands-into-Pharma-Eyes-Big-Growth-Egypt-Plant-Faces-Delay/69955e89d25eafd9cdfd2149</guid><description>Platinum Industries reported a robust 31% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹102.62 Cr in Q3 FY26, with a consolidated revenue of ₹104.67 Cr. The company is aggressively diversifying into pharmaceuticals via Rivadu LifeSciences and oleo chemicals, targeting over 40% revenue growth in FY27. However, investors are watching a small promoter stake sale and delays in the Egypt facility's commissioning, now expected by December 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:39:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69955e89d25eafd9cdfd2148_1771396851989.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MakeMyTrip taps OpenAI to bridge AI inspiration-to-booking gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MakeMyTrip-taps-OpenAI-to-bridge-AI-inspiration-to-booking-gap/69955de8d25eafd9cdfd20ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MakeMyTrip-taps-OpenAI-to-bridge-AI-inspiration-to-booking-gap/69955de8d25eafd9cdfd20ae</guid><description>MakeMyTrip announced a significant collaboration with OpenAI to infuse its travel planning ecosystem with advanced AI capabilities. The partnership aims to seamlessly transition travelers from conversational inspiration to booking through the Myra interface, leveraging OpenAI's APIs to generate structured, bookable options for flights and hotels. This move positions MakeMyTrip to capture high-intent queries and drive transactions, especially targeting India's burgeoning Tier-2 and smaller cities via vernacular and voice-enabled features, reinforcing its dominant market share against AI-focused competitors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:36:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69955de8d25eafd9cdfd20ad_1771396695433.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NLCIL's ₹2,354 Cr Loss Reveals Deep Operational Cracks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NLCILs-2354-Cr-Loss-Reveals-Deep-Operational-Cracks/69955c6d3ec8b0ccb20dc77b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NLCILs-2354-Cr-Loss-Reveals-Deep-Operational-Cracks/69955c6d3ec8b0ccb20dc77b</guid><description>A Comptroller and Auditor General (CAG) report has highlighted nearly ₹2,354 crore in losses for NLC India Limited, primarily stemming from design deficiencies in its thermal power stations, particularly Circulating Fluidised Bed Combustion (CFBC) boilers. These issues led to under-recovery of capacity charges, operational inefficiencies, and safety lapses, including fatal incidents. Despite the company's notable sustainability initiatives, the audit reveals systemic problems impacting profitability and operational reliability. NLC India's stock is trading around ₹261.75, with analysts maintaining a 'BUY' consensus and an average target price of ₹304.00, but these operational challenges pose a significant risk to future performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69955c6d3ec8b0ccb20dc77a_1771396335691.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Navigates Headwinds for Q2 Surge on Systemic Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Navigates-Headwinds-for-Q2-Surge-on-Systemic-Risks/69955bc83ec8b0ccb20dc6f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Navigates-Headwinds-for-Q2-Surge-on-Systemic-Risks/69955bc83ec8b0ccb20dc6f1</guid><description>Gold prices are navigating a complex short-term environment shaped by conflicting US economic signals and seasonal China market closures, leading to range-bound trading. Despite immediate headwinds and profit-taking, underlying drivers such as persistent geopolitical tensions and investor demand for inflation hedges are expected to propel gold towards $6,000 per ounce by the second quarter. Silver prices show signs of potential near-term weakness. Current spot gold is $4,937/Oz, and spot silver is $74.75/Oz.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:27:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69955bc83ec8b0ccb20dc6f0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>R Systems Posts Strong Q4 Growth Fueled by AI Push and Novigo Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/R-Systems-Posts-Strong-Q4-Growth-Fueled-by-AI-Push-and-Novigo-Deal/699559233ec8b0ccb20dc5b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/R-Systems-Posts-Strong-Q4-Growth-Fueled-by-AI-Push-and-Novigo-Deal/699559233ec8b0ccb20dc5b9</guid><description>R Systems International Limited announced robust financial results for Q4 and the full year FY2025, with Q4 revenue climbing 23.6% year-over-year to ₹555.1 Crores and adjusted net profit surging 27.4% to ₹60.4 Crores. The company highlighted strong growth across its full-year performance as well, fueled by strategic investments in Artificial Intelligence and the successful acquisition of Novigo Solutions, which is expected to boost margins and revenue. Management anticipates 2026 to be a pivotal year for AI implementation and project growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:16:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699559233ec8b0ccb20dc5b8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HMPL Loses Subsidiary Control Amidst New Infrastructure Contract</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/HMPL-Loses-Subsidiary-Control-Amidst-New-Infrastructure-Contract/6995586a3ec8b0ccb20dc433</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/HMPL-Loses-Subsidiary-Control-Amidst-New-Infrastructure-Contract/6995586a3ec8b0ccb20dc433</guid><description>Hazoor Multi Projects Limited (HMPL) has seen its shareholding in Vyom Hydrocarbon Private Limited (VHPL) diluted below a controlling threshold following the conversion of Compulsorily Convertible Debentures (CCDs) by Vyom Geophysical Private Limited. This loss of control means VHPL and its subsidiary are no longer consolidated entities. Concurrently, HMPL secured a one-year, ₹44.23 crore contract from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for user fee collection and maintenance. Despite these events, the company has shown year-on-year growth in nine-month revenues and profits, though its stock has experienced remarkable 10,000% growth over five years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:12:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995586a3ec8b0ccb20dc432_1771395388623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys AI Optimism Fails to Lift Stock Amidst Sector Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Optimism-Fails-to-Lift-Stock-Amidst-Sector-Slump/699558673ec8b0ccb20dc41c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Optimism-Fails-to-Lift-Stock-Amidst-Sector-Slump/699558673ec8b0ccb20dc41c</guid><description>Infosys Chairman Nandan Nilekani expressed strong confidence in artificial intelligence opportunities, announcing a partnership with Anthropic for advanced AI solutions. However, this failed to stem a significant share price decline, with the stock falling over 17% in February 2026, underperforming the Nifty. The company is grappling with sector-wide AI disruption fears, persistent technical weakness, and a divergence in analyst sentiment, with some downgrading ratings despite aggressive AI strategy articulation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:12:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699558673ec8b0ccb20dc41b_1771395320492.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stylam Industries: Promoters Exit, New Japanese Owner Takes Charge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stylam-Industries-Promoters-Exit-New-Japanese-Owner-Takes-Charge/699558653ec8b0ccb20dc405</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stylam-Industries-Promoters-Exit-New-Japanese-Owner-Takes-Charge/699558653ec8b0ccb20dc405</guid><description>Stylam Industries Limited is undergoing a major ownership and leadership shift. Its erstwhile promoters have sold their entire 27.12% stake to Japan's AICA Kogyo Company, Limited, leading to their reclassification. This transition also saw the resignation of a Whole Time Director and an Independent Director, while plans are underway to increase managerial pay for the MD and another Whole Time Director, pending shareholder nod.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:12:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699558653ec8b0ccb20dc404_1771395231784.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurionpro Data Center Deal Fuels Growth Amid India's AI Infrastructure Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Aurionpro-Data-Center-Deal-Fuels-Growth-Amid-Indias-AI-Infrastructure-Boom/699557fd3ec8b0ccb20dc315</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Aurionpro-Data-Center-Deal-Fuels-Growth-Amid-Indias-AI-Infrastructure-Boom/699557fd3ec8b0ccb20dc315</guid><description>Aurionpro Solutions' stock saw a notable uptick following the announcement of a substantial data center project win from a global client. This order, spanning three quarters, involves engineering and execution for a Mumbai-based brownfield facility, reinforcing Aurionpro's capabilities in complex infrastructure development. The win aligns with India's rapidly growing data center sector, driven by AI demand and hyperscaler expansion, with Mumbai being the primary hub. Despite recent stock volatility, analysts maintain a positive outlook with a high price target.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:11:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699557fd3ec8b0ccb20dc314_1771395374212.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Tumbles on USFDA Plant Issues, Data Integrity Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Tumbles-on-USFDA-Plant-Issues-Data-Integrity-Fears/699557c83ec8b0ccb20dc266</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Tumbles-on-USFDA-Plant-Issues-Data-Integrity-Fears/699557c83ec8b0ccb20dc266</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma shares declined significantly following USFDA observations at its Unit-7 facility, citing critical issues including equipment cleaning, computer system controls, and particularly, data integrity concerns, with a microbiologist accused of falsifying data. This regulatory action impacts the company's key US generics business and adds to concerns from its recently reported mixed Q3 financial performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:10:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699557c83ec8b0ccb20dc265_1771395148525.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unicommerce Esolutions Surges: Growth Momentum Meets Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Unicommerce-Esolutions-Surges-Growth-Momentum-Meets-Valuation-Scrutiny/699557be3ec8b0ccb20dc24f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Unicommerce-Esolutions-Surges-Growth-Momentum-Meets-Valuation-Scrutiny/699557be3ec8b0ccb20dc24f</guid><description>Unicommerce Esolutions experienced a significant stock surge, climbing 34% over two sessions following robust Q3FY26 results. Revenue jumped 72.2% year-on-year to ₹56.4 crore, while net profit rose 17.4% to ₹7.4 crore. This rally occurred amid a substantial increase in trading volumes, 222 times the 30-day average on the NSE. However, despite the strong top-line growth, adjusted EBITDA margins dipped to 23.8% from 27.1% a year ago, influenced by business mix changes. The company projects continued double-digit growth and plans strategic AI investments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:10:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699557be3ec8b0ccb20dc24e_1771395191748.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech-Led Finance: Bajaj Group Companies Poised for Growth Amidst NBFC Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tech-Led-Finance-Bajaj-Group-Companies-Poised-for-Growth-Amidst-NBFC-Divergence/699557993ec8b0ccb20dc1f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tech-Led-Finance-Bajaj-Group-Companies-Poised-for-Growth-Amidst-NBFC-Divergence/699557993ec8b0ccb20dc1f0</guid><description>DRChoksey Finserv's Managing Director, Deven Choksey, favors non-banking financial companies (NBFCs) with a retail focus and demonstrated technology adoption, specifically naming Bajaj Finance and Bajaj Housing Finance. This preference stems from their superior customer reach, credit underwriting, and loan processing enabled by technology. The firm maintains caution on business process outsourcing (BPO) companies due to AI-driven uncertainties in their revenue models and selectively tracks mid-tier IT firms. The analysis suggests a market bifurcation, favoring diversified, tech-savvy lenders over those facing uncertain technological transitions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:09:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699557993ec8b0ccb20dc1ef_1771395081436.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Shares Tumble on FDA's Dire Unit-7 Findings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Shares-Tumble-on-FDAs-Dire-Unit-7-Findings/699557963ec8b0ccb20dc1d9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Shares-Tumble-on-FDAs-Dire-Unit-7-Findings/699557963ec8b0ccb20dc1d9</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma Ltd. shares fell 4% on Wednesday after the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) issued a Form 483 detailing critical manufacturing and quality control lapses at its Unit-7 facility. The inspection, conducted from January 28 to February 10, 2026, revealed alarming issues, including alleged data falsification by a microbiologist, the presence of E. coli and bird droppings, and systemic deficiencies in equipment cleaning and record-keeping. These findings pose significant risks to Aurobindo's substantial U.S. market business.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:09:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699557963ec8b0ccb20dc1d8_1771395071271.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Credit System Accelerates: Weekly Delinquency Reporting Starts July 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Credit-System-Accelerates-Weekly-Delinquency-Reporting-Starts-July-2026/699557833ec8b0ccb20dc1bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Credit-System-Accelerates-Weekly-Delinquency-Reporting-Starts-July-2026/699557833ec8b0ccb20dc1bd</guid><description>India's credit reporting system is set for a significant acceleration, moving to weekly updates by July 2026. This rapid shift means a single missed loan EMI or credit card payment could impact a borrower's score within days, potentially widening future borrowing costs. While overall NPAs remain low, the increased speed of delinquency reporting intensifies the pressure on borrowers to maintain impeccable payment discipline in an expanding unsecured lending market. This regulatory push for transparency is reshaping risk assessment and consumer financial behavior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:09:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699557833ec8b0ccb20dc1bc_1771395076241.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Industries: Analyst Sees 18% Upside, Risks Remain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Reliance-Industries-Analyst-Sees-18percent-Upside-Risks-Remain/699556d03ec8b0ccb20dc07f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Reliance-Industries-Analyst-Sees-18percent-Upside-Risks-Remain/699556d03ec8b0ccb20dc07f</guid><description>Prabhudas Lilladher maintains a 'BUY' rating on Reliance Industries (RELI), setting a price target of Rs 1,688, suggesting an 18.71% upside from current levels. The brokerage highlights steady performance in the Oil-to-Chemicals (O2C) segment driven by healthy diesel cracks and resilient fuel demand. Growth in Reliance Jio's 5G/FWA subscriber base is seen as a key earnings momentum driver. Despite near-term pressures in petrochemicals and retail segment efficiency lagging peers, the outlook remains constructive due to long-term fundamentals and strategic expansion. The New Energy segment is valued at Rs 111 per share.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:06:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699556d03ec8b0ccb20dc07e_1771394916719.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airbus Eyes India's SAF Boom: Potential Meets Pragmatic Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Airbus-Eyes-Indias-SAF-Boom-Potential-Meets-Pragmatic-Hurdles/699556c73ec8b0ccb20dc037</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Airbus-Eyes-Indias-SAF-Boom-Potential-Meets-Pragmatic-Hurdles/699556c73ec8b0ccb20dc037</guid><description>Airbus views India as a prime candidate for a global sustainable aviation fuel (SAF) hub, citing abundant agricultural resources and engineering talent. While the potential for converting crop residue into SAF is significant, pragmatic challenges related to cost-effective collection, logistical infrastructure, and competition from other feedstock uses present considerable hurdles to rapid scaling. Artificial intelligence may offer efficiency gains, but the economic case for widespread SAF adoption remains a critical factor for India's ambitious green aviation goals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:05:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699556c73ec8b0ccb20dc036_1771394913967.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auditor Flags Impex Ferro: Insolvency Deepens, Finances Unclear</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Auditor-Flags-Impex-Ferro-Insolvency-Deepens-Finances-Unclear/699555263ec8b0ccb20dbf6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Auditor-Flags-Impex-Ferro-Insolvency-Deepens-Finances-Unclear/699555263ec8b0ccb20dbf6d</guid><description>Impex Ferro Tech Limited has received a Qualified Opinion from its auditors for the December 2025 quarter, highlighting material uncertainty regarding its going concern status. The company, already undergoing Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), faces significant accounting concerns, including unprovided interest expenses, uncertain receivables, and creditor claims exceeding book values.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:59:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699555263ec8b0ccb20dbf6c_1771394456548.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silverline Tech Explores ₹80 Cr Investment for AI Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silverline-Tech-Explores-80-Cr-Investment-for-AI-Push/699554af3ec8b0ccb20dbeff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silverline-Tech-Explores-80-Cr-Investment-for-AI-Push/699554af3ec8b0ccb20dbeff</guid><description>Silverline Technologies' board has given an in-principle nod to explore a strategic investment of up to ₹80 Crore from Trueledger Technologies FZE. This proposed investment, which could result in up to a 20% equity stake and values the company at around ₹400 Crore, is aimed at bolstering Silverline's AI-led business strategy, particularly its new 'Silver AI' platform. The move comes as the company seeks to capitalize on the burgeoning artificial intelligence market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:57:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699554af3ec8b0ccb20dbefe_1771394335714.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Stocks: Mid/Small Caps Shine Amidst Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Stocks-MidSmall-Caps-Shine-Amidst-Market-Volatility/699550fc3ec8b0ccb20dbca8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Stocks-MidSmall-Caps-Shine-Amidst-Market-Volatility/699550fc3ec8b0ccb20dbca8</guid><description>Indian equity markets navigated a volatile February, characterized by the Nifty 50 index trading within an 1,800-point range but managing a 1.3% gain. Mid- and small-cap indices, however, outperformed, with the Nifty MidCap 150 and Nifty SmallCap 250 indices rising 2.5% and 2.2%, respectively. This performance divergence highlights sector-specific strength, driven by corporate earnings and individual stock news, rather than broad-based market rallies. Select companies like Torrent Pharmaceuticals, Graphite India, and AU Small Finance Bank are exhibiting significant technical strength, breaking out of consolidation phases, indicating that discerning specific stock narratives is key to generating alpha in the current market environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:41:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699550fc3ec8b0ccb20dbca7_1771393511554.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Cloud Softech Gains ISP License Amid Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Blue-Cloud-Softech-Gains-ISP-License-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/699550f73ec8b0ccb20dbc91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Blue-Cloud-Softech-Gains-ISP-License-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/699550f73ec8b0ccb20dbc91</guid><description>Blue Cloud Softech's stock saw a notable surge, exceeding 6%, following the announcement of receiving a National ISP license from India's Department of Telecommunications. This crucial authorization is intended to accelerate the company's strategic initiatives in AI-driven data centers, sovereign cloud infrastructure, and digital connectivity. The company aims to leverage this license to expand its integrated digital platform across India. Despite the positive regulatory development, the stock's valuation is approaching a point of concern for investors, with some analysts labeling it as 'very expensive' relative to its peers and historical benchmarks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:41:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699550f73ec8b0ccb20dbc90.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aeroflex Hits 52-Week High on Tech Push Amidst Market Weakness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aeroflex-Hits-52-Week-High-on-Tech-Push-Amidst-Market-Weakness/699550f13ec8b0ccb20dbc7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aeroflex-Hits-52-Week-High-on-Tech-Push-Amidst-Market-Weakness/699550f13ec8b0ccb20dbc7a</guid><description>Aeroflex Industries surged to a 52-week high of ₹231.35 on Wednesday, driven by heavy trading volumes that saw over 11 million shares change hands. The company posted record Q3FY26 revenue of ₹121.12 crore, along with its highest-ever EBITDA and profit after tax, fueled by a strategic pivot to value-added products and expansion into data center and AI liquid cooling solutions. Exports also grew a robust 30% year-on-year. ICICI Securities maintains a 'Buy' rating with a ₹245 target, highlighting the niche market entry as a significant growth driver and anticipating sustained EBITDA margins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:41:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699550f13ec8b0ccb20dbc79.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nissan Bets Big: India Revival Hinges on Ambitious SUV Blitz</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nissan-Bets-Big-India-Revival-Hinges-on-Ambitious-SUV-Blitz/6995508e3ec8b0ccb20dbb6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nissan-Bets-Big-India-Revival-Hinges-on-Ambitious-SUV-Blitz/6995508e3ec8b0ccb20dbb6a</guid><description>Nissan Motor India has initiated an aggressive product offensive, launching the seven-seater Gravite MPV and signaling plans for three new SUV models within 12 months, all aimed at a market resurgence in 2026. This strategy targets a broader market segment coverage, from ₹6 lakh to ₹20 lakh, and aims to significantly boost export volumes from India. However, the company faces an intensely competitive Indian automotive landscape and global financial pressures, including a negative P/E ratio, casting a shadow over the execution feasibility of these ambitious plans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:39:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995508e3ec8b0ccb20dbb69_1771393332633.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>E2E Networks Surges on Nvidia AI Deal; Valuation Questions Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/E2E-Networks-Surges-on-Nvidia-AI-Deal-Valuation-Questions-Linger/6995508a3ec8b0ccb20dbb50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/E2E-Networks-Surges-on-Nvidia-AI-Deal-Valuation-Questions-Linger/6995508a3ec8b0ccb20dbb50</guid><description>E2E Networks shares climbed nearly 16% to ₹2,956.20 after announcing a strategic collaboration with Nvidia to build advanced AI factories powered by Blackwell GPUs on its TIR platform. The move targets India's burgeoning AI sector, but the company faces intense competition and significant capital investment demands. Investors will watch for E2E's ability to translate this technological advancement into sustained profitable growth amidst a high valuation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:39:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995508a3ec8b0ccb20dbb4f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI 'Bubble': Value Beyond Hype or Looming Correction?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Bubble-Value-Beyond-Hype-or-Looming-Correction/699550263ec8b0ccb20dba84</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Bubble-Value-Beyond-Hype-or-Looming-Correction/699550263ec8b0ccb20dba84</guid><description>Hemant Taneja, CEO of General Catalyst, views AI's current 'bubble' as beneficial for mobilizing capital and talent, particularly for India's applied AI sector. He distinguishes this from speculative foundational AI investments. However, the Indian IT industry faces significant disruption risks from AI, with concerns about job displacement and revenue erosion for labor-intensive outsourcing models. Despite these headwinds, increased VC funding and a focus on applied solutions offer potential pathways for growth, though sustainable business models remain key.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:37:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699550263ec8b0ccb20dba83.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys AI Push Faces Deployment Gap, Margin Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Push-Faces-Deployment-Gap-Margin-Risks/69954f933ec8b0ccb20db977</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Push-Faces-Deployment-Gap-Margin-Risks/69954f933ec8b0ccb20db977</guid><description>Infosys detailed its AI-first strategy and the substantial AI services market opportunity at AI Day 2026, projecting a USD 300-400 billion market by 2030. Leveraging its Topaz platform, the company aims to move clients from experimentation to scaled deployment. However, a critical 'deployment gap' exists, with foundational model innovation outpacing enterprise readiness due to organizational complexity, legacy systems, and data issues. Concerns around AI-driven productivity impacts and increasing competitive threats loom. Motilal Oswal maintains a target price of INR 1,850, implying 33% upside, but broader market sentiment is tempered by AI disruption risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:35:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69954f933ec8b0ccb20db976.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cigarette Stocks Surge on Pricing Power Amid Excise Hikes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cigarette-Stocks-Surge-on-Pricing-Power-Amid-Excise-Hikes/69954f8f3ec8b0ccb20db960</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cigarette-Stocks-Surge-on-Pricing-Power-Amid-Excise-Hikes/69954f8f3ec8b0ccb20db960</guid><description>ITC and Godfrey Phillips India shares surged on February 18, 2026, driven by significant price increases across their product portfolios to offset recent excise duty hikes. While ITC saw gains of nearly 2% and GPI rallied over 12%, analysts like UBS maintain a 'Buy' on ITC with a revised target, citing the effective passing on of costs. However, the steep tax adjustments also raise concerns about potential volume impacts and increased illicit trade, prompting cautious outlooks from other brokerages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:35:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69954f8f3ec8b0ccb20db95f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ipca Labs: Margin Gains Fuel Buy Call Amidst Sector Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Ipca-Labs-Margin-Gains-Fuel-Buy-Call-Amidst-Sector-Shifts/69954f8d3ec8b0ccb20db949</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Ipca-Labs-Margin-Gains-Fuel-Buy-Call-Amidst-Sector-Shifts/69954f8d3ec8b0ccb20db949</guid><description>Ipca Laboratories' EBITDA surged 19% YoY to ₹5.3bn, beating estimates by 10%, alongside 400bps GMs expansion ex-Unichem, driven by API recovery and domestic formulations. Prabhudas Lilladher maintains a "Buy" with a ₹1,710 target, valuing the stock at 17x FY28E EV/EBITDA. While valuation appears attractive at ~24x FY28E PE, margin sustainability, competitive pressures, and macro factors warrant scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:35:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69954f8d3ec8b0ccb20db948_1771393111646.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MM Forgings: Analyst Upbeat, But Debt and Quality Raise Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MM-Forgings-Analyst-Upbeat-But-Debt-and-Quality-Raise-Flags/69954f873ec8b0ccb20db92f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MM-Forgings-Analyst-Upbeat-But-Debt-and-Quality-Raise-Flags/69954f873ec8b0ccb20db92f</guid><description>MM Forgings (MMFL) sees optimism from Anand Rathi, who maintains a BUY rating and raises the price target, citing projected revenue growth and an attractive valuation supported by the commercial vehicle sector's recovery. However, the company faces headwinds from a recent quality grade downgrade, increasing debt levels, and mixed historical revenue performance, demanding careful investor consideration amid sector tailwinds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:35:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69954f873ec8b0ccb20db92e_1771393037106.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shankara Buildpro Posts 29% Revenue Jump After Listing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shankara-Buildpro-Posts-29percent-Revenue-Jump-After-Listing/69954de53ec8b0ccb20db808</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shankara-Buildpro-Posts-29percent-Revenue-Jump-After-Listing/69954de53ec8b0ccb20db808</guid><description>Shankara Buildpro, newly listed after its demerger, reported a strong Q3 FY26 with overall revenue soaring 29% year-on-year, driven by its steel segment's 34% revenue growth. While the core steel volume increased substantially, the non-steel segment saw a 5% revenue dip due to market challenges. Despite exceptional items impacting the quarterly profit after tax, the company presented an optimistic outlook, targeting ₹10,000 Cr revenue by 2030 and aiming for improved EBITDA margins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:28:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69954de53ec8b0ccb20db807.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurionpro Solutions Lands Big Data Centre Project in Mumbai</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Aurionpro-Solutions-Lands-Big-Data-Centre-Project-in-Mumbai/69954c413ec8b0ccb20db6f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Aurionpro-Solutions-Lands-Big-Data-Centre-Project-in-Mumbai/69954c413ec8b0ccb20db6f0</guid><description>Aurionpro Solutions has won a significant data centre project from a major global developer in Mumbai. This high-value deal, involving design and execution of a brownfield facility within a live operational campus, is set to be completed over the next three quarters. The win underscores Aurionpro's capability in critical infrastructure delivery amidst India's rapidly expanding data centre market, fueled by hyperscaler growth and AI demands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:21:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69954c413ec8b0ccb20db6ef_1771392177282.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BCL Industries Surges on Strong Profit Growth, Ethanol Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/BCL-Industries-Surges-on-Strong-Profit-Growth-Ethanol-Focus/69954c3f3ec8b0ccb20db6da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/BCL-Industries-Surges-on-Strong-Profit-Growth-Ethanol-Focus/69954c3f3ec8b0ccb20db6da</guid><description>BCL Industries reported a robust third quarter for FY26, with consolidated profit after tax (PAT) soaring 69% year-on-year to ₹35 Crores. Earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) grew 41%, with margins expanding significantly. This performance was fueled by a strong showing in the distillery segment, particularly a 60% rise in Extra Neutral Alcohol (ENA) volumes. The company is strategically acquiring full control of Svaksha Distillery and expanding capacity, while also exiting its packaged edible oil business to streamline operations and improve working capital.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:21:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69954c3f3ec8b0ccb20db6d9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KSH International's Credit Rating Upgraded by CARE Ratings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-Internationals-Credit-Rating-Upgraded-by-CARE-Ratings/69954b7f3ec8b0ccb20db642</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-Internationals-Credit-Rating-Upgraded-by-CARE-Ratings/69954b7f3ec8b0ccb20db642</guid><description>KSH International Limited has received a significant upgrade in its credit ratings from CARE Ratings. The company's long-term and short-term bank facilities have been upgraded to 'CARE A; Stable' and 'CARE A1' respectively. This positive rating action follows KSH International's robust audited financial performance for FY2024-25 and strong unaudited results for Q3FY2025-26, which saw substantial revenue growth and significant debt reduction. The 'Stable' outlook indicates confidence in the company's ongoing financial health and operational capabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:17:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69954b7f3ec8b0ccb20db641_1771391938410.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DBL Secures Gujarat Contracts Amidst Analyst Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DBL-Secures-Gujarat-Contracts-Amidst-Analyst-Caution/69954a643ec8b0ccb20db57b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DBL-Secures-Gujarat-Contracts-Amidst-Analyst-Caution/69954a643ec8b0ccb20db57b</guid><description>Dilip Buildcon Limited (DBL) has secured two significant infrastructure projects in Gujarat, totaling ₹1,370.02 crore, bolstering its order book to ₹29,372 crore. The company's stock has rebounded 22% from its 52-week low. However, this performance contrasts with a prevailing 'Sell' consensus among analysts and concerns over margins and growth prospects. DBL's valuation, marked by a low P/E ratio, appears attractive, but potential investors must weigh this against reported operational weaknesses and sector-wide headwinds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:13:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69954a643ec8b0ccb20db57a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Surges Amid Geopolitical Fears; Indian IT Faces AI Disruption</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Gold-Surges-Amid-Geopolitical-Fears-Indian-IT-Faces-AI-Disruption/699549f43ec8b0ccb20db4c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Gold-Surges-Amid-Geopolitical-Fears-Indian-IT-Faces-AI-Disruption/699549f43ec8b0ccb20db4c8</guid><description>Gold prices continue their ascent, trading near $4,934 per ounce on February 18, 2026, propelled by persistent geopolitical tensions and substantial central bank accumulation. Meanwhile, the Indian IT sector grapples with significant sell-offs, with the Nifty IT index down approximately 19% from its February peak, as fears escalate over AI's potential to automate core services. Despite a recent sector-wide rebound, the long-term impact of AI on traditional IT business models remains a critical focus for investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:11:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699549f43ec8b0ccb20db4c7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Stocks Surge on Policy Support, But Margin Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Stocks-Surge-on-Policy-Support-But-Margin-Risks-Loom/6995497a3ec8b0ccb20db3f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Stocks-Surge-on-Policy-Support-But-Margin-Risks-Loom/6995497a3ec8b0ccb20db3f0</guid><description>Major Indian steel companies like Tata Steel, JSW Steel, SAIL, and Jindal Steel saw share prices climb 1-2% on Wednesday, nearing 52-week highs. This rally is underpinned by government safeguard duties and amendments to the MMDR Act, bolstering domestic producers against global oversupply. However, persistent coking coal cost increases and a surplus of Chinese steel exports present significant margin risks. Analysts remain divided, with some anticipating structural rerating while others caution about the sustainability of current valuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:09:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995497a3ec8b0ccb20db3ef_1771391480964.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Trade Realignment: Investor Shifts Amid Tariffs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Global-Trade-Realignment-Investor-Shifts-Amid-Tariffs/699549793ec8b0ccb20db3d9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Global-Trade-Realignment-Investor-Shifts-Amid-Tariffs/699549793ec8b0ccb20db3d9</guid><description>Global trade dynamics are undergoing a significant realignment, driven by escalating US tariffs and a strategic pivot by Europe towards the Indo-Pacific region. This geopolitical recalibration is spurring growth in emerging markets, particularly in Asia, and necessitating a strategic reassessment of investment portfolios. Investors are increasingly leveraging sector rotation strategies to capitalize on evolving global value chains and mitigate risks from fragmented supply networks. The economic outlook for 2026 anticipates moderate global growth, easing inflation, but persistent geopolitical and trade policy uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 05:09:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699549793ec8b0ccb20db3d8_1771391523679.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>