<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate><item><title>US Solar Tariffs: Waaree &amp; Premier Insulated, Growth Outlook Intact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/US-Solar-Tariffs-Waaree-and-Premier-Insulated-Growth-Outlook-Intact/699fcd06cd95b9dc08f995a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/US-Solar-Tariffs-Waaree-and-Premier-Insulated-Growth-Outlook-Intact/699fcd06cd95b9dc08f995a7</guid><description>US preliminary countervailing duties of 126% on Indian solar imports triggered sharp stock declines for Waaree Energies and Premier Energies. However, an analysis reveals that Waaree's US module sales do not utilize India-made cells, thus avoiding the direct tariff. Premier Energies, with minimal overseas revenue, is largely shielded. Motilal Oswal maintains price targets implying significant upside for both, citing resilient business models and robust US market demand driven by AI and data centers. While sector sentiment soured, fundamental insulation remains key.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:33:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fcd06cd95b9dc08f995a6_1772080461243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CreditAccess Grameen: Growth Hype Faces Regulatory Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CreditAccess-Grameen-Growth-Hype-Faces-Regulatory-Headwinds/699fcb24cd95b9dc08f9949f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CreditAccess-Grameen-Growth-Hype-Faces-Regulatory-Headwinds/699fcb24cd95b9dc08f9949f</guid><description>CreditAccess Grameen (CAGR) is poised for a growth trajectory, according to Motilal Oswal, citing retail diversification and risk discipline. However, the microfinance sector is under significant regulatory scrutiny and experiencing loan book contraction. While CAGR's valuation appears reasonable relative to its peers, concerns regarding sustainable margin resilience and funding access for smaller players loom, potentially impacting future reratings. The company's P/E of approximately 42.22x is a premium compared to many peers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:25:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fcb24cd95b9dc08f9949e_1772080036699.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Balu Forge Lands 5-Yr NATO Ammo Shells Deal; Supply Starts April '26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balu-Forge-Lands-5-Yr-NATO-Ammo-Shells-Deal-Supply-Starts-April-26/699fc8e1cd95b9dc08f99326</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balu-Forge-Lands-5-Yr-NATO-Ammo-Shells-Deal-Supply-Starts-April-26/699fc8e1cd95b9dc08f99326</guid><description>Balu Forge Industries has secured a significant 5-year Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) with a NATO-affiliated entity to supply empty shells for large caliber ammunition. Starting April 2026, the company will supply 40,000 units monthly, valued at USD 315 each. This substantial order necessitates capacity expansion beyond current levels, marking a pivotal entry into the defence consumable space.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:15:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc8e1cd95b9dc08f99325_1772079440412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto Rebound Faces Hurdles Amid ETF Flux and Macro Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Crypto-Rebound-Faces-Hurdles-Amid-ETF-Flux-and-Macro-Uncertainty/699fc858cd95b9dc08f99218</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Crypto-Rebound-Faces-Hurdles-Amid-ETF-Flux-and-Macro-Uncertainty/699fc858cd95b9dc08f99218</guid><description>The cryptocurrency market staged a strong recovery, driven by significant spot Bitcoin ETF inflows and short liquidations, pushing Bitcoin towards $68,000 and Ethereum past $2,000. However, this rally is encountering critical resistance zones and mixed macroeconomic indicators. Despite gains in altcoins like Solana and BNB, the sustainability of the advance is questionable, hinging on continued institutional demand, overcoming key technical barriers, and navigating upcoming options expiries amidst an environment of cautious investor sentiment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:13:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc858cd95b9dc08f99217_1772079353402.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LG Electronics: Nomura Bets on Rebound Amidst Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-Electronics-Nomura-Bets-on-Rebound-Amidst-Execution-Hurdles/699fc855cd95b9dc08f99201</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-Electronics-Nomura-Bets-on-Rebound-Amidst-Execution-Hurdles/699fc855cd95b9dc08f99201</guid><description>Nomura has identified LG Electronics as a preferred pick in consumer durables, initiating coverage with a 'Buy' rating and a target of ₹1,836. The brokerage anticipates significant growth driven by consumption recovery, a strong summer season, and expanding exports, projecting 14% revenue growth in FY27 and a 31% EPS CAGR over FY26-28. However, the company recently reported a net loss for Q4 2025, and its strategy to balance premium offerings with an 'Essential' affordable brand, coupled with aggressive export targets, presents execution risks. LG Electronics's current P/E of approximately 12.9 is competitive against peers like Samsung (19.70), but the path to margin expansion and sustained growth requires navigating a dynamic market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:13:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc855cd95b9dc08f99200_1772079374847.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Canara HSBC Life: Growth Story Meets Margin Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Canara-HSBC-Life-Growth-Story-Meets-Margin-Reality/699fc852cd95b9dc08f991ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Canara-HSBC-Life-Growth-Story-Meets-Margin-Reality/699fc852cd95b9dc08f991ea</guid><description>Antique Stock Broking has launched coverage on Canara HSBC Life Insurance Company with a 'Buy' rating and a target price of ₹190, citing strong growth prospects. The company has demonstrated a high individual weighted premium income (WPI) CAGR of 21% over FY15-25, outpacing industry averages. However, its value of new business (VNB) margins, currently around 19.7%, trail those of larger peers. A significant portion of its business, approximately 85-92%, is derived from its bancassurance channel, primarily through Canara Bank and HSBC. This reliance, coupled with a smaller contribution from higher-margin protection products, presents a complex risk-reward profile.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:13:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc852cd95b9dc08f991e9_1772079375233.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sanofi India Shares Slump Amidst Third Quarter Revenue Decline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sanofi-India-Shares-Slump-Amidst-Third-Quarter-Revenue-Decline/699fc7ddcd95b9dc08f99116</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sanofi-India-Shares-Slump-Amidst-Third-Quarter-Revenue-Decline/699fc7ddcd95b9dc08f99116</guid><description>Sanofi India's stock fell over 4% on February 16, 2026, following a weak December quarter earnings report. Net profit dropped 32% year-on-year to ₹61.7 crore, while revenue contracted 18% to ₹420 crore, marking the third consecutive quarter of revenue decline. Operating margins compressed to 21.6%, the lowest since December 2023. This performance contrasts with the broader Indian pharmaceutical sector's expected growth, signaling company-specific headwinds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:11:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc7ddcd95b9dc08f99115_1772079145943.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Home First Finance Shares Slide Amidst Promoter Stake Sale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Home-First-Finance-Shares-Slide-Amidst-Promoter-Stake-Sale/699fc7dbcd95b9dc08f990fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Home-First-Finance-Shares-Slide-Amidst-Promoter-Stake-Sale/699fc7dbcd95b9dc08f990fc</guid><description>Home First Finance Company India Ltd. shares dropped approximately 6% on Thursday, February 26, following a substantial block deal of 5.4% equity worth ₹662.6 crore. This sale, involving promoter entities like True North Fund V LLP and Aether (Mauritius) Ltd., occurred despite the company reporting a robust 44% year-on-year increase in net profit to ₹140.2 crore for the December quarter. The transaction signals a notable shift in significant ownership stakes, prompting investor caution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc7dbcd95b9dc08f990fb_1772079226344.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Record Uncertainty Meets Market Resilience: Is Stability Sustainable?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Record-Uncertainty-Meets-Market-Resilience-Is-Stability-Sustainable/699fc739cd95b9dc08f98fd8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Record-Uncertainty-Meets-Market-Resilience-Is-Stability-Sustainable/699fc739cd95b9dc08f98fd8</guid><description>Global uncertainty has surged to an unprecedented 106,862 in February 2026, driven by volatile US economic policies and trade disputes, notably following a Supreme Court ruling on tariffs. Despite this historic backdrop, equity markets have demonstrated surprising resilience, fueled by investor confidence in central bank backstops, robust corporate earnings, and the persistent narrative of AI's long-term potential. However, this disconnect signals underlying fragility, with analysts forecasting sub-trend global growth and warning of the structural nature of current policy instability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:08:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc739cd95b9dc08f98fd7_1772079028034.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Solar Stocks Rebound as Trade Nuance Eases Tariff Fear</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Indian-Solar-Stocks-Rebound-as-Trade-Nuance-Eases-Tariff-Fear/699fc6eecd95b9dc08f98f66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Indian-Solar-Stocks-Rebound-as-Trade-Nuance-Eases-Tariff-Fear/699fc6eecd95b9dc08f98f66</guid><description>Indian solar stocks staged a rebound on Thursday, paring initial sharp losses triggered by the US imposing preliminary countervailing duties. Investor sentiment improved as brokerages clarified the 126% duties primarily affect modules using India-made solar cells, a segment Waaree Energies and Premier Energies claim to largely avoid. However, the reliance on US export markets and potential for further trade actions introduce persistent headwinds. Waaree Energies traded up near ₹2,700, while Premier Energies saw modest gains, as the market assessed the nuanced impact of the US decision.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:07:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc6eecd95b9dc08f98f65_1772078983828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Proterial Bets Big on India's Energy Future with Steel Plant</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Proterial-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Energy-Future-with-Steel-Plant/699fc60dcd95b9dc08f98ddb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Proterial-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Energy-Future-with-Steel-Plant/699fc60dcd95b9dc08f98ddb</guid><description>Proterial India is launching India's first amorphous electrical steel plant with a Rs 1,350 crore investment, targeting significant reductions in transformer energy losses. This strategic move aligns with India's 'Make in India' and Production Linked Incentive (PLI) schemes, positioning the company to capitalize on the nation's escalating demand for efficient energy infrastructure amid a growing competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:03:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc60dcd95b9dc08f98dda_1772078721113.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Rally on Geopolitical Fears Amid Policy Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rally-on-Geopolitical-Fears-Amid-Policy-Uncertainty/699fc58dcd95b9dc08f98d29</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rally-on-Geopolitical-Fears-Amid-Policy-Uncertainty/699fc58dcd95b9dc08f98d29</guid><description>Gold and silver prices are advancing, buoyed by escalating geopolitical tensions involving US-Iran talks and renewed tariff uncertainty following a Supreme Court ruling. Investors are flocking to these safe-haven assets as the US Dollar Index softens. However, a complex Federal Reserve policy outlook, with inflation moderating but remaining above target, creates a bifurcated market narrative, with analysts offering wildly divergent price forecasts for the remainder of 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:01:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc58dcd95b9dc08f98d28_1772078630135.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks Boost Bond Holdings as Yields Rise, Regulatory Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Boost-Bond-Holdings-as-Yields-Rise-Regulatory-Push/699fc583cd95b9dc08f98d0e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Boost-Bond-Holdings-as-Yields-Rise-Regulatory-Push/699fc583cd95b9dc08f98d0e</guid><description>Indian banks are accelerating government bond purchases, driven by a confluence of higher yields and proximity to regulatory minimums. February saw state-owned lenders acquire ₹225.8 billion ($2.5 billion) in net purchases, the largest monthly volume since 2006. This marks a strategic shift from a year of net selling. The increased demand offers crucial support to India's debt market, which has contended with subdued investor appetite. Analysts expect this activity to push down benchmark yields, as current rates offer an attractive spread over the policy rate.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:01:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc583cd95b9dc08f98d0d_1772078626635.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashapura Minechem: Promoter Trust Acquires 1.75% Stake Via Off-Market Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ashapura-Minechem-Promoter-Trust-Acquires-175percent-Stake-Via-Off-Market-Deal/699fc493cd95b9dc08f98c0f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ashapura-Minechem-Promoter-Trust-Acquires-175percent-Stake-Via-Off-Market-Deal/699fc493cd95b9dc08f98c0f</guid><description>Manan Chetan Shah Family Trust has acquired a 1.75% stake in Ashapura Minechem Limited through an off-market transaction for ₹0 consideration. This move, executed on February 24, 2026, aims to streamline promoter family succession and welfare, leveraging a SEBI exemption order. The company's total equity share capital remains unchanged.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:57:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc493cd95b9dc08f98c0e_1772078332596.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economy: Growth Surge Amidst Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-Growth-Surge-Amidst-Global-Headwinds/699fc3b4cd95b9dc08f98ad1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-Growth-Surge-Amidst-Global-Headwinds/699fc3b4cd95b9dc08f98ad1</guid><description>India's economic trajectory appears strong, with Motilal Oswal forecasting 7.8% real GDP growth for FY26, exceeding official estimates. This optimism is bolstered by sustained services sector expansion and the ripple effects of recent GST rate cuts, which are expected to stimulate demand across various industries. Analysts anticipate inflation to remain within target, leading to stable interest rates through FY27. However, global geopolitical tensions, trade policy shifts, and potential capital flow volatility present significant risks that temper the otherwise bullish outlook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:53:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc3b4cd95b9dc08f98ad0_1772078118226.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Elxsi: Recovery Forecasted, Valuation Questions Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Tata-Elxsi-Recovery-Forecasted-Valuation-Questions-Linger/699fc39fcd95b9dc08f98ab6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Tata-Elxsi-Recovery-Forecasted-Valuation-Questions-Linger/699fc39fcd95b9dc08f98ab6</guid><description>HDFC Securities projects Tata Elxsi's return to low double-digit growth in FY27E, driven by its automotive vertical and core engineering services. However, the brokerage trimmed revenue and EPS forecasts, leading to a revised P/E multiple. Tata Elxsi trades at a significant valuation premium compared to peers like Cyient and L&amp;T Technology Services, raising questions about margin sustainability and growth prospects amidst a broader analyst consensus leaning towards 'Underperform'.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:53:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc39fcd95b9dc08f98ab5_1772078072516.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Smartworks Leases 1.5L Sq Ft Jaipur Space; ₹25 Cr Expansion Planned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Smartworks-Leases-15L-Sq-Ft-Jaipur-Space-25-Cr-Expansion-Planned/699fc32acd95b9dc08f989fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Smartworks-Leases-15L-Sq-Ft-Jaipur-Space-25-Cr-Expansion-Planned/699fc32acd95b9dc08f989fe</guid><description>Smartworks Coworking is leasing 1,49,560 sq ft in Jaipur for ₹25 crore, aiming for April 2026 completion. This expansion boosts its operational capacity by nearly 1.5 lakh sq ft, signalling demand in India's flexible workspace sector. The move supports the company's growth strategy and expands its national footprint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:51:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc32acd95b9dc08f989fd_1772078014949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Websol Energy bags ₹172 Cr solar orders; insulated from US tariffs.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Websol-Energy-bags-172-Cr-solar-orders-insulated-from-US-tariffs/699fc329cd95b9dc08f989e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Websol-Energy-bags-172-Cr-solar-orders-insulated-from-US-tariffs/699fc329cd95b9dc08f989e8</guid><description>Websol Energy has secured three purchase orders for solar modules worth ₹172 crore, covering 85.5 MW capacity, to be delivered by May 2026. The company stated that ongoing US solar tariffs will not affect its operations, as it has no exports to the US market, distinguishing it from broader sector pressures. This comes amid a recent financial turnaround and capacity expansion drive by the company.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc329cd95b9dc08f989e7_1772077969605.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Sector: Emkay's 'Overweight' Call Faces Growth Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Sector-Emkays-Overweight-Call-Faces-Growth-Headwinds/699fc0efcd95b9dc08f98854</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Sector-Emkays-Overweight-Call-Faces-Growth-Headwinds/699fc0efcd95b9dc08f98854</guid><description>Emkay Global Financial Services has shifted to an 'Overweight' stance on the Indian IT sector, identifying attractive entry points post-AI-driven selloffs. While acknowledging AI's potential to boost productivity and create new use cases, the brokerage projects long-term structural growth below 5% in dollar terms. This opportunistic call favors large-cap stocks like Infosys and HCL Tech over Mphasis, suggesting a strategy focused on lower risk rather than broad sector re-rating. The sector has seen a significant February decline, with the Nifty IT index down over 20%, creating valuation comfort but also highlighting underlying sector challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:41:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc0efcd95b9dc08f98853_1772077418657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Faces Downgrade as Cash Burn and Ops Woes Mount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Faces-Downgrade-as-Cash-Burn-and-Ops-Woes-Mount/699fc05dcd95b9dc08f98790</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Faces-Downgrade-as-Cash-Burn-and-Ops-Woes-Mount/699fc05dcd95b9dc08f98790</guid><description>Goldman Sachs downgraded Ola Electric to 'Neutral' with a slashed price target, citing reduced revenue forecasts and market share expectations. The brokerage highlighted significant cash burn, necessitating future fundraising, and identified critical operational improvements needed, including servicing and product reliability. This aligns with an overwhelmingly bearish analyst sentiment and the company's 84% stock decline from its peak, signaling deep-seated challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:39:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fc05dcd95b9dc08f9878f_1772077433595.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aptus Value Housing: Margin Strength Supports Value Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aptus-Value-Housing-Margin-Strength-Supports-Value-Play/699fbf67cd95b9dc08f9868b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aptus-Value-Housing-Margin-Strength-Supports-Value-Play/699fbf67cd95b9dc08f9868b</guid><description>Aptus Value Housing Finance faces market headwinds from tepid growth and rising credit costs, a sector-wide issue. Despite this, the company maintains robust profitability and industry-leading return ratios, with a strategic shift towards higher-ticket loans. Trading at a depressed valuation with a P/E around 13.9x, it presents an attractive risk-reward profile for investors anticipating growth normalization and potential stock re-rating.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:35:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fbf67cd95b9dc08f9868a_1772077223479.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tejas Networks Partners NEC for 5G Radio Manufacturing, Boosts Global Supply Chain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tejas-Networks-Partners-NEC-for-5G-Radio-Manufacturing-Boosts-Global-Supply-Chain/699fbd8bcd95b9dc08f98541</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tejas-Networks-Partners-NEC-for-5G-Radio-Manufacturing-Boosts-Global-Supply-Chain/699fbd8bcd95b9dc08f98541</guid><description>Tejas Networks has entered into a significant agreement with Japan's NEC Corporation to manufacture and supply 5G Massive MIMO radios. This strategic partnership is designed to diversify the global supply chain, enhance resilience for customers, and foster co-creation of advanced 5G solutions. The deal marks an expansion of Tejas Networks' international business and strengthens its position in the global telecom equipment market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:27:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fbd8bcd95b9dc08f98540_1772076483374.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sector Breakouts: Nuvama Analyst Picks Tata Motors, JSW Steel, Colgate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Sector-Breakouts-Nuvama-Analyst-Picks-Tata-Motors-JSW-Steel-Colgate/699fbca3cd95b9dc08f98462</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Sector-Breakouts-Nuvama-Analyst-Picks-Tata-Motors-JSW-Steel-Colgate/699fbca3cd95b9dc08f98462</guid><description>Nuvama's Aakash K Hindocha has recommended three stocks for buying on February 26, 2026: Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (₹382), Colgate-Palmolive (India) (₹2270), and JSW Steel (₹1275). These selections are driven by technical breakouts and sector tailwinds. Tata Motors shows a structural shift, Colgate-Palmolive is breaking out of a corrective channel, and JSW Steel is nearing record highs amid supportive global steel cues. The broader Nifty index is range-bound, while Bank Nifty shows underlying strength.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:23:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fbca3cd95b9dc08f98461_1772076328047.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Organic Recycling Systems inks MoU for Membrane-Based CBG Tech Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Organic-Recycling-Systems-inks-MoU-for-Membrane-Based-CBG-Tech-Boost/699fbb30cd95b9dc08f98359</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Organic-Recycling-Systems-inks-MoU-for-Membrane-Based-CBG-Tech-Boost/699fbb30cd95b9dc08f98359</guid><description>Organic Recycling Systems Limited (ORSL) has signed a strategic Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with SLPP Re-New LLP to bolster Compressed Bio-Gas (CBG) solutions across India. The collaboration focuses on integrating SLPP's advanced membrane purification technology with ORSL's EPC and O&amp;M capabilities, aiming to jointly bid for projects and expand ORSL's clean energy portfolio.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fbb30cd95b9dc08f98358_1772075922789.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Foreign Capital Flocks to India: Value &amp; Earnings Drive Inflows Amid AI Tech Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Foreign-Capital-Flocks-to-India-Value-and-Earnings-Drive-Inflows-Amid-AI-Tech-Woes/699fb8edcd95b9dc08f9806a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Foreign-Capital-Flocks-to-India-Value-and-Earnings-Drive-Inflows-Amid-AI-Tech-Woes/699fb8edcd95b9dc08f9806a</guid><description>Foreign capital is returning to Indian equities in February 2026, outpacing domestic buying for the first time in 17 months, driven by improving earnings momentum and more attractive valuations compared to peers like China. However, significant headwinds persist, particularly the impact of artificial intelligence on the IT sector, which has seen sharp corrections. While capital goods and financial services sectors show strength, investors maintain a cautious stance amidst ongoing global economic uncertainties and sector-specific risks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:07:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb8edcd95b9dc08f98069_1772075552186.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Sector Downgrades Spark Valuation Debate Amid AI Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Sector-Downgrades-Spark-Valuation-Debate-Amid-AI-Shift/699fb8eacd95b9dc08f98053</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Sector-Downgrades-Spark-Valuation-Debate-Amid-AI-Shift/699fb8eacd95b9dc08f98053</guid><description>Brokerages Antique Stock Broking and Jefferies have downgraded major Indian IT firms, including Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) and HCL Technologies (HCLTech), citing AI disruption and hyperscaler capital expenditure shifts. Despite sector-wide downgrades and a significant Nifty IT index decline, a notable valuation disconnect is emerging. While immediate pressures are evident, the market is assessing whether current stock prices adequately reflect the potential for these IT giants to capitalize on the accelerating global AI investment wave and pivot towards higher-value services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:07:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb8eacd95b9dc08f98052_1772075528609.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Job Tsunami: India Faces Costly Adaptation Amid Inequality Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AIs-Job-Tsunami-India-Faces-Costly-Adaptation-Amid-Inequality-Risks/699fb8e4cd95b9dc08f9803c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AIs-Job-Tsunami-India-Faces-Costly-Adaptation-Amid-Inequality-Risks/699fb8e4cd95b9dc08f9803c</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund warns Artificial Intelligence could impact 40% of jobs globally, with emerging economies like India facing significant labor displacement. While India aims for AI leadership with its "AI for All" strategy and initiatives like the IndiaAI Mission, the nation confronts an immense adaptation challenge. The cost of retraining its vast youth population, coupled with persistent digital divides and the risk of exacerbating wealth inequality, presents a complex economic tightrope, demanding urgent policy intervention beyond just job preservation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:07:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb8e4cd95b9dc08f9803b_1772075671944.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Shares Slump on Fraud Fears, BofA Downgrades</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Shares-Slump-on-Fraud-Fears-BofA-Downgrades/699fb8e4cd95b9dc08f98029</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Shares-Slump-on-Fraud-Fears-BofA-Downgrades/699fb8e4cd95b9dc08f98029</guid><description>IDFC First Bank shares plunged after disclosing a ₹590 crore fraud, prompting BofA Securities to downgrade its rating to 'neutral' and slash its price target. The incident has stoked fears of CASA disruption and increased funding costs, leading to significant stock depreciation and analyst revisions of earnings estimates. While management insists the issue is isolated, market reaction indicates a loss of confidence regarding internal controls and the potential impact on future growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:07:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb8e4cd95b9dc08f98028_1772075411817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Near Record High Amid Bullish Forecasts; Risks Loom?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Near-Record-High-Amid-Bullish-Forecasts-Risks-Loom/699fb8dfcd95b9dc08f9800e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Near-Record-High-Amid-Bullish-Forecasts-Risks-Loom/699fb8dfcd95b9dc08f9800e</guid><description>State Bank of India's stock has surged, touching new highs near ₹1,235 as of late February 2026. CLSA maintains an 'Outperform' rating with a ₹1,275 price target, citing strong long-term compounding potential. The bank's Q3 FY26 results showcased a record profit of ₹21,028 crore, a 24.5% year-on-year increase, alongside a raised credit growth outlook to 13-15%. Despite this optimism, the stock's recent consolidation and a declining liquidity coverage ratio merit closer examination against its peer group.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:07:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb8dfcd95b9dc08f9800d_1772075369913.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UBS Bullish on PFL, But Valuation Divide Sparks Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UBS-Bullish-on-PFL-But-Valuation-Divide-Sparks-Debate/699fb8d8cd95b9dc08f97ff7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UBS-Bullish-on-PFL-But-Valuation-Divide-Sparks-Debate/699fb8d8cd95b9dc08f97ff7</guid><description>UBS has launched coverage on Poonawalla Fincorp with a 'buy' recommendation and a ₹640 price target, citing strong management and growth prospects in loan against property and gold loans. However, this optimism is met with a divided analyst consensus, featuring an equal split between 'buy' and 'sell' ratings. Persistent concerns over Poonawalla Fincorp's high valuation multiples and recent profitability challenges contrast sharply with UBS's forward-looking growth projections, creating a complex investment narrative.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:07:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb8d8cd95b9dc08f97ff6_1772075523346.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Renaissance Global Boosts FY27 PAT Forecast on D2C Brand Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Renaissance-Global-Boosts-FY27-PAT-Forecast-on-D2C-Brand-Strategy/699fb7edcd95b9dc08f97ed1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Renaissance-Global-Boosts-FY27-PAT-Forecast-on-D2C-Brand-Strategy/699fb7edcd95b9dc08f97ed1</guid><description>Renaissance Global Limited has raised its FY27 profit forecast to ₹110-₹125.5 Crore, driven by a strategic pivot to a brand-led Direct-to-Consumer (D2C) model. The company is leveraging owned and licensed brands, alongside acquisitions, to capture higher margins and expand market reach, moving away from its traditional B2B manufacturing base.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 03:03:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb7edcd95b9dc08f97ed0_1772075136129.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Solar Industries: Defence Pivot &amp; Record Orders, But Valuation Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Solar-Industries-Defence-Pivot-and-Record-Orders-But-Valuation-Risks-Loom/699fb4b1cd95b9dc08f97d1d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Solar-Industries-Defence-Pivot-and-Record-Orders-But-Valuation-Risks-Loom/699fb4b1cd95b9dc08f97d1d</guid><description>Solar Industries reported robust Q3FY26 results, driven by its defence segment's 72% revenue growth and a record order book exceeding ₹21,000 crore. The pivot to defence, including 155mm shell production, positions it amid global shortages. However, the stock trades at a premium valuation (P/E ~82x), above its historical median, raising questions about future execution and competitive pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:49:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb4b1cd95b9dc08f97d1c_1772074311601.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ortin Global Open Offer: Satija bids 26% stake at ₹14.65; ₹3.1 Cr deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ortin-Global-Open-Offer-Satija-bids-26percent-stake-at-1465-31-Cr-deal/699fb428cd95b9dc08f97caa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ortin-Global-Open-Offer-Satija-bids-26percent-stake-at-1465-31-Cr-deal/699fb428cd95b9dc08f97caa</guid><description>Mr. Parveen Satija has launched a mandatory open offer to acquire 26% of Ortin Global Limited's voting capital at ₹14.65 per share, valuing the deal at approximately ₹3.10 Crores. The offer, set to run from April 10 to April 24, 2026, aims to secure management control and drive future business expansion, potentially positioning Mr. Satija as the new promoter. This move signals a significant shift in the company's ownership structure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:47:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb428cd95b9dc08f97ca9_1772074158261.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Karur Vysya Bank Joins Global Investor Meet, Reaffirms Disclosure Policy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Karur-Vysya-Bank-Joins-Global-Investor-Meet-Reaffirms-Disclosure-Policy/699fb339cd95b9dc08f97c18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Karur-Vysya-Bank-Joins-Global-Investor-Meet-Reaffirms-Disclosure-Policy/699fb339cd95b9dc08f97c18</guid><description>Karur Vysya Bank's top management participated in the 17th Enterprising India Global Investors' meet on February 25, 2026. The bank assured that only publicly available information was shared, adhering to regulatory guidance and ensuring no Unpublished Price Sensitive Information (UPSI) was disclosed. This participation underscores the bank's commitment to transparent investor engagement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:43:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb339cd95b9dc08f97c17_1772074246342.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Piramal Finance Long-Term Debt Rating Upgraded to CARE AA+; Stable by CARE</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Piramal-Finance-Long-Term-Debt-Rating-Upgraded-to-CARE-AA-Stable-by-CARE/699fb1d0cd95b9dc08f97b4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Piramal-Finance-Long-Term-Debt-Rating-Upgraded-to-CARE-AA-Stable-by-CARE/699fb1d0cd95b9dc08f97b4a</guid><description>CARE Ratings has upgraded Piramal Finance's long-term bank facilities and debentures to 'CARE AA+; Stable'. This follows similar positive ratings from CRISIL and S&amp;P Global. The upgrade reflects improved business stability, a steady reduction of legacy exposures, and a significant shift towards a retail-led loan portfolio.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:37:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb1d0cd95b9dc08f97b49_1772073529419.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GlobalFoundries Expands Kolkata Design Hub Amid India's Chip Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GlobalFoundries-Expands-Kolkata-Design-Hub-Amid-Indias-Chip-Ambitions/699fb15ccd95b9dc08f97aab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GlobalFoundries-Expands-Kolkata-Design-Hub-Amid-Indias-Chip-Ambitions/699fb15ccd95b9dc08f97aab</guid><description>GlobalFoundries is expanding its design and testing center in Kolkata, India, occupying 12,000 sq. ft. within the STPI hub. The move focuses on advanced technologies like Gallium Nitride (GaN) and RF design, aligning with India's ambitious semiconductor mission. This expansion signifies deeper US-India tech ties and aims to bolster the nation's burgeoning chip ecosystem, though significant infrastructure and talent challenges persist in India's pursuit of domestic fabrication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fb15ccd95b9dc08f97aaa_1772073381020.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Debt Record: Sovereign Leverage Surges Amidst Moderate Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Debt-Record-Sovereign-Leverage-Surges-Amidst-Moderate-Growth/699faa29cd95b9dc08f95e30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Debt-Record-Sovereign-Leverage-Surges-Amidst-Moderate-Growth/699faa29cd95b9dc08f95e30</guid><description>Global debt surged to a record $348 trillion in 2025, with government borrowing accounting for the bulk of the nearly $29 trillion increase. This marks a significant shift from private sector debt, leaving global balance sheets more exposed to interest rate shifts and investor sentiment. While bond markets show firm demand, moderate global growth projections present challenges in diluting rising debt-to-GDP ratios, particularly in emerging markets facing record refinancing burdens.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:04:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699faa29cd95b9dc08f95e2f_1772071586599.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JPM Boosts Gold Forecast Amid Demand Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/JPM-Boosts-Gold-Forecast-Amid-Demand-Surge/699fa9e2cd95b9dc08f95db8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/JPM-Boosts-Gold-Forecast-Amid-Demand-Surge/699fa9e2cd95b9dc08f95db8</guid><description>JPMorgan Chase has increased its long-term gold price forecast to $4,500 per ounce and maintains a projection of $6,300 per ounce by the end of 2026. This upward revision is driven by persistent institutional demand, strategic portfolio diversification, and continued central bank purchases. While gold has seen substantial gains, silver presents a more mixed outlook, facing near-term pressures despite optimistic long-term potential. Gold prices traded around $5,180 per ounce on February 26, 2026, up 0.41% from the previous day, while spot silver was trading near $90.70 per ounce. The gold-to-silver ratio has compressed significantly, falling to approximately 59:1 by mid-February 2026, indicating silver's strong outperformance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:03:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fa9e2cd95b9dc08f95db7_1772071536957.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manappuram Finance: CEO Leave Sparks Governance Fears Amid Bain Capital Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-CEO-Leave-Sparks-Governance-Fears-Amid-Bain-Capital-Deal/699fa9d8cd95b9dc08f95da1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-CEO-Leave-Sparks-Governance-Fears-Amid-Bain-Capital-Deal/699fa9d8cd95b9dc08f95da1</guid><description>Manappuram Finance shares are under scrutiny following CEO Deepak Reddy's unexpected medical leave, set to last 90-120 days. This leadership void emerges precisely as the company secures final RBI approval for Bain Capital's up to 41.66% stake acquisition, a deal valued at approximately ₹4,385 crore. The timing introduces significant governance and execution risks, potentially complicating the integration of new promoters and adherence to stringent regulatory conditions imposed by the RBI.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:03:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fa9d8cd95b9dc08f95da0_1772071546214.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Rally Fuels Indian Open Amidst FII Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Rally-Fuels-Indian-Open-Amidst-FII-Caution/699fa831cd95b9dc08f95be7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Rally-Fuels-Indian-Open-Amidst-FII-Caution/699fa831cd95b9dc08f95be7</guid><description>Indian markets are poised for a positive opening, mirroring robust global gains. GIFT Nifty signals stability. Despite foreign investor net selling ₹103 crore on Feb 24, domestic institutions aggressively bought shares worth ₹3,161 crore. Oil and gold prices edged higher, while the US dollar index dipped.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:56:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fa831cd95b9dc08f95be6_1772071202745.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>