<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:30:17 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's 2026 Budget: Regional Growth Push Faces Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Budget-Regional-Growth-Push-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/69869350b81b2b81dcfb1c76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Budget-Regional-Growth-Push-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/69869350b81b2b81dcfb1c76</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 signals a strategic shift from metro-centric growth to a regionally grounded economic architecture. While prioritizing connectivity and empowering smaller cities, the success hinges critically on overcoming implementation hurdles, securing private sector investment, and fostering local capabilities. This transition demands sustained effort and place-based strategies to unlock nationwide economic potential beyond major urban hubs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Defense Bets: Elgi, LMW Valuations Face Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defense-Bets-Elgi-LMW-Valuations-Face-Scrutiny/69868f2ab81b2b81dcfb1904</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defense-Bets-Elgi-LMW-Valuations-Face-Scrutiny/69868f2ab81b2b81dcfb1904</guid><description>India's industrial stalwarts Elgi Equipments and Lakshmi Machine Works (LMW) are increasingly aligning with defense and aerospace ambitions. While investor Nemish Shah has significant stakes in both, their recent stock surges are being questioned against ongoing cyclical vulnerabilities and competitive pressures. Elgi's move into high-pressure naval compressors and LMW's role in fighter jet components are driving valuations, but the market may be overlooking inherent sector risks and the disparity between their core and emergent businesses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868f2ab81b2b81dcfb1903.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Jewellery Sector: Growth Amidst Risks &amp; Divergent Stock Fortunes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Jewellery-Sector-Growth-Amidst-Risks-and-Divergent-Stock-Fortunes/69868f1db81b2b81dcfb1894</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Jewellery-Sector-Growth-Amidst-Risks-and-Divergent-Stock-Fortunes/69868f1db81b2b81dcfb1894</guid><description>India's jewellery market is pivoting from cyclical patterns to a structural shift favouring organized retailers. Thangamayil Jewellery demonstrates high capital efficiency with strong regional performance, while P N Gadgil Jewellers leverages its legacy brand for expansion. Despite sector tailwinds, stock performance varies, highlighting distinct risks and investor perceptions. The market now scrutinizes execution, balance-sheet discipline, and the persistent influence of gold price volatility.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:02:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868f1db81b2b81dcfb1893.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPI Surge Elevates Banking Infrastructure to National Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UPI-Surge-Elevates-Banking-Infrastructure-to-National-Risk/69868ea0b81b2b81dcfb173f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UPI-Surge-Elevates-Banking-Infrastructure-to-National-Risk/69868ea0b81b2b81dcfb173f</guid><description>India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) processed an astounding 21.63 billion transactions in December 2025, pushing total annual volume to ₹230 lakh crore. This exponential growth transforms potential IT infrastructure failures from isolated incidents into national-level risks, compelling banks to adopt inherently resilient and intelligent systems. IBM highlights the necessity of 'engineered-in' availability and cryptographic assurance to safeguard an increasingly vital digital financial ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:00:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868ea0b81b2b81dcfb173e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Power Surge: Valuations Test Growth Horizon</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Surge-Valuations-Test-Growth-Horizon/69868e2bb81b2b81dcfb15e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Surge-Valuations-Test-Growth-Horizon/69868e2bb81b2b81dcfb15e1</guid><description>India's electricity demand hit a record 250 GW in FY25, driven by industrialization and cooling needs, projecting a 2,960 TWh future. Power Grid Corp's substantial capital expenditure plans, Tata Power's aggressive renewable pivot, and Hitachi Energy's robust backlog offer growth prospects. However, Hitachi Energy's elevated valuation and potential execution challenges across all three firms warrant investor caution amidst robust sector tailwinds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:58:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868e2bb81b2b81dcfb15e0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Industrial Push: High Ambition Meets Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Industrial-Push-High-Ambition-Meets-Execution-Hurdles/69868dc3b81b2b81dcfb1429</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Industrial-Push-High-Ambition-Meets-Execution-Hurdles/69868dc3b81b2b81dcfb1429</guid><description>India's latest budget outlines an aggressive strategy to transform into a 'strategic industrial power' by targeting high-entry-barrier sectors like semiconductors, AI, and biologics, alongside niche traditional manufacturing. Significant outlays are allocated for initiatives like the Electronics Initiative (₹40,000 crore) and a substantial CCUS push. However, the plan relies heavily on policy incentives and faces formidable global competition, raising questions about execution feasibility and long-term sustainability against established players.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:56:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868dc3b81b2b81dcfb1428.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Farm Shield Risks Wider Friction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-US-Trade-Deal-Farm-Shield-Risks-Wider-Friction/69868dabb81b2b81dcfb1387</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-US-Trade-Deal-Farm-Shield-Risks-Wider-Friction/69868dabb81b2b81dcfb1387</guid><description>India and the United States have agreed to a trade deal that significantly lowers US tariffs on Indian goods from 50% to 18%. However, India's staunch protection of its agricultural sector, excluding items like rice, wheat, dairy, and GM foods, introduces economic friction. This strategy, aimed at safeguarding domestic farmers, risks alienating the US, limiting technological adoption in agriculture, and potentially undermining broader trade benefits, creating a strategic trade-off that warrants close observation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NSE Board Approves Long-Delayed IPO via Offer for Sale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/NSE-Board-Approves-Long-Delayed-IPO-via-Offer-for-Sale/69868cbbb81b2b81dcfb11e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/NSE-Board-Approves-Long-Delayed-IPO-via-Offer-for-Sale/69868cbbb81b2b81dcfb11e0</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange (NSE) board has greenlit its long-awaited Initial Public Offering (IPO), structured as an Offer-for-Sale (OFS). This pivotal decision, following SEBI's no-objection certificate, marks the culmination of a ten-year journey obstructed by regulatory and governance challenges. The exchange, valued at an estimated $58 billion in private markets, is set to provide liquidity for major shareholders like LIC and SBI, although the OFS structure means no new capital will be raised for expansion. A dedicated committee has been formed to manage the listing process.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:52:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868cbbb81b2b81dcfb11df.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vidarbha's Green Steel Push: Rs 25K Cr In New Projects, M&amp;M Invests Big</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vidarbhas-Green-Steel-Push-Rs-25K-Cr-In-New-Projects-MandM-Invests-Big/698688a2b81b2b81dcfb0e97</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vidarbhas-Green-Steel-Push-Rs-25K-Cr-In-New-Projects-MandM-Invests-Big/698688a2b81b2b81dcfb0e97</guid><description>Maharashtra's Vidarbha region is charting a course to become India's steel manufacturing epicenter, fueled by substantial new investments. At the Advantage Vidarbha 2026 event, Union Minister Nitin Gadkari highlighted the region's world-class iron ore reserves, envisioning a future centered on green steel production. Mahindra &amp; Mahindra committed ₹15,000 crore for integrated automotive and tractor facilities, while Super Smelters pledged ₹10,100 crore for a new steel plant, totaling over ₹25,100 crore in new project commitments. This strategic push aims to leverage indigenous resources, create significant employment, and potentially lower production costs compared to international competitors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:34:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698688a2b81b2b81dcfb0e96.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel Profit Soars, But Global Woes Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Profit-Soars-But-Global-Woes-Linger/69868882b81b2b81dcfb0dcb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Profit-Soars-But-Global-Woes-Linger/69868882b81b2b81dcfb0dcb</guid><description>Tata Steel reported a significant Q3 FY26 profit increase to ₹2,730 crore, driven by record domestic delivery volumes that surpassed six million tonnes and a 14% increase in operations. Revenue rose 6% to ₹57,002 crore. Despite weak global steel prices and oversupply concerns, a new three-year import tariff is expected to bolster domestic producers. However, international operations, particularly in the UK, continue to face substantial losses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:34:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868882b81b2b81dcfb0dca.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDBI Bank Sale Proceeds: Bids In, But Valuation Hurdles Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDBI-Bank-Sale-Proceeds-Bids-In-But-Valuation-Hurdles-Loom/69868792b81b2b81dcfb0c78</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDBI-Bank-Sale-Proceeds-Bids-In-But-Valuation-Hurdles-Loom/69868792b81b2b81dcfb0c78</guid><description>Financial bids for IDBI Bank's strategic divestment have been submitted, advancing the government's plan to sell a 60.7% stake valued around ₹33,000 crore by March 2026. This marks a crucial step in India's first privatization of a former state-owned bank via a LIC-led rescue, aiming to transfer full management control. However, the deal faces scrutiny over its precedent-setting nature and valuation hurdles.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:30:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69868792b81b2b81dcfb0c77.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PFC, REC Boards Greenlight Merger in PSU Power Finance Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PFC-REC-Boards-Greenlight-Merger-in-PSU-Power-Finance-Consolidation/698686a2b81b2b81dcfb0aba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PFC-REC-Boards-Greenlight-Merger-in-PSU-Power-Finance-Consolidation/698686a2b81b2b81dcfb0aba</guid><description>The boards of Power Finance Corporation (PFC) and REC have given their in-principle approval to merge the two state-owned entities. This consolidation aims to create a larger balance sheet and strengthen the non-banking financial company (NBFC) structure as part of government initiatives. The move follows Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Budget announcement outlining a restructuring of these public sector undertakings to improve efficiency and scale, particularly as REC's original mandate for rural electrification evolves.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:26:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698686a2b81b2b81dcfb0ab9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FMCG Giants Boost Ad Spend on Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Giants-Boost-Ad-Spend-on-Margin-Gains/6986835eb81b2b81dcfb0848</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Giants-Boost-Ad-Spend-on-Margin-Gains/6986835eb81b2b81dcfb0848</guid><description>Leading Indian consumer goods manufacturers Dabur India, Godrej Consumer Products, and Bajaj Consumer Care are allocating significant portions of their improved operating margins towards enhanced advertising and promotional activities. This strategic reinvestment, driven by falling commodity prices and benign inflation, aims to capitalize on an anticipated surge in consumer demand expected over the next few quarters, fueled by summer seasonality and upcoming sporting events. While commodity costs ease, companies are choosing market share acquisition over pure margin expansion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:12:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6986835eb81b2b81dcfb0847.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>