<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:51:17 +0000</pubDate><item><title>SpaceX Acquires xAI, Forging $1.25T Space-AI Powerhouse</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Science-&amp;-Space/SpaceX-Acquires-xAI-Forging-125T-Space-AI-Powerhouse/6981579f69d815649b721986</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Science-&amp;-Space/SpaceX-Acquires-xAI-Forging-125T-Space-AI-Powerhouse/6981579f69d815649b721986</guid><description>SpaceX has formally absorbed Elon Musk’s artificial intelligence firm, xAI, in a landmark consolidation creating a combined entity valued at approximately $1.25 trillion. This strategic merger fuses SpaceX’s extensive space systems expertise with xAI’s advanced AI capabilities, aiming to establish a vertically integrated innovation engine. The move, announced Monday, February 2, 2026, signals substantial ambitions and sets the stage for a significant initial public offering anticipated in mid-2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:31:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981579f69d815649b721985_1770143505276.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra Lifespace Developers: Technical Breakout Follows Q3 Profit Turnaround</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mahindra-Lifespace-Developers-Technical-Breakout-Follows-Q3-Profit-Turnaround/69815ccb69d815649b721f70</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mahindra-Lifespace-Developers-Technical-Breakout-Follows-Q3-Profit-Turnaround/69815ccb69d815649b721f70</guid><description>Mahindra Lifespace Developers experienced a significant technical breakout, pushing its stock price above ₹375 and back into an established bull channel. This move follows a robust Q3 FY26 performance, which saw the company report a net profit of ₹108.88 crore against a loss in the prior year, alongside a substantial revenue increase of 152.51%. The broader Indian real estate sector outlook for 2026 remains optimistic, fueled by economic momentum and demand for premium properties.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69815ccb69d815649b721f6f_1770143051221.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Plunges Amid Fed Nomination Turmoil; Futures Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Plunges-Amid-Fed-Nomination-Turmoil-Futures-Dip/69815eae69d815649b723e5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Plunges-Amid-Fed-Nomination-Turmoil-Futures-Dip/69815eae69d815649b723e5a</guid><description>Gold prices saw a significant drop around February 1-2, 2026, plummeting by as much as 10-11.4% following the nomination of Kevin Warsh as Federal Reserve chair and a rebound in the US dollar. MCX futures also declined, closing at Rs 143,000 per 10 grams. Analysts predict potential further declines, with support levels near $4,300-$4,320, viewing current dips as potential long-term buying opportunities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:24:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69815eae69d815649b723e59_1770142942032.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Rebound: Shutdown, Fed Policy Shift Spark Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rebound-Shutdown-Fed-Policy-Shift-Spark-Recovery/69815f9669d815649b724692</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rebound-Shutdown-Fed-Policy-Shift-Spark-Recovery/69815f9669d815649b724692</guid><description>Gold and silver prices surged Tuesday, clawing back losses from a steep two-day correction. Traders reassessed positions amid US government shutdown uncertainty and evolving Federal Reserve policy expectations. While the US dollar held firm, its usual dampening effect on gold was counteracted by broader macro worries. Analysts suggest the recent pullback was technical, with long-term uptrends intact for gold, while silver faces a potentially slower recovery due to leverage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69815f9669d815649b724691_1770142712388.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Manufacturing Rebound Lifts Asia Amid Commodity Sell-off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Manufacturing-Rebound-Lifts-Asia-Amid-Commodity-Sell-off/69815f2069d815649b72456d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Manufacturing-Rebound-Lifts-Asia-Amid-Commodity-Sell-off/69815f2069d815649b72456d</guid><description>Asian equities staged a significant recovery, with technology shares spearheading the advance, following a robust expansion in US manufacturing activity that bolstered economic outlook. This rebound occurred against a backdrop of extreme volatility in precious metals, which experienced sharp sell-offs triggered by the Federal Reserve nomination before paring some losses. Regional developments and AI infrastructure demand also shaped market sentiment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:17:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69815f2069d815649b72456c_1770142662646.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Italy Fills India's Precision Gap: A Strategic Tech Partnership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Italy-Fills-Indias-Precision-Gap-A-Strategic-Tech-Partnership/69822ed9d9d43ad9e1779fb4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Italy-Fills-Indias-Precision-Gap-A-Strategic-Tech-Partnership/69822ed9d9d43ad9e1779fb4</guid><description>Italy's role as India's second-largest supplier of metal-forming machine tools, valued at EUR 85 million in 2025, underscores a strategic partnership focused on precision engineering and automation. The recent IMTEX 2026 exhibition and the 'OpportunItaly' program facilitate this deepening industrial integration. India's robust capital expenditure plans, highlighted in the 2026-27 budget, further amplify demand for advanced Italian machinery as the nation prioritizes technological upgrades across its core manufacturing sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:14:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69822ed9d9d43ad9e1779fb3_1770139590412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBA Q3 Revenue Jumps 16.5% On Burger King India Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/RBA-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-165percent-On-Burger-King-India-Growth/69822e5bd9d43ad9e1779b47</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/RBA-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-165percent-On-Burger-King-India-Growth/69822e5bd9d43ad9e1779b47</guid><description>Restaurant Brands Asia's Q3 FY26 revenue climbed 16.5% YoY to ₹577.3 crore, fueled by a 4.5% same-store sales growth for Burger King India. Gross margins improved by 210 bps to 69.9%, with EBITDA up 20.9%. The company aggressively expanded its footprint, adding 44 new outlets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:14:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69822e5bd9d43ad9e1779b46_1770139387348.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Noida Creator Hub: Scale vs. Substance in India's Digital Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Noida-Creator-Hub-Scale-vs-Substance-in-Indias-Digital-Ambition/69823610d9d43ad9e177dfdc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Noida-Creator-Hub-Scale-vs-Substance-in-Indias-Digital-Ambition/69823610d9d43ad9e177dfdc</guid><description>Noida Film City is set to launch a vast integrated ecosystem for content creators, aiming to boost India's digital economy with state-of-the-art facilities and incubation. This ambitious government-backed project seeks to nurture talent across all formats, fostering collaboration and global monetization. However, questions linger regarding its long-term economic feasibility and competitive positioning against established international creative centers, as well as its ability to foster organic creator growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:13:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69823610d9d43ad9e177dfdb_1770141302572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Rebounds: SAMCO Sees Healthy Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Rebounds-SAMCO-Sees-Healthy-Consolidation/698168f969d815649b725658</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Rebounds-SAMCO-Sees-Healthy-Consolidation/698168f969d815649b725658</guid><description>Gold saw a rebound on Tuesday, February 3rd, following recent declines, driven by bargain buying and short-covering. Analysts at SAMCO Securities interpret this move not as a decisive trend change, but as part of a broader consolidation phase. Despite short-term volatility, SAMCO maintains that gold's long-term price structure remains intact, supported by structural drivers like central bank demand and geopolitical risks. This consolidation is viewed as healthy, potentially building a stronger base for future upward movements.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:13:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698168f969d815649b725657_1770142413473.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KEC International Secures Rs 1,020 Cr Orders Across Verticals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Secures-Rs-1020-Cr-Orders-Across-Verticals/6981687d69d815649b72551a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Secures-Rs-1020-Cr-Orders-Across-Verticals/6981687d69d815649b72551a</guid><description>KEC International announced new orders worth Rs. 1,020 Crores across its Civil, Transportation, T&amp;D, and Cables verticals. Key wins include a multispeciality hospital and a railway siding project, adding to its Rs. 20,300 Crores year-to-date intake. These orders highlight continued business momentum for the global EPC major.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:11:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981687d69d815649b725519_1770142274982.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Tariffs Slashed, Markets Surge on Risk-On</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Slashed-Markets-Surge-on-Risk-On/69816f2369d815649b726a86</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Slashed-Markets-Surge-on-Risk-On/69816f2369d815649b726a86</guid><description>A significant trade pact between India and the United States has slashed punitive tariffs on Indian goods from 50% to 18%, effectively ending a year of trade friction. Market analysts hail this as a crucial "risk-on" trigger, expected to lure foreign institutional investors back to Indian equities and stabilize the rupee. The agreement is projected to enhance export competitiveness for sectors like textiles, pharmaceuticals, and auto ancillaries, while strengthening India's macroeconomic fundamentals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69816f2369d815649b726a85_1770141437098.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Cut Boosts Indian Shrimp Exporters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Tariff-Cut-Boosts-Indian-Shrimp-Exporters/6981696e69d815649b7257c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Tariff-Cut-Boosts-Indian-Shrimp-Exporters/6981696e69d815649b7257c0</guid><description>A significant reduction in US import tariffs on Indian shrimp, from 50% to 18%, is expected to restore lost competitiveness and market share for exporters. Companies previously contending with margin pressures and volume losses anticipate improved earnings visibility. While some stocks showed mixed reactions on Monday, the sector is poised for a turnaround following this key trade development.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:56:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981696e69d815649b7257bf_1770141285295.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JK Lakshmi Cement Expands Durg Plant, Hikes Project Cost to ₹3,000 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JK-Lakshmi-Cement-Expands-Durg-Plant-Hikes-Project-Cost-to-3000-Cr/69822658d9d43ad9e176f666</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JK-Lakshmi-Cement-Expands-Durg-Plant-Hikes-Project-Cost-to-3000-Cr/69822658d9d43ad9e176f666</guid><description>JK Lakshmi Cement announced a revised cost of ₹3,000 Crores for its Durg, Chhattisgarh integrated cement plant expansion, up from ₹2,500 Crores. The project, set for completion by March 2028, will boost clinker capacity to 12.3 MTPA and cement capacity to 22.6 MTPA. This move signals the company's aggressive growth strategy amidst evolving market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:50:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69822658d9d43ad9e176f665_1770137467131.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Rebounds Sharply After Steep Decline Amidst Market Turbulence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Rebounds-Sharply-After-Steep-Decline-Amidst-Market-Turbulence/69816d2d69d815649b7265c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Rebounds-Sharply-After-Steep-Decline-Amidst-Market-Turbulence/69816d2d69d815649b7265c3</guid><description>Silver prices showed signs of recovery on February 3, 2026, with spot silver climbing nearly 8% to $82.74 and COMEX futures reaching $85/oz. This rebound follows a dramatic over 35% plunge from ₹4,20,000 per kilogram to ₹2,65,000. The market turbulence was exacerbated by a more than 15% increase in CME silver futures margins in late January 2026, forcing traders to liquidate positions. Analysts point to a fundamental supply deficit and robust industrial demand, particularly in solar energy, EVs, and data centers, as key factors supporting the recovery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69816d2d69d815649b7265c2_1770140770796.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Rebound Sharply After Fed Nominee Shock</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rebound-Sharply-After-Fed-Nominee-Shock/69816da769d815649b72670c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rebound-Sharply-After-Fed-Nominee-Shock/69816da769d815649b72670c</guid><description>Precious metals gold and silver experienced a significant overnight rebound, with gold surpassing $4,850 per ounce and silver climbing past $85 per ounce on COMEX. This recovery follows a dramatic sell-off, largely attributed to President Trump's nomination of Kevin Warsh for Federal Reserve Chair, perceived as a hawkish signal. Despite volatility, underlying support from central bank purchases and fiscal concerns persists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69816da769d815649b72670b_1770140553102.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Faces Volatility Amid Fed Policy, Geopolitical Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Faces-Volatility-Amid-Fed-Policy-Geopolitical-Shifts/69816e9969d815649b72689c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Faces-Volatility-Amid-Fed-Policy-Geopolitical-Shifts/69816e9969d815649b72689c</guid><description>Silver experienced a divergence on February 3, 2026, with Comex prices rising to $82.70 per ounce while MCX futures saw steep declines from recent record highs, settling around ₹2.99 lakh per kilogram. This volatility followed a sharp market correction after the US Federal Reserve held interest rates steady and President Trump nominated Kevin Warsh as the next Fed chair. While geopolitical tensions continue to provide underlying support, recent de-escalation signals and robust US manufacturing data are shifting market sentiment. Investors now eye key economic indicators, including RBI policy and US jobs data, for further direction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69816e9969d815649b72689b_1770140108250.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BASF India Gets NSE Nod for Agri Biz Demerger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/BASF-India-Gets-NSE-Nod-for-Agri-Biz-Demerger/69816f8569d815649b726c3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/BASF-India-Gets-NSE-Nod-for-Agri-Biz-Demerger/69816f8569d815649b726c3d</guid><description>BASF India has received a 'no objection' letter from NSE for its agri business demerger into subsidiary BASIL. This follows BSE's nod. The scheme awaits NCLT approvals, with NSE imposing disclosure conditions and a tight listing timeline for the new entity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69816f8569d815649b726c3c_1770140098104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Truhome Finance Appoints Ex-SBI Chief Khara as Chairperson</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Truhome-Finance-Appoints-Ex-SBI-Chief-Khara-as-Chairperson/6981754069d815649b72789f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Truhome-Finance-Appoints-Ex-SBI-Chief-Khara-as-Chairperson/6981754069d815649b72789f</guid><description>Truhome Finance has appointed Dinesh Kumar Khara, former Chairman of State Bank of India, as its Chairperson for a five-year term. Khara's extensive experience, including orchestrating a major bank merger at SBI, is expected to drive Truhome's expansion and strategic direction in India's competitive mortgage market. Recent financial reports indicate solid AUM growth and comfortable asset quality, though specific live market trading data remains unavailable or inconsistent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981754069d815649b72789e_1770139970542.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Pact Boosts Equities, Eyes Foreign Inflows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Boosts-Equities-Eyes-Foreign-Inflows/69816f9069d815649b726c50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Boosts-Equities-Eyes-Foreign-Inflows/69816f9069d815649b726c50</guid><description>Indian equities registered a notable advance following the announcement of a US-India trade agreement that substantially reduced reciprocal tariffs. The pact is seen as a critical catalyst to reverse recent foreign investor outflows and improve sentiment. Initial market reactions included a sharp surge in Nifty 50 futures and gains in cash equities, signaling a renewed appetite for Indian assets. This development, coupled with recent budget measures, aims to bolster investor confidence and economic growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69816f9069d815649b726c4f_1770139921408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndusInd Bank Taps Piramal Exec for Consumer Finance Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Taps-Piramal-Exec-for-Consumer-Finance-Push/698174b169d815649b7275fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Taps-Piramal-Exec-for-Consumer-Finance-Push/698174b169d815649b7275fb</guid><description>IndusInd Bank has appointed Jagdeep Mallareddy, formerly CEO of retail lending at Piramal Finance, to lead its consumer finance business. This strategic hire, personally selected by CEO Rajiv Anand, is crucial for bolstering the bank's retail pivot and growth ambitions. The move occurs as IndusInd continues to reshape its leadership following significant accounting discrepancies and a period of underperformance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:31:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698174b169d815649b7275fa_1770139857826.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Ups Tax Penalties for Updated Returns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Ups-Tax-Penalties-for-Updated-Returns/6981752969d815649b7277b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Ups-Tax-Penalties-for-Updated-Returns/6981752969d815649b7277b0</guid><description>The Indian government, via the Finance Bill, 2026, has significantly altered rules for filing Updated Income Tax Returns (ITR-U). Taxpayers now have a 48-month window to rectify disclosures, but face escalating additional taxes. New provisions also permit filing post-reassessment notices, albeit with higher penalty rates. These changes signal a drive for enhanced compliance and revenue collection through a more stringent, yet clarified, voluntary disclosure mechanism.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981752969d815649b7277af_1770139759212.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Drug Duty Cuts Offer Targeted Relief</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Budget-2026-Drug-Duty-Cuts-Offer-Targeted-Relief/69818dfd69d815649b72c0b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Budget-2026-Drug-Duty-Cuts-Offer-Targeted-Relief/69818dfd69d815649b72c0b5</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 has greenlit import duty exemptions for seven rare disease drugs and seventeen anti-cancer medications, a move championed by patient groups for offering direct financial relief on prohibitively expensive treatments. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced the measure, continuing a government strategy to lower customs duties on critical imported medicines. While this is projected to reduce out-of-pocket expenses by an estimated 10-15% for individuals bearing the cost, concerns remain that it may not fully address the high base prices of these life-saving therapies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:28:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818dfd69d815649b72c0b4_1770139683499.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UBS Warns: Silver's Wild Ride Makes Long-Term Bets Risky</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/UBS-Warns-Silvers-Wild-Ride-Makes-Long-Term-Bets-Risky/69818d1269d815649b72be19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/UBS-Warns-Silvers-Wild-Ride-Makes-Long-Term-Bets-Risky/69818d1269d815649b72be19</guid><description>Silver prices experienced extraordinary volatility, including a 38% intraday collapse, rarely seen in modern markets. UBS Chief Investment Office advises extreme caution, stating it is too early for long-term exposure. The metal entered the sell-off from an overstretched position, volatility has surged to unprecedented levels, and key demand drivers are weakening.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:20:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818d1269d815649b72be18_1770139216129.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Bharat Forge's Export Boost Amidst Tariffs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-US-Trade-Deal-Bharat-Forges-Export-Boost-Amidst-Tariffs/69822093d9d43ad9e176683a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-US-Trade-Deal-Bharat-Forges-Export-Boost-Amidst-Tariffs/69822093d9d43ad9e176683a</guid><description>The India-US trade agreement reduces tariffs to 18%, signaling a strategic shift and strengthening India's manufacturing export potential. Bharat Forge and other auto component makers anticipate increased market access, particularly for commercial vehicle parts. While a positive step for global supply chain integration, the full impact hinges on leveraging this opportunity amidst potential lingering tariffs and competitive dynamics. The deal aims to foster deeper bilateral economic ties and enhance India's position as a manufacturing hub.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:20:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69822093d9d43ad9e1766839_1770135935053.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zee Entertainment Slashes Jobs Amid Revenue Slump, Eyes 20% EBITDA</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Entertainment-Slashes-Jobs-Amid-Revenue-Slump-Eyes-20percent-EBITDA/69818e0a69d815649b72c15b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Entertainment-Slashes-Jobs-Amid-Revenue-Slump-Eyes-20percent-EBITDA/69818e0a69d815649b72c15b</guid><description>Zee Entertainment Enterprises is intensifying its focus on manpower cost optimization, having already reduced its workforce by 951 employees between FY23 and FY25. This strategic move comes as the broadcast giant grapples with a shrinking pay-TV subscriber base and declining advertising revenue. The company is targeting an 18-20% EBITDA margin by FY26, a significant leap from its current 10.1% in 9M FY26. Deputy CEO Mukund Galgali cited overlaps in linear and digital operations as the genesis for this restructuring.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:18:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818e0a69d815649b72c15a_1770139098785.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pidilite Industries Posts Robust Q3 Growth, Margins Expand on Lower Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pidilite-Industries-Posts-Robust-Q3-Growth-Margins-Expand-on-Lower-Costs/69822000d9d43ad9e1766393</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pidilite-Industries-Posts-Robust-Q3-Growth-Margins-Expand-on-Lower-Costs/69822000d9d43ad9e1766393</guid><description>Pidilite Industries reported a strong Q3 FY26, with standalone net sales up 11.0% YoY to ₹3,425 crore and consolidated net sales rising 10.2% to ₹3,699 crore. Both standalone and consolidated EBITDA and PAT saw double-digit growth. The company benefited from a 24.5% standalone EBITDA margin (up 24 bps) and 24.2% consolidated margin (up 40 bps), driven by 200+ bps gross margin improvement from lower input costs. Underlying volume growth was robust at 9.3% standalone. Management expressed optimism on domestic demand but remains watchful of geopolitical risks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:18:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69822000d9d43ad9e1766392_1770135628341.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sancode Technologies Gets Odisha Nod for ₹1650 Cr Semiconductor Unit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sancode-Technologies-Gets-Odisha-Nod-for-1650-Cr-Semiconductor-Unit/6981900469d815649b72c79a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sancode-Technologies-Gets-Odisha-Nod-for-1650-Cr-Semiconductor-Unit/6981900469d815649b72c79a</guid><description>Sancode Technologies' subsidiary, Sancode Semi, has secured 'in-principal' approval from Odisha's High-Level Clearance Authority for a ₹1,650 crore Outsourced Semiconductor Assembly and Test (OSAT) unit. Proposed in Khordha district, this marks a strategic move into India's burgeoning semiconductor ecosystem, pending further regulatory clearances and compliance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981900469d815649b72c799_1770138975225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Surge Defies Trade Deals Amidst Technical Turmoil</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Surge-Defies-Trade-Deals-Amidst-Technical-Turmoil/69818fdc69d815649b72c69b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Surge-Defies-Trade-Deals-Amidst-Technical-Turmoil/69818fdc69d815649b72c69b</guid><description>Indian gold and silver prices surged Tuesday, defying positive trade pacts with the US and EU. MCX silver jumped 7.42% and gold 3.55%, driven by technical factors, margin requirement adjustments by CME, and speculation around US monetary policy, overriding typical safe-haven demand dips.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:17:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818fdc69d815649b72c69a_1770139068383.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Steel PSUs to Hike Capex 44% Amid Infra Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Steel-PSUs-to-Hike-Capex-44percent-Amid-Infra-Push/6981950969d815649b72d775</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Steel-PSUs-to-Hike-Capex-44percent-Amid-Infra-Push/6981950969d815649b72d775</guid><description>India's public sector steel companies are set for a significant capital expenditure surge, with total spending projected to reach ₹25,125 crore in FY27, a 44% jump from the previous year. Steel Authority of India Limited (SAIL) and National Mineral Development Corporation (NMDC) are leading this investment drive, collectively boosting their planned outlays by 50%. This expansion is fueled by robust expectations for the domestic steel industry, underpinned by government infrastructure initiatives and anticipated economic recovery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981950969d815649b72d774_1770138934464.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kotak Targets India's 55% GVA Services Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Kotak-Targets-Indias-55percent-GVA-Services-Sector/6981902869d815649b72c8e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Kotak-Targets-Indias-55percent-GVA-Services-Sector/6981902869d815649b72c8e7</guid><description>Kotak Mahindra Asset Management Company has introduced the Kotak Services Fund, an open-ended equity scheme targeting India's vital services sector. The fund, which opens for its New Fund Offer (NFO) from February 4 to February 18, aims to capitalize on a sector contributing approximately 55% to India's Gross Value Added (GVA) and employing over 31.5% of the workforce. Leveraging a Growth at Reasonable Price (GARP) strategy and a bottom-up approach, the fund will invest across market capitalizations, focusing on companies exhibiting strong fundamentals and scalability. This launch aligns with structural economic trends of increasing incomes and widespread digital adoption reshaping consumer and business services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:14:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981902869d815649b72c8e6_1770138862200.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Roars Back with 25% January Sales Jump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Roars-Back-with-25percent-January-Sales-Jump/6981941a69d815649b72d378</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Roars-Back-with-25percent-January-Sales-Jump/6981941a69d815649b72d378</guid><description>Bajaj Auto initiated 2026 with significant momentum, posting a 25.3% increase in total vehicle sales for January, reaching 477,422 units compared to 381,040 units in the prior year. This performance, which surpassed analyst estimates, was propelled by balanced growth in both domestic sales and international exports. The company's two-wheeler division saw a 24% rise in total sales, while its commercial vehicle segment experienced a substantial 35% surge. Year-to-date figures, however, reveal a divergence, with export growth offsetting a marginal decline in domestic volumes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981941a69d815649b72d377_1770138807701.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Legal AI Adoption Accelerates: Lawttorney.ai Claims 50K Users Amidst Industry Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Legal-AI-Adoption-Accelerates-Lawttorneyai-Claims-50K-Users-Amidst-Industry-Shift/6981961269d815649b72da38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Legal-AI-Adoption-Accelerates-Lawttorneyai-Claims-50K-Users-Amidst-Industry-Shift/6981961269d815649b72da38</guid><description>Law firms are grappling with escalating litigation, complex compliance, and client demands, driving a significant integration of AI into practice. Lawttorney.ai, an AI legal platform, highlights this trend with reported metrics of over 50,000 users and 1.78 million prompts processed. The platform emphasizes operational impact, citing significant time savings in research and drafting, alongside a strong stance on data safety. These developments occur as AI transitions from experimental tools to foundational legal infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:10:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981961269d815649b72da37_1770138654847.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-EU FTA: Geopolitics Fuels Historic Trade Breakthrough</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Geopolitics-Fuels-Historic-Trade-Breakthrough/6981965069d815649b72db68</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Geopolitics-Fuels-Historic-Trade-Breakthrough/6981965069d815649b72db68</guid><description>After years of stalled negotiations, the India-European Union Free Trade Agreement (FTA) was finalized on January 27, 2026. Driven by geopolitical shifts and supply chain imperatives, this landmark pact represents a strategic recalibration, not merely an economic one. It promises substantial tariff liberalization covering nearly all bilateral trade, unlocks significant market access for key sectors in both economies, and introduces robust regulatory disciplines. The agreement is poised to reshape global trade dynamics and presents profound opportunities and complexities for the legal services market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981965069d815649b72db67_1770138495052.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dabur Restrained by Court Over 'Cool King' Packaging</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dabur-Restrained-by-Court-Over-Cool-King-Packaging/698196b269d815649b72dcc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dabur-Restrained-by-Court-Over-Cool-King-Packaging/698196b269d815649b72dcc3</guid><description>The Delhi High Court has permanently restrained Dabur India Limited from selling its 'Cool King Thanda Tael' product, ruling its packaging infringes upon the distinctive trade dress of Emami Limited's Navratna Ayurvedic Oil. The court found Dabur's design to be a deliberate imitation, leading to potential consumer confusion and upholding Emami's market-leading position in the cooling oil segment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:07:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698196b269d815649b72dcc2_1770138441139.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>D-Propulse Aerospace: ₹25 Cr for Next-Gen Propulsion Tech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/D-Propulse-Aerospace-25-Cr-for-Next-Gen-Propulsion-Tech/698196e969d815649b72ddcb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/D-Propulse-Aerospace-25-Cr-for-Next-Gen-Propulsion-Tech/698196e969d815649b72ddcb</guid><description>D-Propulse Aerospace has secured ₹25 crore from IAN Alpha Fund to advance its proprietary Rotating Detonation Engine (RDE) technology. The infusion will strengthen engineering, computing, and testing infrastructure for next-generation propulsion systems intended for defense and civilian applications. This funding underscores the escalating investor confidence in India's deep-tech aerospace sector, particularly within defense innovation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:07:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698196e969d815649b72ddca_1770138420900.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Avalon Technologies Surges 20% on India-US Tariff Cut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Avalon-Technologies-Surges-20percent-on-India-US-Tariff-Cut/6981984e69d815649b72e13e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Avalon-Technologies-Surges-20percent-on-India-US-Tariff-Cut/6981984e69d815649b72e13e</guid><description>Avalon Technologies Ltd. shares hit a 20% upper circuit at ₹1,022.7 on Tuesday, February 3, 2026, reacting to a new India-US trade agreement. The deal slashes tariffs on exports to the United States from 50% to 18%, a move directly benefiting Avalon, which derives a substantial portion of its revenue from the US market. The company's stock has shown strong performance, gaining in four of the last five sessions and rising 51% over the past year.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:06:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981984e69d815649b72e13d_1770138286058.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FanCode Secures ISL Rights, Eyes Digital Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/FanCode-Secures-ISL-Rights-Eyes-Digital-Dominance/6981975e69d815649b72df54</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/FanCode-Secures-ISL-Rights-Eyes-Digital-Dominance/6981975e69d815649b72df54</guid><description>FanCode has secured exclusive global broadcast rights for the 2025-26 Indian Super League (ISL) season, aiming to bolster its football portfolio with a digital-first strategy. This move by the Dream Sports-owned platform emphasizes high-quality streaming and fan-centric features. The acquisition comes amid a dynamic Indian sports streaming market, with FanCode reinforcing its position against major players like JioCinema and Disney+ Hotstar.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:03:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981975e69d815649b72df53_1770138194135.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Precious Metals Rebound After Margin-Induced Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Rebound-After-Margin-Induced-Sell-Off/698199c269d815649b72e557</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Rebound-After-Margin-Induced-Sell-Off/698199c269d815649b72e557</guid><description>Gold and silver exchange-traded funds (ETFs) snapped a three-day decline on Tuesday, buoyed by a stabilization in precious metal prices. This rebound follows a sharp sell-off that erased significant January gains, largely attributed by analysts to a technical correction rather than fundamental issues. The dramatic drop was triggered by CME Group's decision to increase margin requirements on gold and silver futures, forcing leveraged traders to liquidate positions and amplifying declines already exacerbated by overbought conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698199c269d815649b72e556_1770138033176.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ducon Infratech Secures Policy Validation for Carbon Capture Amidst ₹20,000 Cr CCUS Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Ducon-Infratech-Secures-Policy-Validation-for-Carbon-Capture-Amidst-20000-Cr-CCUS-Push/698198c869d815649b72e2aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Ducon-Infratech-Secures-Policy-Validation-for-Carbon-Capture-Amidst-20000-Cr-CCUS-Push/698198c869d815649b72e2aa</guid><description>Ducon Infratechnologies' early strategy in carbon capture technology has received significant policy validation, coinciding with India's ₹20,000 crore push for Carbon Capture, Utilisation, and Storage (CCUS) initiatives. The company reported FY25 financials of ₹451 crore income, ₹31 crore EBITDA, and ₹14 crore net profit, with management expressing confidence in leveraging this policy tailwind for future growth within the expanding CCUS ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698198c869d815649b72e2a9_1770138016738.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PB Fintech Posts Strong Q3, But QIP Plans Temper Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/PB-Fintech-Posts-Strong-Q3-But-QIP-Plans-Temper-Rally/698198dd69d815649b72e37e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/PB-Fintech-Posts-Strong-Q3-But-QIP-Plans-Temper-Rally/698198dd69d815649b72e37e</guid><description>PB Fintech, operator of Policybazaar, announced a significant 165% year-on-year surge in net profit to ₹189 crore for Q3FY26, with operating revenue climbing 37% to ₹1,771 crore. Despite these strong results, the company's stock saw a notable decline. Investors reacted cautiously to the announcement of a board meeting to consider a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) aimed at funding inorganic expansion, raising concerns about potential dilution and management bandwidth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:59:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698198dd69d815649b72e37d_1770137956445.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>