<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:48:44 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Oyo Parent PRISM Eyes $8B IPO Amid Profit Turnaround</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Oyo-Parent-PRISM-Eyes-8B-IPO-Amid-Profit-Turnaround/69858b9be769d12df1d55673</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Oyo-Parent-PRISM-Eyes-8B-IPO-Amid-Profit-Turnaround/69858b9be769d12df1d55673</guid><description>PRISM, the parent company of hospitality major OYO, has filed for an Initial Public Offering (IPO) with India's SEBI, targeting a valuation between $7 billion and $8 billion. This second attempt follows a reported profit after tax of Rs 245 crore and a 20% revenue increase to Rs 6,253 crore for the fiscal year ending March 31, 2025. The company previously withdrew its IPO plans in 2021 amid market volatility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:35:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69858b9be769d12df1d55672_1770360003079.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Rate Pause Sparks Sell-off; Liquidity Focus Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Rate-Pause-Sparks-Sell-off-Liquidity-Focus-Mounts/69858b85e769d12df1d5558f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Rate-Pause-Sparks-Sell-off-Liquidity-Focus-Mounts/69858b85e769d12df1d5558f</guid><description>Indian equity markets extended losses following the Reserve Bank of India's decision to maintain the repo rate at 5.25% and a neutral policy stance. While the move was expected, upward inflation revisions and concerns over currency stability have shifted the central bank's focus to liquidity management. This has triggered a sell-off, particularly in rate-sensitive IT and banking stocks, despite an improved GDP growth forecast for FY27.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI's Digital Leap Fuels MSME Growth, Stability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Digital-Leap-Fuels-MSME-Growth-Stability/69858b64e769d12df1d55474</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Digital-Leap-Fuels-MSME-Growth-Stability/69858b64e769d12df1d55474</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is launching a unified digital portal to enhance the Lead Bank Scheme's efficiency and transparency. This initiative complements a proposal to double collateral-free loans for MSMEs to ₹20 lakh, addressing credit access gaps. Concurrently, the RBI is strengthening digital banking safety with draft guidelines and a framework for customer compensation up to ₹25,000 for small fraud losses. These moves align with a neutral monetary policy stance, holding the repo rate at 5.25%, supported by robust GDP growth projections and easing inflation, all set against the backdrop of significant trade agreements with the EU and US.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Boosts FY27 Growth Outlook; Inflation Risks Shift to Precious Metals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Boosts-FY27-Growth-Outlook-Inflation-Risks-Shift-to-Precious-Metals/69858aebe769d12df1d552f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Boosts-FY27-Growth-Outlook-Inflation-Risks-Shift-to-Precious-Metals/69858aebe769d12df1d552f2</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has revised its real GDP growth projections upward for the first two quarters of FY27 to 6.9% and 7.0%, respectively, signaling resilience amid a challenging global economic climate. Governor Sanjay Malhotra highlighted robust domestic drivers for this optimism. Concurrently, the RBI adjusted its Consumer Price Index (CPI) inflation estimates higher for FY26 and the first half of FY27, attributing the shift primarily to increased precious metal prices, while underlying inflationary pressures are noted as remaining subdued and near the central bank's target.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:32:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69858aebe769d12df1d552f1_1770359711086.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>InMobi IPO: India's First Unicorn Eyes $5B Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/InMobi-IPO-Indias-First-Unicorn-Eyes-5B-Valuation/69858a71e769d12df1d5516d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/InMobi-IPO-Indias-First-Unicorn-Eyes-5B-Valuation/69858a71e769d12df1d5516d</guid><description>India's pioneering tech firm, InMobi, is preparing for a significant domestic Initial Public Offering (IPO), reportedly aiming for a valuation between $4 billion and $5 billion. The adtech giant is engaging eight investment banks for the offering, which follows a strategic redomiciling from Singapore to India. The company is also pursuing a pre-IPO funding round to bolster its balance sheet ahead of the public listing. This move leverages InMobi's 'first unicorn' status and its evolving AI-driven consumer technology ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cummins India Margins Hum Amid Demand Woes; Data Centers Lead</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cummins-India-Margins-Hum-Amid-Demand-Woes-Data-Centers-Lead/6985889ae769d12df1d54edb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cummins-India-Margins-Hum-Amid-Demand-Woes-Data-Centers-Lead/6985889ae769d12df1d54edb</guid><description>Cummins India reported a 1% revenue increase and a 6% EBITDA climb, expanding margins to 20.77% due to cost efficiencies and a favorable business mix. Data centers, services, and CPCB IV+ engines are driving growth, offsetting weaknesses in industrial segments. The company's valuation remains premium, reflecting optimism for sustained double-digit revenue growth projected for FY26, fueled by expanding data center demand and infrastructure projects. Despite mixed performance across some traditional sectors, the company's strategic shift towards high-growth areas supports its outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:22:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985889ae769d12df1d54eda_1770359204211.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Holds Rates Steady Amidst Trade Wins; Growth Outlook Strengthened</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Steady-Amidst-Trade-Wins-Growth-Outlook-Strengthened/698587a3e769d12df1d54cf8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Steady-Amidst-Trade-Wins-Growth-Outlook-Strengthened/698587a3e769d12df1d54cf8</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee unanimously kept the repo rate at 5.25%, retaining a neutral stance. Governor Sanjay Malhotra cited robust domestic demand fueling a projected 7.4% GDP growth for 2025-26 and inflation remaining under control. Crucially, new trade agreements with the EU and the US are expected to significantly bolster economic resilience and sustain growth momentum despite global headwinds. This strategic pause signals confidence in India's internal economic drivers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:18:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698587a3e769d12df1d54cf7_1770358768473.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>QSR Revival Meets Defense Policy Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/QSR-Revival-Meets-Defense-Policy-Headwinds/69858732e769d12df1d54b79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/QSR-Revival-Meets-Defense-Policy-Headwinds/69858732e769d12df1d54b79</guid><description>The market shows diverging trends as QSR stocks signal a discretionary spending revival, driven by innovation and expansion. Simultaneously, Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd (HAL) faces scrutiny due to evolving defense procurement policies that challenge its large order book, while Kaynes Technology navigates a complex growth path hinging on FY26 projections amidst valuation concerns. Nykaa demonstrates robust Q3 performance, signaling resilience in the consumer discretionary space.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:16:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69858732e769d12df1d54b78_1770358666183.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Rides AI Data Centers, Energy Transition Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Rides-AI-Data-Centers-Energy-Transition-Boom/69858662e769d12df1d549ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Rides-AI-Data-Centers-Energy-Transition-Boom/69858662e769d12df1d549ac</guid><description>Hitachi Energy India shares advanced Friday, February 6, as the company reaffirmed its double-digit operational EBITDA guidance for the upcoming fiscal year. This confidence stems from 70% of its order book being on flexible pricing, shielding it from commodity inflation. The company sees significant growth in AI-ready data centers, estimating a 10-15% share of India's total data center capital expenditure. Strong Q3 results, featuring a 90.5% year-on-year profit jump to ₹261 crore and revenue growth of 28.52%, fueled investor optimism. With 11 out of 13 analysts rating the stock a 'buy', its strategic positioning appears to be gaining traction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:12:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69858662e769d12df1d549ab_1770358618541.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Eases NBFC Rules: Growth vs. Stability Balance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Eases-NBFC-Rules-Growth-vs-Stability-Balance/69858640e769d12df1d548e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Eases-NBFC-Rules-Growth-vs-Stability-Balance/69858640e769d12df1d548e0</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has introduced regulatory reforms to ease the operational burden on non-banking financial companies (NBFCs). Entities with assets below ₹1,000 crore, lacking public access or customer interface, will be exempt from mandatory RBI registration. Further flexibility is granted by easing prior approval requirements for branch openings. Governor Sanjay Malhotra highlighted that these measures, alongside continued liquidity injections, aim to support financial stability and sector resilience amid healthy credit growth across large industries and banks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:12:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69858640e769d12df1d548df_1770358800007.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Derivative Rule Shake-Up: Broker Stocks React, Volatility Fears Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SEBI-Derivative-Rule-Shake-Up-Broker-Stocks-React-Volatility-Fears-Rise/698585bfe769d12df1d5475e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SEBI-Derivative-Rule-Shake-Up-Broker-Stocks-React-Volatility-Fears-Rise/698585bfe769d12df1d5475e</guid><description>SEBI's decision to eliminate calendar spread benefits for single stock derivatives on expiry day, effective May 5, 2026, triggered an initial sell-off in broking stocks like Angel One, Groww, BSE, and 5paisa. The change increases margin requirements on expiry sessions by treating spreads as independent legs, a move aimed at mitigating systemic risk. This could lead to higher volatility and potentially reduced liquidity on expiry days, impacting the revenue streams of derivative-heavy brokers. While companies are showing signs of recovery, the long-term effects on trading volumes and market dynamics are under scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:10:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698585bfe769d12df1d5475d_1770358291521.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Allcargo Logistics Reports 50% PBT Surge Post-Integration</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Allcargo-Logistics-Reports-50percent-PBT-Surge-Post-Integration/698584d1e769d12df1d5459f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Allcargo-Logistics-Reports-50percent-PBT-Surge-Post-Integration/698584d1e769d12df1d5459f</guid><description>Allcargo Logistics declared its Q3FY26 results, labeling the period a 'transition quarter' after integrating domestic supply chain businesses. The company reported a 7% Year-to-Date (YTD) revenue increase and a significant 50% surge in Profit Before Tax (PBT). The Express Distribution segment excelled with 19% YoY EBITDA growth, while Contract Logistics saw subdued demand. Management anticipates steady revenue growth with EBITDA and PBT outpacing topline expansion, focusing on yield-led margins and technology.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:06:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698584d1e769d12df1d5459e_1770358129677.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Dips Amidst Margin Hikes, But Rate Cut Hopes Offer Support</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Gold-Dips-Amidst-Margin-Hikes-But-Rate-Cut-Hopes-Offer-Support/698583eee769d12df1d5436e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Gold-Dips-Amidst-Margin-Hikes-But-Rate-Cut-Hopes-Offer-Support/698583eee769d12df1d5436e</guid><description>On February 6, 2026, gold prices in India saw a marginal decline, with 24K gold trading at ₹151,770 per 10 grams. This dip was primarily driven by increased margin requirements by the CME on gold futures and a perceived strengthening of the US dollar amidst tech equity sell-offs. However, underlying support for gold remains robust, fueled by expectations of US Federal Reserve rate cuts and persistent geopolitical uncertainties. India's gold prices continue to trade at a notable premium compared to Dubai.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:02:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698583eee769d12df1d5436d_1770358208145.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Prices Crash 4.87% in India as Global Rout Deepens</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Prices-Crash-487percent-in-India-as-Global-Rout-Deepens/69858368e769d12df1d541f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Prices-Crash-487percent-in-India-as-Global-Rout-Deepens/69858368e769d12df1d541f9</guid><description>Silver prices tumbled 4.87% across India on Friday, with 1 kg trading at ₹234,850. This sharp decline mirrors significant global volatility, as COMEX silver plunged over 9% before a partial rebound. The metal has now erased its year-to-date gains, marking its steepest collapse since 1980.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:00:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69858368e769d12df1d541f8_1770357699059.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Forex Reserves Surge to Record $723.8 Billion, Shielding Economy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Surge-to-Record-7238-Billion-Shielding-Economy/69858021e769d12df1d53de5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Surge-to-Record-7238-Billion-Shielding-Economy/69858021e769d12df1d53de5</guid><description>India's foreign exchange reserves have reached an unprecedented $723.8 billion as of January 30, Reserve Bank of India Governor Sanjay Malhotra announced Friday. The stockpile, an all-time high, provides a critical buffer, covering over 11 months of merchandise imports. Malhotra expressed confidence in the nation's resilient external sector and its ability to meet financing requirements comfortably.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:46:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69858021e769d12df1d53de4_1770356925829.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hexaware Tech Stock Plummets 20% Post-Earnings as Margins Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexaware-Tech-Stock-Plummets-20percent-Post-Earnings-as-Margins-Squeeze/69857f41e769d12df1d53bc9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexaware-Tech-Stock-Plummets-20percent-Post-Earnings-as-Margins-Squeeze/69857f41e769d12df1d53bc9</guid><description>Hexaware Technologies faced a sharp sell-off, with shares plummeting nearly 20% from their IPO price and hitting a low of ₹572.50 on February 6, 2026. The decline followed weak Q4 2025 results, where revenue met expectations but operating margins contracted by 60 basis points, missing forecasts. This performance triggered downgrades from major institutions like JPMorgan and HSBC, citing growth concerns amid a challenging macro environment. Despite management's projection of improved revenue growth and stable EBIT margins for 2026, the market reacted negatively to the immediate profitability squeeze.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:42:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69857f41e769d12df1d53bc8_1770356937826.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nasdaq Drops 6% on Fed Liquidity Fears; Tech Capex Under Fire</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nasdaq-Drops-6percent-on-Fed-Liquidity-Fears-Tech-Capex-Under-Fire/69857f34e769d12df1d53b48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nasdaq-Drops-6percent-on-Fed-Liquidity-Fears-Tech-Capex-Under-Fire/69857f34e769d12df1d53b48</guid><description>The Nasdaq Composite has fallen 6% on growing concerns about the U.S. Federal Reserve's potential hawkish pivot, signaling an end to prolonged easy liquidity. This shift, coupled with doubts over the returns from Microsoft's substantial capital expenditures on AI infrastructure, has injected nervousness into big tech and AI sectors. The market is now grappling with reduced liquidity and a smaller Fed balance sheet. Meanwhile, India's equity market faces investor skepticism despite recent policy signals, awaiting tangible actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:42:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69857f34e769d12df1d53b47_1770357242422.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Unifies Data, Boosts MSME Loans Amid Digital Safety Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Unifies-Data-Boosts-MSME-Loans-Amid-Digital-Safety-Push/69857ef3e769d12df1d539a4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Unifies-Data-Boosts-MSME-Loans-Amid-Digital-Safety-Push/69857ef3e769d12df1d539a4</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is launching a unified portal for the Lead Bank Scheme, streamlining data management for banking operations. Concurrently, it proposes doubling the collateral-free loan cap for MSMEs to ₹20 lakh, aiming to enhance credit access. These measures are complemented by new draft guidelines for digital banking safety and a framework to compensate customers for losses in small-value fraudulent transactions. These initiatives collectively signal a push for greater transparency, financial inclusion, and a more secure digital financial ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:41:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69857ef3e769d12df1d539a3_1770357405403.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Boosts MSMEs: Loan Cap Doubles, Rates Stable</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Boosts-MSMEs-Loan-Cap-Doubles-Rates-Stable/69857ed6e769d12df1d538da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Boosts-MSMEs-Loan-Cap-Doubles-Rates-Stable/69857ed6e769d12df1d538da</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has proposed a significant doubling of the collateral-free loan cap for MSMEs to ₹20 lakh, aiming to enhance credit access and stimulate economic activity. Concurrently, the Monetary Policy Committee has maintained the repo rate at 5.25% with a neutral stance, signaling a balanced approach to managing inflation and supporting growth. This move aims to reduce reliance on informal lending and bolster the crucial MSME sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:40:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69857ed6e769d12df1d538d9_1770357746802.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Holds Repo Rate: Stability for EMIs, Affordability Woes Persist</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBI-Holds-Repo-Rate-Stability-for-EMIs-Affordability-Woes-Persist/69857ebae769d12df1d537d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBI-Holds-Repo-Rate-Stability-for-EMIs-Affordability-Woes-Persist/69857ebae769d12df1d537d3</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has maintained its repo rate at 5.25%, ensuring home loan EMIs remain stable for borrowers and providing predictability for new buyers. While industry stakeholders welcome this policy continuity, it offers limited support for housing demand, which continues to be challenged by rising property prices. The Union Budget 2026-27 also provided no significant relief for the affordable housing segment, underscoring a widening gap between the RBI's stable monetary stance and the sector's need for demand-boosting stimuli.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:40:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69857ebae769d12df1d537d2_1770357982034.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DHFL Cleared in Yes Bank Money Laundering Case on Immunity Grounds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/DHFL-Cleared-in-Yes-Bank-Money-Laundering-Case-on-Immunity-Grounds/69857e3fe769d12df1d53663</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/DHFL-Cleared-in-Yes-Bank-Money-Laundering-Case-on-Immunity-Grounds/69857e3fe769d12df1d53663</guid><description>Mumbai's sessions court has closed proceedings against Dewan Housing Finance Corporation Limited (DHFL) in the Yes Bank money laundering case. The court ruled DHFL is entitled to immunity under Section 32A of the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC) after its resolution plan's approval. This decision shields the company from prosecution for past offences, but individual liability for former officers and directors remains intact.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:38:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69857e3fe769d12df1d53662_1770358440720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Opens Bank Lending for REITs, Deepening Real Estate Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBI-Opens-Bank-Lending-for-REITs-Deepening-Real-Estate-Capital/69857dcee769d12df1d534dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBI-Opens-Bank-Lending-for-REITs-Deepening-Real-Estate-Capital/69857dcee769d12df1d534dd</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has greenlit direct bank lending to Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs), a significant policy shift aimed at diversifying financing avenues beyond capital markets and providing stable, long-term funding. This move is expected to enhance financial flexibility for the sector. Concurrently, the Monetary Policy Committee, led by Governor Sanjay Malhotra, maintained the benchmark repo rate at 5.25%, signaling a continued focus on assessing economic transmission while supporting growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:36:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69857dcee769d12df1d534dc_1770358980893.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Overhauls Finance Sector: Focus on Resilience and Inclusion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Overhauls-Finance-Sector-Focus-on-Resilience-and-Inclusion/69857d54e769d12df1d52f01</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Overhauls-Finance-Sector-Focus-on-Resilience-and-Inclusion/69857d54e769d12df1d52f01</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has unveiled a comprehensive suite of regulatory and policy reforms designed to bolster customer safeguards, advance financial inclusion, and streamline the ease of doing business for financial entities. Key measures include increased MSME collateral-free loan limits, proposed compensation for small-value fraud victims, regulatory relief for NBFCs and UCBs, and measures to deepen financial markets through revised ECB and VRR frameworks. These initiatives underscore a strategic intent to foster a more robust and competitive financial architecture.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:34:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69857d54e769d12df1d52f00_1770356197834.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Surfaces Revenue Surges 28%, But Net Losses Deepen Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Global-Surfaces-Revenue-Surges-28percent-But-Net-Losses-Deepen-Sharply/69857cdbe769d12df1d52d50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Global-Surfaces-Revenue-Surges-28percent-But-Net-Losses-Deepen-Sharply/69857cdbe769d12df1d52d50</guid><description>Global Surfaces Limited (GSL) reported a robust 28.6% year-over-year revenue growth to ₹593 million in Q3 FY26. However, the company continued to post significant net losses, with a PAT of ₹(33) million and negative margins. For the nine-month period, revenue grew 25.0% to ₹1,878 million, while losses narrowed to ₹(85) million, aided by an improved EBITDA of ₹76 million. Management is implementing focused cost optimization and strategic shifts towards value-added products, expecting gradual benefits.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:32:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69857cdbe769d12df1d52d4f_1770356066623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Spice Lounge Food Works Surges on Experiential Push, Valuation Questions Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Spice-Lounge-Food-Works-Surges-on-Experiential-Push-Valuation-Questions-Loom/69857993e769d12df1d5258c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Spice-Lounge-Food-Works-Surges-on-Experiential-Push-Valuation-Questions-Loom/69857993e769d12df1d5258c</guid><description>Spice Lounge Food Works Limited shares experienced a 5% upper circuit, closing at ₹31.25, following robust H1 FY26 financial results showing a 337% sales increase and 169% profit growth. The company is strategically expanding into the experiential economy via live events managed by its subsidiary, XORA World. Despite a market cap exceeding ₹2,100 crore and substantial long-term returns, exceptionally high valuation multiples and a recent significant shift in shareholding structure present areas for investor scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:18:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69857993e769d12df1d5258b_1770355294340.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Holds Rates Amid India's 7.4% Growth Forecast</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Amid-Indias-74percent-Growth-Forecast/6985791ae769d12df1d52438</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Amid-Indias-74percent-Growth-Forecast/6985791ae769d12df1d52438</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India projects India's GDP to grow by 7.4% for FY26, driven by Union Budget measures and strong exports. Governor Sanjay Malhotra announced the repo rate would remain unchanged at 5.25%, maintaining a neutral stance, as inflation forecasts were marginally revised upwards to 2.1% for FY26. Monetary policy will now be guided by new data from a revised inflation series, with future quarterly projections deferred to April. The Nifty 50 trades at a P/E of 22.2, with market capitalization around $5 trillion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:16:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985791ae769d12df1d52437_1770355557961.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Holds Rates Steady, Eyes Fiscal Health Amidst Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Steady-Eyes-Fiscal-Health-Amidst-Global-Headwinds/698578c4e769d12df1d522c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Steady-Eyes-Fiscal-Health-Amidst-Global-Headwinds/698578c4e769d12df1d522c0</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) kept the repo rate unchanged at 5.25%, retaining a 'neutral' stance. Governor Sanjay Malhotra cited robust GDP growth forecasts (Q1 FY27 at 6.9%, Q2 FY27 at 7%) and benign inflation below the tolerance band. However, the decision reflects a strategic focus on fiscal sustainability and managing geopolitical friction, limiting immediate room for further easing despite significant trade agreements with the EU and US. Analysts expect a sustained 'wait-and-watch' period.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:14:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698578c4e769d12df1d522bf_1770355440956.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amazon's $200B AI Bet Sparks Sell-Off, Signals Fierce Cloud Battle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazons-200B-AI-Bet-Sparks-Sell-Off-Signals-Fierce-Cloud-Battle/698578abe769d12df1d521cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazons-200B-AI-Bet-Sparks-Sell-Off-Signals-Fierce-Cloud-Battle/698578abe769d12df1d521cc</guid><description>Amazon projected over $200 billion in capital expenditures for 2026, primarily targeting AI infrastructure, triggering an 11.5% drop in after-hours trading. This aggressive spending, higher than market expectations, places Amazon in a strategic battle for cloud supremacy, particularly against Google Cloud's accelerating growth. While investors balk at the capital intensity, the investment is framed as essential for maintaining AWS leadership. The company also reported strong advertising growth and a streamlined physical retail approach, contrasting with the heavy AI-related outlays.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:14:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698578abe769d12df1d521cb_1770356196397.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Holds Rates Steady, Flags Resilient Growth Amid Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Steady-Flags-Resilient-Growth-Amid-Global-Headwinds/6985782be769d12df1d52058</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Steady-Flags-Resilient-Growth-Amid-Global-Headwinds/6985782be769d12df1d52058</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) kept the policy repo rate unchanged at 5.25%, marking the third pause in four meetings. Governor Sanjay Malhotra announced revised FY27 GDP growth projections of 6.9% for Q1 and 7.0% for Q2. This decision reflects a strategic pivot towards managing liquidity and ensuring transmission of previous rate cuts, balancing domestic economic resilience against persistent global uncertainties. Inflation remains comfortably below target, providing room for the RBI to monitor evolving economic conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:12:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985782be769d12df1d52057_1770354900417.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Signals Inflation Uptick, Holds Rates Steady Amid Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Signals-Inflation-Uptick-Holds-Rates-Steady-Amid-Growth/698577b3e769d12df1d51ee6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Signals-Inflation-Uptick-Holds-Rates-Steady-Amid-Growth/698577b3e769d12df1d51ee6</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) maintained the policy repo rate at 5.25% on February 6, 2026. While projecting FY26 CPI inflation at 2.1%, the RBI flagged an upward revision for Q4 FY26 to 3.2% and Q1/Q2 FY27 to 4.0% and 4.2% respectively, citing pressures including precious metals. The committee retained a neutral stance, emphasizing data dependency for future actions. Strong domestic growth, buoyed by recent trade deals with the EU and US, continues to be a key economic driver, though external headwinds from geopolitical events are noted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698577b3e769d12df1d51ee5_1770354845108.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Pauses Rate Cuts, Shifts Focus to Yields, Liquidity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Pauses-Rate-Cuts-Shifts-Focus-to-Yields-Liquidity/698575d6e769d12df1d51c14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Pauses-Rate-Cuts-Shifts-Focus-to-Yields-Liquidity/698575d6e769d12df1d51c14</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India maintained its benchmark repo rate at 5.25%, signaling a pause in its aggressive 2025 easing cycle and adopting a neutral stance. The Monetary Policy Committee is now prioritizing liquidity management and yield-curve stability over additional rate adjustments. This strategic shift occurs against a backdrop of robust economic growth projections for FY26, evolving inflation dynamics, significant government borrowing, and structural tailwinds from recent trade agreements with the U.S. and European Union.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:02:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698575d6e769d12df1d51c13_1770354252177.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Awfis Sees 20% Revenue Surge, Expands Margins; Revises Seat Growth Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Awfis-Sees-20percent-Revenue-Surge-Expands-Margins-Revises-Seat-Growth-Target/6985755de769d12df1d51ac5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Awfis-Sees-20percent-Revenue-Surge-Expands-Margins-Revises-Seat-Growth-Target/6985755de769d12df1d51ac5</guid><description>Awfis Space Solutions posted a robust Q3 FY26, with operating revenue climbing 20% YoY to ₹382 crore and EBITDA margins expanding by 270 basis points to 36.5%. The company added over 8,000 seats, increasing operational capacity to 152,000, and saw overall occupancy rise to 75%. Management revised FY26 seat addition guidance downwards to 32,000-33,000, signalling a strategic focus on occupancy and profitability. Growth was primarily driven by the co-working segment, bolstered by strong traction from GCC and enterprise clients.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:00:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985755de769d12df1d51ac4_1770354142737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trade Deal Boosts Metals &amp; Energy Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Trade-Deal-Boosts-Metals-and-Energy-Amid-Market-Volatility/698574e2e769d12df1d51930</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Trade-Deal-Boosts-Metals-and-Energy-Amid-Market-Volatility/698574e2e769d12df1d51930</guid><description>Indian equity markets navigated significant volatility last week, influenced by the Union Budget and a US-India trade agreement. While the Nifty fluctuated between 24,572 and 26,341, the trade deal's tariff reductions offer a tangible boost to industrial sectors. Bajaj Broking highlighted Lloyds Metals and Energy and JSW Energy as key picks, projecting substantial returns. Lloyds Metals &amp; Energy reported record quarterly earnings, while JSW Energy showed positive technical signals, positioning both for potential upside despite broader economic uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:58:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698574e2e769d12df1d5192f_1770353997931.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Firms on Trade Deal Hopes; RBI Policy Decision Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Firms-on-Trade-Deal-Hopes-RBI-Policy-Decision-Looms/6985746be769d12df1d517df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Firms-on-Trade-Deal-Hopes-RBI-Policy-Decision-Looms/6985746be769d12df1d517df</guid><description>The Indian rupee strengthened by 9 paise to 90.25 against the US dollar on Friday, buoyed by tentative optimism surrounding an India-US trade deal. However, market sentiment remains cautious as investors await the Reserve Bank of India's monetary policy announcement later today. Equities opened subdued, with the Nifty 50 and BSE Sensex trading lower in early deals, reflecting investor hesitancy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:56:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985746be769d12df1d517de_1770354295087.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCX Gold Plummets 23%, Silver Sheds ₹2 Lakh From Peak</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Gold-Plummets-23percent-Silver-Sheds-2-Lakh-From-Peak/6985719ae769d12df1d514f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Gold-Plummets-23percent-Silver-Sheds-2-Lakh-From-Peak/6985719ae769d12df1d514f2</guid><description>MCX Gold and Silver futures experienced sharp declines, down 23.3% and nearly ₹2 lakh from record highs, respectively. This plunge follows significant losses in international markets, driven by profit-taking, a stronger US dollar, and increased margin requirements on exchanges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:44:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985719ae769d12df1d514f1_1770353270044.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LIC Jumps 5% on Q3 Profit; Targets Face Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Jumps-5percent-on-Q3-Profit-Targets-Face-Scrutiny/698570ade769d12df1d51359</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Jumps-5percent-on-Q3-Profit-Targets-Face-Scrutiny/698570ade769d12df1d51359</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) shares climbed 4.3% on Friday, driven by a 17.5% surge in Q3 FY26 net profit to ₹12,930 crore and a 17% rise in net premium income to ₹1.26 trillion. This performance bolstered analyst confidence, with JM Financial and Antique Stock Broking maintaining 'Buy' ratings and reiterating price targets around ₹1,100-₹1,111. Despite robust growth figures, particularly in individual APE, the stock's substantial rally prompts scrutiny regarding valuation sustainability against an evolving competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:40:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698570ade769d12df1d51358_1770353150099.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Breaches $60K Amidst Global Liquidity Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Breaches-60K-Amidst-Global-Liquidity-Squeeze/69857031e769d12df1d5120e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Breaches-60K-Amidst-Global-Liquidity-Squeeze/69857031e769d12df1d5120e</guid><description>Bitcoin experienced a dramatic price decline, testing the critical $60,000 support level and hitting a 16-month low. The sell-off is attributed to a confluence of factors, including extensive liquidations exceeding $1 billion, significant outflows from spot Bitcoin ETFs totaling billions monthly, and a widespread risk-off sentiment mirroring downturns in technology stocks and precious metals. This broad market contraction has seen the total cryptocurrency market cap shrink by trillions from its peak, underscoring a systemic liquidity squeeze rather than asset-specific stress. Despite brief recoveries, investor sentiment remains cautious, with markets closely monitoring global risk trends and liquidity conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:38:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69857031e769d12df1d5120d_1770352840148.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Regulators Tighten Grip: Mining &amp; Industry Face Rising ESG Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Regulators-Tighten-Grip-Mining-and-Industry-Face-Rising-ESG-Costs/69856f44e769d12df1d50bff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Regulators-Tighten-Grip-Mining-and-Industry-Face-Rising-ESG-Costs/69856f44e769d12df1d50bff</guid><description>India's National Green Tribunal (NGT) is escalating enforcement, with recent orders targeting illegal river mining in Chhattisgarh and environmental norm violations by Jindal Steel &amp; Power Limited (JSPL) at its Utkal C-Block coal mine. These actions highlight a broader trend of increased regulatory oversight and rising ESG compliance costs for resource-intensive industries. JSPL, a large-cap entity with a market capitalization around ₹118,000-120,000 crore and a TTM P/E ratio fluctuating between approximately 24x and 59x, faces specific scrutiny. The broader mining sector's average P/E sits near 18.94x, while the infrastructure sector's P/E is around 21.6x, indicating potential valuation sensitivities. Companies must navigate heightened environmental, social, and governance (ESG) demands, impacting operational expenditures and investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:34:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69856f44e769d12df1d50bfe_1770352515583.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty, Sensex Dip Ahead of RBI Policy; Global Cues Weigh</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Sensex-Dip-Ahead-of-RBI-Policy-Global-Cues-Weigh/69856d61e769d12df1d50512</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Sensex-Dip-Ahead-of-RBI-Policy-Global-Cues-Weigh/69856d61e769d12df1d50512</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks Nifty50 and BSE Sensex opened lower on Thursday, caught in a cautious mood ahead of the Reserve Bank of India's monetary policy announcement. Global markets also signaled weakness, with major Asian indices and US futures trading in the red. Analysts highlight concerns over foreign institutional investor (FII) selling and a risk-off sentiment globally. Investors are anticipating the RBI's stance on interest rates and its outlook on economic growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:26:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69856d61e769d12df1d50511_1770352507150.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent's Margin Surge: A Tactical Value Play Amidst Retail Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trents-Margin-Surge-A-Tactical-Value-Play-Amidst-Retail-Shifts/69856b85e769d12df1d502f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trents-Margin-Surge-A-Tactical-Value-Play-Amidst-Retail-Shifts/69856b85e769d12df1d502f5</guid><description>Trent Limited posted strong Q3 FY26 results, notably improving EBITDA margins by approximately 200 basis points year-over-year to 20.2%, driven by cost efficiencies and operational leverage. This performance occurred despite a moderated revenue growth of 15% YoY, influenced by consumer spending shifts post-GST adjustments. The company's aggressive network expansion continues, with a ~30% rise in store count and a 40% increase in business area. Despite a ~28% stock price correction over the past year, Trent's current P/E of around 80-90x is at the lower end of its historical trading range, presenting a compelling valuation thesis.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:18:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69856b85e769d12df1d502f4_1770351725084.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>