<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:05:48 +0000</pubDate><item><title>AI Chatbots Spark Alarming Psychosis Cases: Doctors Raise Urgent Mental Health Concerns!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Chatbots-Spark-Alarming-Psychosis-Cases-Doctors-Raise-Urgent-Mental-Health-Concerns/6950a91b4342f77179da5371</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Chatbots-Spark-Alarming-Psychosis-Cases-Doctors-Raise-Urgent-Mental-Health-Concerns/6950a91b4342f77179da5371</guid><description>Top psychiatrists are increasingly linking AI chatbot use, like OpenAI's ChatGPT, to psychosis cases. Experts have documented dozens of patients exhibiting delusions and severe mental distress after prolonged AI conversations. While companies like OpenAI are enhancing safety features, these incidents highlight potential risks of highly interactive AI, prompting concerns about societal impact and leading to wrongful death lawsuits.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:41:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950a91b4342f77179da5370_1766894042917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 में किस सेक्टर पर दांव? Devina Mehra ने बताई IT, Currency Risks की पूरी कहानी!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-म-कस-सकटर-पर-दव-Devina-Mehra-न-बतई-IT-Currency-Risks-क-पर-कहन/6950a2444342f77179da4d7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-म-कस-सकटर-पर-दव-Devina-Mehra-न-बतई-IT-Currency-Risks-क-पर-कहन/6950a2444342f77179da4d7a</guid><description>First Global की Devina Mehra का 2026 के लिए बड़ा विश्लेषण: इंडेक्स टारगेट पर ध्यान देने के बजाय IT सर्विसेज जैसे सेक्टर्स पर फोकस करें। उन्होंने करेंसी उतार-चढ़ाव, GST और टैरिफ जैसे पॉलिसी जोखिमों को निवेश के लिए महत्वपूर्ण बताया है।</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:12:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950a2444342f77179da4d79_1766892421851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026-27: Demand-Led Growth &amp; RBI Synergy to Power Economy - EY Forecasts!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-27-Demand-Led-Growth-and-RBI-Synergy-to-Power-Economy-EY-Forecasts/69509a1e4342f77179da48a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-27-Demand-Led-Growth-and-RBI-Synergy-to-Power-Economy-EY-Forecasts/69509a1e4342f77179da48a6</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 is poised to boost growth by fostering domestic demand through fiscal measures, aligning with the RBI's supportive monetary policy. EY's report forecasts sustained 6.5% growth, dependent on private investment and eased supply chains. The government aims to meet its 4.4% fiscal deficit target via expenditure cuts and non-tax revenue, despite potential tax collection challenges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 02:38:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69509a1e4342f77179da48a5_1766890086068.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI BOOM SHAKEN? Michael Burry's Massive Bet Against Nvidia &amp; Palantir Sparks Bubble Fears!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-BOOM-SHAKEN-Michael-Burrys-Massive-Bet-Against-Nvidia-and-Palantir-Sparks-Bubble-Fears/6950996a4342f77179da47b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-BOOM-SHAKEN-Michael-Burrys-Massive-Bet-Against-Nvidia-and-Palantir-Sparks-Bubble-Fears/6950996a4342f77179da47b8</guid><description>Investor Michael Burry, famous for his "Big Short" bet, is now targeting AI giants Nvidia and Palantir Technologies, warning of a market bubble. He has placed significant bets against these companies, drawing parallels to the dot-com era. While his timing is often debated, Burry's contrarian stance is capturing attention from investors anxious about the rapid rise of AI stocks and their valuation disconnect from reality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 02:33:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950996a4342f77179da47b7_1766889954576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Electric Trucks Revolution: Battery Swapping Ignites India's Logistics Green Transformation!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Electric-Trucks-Revolution-Battery-Swapping-Ignites-Indias-Logistics-Green-Transformation/69508dd44342f77179da2a4e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Electric-Trucks-Revolution-Battery-Swapping-Ignites-Indias-Logistics-Green-Transformation/69508dd44342f77179da2a4e</guid><description>Battery swapping technology, previously for two-wheelers, is now being deployed for 55-tonne electric trucks in India by Blue Energy Motors and Montra Electric. This innovation aims to achieve price parity with diesel trucks by removing battery costs and drastically reducing charging times, promising to decarbonize India's massive freight sector and boost operational efficiency in logistics.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:45:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69508dd44342f77179da2a4d_1766887022622.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Beyond Buffett: Greg Abel's 5 Bold Moves to Shape Berkshire Hathaway's $334B Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Beyond-Buffett-Greg-Abels-5-Bold-Moves-to-Shape-Berkshire-Hathaways-334B-Future/69508d194342f77179da299f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Beyond-Buffett-Greg-Abels-5-Bold-Moves-to-Shape-Berkshire-Hathaways-334B-Future/69508d194342f77179da299f</guid><description>Warren Buffett is transitioning leadership at Berkshire Hathaway, with Greg Abel set to become CEO by year-end 2025. Abel, a trained accountant and former head of Berkshire Hathaway Energy, is expected to bring a more active management style and potentially shift investment focus toward technology and renewables, leveraging the company's record $334 billion cash pile. His tenure, beginning January 1, 2026, marks a new chapter focused on operational rigor and substance over showmanship, aiming to maintain the conglomerate's growth engine.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:41:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69508d194342f77179da299e_1766886752534.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways Unleashes Mega Safety Budget! ₹1.3 Lakh Crore Boost for 'Kavach' — Top Stocks to Watch Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Railways-Unleashes-Mega-Safety-Budget-13-Lakh-Crore-Boost-for-Kavach-Top-Stocks-to-Watch-Now/6950870e4342f77179da25ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Railways-Unleashes-Mega-Safety-Budget-13-Lakh-Crore-Boost-for-Kavach-Top-Stocks-to-Watch-Now/6950870e4342f77179da25ed</guid><description>Indian Railways is planning a record rail safety budget exceeding ₹1.3 lakh crore for FY27, a significant increase aimed at enhancing safety and preventing accidents. This allocation, potentially half of the total railway capex, is expected to strongly benefit companies manufacturing the indigenous 'Kavach' train collision avoidance system. Key players like HBL Engineering, Kernex Microsystems, and Concord Control Systems are poised to be major beneficiaries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:14:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950870e4342f77179da25ec_1766885211311.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hidden Indian Gems: 2 Debt-Free Smallcaps Poised for 2026 Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hidden-Indian-Gems-2-Debt-Free-Smallcaps-Poised-for-2026-Growth/695086784342f77179da2525</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hidden-Indian-Gems-2-Debt-Free-Smallcaps-Poised-for-2026-Growth/695086784342f77179da2525</guid><description>Two smallcap companies, Jyoti Resins and Adhesives Ltd. and Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd., are gaining investor attention for their robust financial health and growth potential. Both operate with virtually no debt, boasting high Return on Capital Employed (ROCE) significantly above industry medians. Jyoti Resins, known for its EURO 7000 adhesive brand, has seen over 800% stock growth since 2020. Garuda Construction, a civil engineering specialist, has demonstrated impressive EBITDA and profit growth. With ambitious expansion plans, these firms are recommended for investor watchlists targeting 2026.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:14:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695086784342f77179da2524_1766885134676.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Rally Cools! 3 Indian Micro-Cap Stocks Poised for Explosive 2026 Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Rally-Cools-3-Indian-Micro-Cap-Stocks-Poised-for-Explosive-2026-Growth/695086274342f77179da24bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Rally-Cools-3-Indian-Micro-Cap-Stocks-Poised-for-Explosive-2026-Growth/695086274342f77179da24bc</guid><description>While gold and silver saw massive rallies in 2025, India's major stock indices like Nifty 50 and BSE Sensex delivered modest returns. Amidst this, three micro-cap stocks—Strides Pharma Science Ltd, Cemindia Projects Ltd, and Sandur Manganese and Iron Ores Ltd—have been identified using key technical indicators as potential outperformers for 2026. These selections, based on signals like RSI, MACD, and ADX, suggest significant long-term potential, especially after notable price breakouts and consolidation phases.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:14:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695086274342f77179da24bb_1766885006222.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Wines Conquer Global Markets: Fruit-Based Brews Spark Export Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Wines-Conquer-Global-Markets-Fruit-Based-Brews-Spark-Export-Boom/695079e74342f77179da1ff9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Wines-Conquer-Global-Markets-Fruit-Based-Brews-Spark-Export-Boom/695079e74342f77179da1ff9</guid><description>India's non-grape wines, made from fruits like jamun, mango, and apple, are achieving significant export success, reaching markets like the US, UAE, and UK. Exports surged to a record $6.7 million in the first seven months of the fiscal year, more than doubling the previous year's performance. This growth is driven by companies like Sula Vineyards and newer players, as they focus on international markets due to tepid domestic sales.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:21:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695079e74342f77179da1ff8_1766881855363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>