<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:27:26 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Bank Nifty Rockets Past 59,000! Recovery Rally or Just a Pause? Analysts Reveal Key Levels</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-Nifty-Rockets-Past-59000-Recovery-Rally-or-Just-a-Pause-Analysts-Reveal-Key-Levels/69536fc24342f77179e59c93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-Nifty-Rockets-Past-59000-Recovery-Rally-or-Just-a-Pause-Analysts-Reveal-Key-Levels/69536fc24342f77179e59c93</guid><description>The Nifty Bank index bounced back strongly, recovering over 300 points from its day's low to briefly cross the 59,000 mark, ending a four-session losing streak. Axis Bank and Canara Bank led the gains, while ICICI Bank and HDFC Bank faced declines. Analysts anticipate consolidation between 58,500 and 60,100, advising caution and highlighting crucial support and resistance levels for future movements.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:14:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69536fc24342f77179e59c92_1767076002646.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Russian Oil to India Hits 3-Year Low: Will Reliance Industries' Resumption Stem the Decline?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Russian-Oil-to-India-Hits-3-Year-Low-Will-Reliance-Industries-Resumption-Stem-the-Decline/69536ee14342f77179e5999b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Russian-Oil-to-India-Hits-3-Year-Low-Will-Reliance-Industries-Resumption-Stem-the-Decline/69536ee14342f77179e5999b</guid><description>Russian crude oil deliveries to India are on track for a three-year low in December, averaging about 1.1 million barrels per day. This decline is driven by heightened US scrutiny and sanctions impacting Russian energy producers. While Reliance Industries Ltd. has resumed purchases from non-blacklisted Russian suppliers, potentially limiting further drops early next year, other refiners like Mangalore Refinery and Petrochemicals Ltd. have ceased imports this month.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:11:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69536ee14342f77179e5999a_1767075615708.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹2,028 Crore Solar Order: Grew Solar to Power UP Uttar Pradesh with NTPC Renewables Deal!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Massive-2028-Crore-Solar-Order-Grew-Solar-to-Power-UP-Uttar-Pradesh-with-NTPC-Renewables-Deal/69536e6e4342f77179e59844</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Massive-2028-Crore-Solar-Order-Grew-Solar-to-Power-UP-Uttar-Pradesh-with-NTPC-Renewables-Deal/69536e6e4342f77179e59844</guid><description>Grew Solar, a solar module manufacturer, has secured a significant ₹2,028 crore contract from NTPC Renewable Energy Limited. The deal involves supplying approximately 1,464.5 MW of high-efficiency solar PV modules for deployment across multiple sites in Uttar Pradesh. This order highlights Grew Solar's growing capabilities and commitment to India's renewable energy expansion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:08:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69536e6e4342f77179e59843_1767075515765.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economy on Fire: 2025 Set for Historic Growth &amp; Lowest Inflation Ever!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-on-Fire-2025-Set-for-Historic-Growth-and-Lowest-Inflation-Ever/69536d2f4342f77179e594fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-on-Fire-2025-Set-for-Historic-Growth-and-Lowest-Inflation-Ever/69536d2f4342f77179e594fa</guid><description>India is poised for a historic economic year in 2025, with its GDP growing strongly at 8.2% in Q2 FY25-26 and inflation hitting a remarkable low of 0.71% by November. Unemployment has also dropped to 4.7%, with exports showing robust growth. The government hails this as a "Goldilocks moment," solidifying India's position as the world's fourth-largest economy with a bright future outlook.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:02:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69536d2f4342f77179e594f9_1767075212538.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eternal Stock Plummets 25% From Peak: Is a Competitor's IPO and CFO Exit Triggering Investor Panic?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eternal-Stock-Plummets-25percent-From-Peak-Is-a-Competitors-IPO-and-CFO-Exit-Triggering-Investor-Panic/69536a264342f77179e58e9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eternal-Stock-Plummets-25percent-From-Peak-Is-a-Competitors-IPO-and-CFO-Exit-Triggering-Investor-Panic/69536a264342f77179e58e9b</guid><description>Eternal, the parent company of Zomato and Blinkit, has seen its shares drop 25% from a record high, hitting a five-month low. The decline is attributed to the resignation of Blinkit's CFO and intensifying competition in the quick commerce sector, alongside a rival's IPO filing. Despite these near-term concerns, analysts maintain a positive long-term view, citing robust financials and a revised target price of ₹400.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:46:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69536a264342f77179e58e9a_1767074588325.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vijay Kedia's Fund Buys Stake in Mangalam Drugs; Shares Jump to 5% Upper Circuit!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Vijay-Kedias-Fund-Buys-Stake-in-Mangalam-Drugs-Shares-Jump-to-5percent-Upper-Circuit/6953697e4342f77179e58cd9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Vijay-Kedias-Fund-Buys-Stake-in-Mangalam-Drugs-Shares-Jump-to-5percent-Upper-Circuit/6953697e4342f77179e58cd9</guid><description>Kedia Securities, the investment arm of ace investor Vijay Kedia, has acquired a significant stake in Mangalam Drugs and Organics. This move triggered a sharp rise in the company's stock, leading it to hit the 5 per cent upper circuit on the BSE at ₹26.28 per share, signaling renewed investor interest.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:45:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953697e4342f77179e58cd8_1767074334983.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Bubble Warning! Expert Predicts Massive Crash: Is Your Portfolio Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Bubble-Warning-Expert-Predicts-Massive-Crash-Is-Your-Portfolio-Safe/6953681b4342f77179e589b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Bubble-Warning-Expert-Predicts-Massive-Crash-Is-Your-Portfolio-Safe/6953681b4342f77179e589b0</guid><description>Global strategist Amit Goel warns that silver's recent price surge is a "classic commodity bubble" detached from fundamental realities, comparable to historical market manias like the 2008 oil peak. Despite potential short-term advances towards $100, he anticipates a severe 50-60% correction, noting speculative drivers and ETF outflows over genuine investment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:40:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953681b4342f77179e589af_1767074012418.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin's $90K Dream Shattered: Why Prices Plummeted Amidst Thin Year-End Liquidity!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoins-90K-Dream-Shattered-Why-Prices-Plummeted-Amidst-Thin-Year-End-Liquidity/6953675c4342f77179e58739</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoins-90K-Dream-Shattered-Why-Prices-Plummeted-Amidst-Thin-Year-End-Liquidity/6953675c4342f77179e58739</guid><description>Bitcoin's price dropped 3.23% in a day to $87,264 after failing to hold above $90,000, leading to over $100 billion wiped from the crypto market cap. Analysts cite thin year-end liquidity and triggered long liquidations as key reasons for the decline. Immediate support is seen around $87,000–$87,300, with short-term trading expected between $87K and $89K. Volatility affected other major cryptocurrencies, though some smaller tokens saw gains.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:40:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953675c4342f77179e58738_1767073698360.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Car Recall Crisis Solved? 8-Year Low Signals Quality Leap, But Who Benefited Most?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Car-Recall-Crisis-Solved-8-Year-Low-Signals-Quality-Leap-But-Who-Benefited-Most/695367e34342f77179e588c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Car-Recall-Crisis-Solved-8-Year-Low-Signals-Quality-Leap-But-Who-Benefited-Most/695367e34342f77179e588c9</guid><description>Vehicle recalls in India hit an eight-year low in 2025, with just 119,173 units recalled. Industry experts attribute this significant decline to enhanced manufacturing quality and stricter internal checks by automakers. Maruti Suzuki led recalls with nearly 40,000 units of the Grand Vitara, while Skoda-Volkswagen, Toyota, Mercedes-Benz, and Kia also issued recalls for various safety-related defects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:40:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695367e34342f77179e588c8_1767073874099.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Inflation Tumbles! New CPI Series &amp; RBI Policy Shake-Up Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Inflation-Tumbles-New-CPI-Series-and-RBI-Policy-Shake-Up-Ahead/695366024342f77179e583c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Inflation-Tumbles-New-CPI-Series-and-RBI-Policy-Shake-Up-Ahead/695366024342f77179e583c2</guid><description>India anticipates subdued inflation through 2026, driven by falling food prices and GST cuts. A new, more accurate Consumer Price Index (CPI) series is launching in February 2026. This low inflation trend provides the Reserve Bank of India room for potential rate cuts, though future projections suggest a stabilization around 4-5% in 2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:33:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695366024342f77179e583c1_1767073645135.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VST Tillers Rockets 70% in 6 Months to New Highs – What's Powering This Tractor Stock's Incredible Run?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/VST-Tillers-Rockets-70percent-in-6-Months-to-New-Highs-Whats-Powering-This-Tractor-Stocks-Incredible-Run/695362c14342f77179e576d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/VST-Tillers-Rockets-70percent-in-6-Months-to-New-Highs-Whats-Powering-This-Tractor-Stocks-Incredible-Run/695362c14342f77179e576d7</guid><description>VST Tillers Tractors shares have soared to a new peak of ₹6,225, marking an impressive 70% surge in just six months. This growth significantly outperforms the BSE Sensex. The company reported record turnover and EBITDA for H1FY26, driven by strong domestic tractor sales and a remarkable 42% increase in Power Weeder demand. Positive industry trends like farm mechanization and government support are further bolstering the outlook for this smallcap tractor manufacturer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:12:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695362c14342f77179e576d6_1767072518720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Finance Stock Skyrockets After Massive FDI Deal &amp; Top Rating Upgrade – What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Stock-Skyrockets-After-Massive-FDI-Deal-and-Top-Rating-Upgrade-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/695362484342f77179e5756c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Stock-Skyrockets-After-Massive-FDI-Deal-and-Top-Rating-Upgrade-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/695362484342f77179e5756c</guid><description>Shriram Finance shares rose 2.2% after Care Ratings upgraded its debt instruments to 'CARE AAA'. The company also announced a significant ₹39,618 crore ($4.4 billion) preferential issue to Japan's MUFG Bank for a 20% stake, boosting growth forecasts and capital adequacy. The stock has rallied 13% in the past month.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:12:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695362484342f77179e5756b_1767072393710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Deccan Gold Mines Shares PLUNGE 10% After Rights Issue: Is This a Buying Opportunity or a Warning Sign?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Deccan-Gold-Mines-Shares-PLUNGE-10percent-After-Rights-Issue-Is-This-a-Buying-Opportunity-or-a-Warning-Sign/6953629b4342f77179e57677</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Deccan-Gold-Mines-Shares-PLUNGE-10percent-After-Rights-Issue-Is-This-a-Buying-Opportunity-or-a-Warning-Sign/6953629b4342f77179e57677</guid><description>Deccan Gold Mines saw its share price drop by nearly 10% on Tuesday due to increased selling pressure following its rights issue. The stock is approaching its 52-week low, trading below its 200-day moving average. This downturn coincides with global volatility in non-ferrous metals. The company recently approved allotting 39.3 million shares at ₹80 each and is also exploring a tungsten project in Spain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:11:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953629b4342f77179e57676_1767072574666.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Gains on Strong IIP Data; Watch Out for FII Outflows &amp; Market Dip!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Gains-on-Strong-IIP-Data-Watch-Out-for-FII-Outflows-and-Market-Dip/6953624b4342f77179e575a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Gains-on-Strong-IIP-Data-Watch-Out-for-FII-Outflows-and-Market-Dip/6953624b4342f77179e575a1</guid><description>The Indian rupee strengthened by 3 paise to trade at 89.95 against the US dollar in early Tuesday trade. This rise was supported by a weaker US dollar globally and robust Industrial Production (IIP) data, which hit a 25-month high of 6.7% in November. However, significant foreign institutional investor outflows, slightly elevated crude oil prices, and a weak opening in domestic stock markets limited the rupee's upward movement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:11:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953624b4342f77179e575a0_1767072550449.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Young Indians Embrace Early Credit &amp; Homeownership: PB Fintech Data Reveals Major Shift!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Young-Indians-Embrace-Early-Credit-and-Homeownership-PB-Fintech-Data-Reveals-Major-Shift/6953615d4342f77179e5729b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Young-Indians-Embrace-Early-Credit-and-Homeownership-PB-Fintech-Data-Reveals-Major-Shift/6953615d4342f77179e5729b</guid><description>PB Fintech's analysis shows younger Indians are entering the credit market earlier and opting for secured products. Home loan borrowers under 30 have nearly doubled since 2022, while secured credit card growth surged 62%. Delhi NCR and Mumbai lead these trends, indicating a more informed and deliberate approach to credit among the youth, potentially fostering healthier credit profiles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:11:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953615d4342f77179e5729a_1767072167335.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DBS Economist's Bold Prediction: India's 10% GDP Surge Ahead! Is US Uncertainty the Only Roadblock?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/DBS-Economists-Bold-Prediction-Indias-10percent-GDP-Surge-Ahead-Is-US-Uncertainty-the-Only-Roadblock/695360ce4342f77179e570b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/DBS-Economists-Bold-Prediction-Indias-10percent-GDP-Surge-Ahead-Is-US-Uncertainty-the-Only-Roadblock/695360ce4342f77179e570b1</guid><description>DBS Group Chief Economist Taimur Baig forecasts India's nominal GDP growth to hit 10% in 2026, expecting strong corporate earnings. He advises Indian businesses to diversify away from the US market due to its uncertainties, recommending focus on the Middle East, Europe, and East Asia. Baig views foreign private equity exits positively, signaling market maturity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:06:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695360ce4342f77179e570b0_1767072029517.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sundrex Oil Company IPO: Shares Plummet 20% on Debut! Investors Face Immediate Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sundrex-Oil-Company-IPO-Shares-Plummet-20percent-on-Debut-Investors-Face-Immediate-Losses/695360894342f77179e5701d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sundrex-Oil-Company-IPO-Shares-Plummet-20percent-on-Debut-Investors-Face-Immediate-Losses/695360894342f77179e5701d</guid><description>Sundrex Oil Company made a weak market debut on December 30, listing on the NSE Emerge platform at Rs 68.80 per share. This represents a steep 20 percent discount to its IPO price of Rs 86, resulting in an initial market capitalization of Rs 92.15 crore and immediate paper losses for investors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:06:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695360894342f77179e5701c_1767072062441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Future: Global Giants Pledge $100 Billion! What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Future-Global-Giants-Pledge-100-Billion-Whats-Next/695360764342f77179e56fc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Future-Global-Giants-Pledge-100-Billion-Whats-Next/695360764342f77179e56fc3</guid><description>Major global tech leaders like Amazon, Microsoft, and Google are investing nearly $100 billion in India's AI ecosystem. This significant capital infusion focuses on data centers, cloud platforms, and chip design, positioning India as a strategic AI hub. Driven by corporate demand for AI at scale and geopolitical considerations, the investment aims to bolster local infrastructure despite challenges like talent scarcity and energy needs. Key trends for 2026 include increased private equity funding and a shift towards silicon and data center growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:06:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695360764342f77179e56fc2_1767071940564.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kerala's Tech Revolution: 'Thirike' Campaign Invites Global Talent Home, Sparks Investment Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Keralas-Tech-Revolution-Thirike-Campaign-Invites-Global-Talent-Home-Sparks-Investment-Boom/69535e6e4342f77179e56aa8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Keralas-Tech-Revolution-Thirike-Campaign-Invites-Global-Talent-Home-Sparks-Investment-Boom/69535e6e4342f77179e56aa8</guid><description>Kerala Startup Mission (KSUM) launches the 'Thirike' campaign to build a database of tech professionals working outside the state, aiming to attract IT/ITES investments. KSUM plans to replicate IvyCap Ventures' model by creating diaspora-funded venture capital, and is developing its own GPU system for startups. The state also seeks sustainable energy solutions for future data centers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 05:01:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69535e6e4342f77179e56aa7_1767071404300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Bond Market's 2025 Rollercoaster: Will 2026 Bring Calm or Chaos?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Bond-Markets-2025-Rollercoaster-Will-2026-Bring-Calm-or-Chaos/69535cb34342f77179e56418</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Bond-Markets-2025-Rollercoaster-Will-2026-Bring-Calm-or-Chaos/69535cb34342f77179e56418</guid><description>The Indian bond market experienced a dramatic shift in 2025, starting with strong gains driven by RBI rate cuts and fiscal discipline, only to reverse sharply in the second half. Factors like rupee depreciation, concerns over fiscal trajectory, and unfavorable supply-demand dynamics have led to volatility and a widening yield curve, leaving investors questioning if stability will return by 2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:45:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69535cb34342f77179e56417_1767070973201.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Ports Tumbles Below Critical 4-Month Support! ICICI Bank, Asahi India Also Signal Danger – What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Adani-Ports-Tumbles-Below-Critical-4-Month-Support-ICICI-Bank-Asahi-India-Also-Signal-Danger-Whats-Next/69535c3a4342f77179e562be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Adani-Ports-Tumbles-Below-Critical-4-Month-Support-ICICI-Bank-Asahi-India-Also-Signal-Danger-Whats-Next/69535c3a4342f77179e562be</guid><description>Adani Ports has declined over 4% in December, slipping below its 20-day and 50-day moving averages. Crucially, the stock broke below the Supertrend line indicator for the first time in almost four months. Similarly, ICICI Bank and Asahi India Glass also closed below this key technical indicator, suggesting a potential negative trend shift for investors to monitor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:37:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69535c3a4342f77179e562bd_1767070858801.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal's 2026 Stock Picks Revealed! Bharti Airtel, SBI, HCLTech Among Top Bets for Market Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Motilal-Oswals-2026-Stock-Picks-Revealed-Bharti-Airtel-SBI-HCLTech-Among-Top-Bets-for-Market-Recovery/69535b6c4342f77179e5603f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Motilal-Oswals-2026-Stock-Picks-Revealed-Bharti-Airtel-SBI-HCLTech-Among-Top-Bets-for-Market-Recovery/69535b6c4342f77179e5603f</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Wealth Management forecasts a strong recovery and steady growth for Indian equities in 2026, driven by improving corporate earnings and supportive policies. They highlight long-term structural growth factors like favourable demographics and digital adoption. The firm expects Nifty earnings growth to bounce significantly to 9% in FY26E. Key investment themes include Financials, Consumption, Manufacturing, and Digital/Healthcare. Motilal Oswal has identified specific stock picks for 2026, including Bharti Airtel, State Bank of India (SBI), HCLTech, TVS Motor, Max Financial, Biocon, JK Cement, Poonawalla Fincorp, and Privi Speciality, along with target prices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:37:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69535b6c4342f77179e5603e_1767070826212.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indigo Paints Soars: Motilal Oswal Sees Big Demand Comeback &amp; Raises Target!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indigo-Paints-Soars-Motilal-Oswal-Sees-Big-Demand-Comeback-and-Raises-Target/69535bc84342f77179e56191</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indigo-Paints-Soars-Motilal-Oswal-Sees-Big-Demand-Comeback-and-Raises-Target/69535bc84342f77179e56191</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services Limited reiterates a 'Buy' rating on Indigo Paints with a target price of ₹1,450. The brokerage anticipates a significant demand recovery beyond the current quarter, expecting Indigo Paints to outpace industry growth through expanded distribution and brand appeal, particularly in non-metro markets. Easing competition and potential margin improvements further strengthen the positive outlook.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:37:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69535bc84342f77179e56190_1767070803261.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty 500's Wild Ride: 2025's Shocking Wealth Creators &amp; Biggest Losers Revealed! Are YOUR Stocks Among Them?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-500s-Wild-Ride-2025s-Shocking-Wealth-Creators-and-Biggest-Losers-Revealed-Are-YOUR-Stocks-Among-Them/69535b614342f77179e55ff8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-500s-Wild-Ride-2025s-Shocking-Wealth-Creators-and-Biggest-Losers-Revealed-Are-YOUR-Stocks-Among-Them/69535b614342f77179e55ff8</guid><description>India's Nifty 500 index ended 2025 with mixed results, up 5.84%, amidst global challenges. Force Motors surged 191% to become the top wealth creator, while Tejas Networks plunged 61.6% as the biggest wealth destroyer. Experts anticipate a favorable year for small and mid-cap stocks in 2026 due to attractive valuations and strong domestic investor flows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:37:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69535b614342f77179e55ff7_1767070774060.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Energy Exchange (IEX) Stock Plummets! Analyst Issues Dire 'Sell on Rally' Advice as Regulatory Storm Brews!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indian-Energy-Exchange-IEX-Stock-Plummets-Analyst-Issues-Dire-Sell-on-Rally-Advice-as-Regulatory-Storm-Brews/69535a724342f77179e55cc5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indian-Energy-Exchange-IEX-Stock-Plummets-Analyst-Issues-Dire-Sell-on-Rally-Advice-as-Regulatory-Storm-Brews/69535a724342f77179e55cc5</guid><description>Indian Energy Exchange (IEX) shares are facing intense pressure due to significant regulatory challenges from the Central Electricity Regulatory Commission (CERC). Reports suggest CERC is introducing a framework for Virtual Power Purchase Agreements (VPPAs) and may slash transaction fees by up to 25%, impacting IEX's market dominance and profitability. Analyst Pradip Halder of PHD Capital strongly advises selling IEX on any bounce, citing weak charts and potential further declines towards Rs 110-115 if key support levels break. Investor sentiment remains cautious amidst policy uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:36:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69535a724342f77179e55cc4_1767070557240.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking Prediction: Petronet LNG Set for Massive 44% Surge? Brokerage Names 2026 'Top Pick'!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Shocking-Prediction-Petronet-LNG-Set-for-Massive-44percent-Surge-Brokerage-Names-2026-Top-Pick/69535a7c4342f77179e55d35</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Shocking-Prediction-Petronet-LNG-Set-for-Massive-44percent-Surge-Brokerage-Names-2026-Top-Pick/69535a7c4342f77179e55d35</guid><description>Brokerage firm Investec has identified Petronet LNG as its 'top pick' for 2026, initiating a 'buy' recommendation with a ₹400 price target, implying an impressive 44% upside. This bullish outlook is driven by an anticipated sharp increase in global LNG supply by 7% in 2026, led by producers in the US, Canada, Qatar, and Africa. Investec believes this will create a favorable pricing environment for India, reviving industrial demand. Petronet LNG's completed capacity expansion and existing contracts provide strong protection, trading below historical valuations after recent corrections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:36:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69535a7c4342f77179e55d34_1767070523931.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Orient Technologies Announces 1:10 Bonus Share Payout: A Windfall for 82,000 Retail Investors?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Orient-Technologies-Announces-110-Bonus-Share-Payout-A-Windfall-for-82000-Retail-Investors/69535a744342f77179e55cf0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Orient-Technologies-Announces-110-Bonus-Share-Payout-A-Windfall-for-82000-Retail-Investors/69535a744342f77179e55cf0</guid><description>Orient Technologies Ltd. has received shareholder approval to issue bonus shares in a 1:10 ratio, its first since listing. This move will reward approximately 82,000 retail shareholders, who hold a significant stake in the company. The decision, approved by the board in November, will be funded by capitalizing ₹4.16 crore from the Securities Premium Account. The stock saw a positive reaction following the announcement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:36:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69535a744342f77179e55cef_1767070762480.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IPO Lock-in Expires! Pace Digitek &amp; Ellenbarrie Shares Tumble Below Launch Price – Sell-off Looms?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Lock-in-Expires-Pace-Digitek-and-Ellenbarrie-Shares-Tumble-Below-Launch-Price-Sell-off-Looms/6953599e4342f77179e55a5e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Lock-in-Expires-Pace-Digitek-and-Ellenbarrie-Shares-Tumble-Below-Launch-Price-Sell-off-Looms/6953599e4342f77179e55a5e</guid><description>The shareholder lock-in period for Pace Digitek and Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases ended on December 30, making millions of shares available for trading. Both companies' stocks are already trading significantly below their IPO prices, with Pace Digitek down 15% from its ₹219 issue price and Ellenbarrie down nearly 16% from ₹400. This expiry could introduce further selling pressure and volatility.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:36:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953599e4342f77179e55a5d_1767070398988.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-NZ FTA: UPI &amp; Fintech Set to Conquer New Zealand Market in Massive Cross-Border Payments Push!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-NZ-FTA-UPI-and-Fintech-Set-to-Conquer-New-Zealand-Market-in-Massive-Cross-Border-Payments-Push/695359684342f77179e55965</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-NZ-FTA-UPI-and-Fintech-Set-to-Conquer-New-Zealand-Market-in-Massive-Cross-Border-Payments-Push/695359684342f77179e55965</guid><description>India and New Zealand have signed a Free Trade Agreement (FTA) expanding financial services cooperation, notably allowing Indian digital payment platforms like UPI to operate in New Zealand. This pact aims to boost real-time cross-border transactions, reduce remittance costs, and enhance settlement efficiency, opening significant market opportunities for Indian fintech companies and financial institutions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:36:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695359684342f77179e55964_1767070171396.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Novo Nordisk Halves Wegovy Price in China: Is a Generic Tsunami Coming?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisk-Halves-Wegovy-Price-in-China-Is-a-Generic-Tsunami-Coming/695359184342f77179e5588d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisk-Halves-Wegovy-Price-in-China-Is-a-Generic-Tsunami-Coming/695359184342f77179e5588d</guid><description>Danish drug giant Novo Nordisk has slashed the price of its blockbuster obesity drug Wegovy in China ahead of its semaglutide patent expiry in March. The significant price cut aims to improve patient access and affordability while bracing for an anticipated surge in cheaper generic versions and increased competition from domestic players like Innovent Biologics Inc.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:36:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695359184342f77179e5588c_1767070149752.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metals Skyrocket Past Stocks: The Shocking Reason Why Investors Are Rushing to Gold, Silver &amp; Copper!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metals-Skyrocket-Past-Stocks-The-Shocking-Reason-Why-Investors-Are-Rushing-to-Gold-Silver-and-Copper/695358e74342f77179e557cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metals-Skyrocket-Past-Stocks-The-Shocking-Reason-Why-Investors-Are-Rushing-to-Gold-Silver-and-Copper/695358e74342f77179e557cc</guid><description>Metals like gold, silver, and copper significantly outperformed stocks in 2025. This surge was driven by global economic shifts favoring physical assets over financial assumptions. Key factors include central bank diversification away from the US dollar (with India, China, Poland buying gold), geopolitical tensions acting as a hedge, and industrial demand for silver and copper driven by EVs, AI data centers, and renewable energy projects. Supply constraints also played a crucial role.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:33:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695358e74342f77179e557cb_1767069999349.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gaming Stock Nazara Technologies Rockets Higher? Analyst Firm Issues STRONG BUY with Rs 390 Target!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Gaming-Stock-Nazara-Technologies-Rockets-Higher-Analyst-Firm-Issues-STRONG-BUY-with-Rs-390-Target/6953586f4342f77179e555ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Gaming-Stock-Nazara-Technologies-Rockets-Higher-Analyst-Firm-Issues-STRONG-BUY-with-Rs-390-Target/6953586f4342f77179e555ea</guid><description>Choice Institutional Equities has issued a 'Buy' recommendation for Nazara Technologies, setting a target price of INR 390. The report highlights a strategic portfolio reset aimed at boosting earnings quality, with core gaming expected to drive growth with 20-25% EBITDA margins. The company's focus on AI-enabled immersive experiences, global IP acquisition, and over 90% overseas revenue positions it for compounded growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:31:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953586f4342f77179e555e9_1767069874492.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Natural Gas Super-Cycle Incoming? AI Demand Sparks Fierce Debate – Or Is It a Trap?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Natural-Gas-Super-Cycle-Incoming-AI-Demand-Sparks-Fierce-Debate-Or-Is-It-a-Trap/695357bf4342f77179e553c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Natural-Gas-Super-Cycle-Incoming-AI-Demand-Sparks-Fierce-Debate-Or-Is-It-a-Trap/695357bf4342f77179e553c2</guid><description>A hypothesis suggests the AI boom will drive massive electricity demand, leading to a natural gas super-cycle. However, this article argues against it, citing natural gas's inherent volatility and the availability of diverse energy sources beyond natural gas for AI power generation. Recent sharp price drops, like a 30.91 percent fall in December, are presented as evidence against the super-cycle theory, indicating significant risks for traders.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:31:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695357bf4342f77179e553c1_1767069968689.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 25,000 Crore Fund to Revive Stalled Infra Projects? Budget 2027 May Hold the Key!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rs-25000-Crore-Fund-to-Revive-Stalled-Infra-Projects-Budget-2027-May-Hold-the-Key/695357d64342f77179e55424</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rs-25000-Crore-Fund-to-Revive-Stalled-Infra-Projects-Budget-2027-May-Hold-the-Key/695357d64342f77179e55424</guid><description>The Indian government is considering a Rs 25,000 crore risk guarantee fund to help stalled infrastructure projects. This fund, possibly announced in the Union Budget for FY27, aims to reduce financing risks for lenders and encourage more loans for delayed developments. Modeled on existing small business schemes, it's expected to be managed with guarantees from the National Credit Guarantee Trustee Co. (NCGTC) and recommendations from NaBFID, boosting crucial infrastructure spending needed for economic growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 04:31:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695357d64342f77179e55423_1767069729416.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Wobble: Sensex &amp; Nifty Open Lower, Tata Steel Faces 1% Dip!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Wobble-Sensex-and-Nifty-Open-Lower-Tata-Steel-Faces-1percent-Dip/695350104342f77179e53c18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Wobble-Sensex-and-Nifty-Open-Lower-Tata-Steel-Faces-1percent-Dip/695350104342f77179e53c18</guid><description>Indian stock markets began the trading session on a subdued note, with the benchmark Sensex opening 130 points lower and the Nifty trading below the crucial 26,000 mark. Adding to the downward pressure, shares of Tata Steel saw a 1% decline in early trading, reflecting broader market sentiment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:58:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695350104342f77179e53c17_1767067759156.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Data Centre Boom: 5 Stocks Poised for Massive Growth as $30 Billion Pours In!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Data-Centre-Boom-5-Stocks-Poised-for-Massive-Growth-as-30-Billion-Pours-In/695350254342f77179e53c7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Data-Centre-Boom-5-Stocks-Poised-for-Massive-Growth-as-30-Billion-Pours-In/695350254342f77179e53c7b</guid><description>India is rapidly becoming a global AI data centre hub, addressing a significant capacity gap with a projected $30 billion investment. This multi-year expansion, driven by global tech giants, creates vast opportunities in infrastructure services. Five Indian companies—E2E Networks, Netweb Technologies, Cummins India, KRN Heat Exchanger, and Orient Technologies—are identified as potential beneficiaries of this booming sector. Investors are advised to focus on company fundamentals for sustained growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:56:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695350254342f77179e53c7a_1767067888512.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin's Shocking New Role: Not Replacing Banks, But Becoming Their Secret Reserve Asset!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bitcoins-Shocking-New-Role-Not-Replacing-Banks-But-Becoming-Their-Secret-Reserve-Asset/69534fe94342f77179e53b6f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bitcoins-Shocking-New-Role-Not-Replacing-Banks-But-Becoming-Their-Secret-Reserve-Asset/69534fe94342f77179e53b6f</guid><description>Bitcoin is evolving beyond its initial vision of disrupting banks to become a quiet reserve asset within the traditional financial system. Major institutions like U.S. Bancorp, BNY Mellon, and Deutsche Börse are building infrastructure for digital asset custody and settlement. Regulatory frameworks are emerging, allowing banks to hold crypto assets, positioning Bitcoin as a foundational asset similar to gold. This integration signifies a major shift for investors monitoring institutional adoption and the future of finance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:56:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69534fe94342f77179e53b6e_1767067755850.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking Bail Twist: WinZo Co-founder Saumya Rathore Freed, Paavan Nanda Remains in Custody Amid Money Laundering Probe!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Shocking-Bail-Twist-WinZo-Co-founder-Saumya-Rathore-Freed-Paavan-Nanda-Remains-in-Custody-Amid-Money-Laundering-Probe/69534f464342f77179e539c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Shocking-Bail-Twist-WinZo-Co-founder-Saumya-Rathore-Freed-Paavan-Nanda-Remains-in-Custody-Amid-Money-Laundering-Probe/69534f464342f77179e539c1</guid><description>A Bengaluru court granted bail to Saumya Singh Rathore, co-founder of Winzo Games Pvt Ltd, in an Enforcement Directorate (ED) money laundering case under the PMLA. However, the bail plea of co-founder Paavan Nanda was rejected, and he was taken into ED custody. The case involves allegations of algorithmic manipulation, ₹177 crore wrongful gains, and transnational fund flows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:55:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69534f464342f77179e539c0_1767067872278.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric's Roadster X+ with 4680 Bharat Cell Gets Government Nod! India's EV Future Just Accelerated!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-Roadster-X-with-4680-Bharat-Cell-Gets-Government-Nod-Indias-EV-Future-Just-Accelerated/69534f354342f77179e5396d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-Roadster-X-with-4680-Bharat-Cell-Gets-Government-Nod-Indias-EV-Future-Just-Accelerated/69534f354342f77179e5396d</guid><description>Ola Electric's flagship electric motorcycle, the Roadster X+ (9.1 kWh), powered by its indigenously developed 4680 Bharat Cell battery, has received government certification from iCAT under CMVR, 1989. This marks India's first electric motorcycle with an in-house developed battery pack, offering a remarkable 500 km range. This milestone signifies Ola Electric's commitment to end-to-end EV technology development in India and is set to accelerate electric vehicle adoption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:55:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69534f354342f77179e5396c_1767067640649.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Bonds Surge: Investors Chase 2-Year High Yields as RBI Stays Dovish!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Bonds-Surge-Investors-Chase-2-Year-High-Yields-as-RBI-Stays-Dovish/69534de74342f77179e53609</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Bonds-Surge-Investors-Chase-2-Year-High-Yields-as-RBI-Stays-Dovish/69534de74342f77179e53609</guid><description>Indian investors are flocking to short-term government bonds, particularly those with three- to five-year maturities, seeking to profit from carry trades. This strategy, capitalizing on the gap between low borrowing costs and higher bond yields, is thriving due to the Reserve Bank of India's projected gradual inflation rise and stable policy rates. Major international banks are increasing their positions in this lucrative trade, which offers the highest returns in over two years.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:50:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69534de74342f77179e53608_1767067355721.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>