<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><item><title>CSB Bank Profit Flat YoY, Eyes 15% ROE Amid Strong Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CSB-Bank-Profit-Flat-YoY-Eyes-15percent-ROE-Amid-Strong-Growth/6982099cd9d43ad9e174f78f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CSB-Bank-Profit-Flat-YoY-Eyes-15percent-ROE-Amid-Strong-Growth/6982099cd9d43ad9e174f78f</guid><description>CSB Bank reported flat net profit of ₹153 crore for Q3 FY26, despite a significant 32% rise in operating profit and 21% YoY growth in Net Interest Income. NIM hit a fiscal high of 3.86%. The bank forecasts &gt;25% advance growth and targets 15% ROE in FY27, while managing elevated NPAs and a high cost-to-income ratio.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:21:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982099cd9d43ad9e174f78e_1770129984988.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Restaurant Brands Asia Q3 Revenue Climbs 16%, Losses Narrow Amid Promoter Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Restaurant-Brands-Asia-Q3-Revenue-Climbs-16percent-Losses-Narrow-Amid-Promoter-Shift/698208a3d9d43ad9e174ef29</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Restaurant-Brands-Asia-Q3-Revenue-Climbs-16percent-Losses-Narrow-Amid-Promoter-Shift/698208a3d9d43ad9e174ef29</guid><description>Restaurant Brands Asia's Q3 FY26 saw revenue climb 16.53% YoY to ₹5,773M standalone, with losses narrowing significantly. Consolidated revenue grew 11.87% to ₹7,148M. An exceptional item impacted results. Crucially, the board approved revisions for promoter classification and special rights, subject to approvals, marking a potential shift in control. No future guidance was issued.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:16:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698208a3d9d43ad9e174ef28_1770129781381.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Peak XV Partners Loses Trio of Senior Investment Stars Amid AI Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Peak-XV-Partners-Loses-Trio-of-Senior-Investment-Stars-Amid-AI-Shift/6981c41ed9d43ad9e173866c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Peak-XV-Partners-Loses-Trio-of-Senior-Investment-Stars-Amid-AI-Shift/6981c41ed9d43ad9e173866c</guid><description>Peak XV Partners confirmed the departure of Ashish Agrawal, Ishaan Mittal, and Tejeshwi Sharma. The venture capital firm stated the exits were mutually decided and part of a strategic evolution driven by artificial intelligence. This move signals Peak XV's adaptation to new technological disruptions and its plan to integrate AI-native investors. The firm reaffirmed its commitment to the Indian venture ecosystem, where it has invested for over two decades.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c41ed9d43ad9e173866b_1770130916687.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises PAT Surges 193% on Asset Sales; Debt Climbs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Enterprises-PAT-Surges-193percent-on-Asset-Sales-Debt-Climbs/6981c2bad9d43ad9e1738153</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Enterprises-PAT-Surges-193percent-on-Asset-Sales-Debt-Climbs/6981c2bad9d43ad9e1738153</guid><description>Adani Enterprises posted a 193% YoY PAT jump for 9M FY26, boosted by ₹9,215 Cr exceptional gains from asset sales. Q3 revenue rose 8%, EBITDA 15%. However, 9M EBITDA saw a 3% dip, and net external debt increased significantly to ₹49,306 Cr. Key milestones include Navi Mumbai Airport's operationalization and successful capital raises.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c2bad9d43ad9e1738152_1770130633999.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Recovers as UBS Affirms Bull Market Amidst Fed Nomination Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Recovers-as-UBS-Affirms-Bull-Market-Amidst-Fed-Nomination-Fears/6981c28ad9d43ad9e1738054</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Recovers-as-UBS-Affirms-Bull-Market-Amidst-Fed-Nomination-Fears/6981c28ad9d43ad9e1738054</guid><description>Gold experienced a sharp, multi-day decline, its steepest in over a decade, triggered by the nomination of Kevin Warsh as Federal Reserve chair. Despite this volatility, UBS maintains its 'Attractive' rating for gold, projecting a mid-year 2026 target of $6,200 per ounce. The firm asserts that the conditions typically ending a gold bull market are absent, pointing to robust demand from central banks and investors, persistent geopolitical uncertainty, and expectations for further monetary easing, which collectively support the ongoing uptrend.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c28ad9d43ad9e1738053_1770130472701.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Raymond Realty Surges 47% in Bookings, Pivots to Asset-Light JDA Model</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Raymond-Realty-Surges-47percent-in-Bookings-Pivots-to-Asset-Light-JDA-Model/69820410d9d43ad9e174c72f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Raymond-Realty-Surges-47percent-in-Bookings-Pivots-to-Asset-Light-JDA-Model/69820410d9d43ad9e174c72f</guid><description>Raymond Realty reported a strong Q3 FY26 with booking value up 47% YoY to INR 743 cr and income up 56% to INR 766 cr. The company is aggressively shifting to an asset-light Joint Development Agreement (JDA) model, aiming for 50% of pre-sales from JDAs by FY28 to scale footprint and improve margins from the current 13% to 18-20%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:54:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69820410d9d43ad9e174c72e_1770129024762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Unleashes Aggressive 8-Product Offensive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Unleashes-Aggressive-8-Product-Offensive/6981c3ebd9d43ad9e1738577</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Unleashes-Aggressive-8-Product-Offensive/6981c3ebd9d43ad9e1738577</guid><description>Bajaj Auto is initiating an aggressive product offensive, planning eight new or updated models across its Pulsar line within the next four to five months. This strategic move aims to bolster its position in the competitive 125cc-plus motorcycle segment and capture market share. The company also revealed plans to introduce a new brand targeting the 125cc segment and explore off-road motorcycle formats. This initiative comes as Bajaj Auto reported strong Q3 FY26 results, with record revenues and profits, despite facing challenges in domestic market share.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c3ebd9d43ad9e1738576_1770130236914.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nazara Revenue Falls 24%, But EBITDA Jumps 29% on Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nazara-Revenue-Falls-24percent-But-EBITDA-Jumps-29percent-on-Margin-Gains/6982018fd9d43ad9e174b407</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nazara-Revenue-Falls-24percent-But-EBITDA-Jumps-29percent-on-Margin-Gains/6982018fd9d43ad9e174b407</guid><description>Nazara Technologies reported a 24.1% YoY revenue decline to INR 406 Cr in Q3FY26, mainly due to Nodwin's de-consolidation, though adjusted revenue rose 9.8%. EBITDA surged 29.4% to INR 67.8 Cr, with margins expanding to 16.7%. However, PAT from continued operations fell 77% YoY for 9MFY26, contrasting with strong EBITDA growth driven by Centres of Excellence strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:40:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982018fd9d43ad9e174b406_1770128060883.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Crypto Investors Buy Dips Amid Global Bitcoin Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Indian-Crypto-Investors-Buy-Dips-Amid-Global-Bitcoin-Slump/6981c36bd9d43ad9e17383e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Indian-Crypto-Investors-Buy-Dips-Amid-Global-Bitcoin-Slump/6981c36bd9d43ad9e17383e5</guid><description>Bitcoin prices have tumbled to $74,500, driven by global economic uncertainties and a risk-off sentiment following the Federal Reserve's unchanged interest rates. Despite this downturn, Indian cryptocurrency exchanges are witnessing a surge in buying activity, with volumes jumping by up to 90% on platforms like Mudrex. This local resilience highlights a divergence in investor behavior, as global markets brace for further volatility while Indian traders see an accumulation opportunity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:40:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c36bd9d43ad9e17383e4_1770129603615.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fractal IPO: Investor Exit Meets AI Growth Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-IPO-Investor-Exit-Meets-AI-Growth-Ambition/6981c45dd9d43ad9e17387e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-IPO-Investor-Exit-Meets-AI-Growth-Ambition/6981c45dd9d43ad9e17387e3</guid><description>Fractal Analytics is launching an Initial Public Offering (IPO) to raise ₹2,833.9 crore, comprising fresh issuance and a substantial Offer for Sale (OFS). Scheduled for February 9-11, 2026, the IPO sees existing investors like Apax Partners and TPG divesting significant stakes. This move fuels Fractal's continued investment in its high-margin, though loss-making, Fractal Alpha division and core AI solutions, amidst robust revenue growth and narrowing losses, positioning it within India's rapidly expanding AI market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c45dd9d43ad9e17387e2_1770129407591.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys Powers Citizens Bank AI Hub for Digital Banking Transformation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Powers-Citizens-Bank-AI-Hub-for-Digital-Banking-Transformation/698200b0d9d43ad9e174aaf9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Powers-Citizens-Bank-AI-Hub-for-Digital-Banking-Transformation/698200b0d9d43ad9e174aaf9</guid><description>Infosys partners with Citizens Bank to establish an AI-first Innovation Hub in Bengaluru. The collaboration leverages Infosys Topaz Fabric™ to accelerate Citizens' digital banking transformation, enhancing product development and customer experience through advanced AI, cloud, and cybersecurity. This strategic move positions Citizens as a technology-driven institution and bolsters Infosys's AI service offerings in the financial sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698200b0d9d43ad9e174aaf8_1770127686209.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kiduja India Turns Profitable, Auditors Raise Going Concern Red Flag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kiduja-India-Turns-Profitable-Auditors-Raise-Going-Concern-Red-Flag/6981c5c9d9d43ad9e1738d3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kiduja-India-Turns-Profitable-Auditors-Raise-Going-Concern-Red-Flag/6981c5c9d9d43ad9e1738d3f</guid><description>Kiduja India Ltd reported a Q3 FY26 profit of ₹117.28 lakhs, a sharp turnaround from last year's loss, driven by investment sales. However, statutory auditors have flagged a "material uncertainty" about the company's ability to continue as a going concern due to accumulated losses and negative net worth, despite promoter assurances.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:33:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c5c9d9d43ad9e1738d3e_1770129195845.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Greenlam Posts Q3 Loss Despite 17% Revenue Growth, Profit Plummets 77%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Greenlam-Posts-Q3-Loss-Despite-17percent-Revenue-Growth-Profit-Plummets-77percent/6981c6bfd9d43ad9e1739291</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Greenlam-Posts-Q3-Loss-Despite-17percent-Revenue-Growth-Profit-Plummets-77percent/6981c6bfd9d43ad9e1739291</guid><description>Greenlam Industries reported a consolidated net loss of INR 0.6 crore for Q3 FY'26, despite a robust 17.3% YoY revenue growth to INR 706 crores. The company cited forex fluctuations, exceptional wage code costs, and higher operating expenses. For the nine months, net profit plummeted 77% YoY to INR 15.5 crores. While gross margins improved, EBITDA margins compressed, and the plywood segment continued to report losses. Management reaffirmed FY'26 revenue guidance and targets breakeven for plywood and chipboard by FY'27.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:26:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c6bfd9d43ad9e1739290_1770128812542.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paradeep Phosphates Q3 Profit Dips 13% Despite Revenue Surge; 9M Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Paradeep-Phosphates-Q3-Profit-Dips-13percent-Despite-Revenue-Surge-9M-Soars/6981fcc4d9d43ad9e1748ddc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Paradeep-Phosphates-Q3-Profit-Dips-13percent-Despite-Revenue-Surge-9M-Soars/6981fcc4d9d43ad9e1748ddc</guid><description>Paradeep Phosphates (PPL) reported a 13% YoY dip in Q3 FY26 net profit to ₹1,821 million, contrasting with a 15.2% revenue increase. However, 9M FY26 performance was robust, with net profit soaring 71.6% YoY to ₹8,407 million on 34.1% revenue growth. The company highlighted successful MCFL merger integration and ongoing capacity expansion plans, including 100% backward integration in phosphoric acid.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:15:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981fcc4d9d43ad9e1748ddb_1770126688230.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GE Vernova T&amp;D India Posts 58% Revenue Jump, Order Book Up 41%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GE-Vernova-TandD-India-Posts-58percent-Revenue-Jump-Order-Book-Up-41percent/6981cc19d9d43ad9e173a398</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GE-Vernova-TandD-India-Posts-58percent-Revenue-Jump-Order-Book-Up-41percent/6981cc19d9d43ad9e173a398</guid><description>GE Vernova T&amp;D India reported a stellar Q3 FY'26 with revenue jumping 58% YoY to INR 17 billion and profit before tax more than doubling. Order bookings surged 41% YoY to INR 29.4 billion, expanding the backlog to INR 143.8 billion. Management remains optimistic about growth drivers from India's energy targets, grid modernization, and renewable integration, maintaining a debt-free status and planning significant capex.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:12:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981cc19d9d43ad9e173a397_1770127881455.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nazara Technologies Q3 Earnings Surge on Profit-Led Growth and Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nazara-Technologies-Q3-Earnings-Surge-on-Profit-Led-Growth-and-Investments/6981fabcd9d43ad9e1747f6f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nazara-Technologies-Q3-Earnings-Surge-on-Profit-Led-Growth-and-Investments/6981fabcd9d43ad9e1747f6f</guid><description>Nazara Technologies reported robust Q3 FY26 results with revenue at INR 406 Cr and EBITDA up 29.4% YoY to INR 67.8 Cr, improving margins to 16.7%. For 9MFY26, revenue grew 29.7% YoY to INR 1,431 Cr, and EBITDA surged 73% YoY to INR 177 Cr with expanded margins. The company highlighted efficiency gains, new launch leverage, and strategic investments, including INR 15 Cr into Rusk Media and board approval for nCore Games. Operational wins include Kiddopia subscriber growth and Animal Jam expansion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:06:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981fabcd9d43ad9e1747f6e_1770126319308.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apcotex Q3: Profit Jumps 91% on Margin Gains, Future Growth Fuels Optimism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Apcotex-Q3-Profit-Jumps-91percent-on-Margin-Gains-Future-Growth-Fuels-Optimism/6981c65bd9d43ad9e1738ff5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Apcotex-Q3-Profit-Jumps-91percent-on-Margin-Gains-Future-Growth-Fuels-Optimism/6981c65bd9d43ad9e1738ff5</guid><description>Apcotex Industries reported a strong Q3 FY'26 with PAT soaring 91% YoY to ₹22 Cr on a 10% volume growth. Despite a 7% revenue dip to ₹332 Cr due to falling prices, operating EBITDA surged 61% to ₹44 Cr, expanding margins to 13.12%. The 9M FY'26 saw record volumes and a 42% EBITDA jump. Management forecasts 12-16% EBITDA margins, supported by new projects adding ₹550-600 Cr to topline by FY'27, even as nitrile latex overcapacity persists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:04:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c65bd9d43ad9e1738ff4_1770127485485.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SJS Enterprises Hits Record Revenue, Margins On Auto &amp; Export Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SJS-Enterprises-Hits-Record-Revenue-Margins-On-Auto-and-Export-Boom/6981c68cd9d43ad9e1739114</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SJS-Enterprises-Hits-Record-Revenue-Margins-On-Auto-and-Export-Boom/6981c68cd9d43ad9e1739114</guid><description>SJS Enterprises achieved record consolidated revenue of ₹2,435.3 million (+36.4% YoY) and highest-ever EBITDA (30.5%) and PAT (18.5%) margins in Q3 FY26. Strong 46% growth in automotive and a 146.2% surge in exports fueled performance. The company also signed a key technology license with BOE Varitronix for automotive display solutions and is expanding capacity internally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c68cd9d43ad9e1739113_1770127324119.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Varroc Engineering Secures EV Charger Contract Amidst Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Varroc-Engineering-Secures-EV-Charger-Contract-Amidst-Profit-Slump/6981f9c8d9d43ad9e1747b0d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Varroc-Engineering-Secures-EV-Charger-Contract-Amidst-Profit-Slump/6981f9c8d9d43ad9e1747b0d</guid><description>Varroc Engineering secured a six-year contract to supply AC bi-directional wall chargers to a global EV OEM, valued at approximately $48 million annually at peak production. This strategic win aims to expand its footprint in electric mobility, offering a critical pathway to offset recent profit declines and margin contractions reported in Q4. While the deal signals future growth, its long-term impact hinges on execution and market competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:02:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981f9c8d9d43ad9e1747b0c_1770125959907.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharat Coking Coal Posts Steep Loss, Revenue Plunges Post-Listing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Bharat-Coking-Coal-Posts-Steep-Loss-Revenue-Plunges-Post-Listing/6981c983d9d43ad9e1739a15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Bharat-Coking-Coal-Posts-Steep-Loss-Revenue-Plunges-Post-Listing/6981c983d9d43ad9e1739a15</guid><description>Bharat Coking Coal Limited (BCCL) has reported a substantial financial downturn for Q3 FY26, posting a net loss of ₹22.88 crore against a profit of ₹424.99 crore in the prior year. Revenue from operations fell 25.43% YoY to ₹2,584.77 crore. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, net profit slumped to ₹101.00 crore from ₹1,173.69 crore, with revenue declining 14.18%. Production and offtake figures also saw decreases.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:58:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c983d9d43ad9e1739a14_1770127113079.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KPI Green Energy Surges on Stellar Q3 Results, Eyes Botswana Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Surges-on-Stellar-Q3-Results-Eyes-Botswana-Expansion/6981c99cd9d43ad9e1739b26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Surges-on-Stellar-Q3-Results-Eyes-Botswana-Expansion/6981c99cd9d43ad9e1739b26</guid><description>KPI Green Energy reported its seventh consecutive quarter of record revenue, with Q3 FY26 sales at ₹676 crores (+45% YoY). EBITDA surged 73% to ₹251 crores, and PAT grew 48% to ₹126 crores. The company secured key EPC contracts and signed an MOU with Botswana for 5 GW renewable energy, aiming for 10 GW by 2030 and increasing IPP focus.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981c99cd9d43ad9e1739b25_1770126600772.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Consumer Care Hits 7-Year Peak Amid Robust Q3 Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bajaj-Consumer-Care-Hits-7-Year-Peak-Amid-Robust-Q3-Growth/6981cc79d9d43ad9e173a57f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bajaj-Consumer-Care-Hits-7-Year-Peak-Amid-Robust-Q3-Growth/6981cc79d9d43ad9e173a57f</guid><description>Bajaj Consumer Care shares soared to a seven-year high, fueled by a robust 32.7% YoY net sales increase and a 109% EBITDA surge in Q3FY26. This performance stemmed from significant volume growth in key products and margin expansion. Despite a recent industry downturn, the company's strong operational improvements are attracting investor attention, though its P/E ratio is nearing historical highs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:48:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981cc79d9d43ad9e173a57e_1770126384564.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EU-Mercosur Deal Stalls: Strategy vs. Farmer Fury</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/EU-Mercosur-Deal-Stalls-Strategy-vs-Farmer-Fury/6981f6fdd9d43ad9e17466f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/EU-Mercosur-Deal-Stalls-Strategy-vs-Farmer-Fury/6981f6fdd9d43ad9e17466f0</guid><description>Signed in January, the expansive EU-Mercosur trade agreement is confronting significant headwinds. Widespread farmer protests across Europe signal deep dissatisfaction over anticipated competition from cheaper agricultural imports. A European Parliament vote has sent the deal to the European Court of Justice for review, potentially delaying implementation for years. This legislative and political friction underscores the EU's challenge in balancing its strategic need for critical raw materials with the potent demands of its agricultural sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981f6fdd9d43ad9e17466ef_1770125332428.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GPT Infra Buys Signaling Firm, Order Book Surges 3.75x Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GPT-Infra-Buys-Signaling-Firm-Order-Book-Surges-375x-Revenue/6981cca1d9d43ad9e173a69f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GPT-Infra-Buys-Signaling-Firm-Order-Book-Surges-375x-Revenue/6981cca1d9d43ad9e173a69f</guid><description>GPT Infraprojects announced a ₹154 Cr acquisition of Alcon Builders to enter the high-margin signaling EPC segment. Q3 FY'26 revenue grew 2% to ₹283.9 Cr, while 9M FY'26 PAT rose to ₹65.4 Cr. The company's net order book stands strong at ₹4,415 Cr (3.75x FY'25 revenue), with a revised FY'26 order inflow target of ₹2,500 Cr, promising over 25% revenue growth in FY'27.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:42:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981cca1d9d43ad9e173a69e_1770126173016.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCI Express Declares Dividend, Faces ₹51 Cr GST Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/TCI-Express-Declares-Dividend-Faces-51-Cr-GST-Demand/6981cd03d9d43ad9e173a906</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/TCI-Express-Declares-Dividend-Faces-51-Cr-GST-Demand/6981cd03d9d43ad9e173a906</guid><description>TCI Express announced a ₹7 per share interim dividend for FY26 alongside its Q3 FY26 results, showing a 9% YoY growth in Net Profit to ₹22.54 Cr. However, the company disclosed a significant ₹51.36 Cr GST demand order, which, despite a rejected appeal, the management believes will not adversely impact financials. Nine-month data comparisons were noted as unreliable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:36:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981cd03d9d43ad9e173a905_1770125810801.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>REC Denies PFC Merger Talks Amid Budget Restructuring Proposal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/REC-Denies-PFC-Merger-Talks-Amid-Budget-Restructuring-Proposal/6981cfb5d9d43ad9e173b28b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/REC-Denies-PFC-Merger-Talks-Amid-Budget-Restructuring-Proposal/6981cfb5d9d43ad9e173b28b</guid><description>REC Limited clarified to stock exchanges that it is not engaged in merger discussions with PFC, contrary to a recent Economic Times report. While denying current talks, REC acknowledged the Union Budget's proposal for restructuring state-run NBFCs like PFC and REC, noting the material impact will be deliberated by its board.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:35:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981cfb5d9d43ad9e173b28a_1770125726312.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IOC's SAF Certification: Green Fuel Goals Meet UCO Supply Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IOCs-SAF-Certification-Green-Fuel-Goals-Meet-UCO-Supply-Reality/6981f5f6d9d43ad9e17461f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IOCs-SAF-Certification-Green-Fuel-Goals-Meet-UCO-Supply-Reality/6981f5f6d9d43ad9e17461f1</guid><description>Indian Oil Corporation (IOC) achieved India's first certification for Sustainable Aviation Fuel (SAF) production at its Panipat refinery in December 2025. This milestone supports India's ambitious emission reduction targets, aiming for 1% SAF blending by 2027. However, the crucial reliance on used cooking oil (UCO) presents significant collection and cost challenges, with SAF currently three to four times more expensive than conventional jet fuel. IOC's strategic valuation and market position will be tested as it navigates these economic and operational hurdles to meet national sustainability goals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:34:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981f5f6d9d43ad9e17461f0_1770125207513.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banking Reforms: Panel to Weigh Corporate Entry for Viksit Bharat Goals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banking-Reforms-Panel-to-Weigh-Corporate-Entry-for-Viksit-Bharat-Goals/6981dc4ad9d43ad9e173dbf3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banking-Reforms-Panel-to-Weigh-Corporate-Entry-for-Viksit-Bharat-Goals/6981dc4ad9d43ad9e173dbf3</guid><description>A high-level committee has been established to review India's banking sector, focusing on capital adequacy and the potential entry of corporate entities. This initiative, tied to the 'Viksit Bharat' development agenda, aims to address the significant capital requirements needed for national growth. The review will weigh the benefits of rapid corporate investment against potential risks, considering organic expansion and FDI as alternative capital sources. The committee's recommendations are expected to shape the future structure and competitiveness of Indian banking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:34:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981dc4ad9d43ad9e173dbf2_1770125610445.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nazara Tech: ₹91,470 Cr Gaming Law Hit, ₹11,870 Cr GST Threat Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nazara-Tech-91470-Cr-Gaming-Law-Hit-11870-Cr-GST-Threat-Looms/6981f56ed9d43ad9e1745d6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nazara-Tech-91470-Cr-Gaming-Law-Hit-11870-Cr-GST-Threat-Looms/6981f56ed9d43ad9e1745d6a</guid><description>Nazara Technologies reported a severe hit in Q3 FY26 consolidated profit, plummeting 85% YoY to ₹1,109 lakh, driven by a massive ₹91,470 lakh impairment loss on investments due to the new online gaming law. While 9M FY26 revenue grew 29.7%, profit before tax collapsed 89.9%. The company also faces a substantial ₹11,870.99 Crore contingent GST liability. Standalone revenue improved, but net losses widened significantly due to impairments. No guidance was issued.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981f56ed9d43ad9e1745d69_1770125463719.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC Rejects Tax Evidence in Flipkart Antitrust Case</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SC-Rejects-Tax-Evidence-in-Flipkart-Antitrust-Case/6981f4dbd9d43ad9e1745986</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SC-Rejects-Tax-Evidence-in-Flipkart-Antitrust-Case/6981f4dbd9d43ad9e1745986</guid><description>India's Supreme Court has sent the six-year-old abuse of dominance case against Flipkart back to the National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) for a fresh review. The apex court emphasized that the NCLAT must conduct its reconsideration independently, specifically excluding material derived from income tax proceedings that were later overturned. This directive highlights the critical importance of legally relevant evidence and principles of fairness in competition law adjudication, potentially setting a precedent for how digital platforms' market conduct is assessed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981f4dbd9d43ad9e1745985_1770125483261.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors Q3 FY26: Revenue Soars 17%, FCF Hits ₹4800 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Tata-Motors-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Soars-17percent-FCF-Hits-4800-Cr/6981f354d9d43ad9e1744bb9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Tata-Motors-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Soars-17percent-FCF-Hits-4800-Cr/6981f354d9d43ad9e1744bb9</guid><description>Tata Motors posted robust Q3 FY26 results with revenue jumping 17% YoY to ₹21,533 Cr, driven by 20% higher wholesale volumes. The company achieved strong free cash flow of approximately ₹4,800 Cr and maintained a healthy net cash position. Despite significant exceptional items totaling ₹1,600 Cr, operating margins improved, with the CV segment hitting a 10.6% EBIT margin. Management expressed confidence in sustained momentum, supported by new product launches and the ongoing IVECO acquisition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:19:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981f354d9d43ad9e1744bb8_1770124370580.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New India Assurance PAT Plummets 55% Amidst Provision Impact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/New-India-Assurance-PAT-Plummets-55percent-Amidst-Provision-Impact/6981d727d9d43ad9e173c63d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/New-India-Assurance-PAT-Plummets-55percent-Amidst-Provision-Impact/6981d727d9d43ad9e173c63d</guid><description>New India Assurance reported a Q3 FY26 PAT decline of 55.5% YoY to ₹367 Cr, heavily impacted by ₹759 Cr in provisions for wage arrears and retirement benefits. Despite this, Gross Written Premium (GWP) grew 8.37% YoY to ₹11,680 Cr, and Profit Before Tax (PBT) surged 265.6% to ₹4,283 Cr, driven by a substantial ₹4,316 Cr swing in 'Other Income'. The company gained market share to 13.40% in 9M FY26. A discrepancy was noted between management commentary and reported figures for 9M PBT growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981d727d9d43ad9e173c63c_1770124527332.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCMIL Surges 241% Profit, Upgrades Tech, Eyes Debt-Free Status</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MCMIL-Surges-241percent-Profit-Upgrades-Tech-Eyes-Debt-Free-Status/6981f27cd9d43ad9e174465d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MCMIL-Surges-241percent-Profit-Upgrades-Tech-Eyes-Debt-Free-Status/6981f27cd9d43ad9e174465d</guid><description>Manaksia Coated Metals (MCMIL) reported a robust 9M FY26 with 15% revenue growth and a massive 241% jump in net profit to ₹35.32 Cr, fueled by expanding EBITDA margins. Despite a planned Q3 shutdown, net profit still rose 47% YoY. The company is aggressively deleveraging towards a Net Debt/EBITDA below 1x and eyes significant growth from new Alu-Zinc tech, expanded colour coating capacity, and a ₹350 Cr export order book.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:14:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981f27cd9d43ad9e174465c_1770124279595.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>V2 Retail Q3 Revenue Plummets 96%, PAT Diverges Amidst One-Offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/V2-Retail-Q3-Revenue-Plummets-96percent-PAT-Diverges-Amidst-One-Offs/6981f23fd9d43ad9e1744509</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/V2-Retail-Q3-Revenue-Plummets-96percent-PAT-Diverges-Amidst-One-Offs/6981f23fd9d43ad9e1744509</guid><description>V2 Retail reported a drastic 96% year-on-year revenue decline for Q3 FY26, with standalone revenue falling to ₹2,730.18 Lakhs. Despite this, standalone PAT surged approximately 450% due to a significant exceptional gain from lease reassessments. However, consolidated PAT plummeted 80.07% YoY. The company also raised ~₹400 Crores via QIP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:13:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981f23fd9d43ad9e1744508_1770123962071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rubicon Research: Stellar 52% Revenue Jump, Profit Soars 91%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Rubicon-Research-Stellar-52percent-Revenue-Jump-Profit-Soars-91percent/6981e25ed9d43ad9e173ef88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Rubicon-Research-Stellar-52percent-Revenue-Jump-Profit-Soars-91percent/6981e25ed9d43ad9e173ef88</guid><description>Rubicon Research reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue climbing 51.7% YoY to ₹4,755 million, driven by strong USD-denominated sales. Profit After Tax soared 91.2% YoY to ₹728 million. While gross margins compressed due to reliance on outsourced manufacturing, operating EBITDA margins held steady at 22.7%. The company anticipates margin improvement post-mid-2026 with its Pithampur facility's ramp-up.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e25ed9d43ad9e173ef87_1770124169093.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE Flags Digital Scams Amidst India's Retail Investor Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-Flags-Digital-Scams-Amidst-Indias-Retail-Investor-Boom/6981dd40d9d43ad9e173de7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-Flags-Digital-Scams-Amidst-Indias-Retail-Investor-Boom/6981dd40d9d43ad9e173de7a</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange (NSE) has issued a stern warning against illegal trading operations, particularly those leveraging social media and mobile applications, promising assured returns. This advisory targets schemes like 'dabba trading,' which operate outside regulatory frameworks and carry severe legal penalties. The warning comes amid a significant surge in retail investor participation in Indian markets, making this demographic a prime target for sophisticated digital scams.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:04:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981dd40d9d43ad9e173de79_1770123857589.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Finance upgraded: Valuation reset fuels Buy rating</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Cholamandalam-Finance-upgraded-Valuation-reset-fuels-Buy-rating/6981f0add9d43ad9e1743c65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Cholamandalam-Finance-upgraded-Valuation-reset-fuels-Buy-rating/6981f0add9d43ad9e1743c65</guid><description>Cholamandalam Investment &amp; Finance Company delivered stronger-than-expected quarterly results, marked by stable net interest income and easing credit costs from asset quality stabilization. Disbursements grew robustly, led by vehicle finance, supporting the company's asset under management (AUM) growth targets. Following a recent price correction, analysts have upgraded the stock to 'Buy', citing attractive valuation multiples and potential for upside.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:03:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981f0add9d43ad9e1743c64_1770123679545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asian Hotels North Raises ₹340 Cr From Elana Holdings, New Majority Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Asian-Hotels-North-Raises-340-Cr-From-Elana-Holdings-New-Majority-Stake/6981dddad9d43ad9e173e148</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Asian-Hotels-North-Raises-340-Cr-From-Elana-Holdings-New-Majority-Stake/6981dddad9d43ad9e173e148</guid><description>Asian Hotels (North) Limited has successfully completed a preferential allotment, raising approximately ₹340 Crores from ELANA HOLDINGS PTE. LTD. at ₹330 per share. This issuance significantly increases the company's paid-up equity capital and establishes ELANA HOLDINGS as the new majority shareholder with a 54.37% stake. The capital infusion signals investor confidence and a strategic shift.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:03:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981dddad9d43ad9e173e147_1770123788363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Varroc Engineering Wins 6-Year EV Charger Deal Worth ₹4,391 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Varroc-Engineering-Wins-6-Year-EV-Charger-Deal-Worth-4391-Cr/6981df48d9d43ad9e173e615</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Varroc-Engineering-Wins-6-Year-EV-Charger-Deal-Worth-4391-Cr/6981df48d9d43ad9e173e615</guid><description>Varroc Engineering has landed a significant six-year contract to supply advanced AC bi-directional wall chargers to a leading global EV OEM. The deal, projected to generate ₹4,391 million annually at peak capacity, marks a substantial expansion for Varroc in the electric mobility ecosystem and validates its advanced automotive technology capabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:02:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981df48d9d43ad9e173e614_1770123740472.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India Grounds 787: Switch Defect Reignites Boeing Safety Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Grounds-787-Switch-Defect-Reignites-Boeing-Safety-Scrutiny/6981ef77d9d43ad9e17434ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Grounds-787-Switch-Defect-Reignites-Boeing-Safety-Scrutiny/6981ef77d9d43ad9e17434ce</guid><description>Air India has grounded one of its 33 Boeing 787 aircraft for a precautionary fleet-wide inspection after a pilot reported a fuel control switch defect. The incident, where a switch reportedly slipped from 'RUN' to 'CUTOFF' and failed to lock, mirrors preliminary findings in the fatal June 2025 Ahmedabad crash. This event intensifies scrutiny on Boeing's 787 production quality and its component suppliers, including Honeywell, amidst ongoing regulatory oversight.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:01:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981ef77d9d43ad9e17434cd_1770123312747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>