<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:35 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Sebi Mandates Social Media ID Disclosure for Financial Firms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Mandates-Social-Media-ID-Disclosure-for-Financial-Firms/69a040569e91847a1e78ca49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Mandates-Social-Media-ID-Disclosure-for-Financial-Firms/69a040569e91847a1e78ca49</guid><description>Effective May 1, 2026, the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) mandates that all regulated financial entities and their agents prominently display their registered name and number on social media. This directive aims to clearly distinguish legitimate financial advice from unregulated content and combat the rise of fraudulent schemes and market manipulation prevalent on digital platforms. The move signals Sebi's increased focus on oversight within the burgeoning 'finfluencer' economy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:45:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a040569e91847a1e78ca48_1772110025900.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jio Finance Infuses ₹1999.88 Cr into Subsidiary Jio Credit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jio-Finance-Infuses-199988-Cr-into-Subsidiary-Jio-Credit/69a03fda9e91847a1e78c96e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jio-Finance-Infuses-199988-Cr-into-Subsidiary-Jio-Credit/69a03fda9e91847a1e78c96e</guid><description>Jio Finance has injected ₹1999.88 crore into its wholly-owned subsidiary, Jio Credit Limited (JCL), through the subscription of over 3.35 crore equity shares at a premium. This significant capital infusion is earmarked to bolster JCL's business operations, reinforcing Jio Finance's commitment to expanding its financial services footprint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:43:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a03fda9e91847a1e78c96d_1772109891446.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IMP Powers Seeks Shareholder Nod for ₹200 Cr Related Party Deals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IMP-Powers-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-200-Cr-Related-Party-Deals/69a03f009e91847a1e78c82c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IMP-Powers-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-200-Cr-Related-Party-Deals/69a03f009e91847a1e78c82c</guid><description>IMP Powers Ltd is seeking shareholder approval via postal ballot for two significant related party transactions, each valued at ₹100 crore, with GSEC Limited and Electrify Energy Private Limited for FY 2026-27. These deals aim to drive expansion and market reach but raise concerns due to their scale relative to the company's recent turnover and its history.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:39:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a03f009e91847a1e78c82b_1772109694726.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Trade Surge with Customs Overhaul Amidst Global Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Trade-Surge-with-Customs-Overhaul-Amidst-Global-Uncertainty/69a03e799e91847a1e78c75a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Trade-Surge-with-Customs-Overhaul-Amidst-Global-Uncertainty/69a03e799e91847a1e78c75a</guid><description>India is implementing significant customs reforms, pivoting to a partnership model leveraging technology to enhance exporter access to global markets, supporting domestic manufacturing and startups. This initiative coincides with the imminent implementation of a new Income Tax Act. However, global trade headwinds, including rising tariffs and a widening trade deficit, coupled with persistent operational challenges in customs, present significant hurdles to achieving these ambitions. While India has improved its trade facilitation scores, its global competitiveness remains tested.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a03e799e91847a1e78c759_1772109597520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHIT 'IND AAA'/Stable Rating Affirmed; INR34B Loan Facilities Rated</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NHIT-IND-AAAStable-Rating-Affirmed-INR34B-Loan-Facilities-Rated/69a03db69e91847a1e78c65a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NHIT-IND-AAAStable-Rating-Affirmed-INR34B-Loan-Facilities-Rated/69a03db69e91847a1e78c65a</guid><description>India Ratings has affirmed National Highways Infra Trust's (NHIT) 'IND AAA'/Stable credit rating, reinforcing its strong financial health and stability. The agency also assigned ratings to NHIT's proposed bank loan facilities worth INR34 billion, signaling confidence in its funding capabilities. The trust's diversified portfolio of 28 toll road assets and stable revenue outlook underpin these positive ratings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:33:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a03db69e91847a1e78c659_1772109290382.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IOCL Board to consider 2nd interim dividend on March 6; trading window shut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IOCL-Board-to-consider-2nd-interim-dividend-on-March-6-trading-window-shut/69a03d0d9e91847a1e78c5b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IOCL-Board-to-consider-2nd-interim-dividend-on-March-6-trading-window-shut/69a03d0d9e91847a1e78c5b1</guid><description>Indian Oil Corporation Limited (IOCL) will convene a Board of Directors meeting on March 6, 2026, to deliberate on declaring the second interim dividend for the fiscal year 2025-26. Ahead of this crucial announcement, the company has initiated a trading window closure for its 'Insiders' effective February 27, 2026. This move signals potential shareholder returns and highlights the company's commitment to rewarding investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:31:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a03d0d9e91847a1e78c5b0_1772109122225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GRM Overseas Acquires UAE Firm for AED 50k, Eyes Middle East Rice Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GRM-Overseas-Acquires-UAE-Firm-for-AED-50k-Eyes-Middle-East-Rice-Hub/69a03b269e91847a1e78c429</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GRM-Overseas-Acquires-UAE-Firm-for-AED-50k-Eyes-Middle-East-Rice-Hub/69a03b269e91847a1e78c429</guid><description>GRM Overseas Limited has acquired GRM Arabia FZCO, a newly incorporated entity, for AED 50,000 to establish a crucial distribution and marketing hub in the UAE. This strategic move aims to bolster the company's presence in the Middle East rice market, leveraging Dubai's re-export gateway potential. The acquisition aligns with GRM Overseas' ongoing efforts to expand its international footprint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:23:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a03b269e91847a1e78c428_1772108696445.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zinema Media to Raise ₹14.8 Cr via Preferential Issue, Eyes 60% Stake in Beontyme Tech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zinema-Media-to-Raise-148-Cr-via-Preferential-Issue-Eyes-60percent-Stake-in-Beontyme-Tech/69a03aaf9e91847a1e78c35b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zinema-Media-to-Raise-148-Cr-via-Preferential-Issue-Eyes-60percent-Stake-in-Beontyme-Tech/69a03aaf9e91847a1e78c35b</guid><description>Zinema Media and Entertainment Limited is set to convene a board meeting on March 2, 2026, to discuss a significant ₹14.80 crore preferential issue aimed at bolstering its finances. The company also plans to acquire up to a 60% stake in Beontyme Technologies Private Limited through a share swap, a move that could reshape its strategic direction. Both proposals are contingent on shareholder approval, introducing a critical next step for investors to monitor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:21:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a03aaf9e91847a1e78c35a_1772108603150.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Volume Breakouts Mask Risk for 3 Indian Stocks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Volume-Breakouts-Mask-Risk-for-3-Indian-Stocks/69a03a8c9e91847a1e78c32d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Volume-Breakouts-Mask-Risk-for-3-Indian-Stocks/69a03a8c9e91847a1e78c32d</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks traded flat on February 25, 2026, as pharmaceutical stocks outperformed. Amidst this consolidation, Renaissance Global Ltd, Tejas Networks Ltd, and Jammu and Kashmir Bank Ltd registered notable price-volume breakouts, attracting technical traders. However, a deeper analysis reveals significant valuation concerns and sector-specific risks that temper the bullish narrative for these stocks, even as the broader IT and banking sectors exhibit resilience.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:20:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a03a8c9e91847a1e78c32c_1772108575170.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aptus Pharma Expands into Life-Saving Injectables and ICU Care</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aptus-Pharma-Expands-into-Life-Saving-Injectables-and-ICU-Care/69a039de9e91847a1e78c1ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aptus-Pharma-Expands-into-Life-Saving-Injectables-and-ICU-Care/69a039de9e91847a1e78c1ed</guid><description>Aptus Pharma Limited is strategically expanding its product portfolio by entering the high-acuity Life-Saving Injectables and ICU Care segments. This move aims to bolster its presence in critical therapeutic areas and complement its existing OTC and Uro Care offerings, targeting the growing demand for emergency and intensive care treatments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:17:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a039de9e91847a1e78c1ec_1772108365761.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NVIDIA Skyrockets; Salesforce Cautions as Tech Sector Diverges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NVIDIA-Skyrockets-Salesforce-Cautions-as-Tech-Sector-Diverges/69a039d69e91847a1e78c1b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NVIDIA-Skyrockets-Salesforce-Cautions-as-Tech-Sector-Diverges/69a039d69e91847a1e78c1b6</guid><description>NVIDIA Corporation shattered revenue records, fueled by insatiable AI and data center demand, reporting $68.1 billion for Q4 FY2026. Despite stellar performance, its stock saw a muted reaction, suggesting peak AI expectations. Conversely, Salesforce Inc. announced better-than-expected results but issued a subdued forecast, raising alarms for the software sector and potentially impacting global enterprise technology spending. This divergence highlights a growing split within the tech industry, with significant implications for downstream service providers like Indian IT firms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:17:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a039d69e91847a1e78c1b5_1772108389793.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Shifts Gold, Silver ETFs to Domestic Spot Prices</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Shifts-Gold-Silver-ETFs-to-Domestic-Spot-Prices/69a0394d9e91847a1e78c127</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Shifts-Gold-Silver-ETFs-to-Domestic-Spot-Prices/69a0394d9e91847a1e78c127</guid><description>India's Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) is overhauling the valuation methodology for physical gold and silver held by mutual funds and Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs). Effective April 1, 2026, the benchmark price will transition from London Bullion Market Association (LBMA) AM fixing to polled spot prices published by recognized domestic stock exchanges. This move aims to enhance the reflection of local market conditions and standardize valuation practices across the industry, with AMFI set to define uniform implementation policies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:15:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0394d9e91847a1e78c126_1772108244937.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRCON International: Patna HC Upholds ₹108.75 Cr VAT Demand; ₹81.36 Cr Net Due</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IRCON-International-Patna-HC-Upholds-10875-Cr-VAT-Demand-8136-Cr-Net-Due/69a036f19e91847a1e78bf01</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IRCON-International-Patna-HC-Upholds-10875-Cr-VAT-Demand-8136-Cr-Net-Due/69a036f19e91847a1e78bf01</guid><description>IRCON International has received a significant judgement from the Patna High Court regarding VAT assessments for its Ganga Bridge Project. The court upheld a total demand of ₹108.75 crore for assessment years 2010-11 to 2016-17. IRCON has already paid ₹27.39 crore, leaving a net outstanding of ₹81.36 crore plus interest. The company is now reviewing the detailed order to consider further actions, including a potential appeal. This confirms a substantial past financial liability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:05:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a036f19e91847a1e78bf00_1772107561946.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Krypton Industries Forms New Tyre Unit Subsidiary, Eyes Manufacturing Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Krypton-Industries-Forms-New-Tyre-Unit-Subsidiary-Eyes-Manufacturing-Expansion/69a0358b9e91847a1e78bda2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Krypton-Industries-Forms-New-Tyre-Unit-Subsidiary-Eyes-Manufacturing-Expansion/69a0358b9e91847a1e78bda2</guid><description>Krypton Industries Limited has established a new subsidiary, Krypton Tyres Limited, marking its re-entry into the tyre manufacturing sector. Incorporated on February 26, 2026, with an authorized share capital of ₹10 lakh, this move signals a strategic expansion into a competitive but vital industry. The company already has historical ties to tyre production.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0358b9e91847a1e78bda1_1772107283999.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nova Iron &amp; Steel Posts Q3 Loss; Auditor Flags Debt Default &amp; Regulatory Issues</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nova-Iron-and-Steel-Posts-Q3-Loss-Auditor-Flags-Debt-Default-and-Regulatory-Issues/69a035889e91847a1e78bd8c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nova-Iron-and-Steel-Posts-Q3-Loss-Auditor-Flags-Debt-Default-and-Regulatory-Issues/69a035889e91847a1e78bd8c</guid><description>Nova Iron &amp; Steel reported a net loss of ₹11.77 crore for Q3 FY26 and ₹10.62 crore for the nine-month period ended December 31, 2025. The company's auditor issued a qualified opinion, citing an 'event of default' due to inability to repay debt, leading to asset disposal. Concerns also include unrecognised interest costs and potential regulatory non-compliance with shareholder approval for asset sales.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:59:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a035889e91847a1e78bd8b_1772107253993.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Federal Bank Earns 'Leader' ESG Rating of 78 from NSE</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Federal-Bank-Earns-Leader-ESG-Rating-of-78-from-NSE/69a034b19e91847a1e78bc6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Federal-Bank-Earns-Leader-ESG-Rating-of-78-from-NSE/69a034b19e91847a1e78bc6b</guid><description>Federal Bank has been assigned an 'Excellent' ESG rating of 78 by NSE Sustainability Ratings &amp; Analytics, classifying it as a 'Leader' for FY 2025. This recognition, based on publicly available information, highlights the bank's commitment to environmental, social, and governance practices, positioning it favourably among peers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:55:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a034b19e91847a1e78bc6a_1772107033788.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sai Life Sciences Secures AA (Stable) Rating for ₹768.6 Cr Facilities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Secures-AA-Stable-Rating-for-7686-Cr-Facilities/69a034989e91847a1e78bc4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Secures-AA-Stable-Rating-for-7686-Cr-Facilities/69a034989e91847a1e78bc4f</guid><description>Sai Life Sciences Limited has received significant credit ratings from ICRA Limited. The company secured a long-term rating of 'AA (Stable)' for its fund-based instruments and 'A1+ (Stable)' for its non-fund-based instruments, covering a total amount of ₹768.60 crore. This reflects the rating agency's confidence in the company's financial stability and creditworthiness, potentially easing future borrowing costs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:55:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a034989e91847a1e78bc4e_1772107049177.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sudarshan Pharma GST Inspection Concludes; No Violations Found</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sudarshan-Pharma-GST-Inspection-Concludes-No-Violations-Found/69a034249e91847a1e78bbb6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sudarshan-Pharma-GST-Inspection-Concludes-No-Violations-Found/69a034249e91847a1e78bbb6</guid><description>Sudarshan Pharma Industries Limited has concluded a Goods and Service Tax (GST) inspection at its registered office. The operation, conducted by the Maharashtra GST Department from February 21 to February 25, 2026, found no violations attributable to the company and is not expected to have a material impact on its financials or operations. This outcome provides clarity on regulatory compliance for the pharmaceutical manufacturer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:53:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a034249e91847a1e78bbb5_1772106891441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oriental Trimex Board Approves $43M FCCB Fundraise, Boosts Borrowing Limit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oriental-Trimex-Board-Approves-43M-FCCB-Fundraise-Boosts-Borrowing-Limit/69a033a79e91847a1e78bb25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oriental-Trimex-Board-Approves-43M-FCCB-Fundraise-Boosts-Borrowing-Limit/69a033a79e91847a1e78bb25</guid><description>Oriental Trimex Limited's Board of Directors has approved a significant fundraising initiative, greenlighting the issuance of Foreign Currency Convertible Bonds (FCCBs) worth up to USD 43 million. The company also proposed substantial increases in its borrowing limits and authorized share capital, signalling a move to enhance financial flexibility for future growth or strategic objectives. These crucial decisions are pending shareholder and regulatory approvals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:51:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a033a79e91847a1e78bb24_1772106722366.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes AI for Development, Not Speculation; Regulators Gear Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-AI-for-Development-Not-Speculation-Regulators-Gear-Up/69a032d49e91847a1e78ba09</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-AI-for-Development-Not-Speculation-Regulators-Gear-Up/69a032d49e91847a1e78ba09</guid><description>India's Chief Economic Advisor V. Anantha Nageswaran has outlined a strategic approach to Artificial Intelligence, prioritizing its integration for long-term economic development over speculative gains. This 'second-mover advantage' strategy emphasizes careful observation before large-scale capital deployment, aiming for sustainable productivity gains. However, the rapid evolution of AI-enabled finance introduces significant risks, including algorithmic trading amplification and market shock transmission, demanding proactive regulatory adaptation and patient capital infusion. The IT sector faces disruption, while broader economic goals require sustained capital mobilization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:47:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a032d49e91847a1e78ba08_1772106588220.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>La Opala RG: Promoter Ups Stake by 0.06% to 46.83% in ₹1.30 Cr Buy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/La-Opala-RG-Promoter-Ups-Stake-by-006percent-to-4683percent-in-130-Cr-Buy/69a032be9e91847a1e78b9b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/La-Opala-RG-Promoter-Ups-Stake-by-006percent-to-4683percent-in-130-Cr-Buy/69a032be9e91847a1e78b9b9</guid><description>La Opala RG's promoter, Genesis Exports Private Limited, has increased its stake in the opal glass tableware manufacturer by acquiring 62,900 equity shares for ₹1.30 crore. This transaction on February 24, 2026, marginally pushed the promoter's holding from 46.77% to 46.83%. The move signals continued confidence from the core stakeholders in the company's prospects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:47:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a032be9e91847a1e78b9b8_1772106533349.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Adoption Soars, But E-commerce Infrastructure Holds The Line</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Adoption-Soars-But-E-commerce-Infrastructure-Holds-The-Line/69a032519e91847a1e78b8fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Adoption-Soars-But-E-commerce-Infrastructure-Holds-The-Line/69a032519e91847a1e78b8fd</guid><description>Artificial intelligence adoption in India is rapidly expanding, with 100 million daily active users engaging on AI applications for an average of 18 minutes. While AI shows potential to influence consumer purchasing decisions, particularly in shopping-related queries, established e-commerce players' robust physical logistics and infrastructure present a significant competitive advantage. Companies like Swiggy and Eternal face escalating threats from tech giants and the operational hurdles of diversifying into non-grocery sectors, rather than AI itself.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:45:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a032519e91847a1e78b8fc_1772106427560.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Air Crisis: ₹24 Lakh Crore Economic Drain Vs. Health Budget</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Air-Crisis-24-Lakh-Crore-Economic-Drain-Vs-Health-Budget/69a032479e91847a1e78b8e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Air-Crisis-24-Lakh-Crore-Economic-Drain-Vs-Health-Budget/69a032479e91847a1e78b8e2</guid><description>Air pollution in India is exacting a devastating economic toll, costing an estimated ₹24 lakh crore ($260 billion) annually, equivalent to 6% of GDP, and significantly reducing life expectancy. This massive financial burden, stemming from lost productivity and healthcare costs, far exceeds India's national health budget, highlighting a critical underinvestment in public health infrastructure and environmental mitigation. The pervasive threat extends to emerging issues like microplastics, compounding the systemic economic risk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:45:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a032479e91847a1e78b8e1_1772106445142.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC Pushes Aravalli Mining Halt Amid Expert Search</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-Pushes-Aravalli-Mining-Halt-Amid-Expert-Search/69a031919e91847a1e78b7c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-Pushes-Aravalli-Mining-Halt-Amid-Expert-Search/69a031919e91847a1e78b7c4</guid><description>The Supreme Court of India has formally requested the central government to propose environmental and forest experts for a committee tasked with re-examining the definition of the Aravalli Hills. This development includes an extension of the existing interim stay on mining activities within the region. The court's action stems from previous judgments that generated significant criticism regarding potential loopholes in environmental protection, highlighting ongoing regulatory ambiguity and its impact on resource extraction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:42:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a031919e91847a1e78b7c3_1772106273167.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brigade Enterprises, Primus Senior Living JV for ₹750 Cr South India Senior Living Projects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Brigade-Enterprises-Primus-Senior-Living-JV-for-750-Cr-South-India-Senior-Living-Projects/69a031519e91847a1e78b75f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Brigade-Enterprises-Primus-Senior-Living-JV-for-750-Cr-South-India-Senior-Living-Projects/69a031519e91847a1e78b75f</guid><description>Brigade Enterprises and Primus Senior Living have inked a strategic partnership to develop three senior living communities across South India, aiming for a Gross Development Value (GDV) of ₹750 crore. The joint venture leverages Brigade's real estate development prowess and Primus's expertise in senior living ecosystems to tap into India's rapidly expanding elder care housing market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:41:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a031519e91847a1e78b75e_1772106210904.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sun TV Board to Meet March 6 for Interim Dividend; Trading Window Closes Feb 27</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Sun-TV-Board-to-Meet-March-6-for-Interim-Dividend-Trading-Window-Closes-Feb-27/69a02fe89e91847a1e78b5d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Sun-TV-Board-to-Meet-March-6-for-Interim-Dividend-Trading-Window-Closes-Feb-27/69a02fe89e91847a1e78b5d0</guid><description>Sun TV Network Limited has announced a board meeting on March 6, 2026, to consider an interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. The company will close its trading window from February 27, 2026, until 48 hours after the meeting outcome. This move signals potential shareholder returns amid ongoing business operations and past governance scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:35:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a02fe89e91847a1e78b5cf_1772105820473.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UVS Hospitality EGM to OK ₹50 Cr Capital Hike, Calcio Restaurants Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/UVS-Hospitality-EGM-to-OK-50-Cr-Capital-Hike-Calcio-Restaurants-Acquisition/69a02f729e91847a1e78b53c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/UVS-Hospitality-EGM-to-OK-50-Cr-Capital-Hike-Calcio-Restaurants-Acquisition/69a02f729e91847a1e78b53c</guid><description>UVS Hospitality and Services Limited has called an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) for March 20, 2026, to seek shareholder approval for a significant corporate restructuring. The proposals include increasing authorized share capital to ₹50 crore, acquiring up to 51% of Calcio Restaurants Private Limited via share swap, and raising funds through preferential issues of shares and warrants. The meeting will also vote on appointing Mrs. Prathima Madineni as Managing Director.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a02f729e91847a1e78b53b_1772105643022.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BPCL Incorporates Singapore Subsidiary for Global Energy Trading</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BPCL-Incorporates-Singapore-Subsidiary-for-Global-Energy-Trading/69a02c2a9e91847a1e78b346</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BPCL-Incorporates-Singapore-Subsidiary-for-Global-Energy-Trading/69a02c2a9e91847a1e78b346</guid><description>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd (BPCL) has incorporated Bharat Petroleum Global Energy Services (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. with USD 2 million capital. The entity aims to establish a trading desk for crude oil, natural gas, petroleum, and petrochemical products. This strategic move signals BPCL's expansion into international energy trading, seeking greater flexibility in feedstock procurement, cost reduction, and margin enhancement, mirroring efforts by peers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:19:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a02c2a9e91847a1e78b345_1772104880241.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCLTech Forges IIT Kanpur Pact to Lead Deep Tech for GCCs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTech-Forges-IIT-Kanpur-Pact-to-Lead-Deep-Tech-for-GCCs/69a02bd29e91847a1e78b2e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTech-Forges-IIT-Kanpur-Pact-to-Lead-Deep-Tech-for-GCCs/69a02bd29e91847a1e78b2e1</guid><description>HCLTech has inked a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with IIT Kanpur to transform cutting-edge research into scalable solutions for Global Capability Centers (GCCs). This alliance targets AI, robotics, and cybersecurity, positioning HCLTech as a strategic GCC partner by leveraging academic research and startup ecosystems. The initiative aims to shift GCC operations from traditional talent-led models to research-driven innovation, enhancing time-to-market and offering niche skills access. This move aligns with India's ambition to achieve $100 billion in GCC exports by 2030, a significant driver for the nation's technology sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:17:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a02bd29e91847a1e78b2e0_1772104839683.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OneSource Pharma Secures NSE/BSE No Objection for Steriscience Merger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/OneSource-Pharma-Secures-NSEBSE-No-Objection-for-Steriscience-Merger/69a02b389e91847a1e78b1fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/OneSource-Pharma-Secures-NSEBSE-No-Objection-for-Steriscience-Merger/69a02b389e91847a1e78b1fe</guid><description>OneSource Specialty Pharma Limited has achieved a significant milestone, securing 'No Objection' or 'No Adverse Observation Letters' from both the NSE and BSE for its proposed merger scheme with Steriscience group entities. The approvals, dated February 25, 2026, allow the company to proceed towards seeking necessary sanctions from the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) and other authorities. This marks a crucial step in consolidating operations across multiple entities into OneSource.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:15:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a02b389e91847a1e78b1fd_1772104610609.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lupin Hits 91/100 in S&amp;P ESG, Ranks 1st Globally in Pharma</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Hits-91100-in-SandP-ESG-Ranks-1st-Globally-in-Pharma/69a02ac49e91847a1e78b15a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Hits-91100-in-SandP-ESG-Ranks-1st-Globally-in-Pharma/69a02ac49e91847a1e78b15a</guid><description>Lupin Limited has achieved a remarkable score of 91 out of 100 in the S&amp;P Global Corporate Sustainability Assessment 2025. This places the company at the forefront, ranking first globally in the pharmaceutical sector and first across all sectors in India. This is Lupin's third consecutive year of inclusion in the prestigious Sustainability Yearbook 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:13:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a02ac49e91847a1e78b159_1772104511983.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nuvama Sees Upside in Auto, Renewables: A Deeper Look</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Nuvama-Sees-Upside-in-Auto-Renewables-A-Deeper-Look/69a029e39e91847a1e78aff5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Nuvama-Sees-Upside-in-Auto-Renewables-A-Deeper-Look/69a029e39e91847a1e78aff5</guid><description>Brokerage Nuvama maintains 'Buy' ratings on Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, Schaeffler India, and Waaree Energies, citing growth plans and recent performance. However, deeper analysis points to premium valuations for Schaeffler India and Waaree Energies, alongside execution risks and sector-specific challenges. Mahindra &amp; Mahindra faces scrutiny on its diversified growth sustainability and valuation, despite robust historical performance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:09:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a029e39e91847a1e78aff4_1772104296223.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's E20 Petrol Mandate: Margin Squeeze Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-E20-Petrol-Mandate-Margin-Squeeze-Looms/69a029d79e91847a1e78afdb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-E20-Petrol-Mandate-Margin-Squeeze-Looms/69a029d79e91847a1e78afdb</guid><description>India's mandatory nationwide E20 petrol with minimum RON 95, effective April 1, 2026, targets reduced oil imports and emissions. However, oil marketing companies face margin pressure due to rising ethanol costs and higher RON specifications. The automotive sector navigates vehicle compatibility concerns, while a significant ethanol supply glut raises questions about long-term program viability and farmer incomes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:09:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a029d79e91847a1e78afda_1772104302654.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sharpline Broadcast: Sharp Eye Medicare acquires 9.98% stake via preferential allotment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Sharpline-Broadcast-Sharp-Eye-Medicare-acquires-998percent-stake-via-preferential-allotment/69a0295b9e91847a1e78aefa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Sharpline-Broadcast-Sharp-Eye-Medicare-acquires-998percent-stake-via-preferential-allotment/69a0295b9e91847a1e78aefa</guid><description>Sharp Eye Medicare Private Limited has become a significant shareholder in Sharpline Broadcast Limited, acquiring 28,57,142 equity shares, representing 9.98% of the company's paid-up equity capital. This marks the first-time acquisition by Sharp Eye Medicare, crossing the 5% regulatory threshold and signalling a shift in Sharpline Broadcast's ownership structure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:07:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0295b9e91847a1e78aef9_1772104122917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DGCA Refund Rules Tighten Grip on Airline Profitability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/DGCA-Refund-Rules-Tighten-Grip-on-Airline-Profitability/69a028999e91847a1e78adc9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/DGCA-Refund-Rules-Tighten-Grip-on-Airline-Profitability/69a028999e91847a1e78adc9</guid><description>The Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA) has revised air ticket refund norms, empowering passengers with a 48-hour no-charge cancellation/modification window and mandating refunds within 14 working days. This regulatory shift, aimed at enhancing passenger rights, introduces potential cost pressures and operational complexities for airlines already navigating a challenging financial climate. The move follows extensive passenger complaints and significant disruptions, notably the IndiGo operational crisis in December 2025, underscoring a move towards greater airline accountability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:03:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a028999e91847a1e78adc8_1772103994187.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IOB Assigned Fitch BBB- Rating with Stable Outlook; Viability Rating at 'bb'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IOB-Assigned-Fitch-BBB-Rating-with-Stable-Outlook-Viability-Rating-at-bb/69a027f29e91847a1e78ad11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IOB-Assigned-Fitch-BBB-Rating-with-Stable-Outlook-Viability-Rating-at-bb/69a027f29e91847a1e78ad11</guid><description>Indian Overseas Bank (IOB) has secured new global credit ratings from Fitch Ratings, including a Long Term Issuer Default Rating (LT-IDR) of 'BBB-/Stable' and a Viability Rating (VR) of 'bb'. The Short Term IDR is 'F3', and the Government Support Rating (GSR) is 'bbb-'. These ratings, verified on February 26, 2026, reflect the bank's evolving financial standing and its relationship with government backing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:01:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a027f29e91847a1e78ad10_1772103779591.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Greaves Electric Mobility Enters Nepal; Eyes IPO</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Greaves-Electric-Mobility-Enters-Nepal-Eyes-IPO/69a027ef9e91847a1e78acfb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Greaves-Electric-Mobility-Enters-Nepal-Eyes-IPO/69a027ef9e91847a1e78acfb</guid><description>Greaves Electric Mobility (GEM), a subsidiary of Greaves Cotton, has entered Nepal, marking its first international market. The company launched its Ampere Nexus electric scooter through a partnership with STC Auto Solution. GEM is also advancing plans for an Initial Public Offering (IPO), signaling significant growth and expansion strategies within the electric vehicle sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 11:01:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a027ef9e91847a1e78acfa_1772104136071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Novartis India Receives ₹5056 Cr Open Offer Statement from WaveRise, ChrysCapital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novartis-India-Receives-5056-Cr-Open-Offer-Statement-from-WaveRise-ChrysCapital/69a026139e91847a1e78ab9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novartis-India-Receives-5056-Cr-Open-Offer-Statement-from-WaveRise-ChrysCapital/69a026139e91847a1e78ab9e</guid><description>Novartis India Limited has formally acknowledged receipt of a Detailed Public Statement (DPS) for a significant open offer valued at ₹5,056.74 crore. The offer is being made by WaveRise Investments Limited, ChrysCapital Fund X, and Two Infinity Partners. This development signals a potential change in ownership structure for the pharmaceutical firm, which reported FY2024 revenues of ₹257.33 crore but a net profit of only ₹2.09 crore.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:53:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a026139e91847a1e78ab9d_1772103335110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JMD Realtors Acquires 12.47% Stake in Sharpline Broadcast at ₹10/Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/JMD-Realtors-Acquires-1247percent-Stake-in-Sharpline-Broadcast-at-10Share/69a025989e91847a1e78ab20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/JMD-Realtors-Acquires-1247percent-Stake-in-Sharpline-Broadcast-at-10Share/69a025989e91847a1e78ab20</guid><description>JMD Realtors Private Limited has acquired 35,71,428 equity shares, or 12.47% of paid-up capital, in Sharpline Broadcast Limited via preferential allotment at ₹10 per share. This move triggers SEBI disclosure requirements by crossing the 5% threshold. The shares were allotted pursuant to the conversion of a loan, signaling a potential financial restructuring for the media company.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:51:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a025989e91847a1e78ab1f_1772103164755.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samsung Bets Big on India: AI for Entry-Level Phones</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Samsung-Bets-Big-on-India-AI-for-Entry-Level-Phones/69a022ee9e91847a1e78a8a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Samsung-Bets-Big-on-India-AI-for-Entry-Level-Phones/69a022ee9e91847a1e78a8a7</guid><description>Samsung is strategically expanding its AI smartphone capabilities into India's entry-level market, targeting devices priced around ₹15,000. This move, spearheaded by the Galaxy A series, aims to capture market share and drive volume, despite escalating component costs and intense competition from rivals like Vivo and Oppo. The company is also bolstering its retail presence and affordability schemes to support this aggressive expansion, signaling a significant bet on AI-driven growth in the price-sensitive Indian segment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 10:39:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a022ee9e91847a1e78a8a6_1772102426783.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>