<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:30:46 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Solar Exports: Tariff Cut Offers Breather, Not Respite</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Solar-Exports-Tariff-Cut-Offers-Breather-Not-Respite/698f95837e6478cdfc273048</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Solar-Exports-Tariff-Cut-Offers-Breather-Not-Respite/698f95837e6478cdfc273048</guid><description>India's solar exporters secured a tactical win with US tariffs reduced to 18% from 25%, offering immediate pricing relief and boosting overseas sales. However, this benefit is shadowed by the US's aggressive push for domestic solar manufacturing under the Inflation Reduction Act, which is projected to rapidly diminish import reliance. Indian manufacturers must accelerate deep vertical integration to navigate this evolving global competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:20:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f95837e6478cdfc273047.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Spectrum Not Corporate Asset: SC Ruling Redefines Telco Insolvency</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Spectrum-Not-Corporate-Asset-SC-Ruling-Redefines-Telco-Insolvency/698f950d7e6478cdfc273006</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Spectrum-Not-Corporate-Asset-SC-Ruling-Redefines-Telco-Insolvency/698f950d7e6478cdfc273006</guid><description>The Supreme Court has ruled that telecom spectrum is a public resource and cannot be treated as a corporate asset under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC). This landmark judgment prohibits distressed telecom operators from using spectrum rights to restructure debt or repay creditors. The decision elevates the government's claim priority for spectrum dues and fundamentally alters financial restructuring avenues for the sector, potentially impacting lender recovery prospects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:18:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f950d7e6478cdfc273005.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Empowers Banks: New M&amp;A Finance Rules Spark Sector Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Empowers-Banks-New-MandA-Finance-Rules-Spark-Sector-Shift/698f950c7e6478cdfc272ffe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Empowers-Banks-New-MandA-Finance-Rules-Spark-Sector-Shift/698f950c7e6478cdfc272ffe</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has finalized rules allowing Indian banks to finance corporate acquisitions, a significant policy shift enabling participation in a market previously dominated by foreign lenders and non-bank entities. This move permits up to 20% of a bank's eligible capital to be used for such financing, with a lending limit of 75% of the acquisition value. The change aims to foster credit growth and enhance the competitiveness of Indian banks within a burgeoning M&amp;A environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:18:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f950c7e6478cdfc272ffd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Overhauls ETF Pricing: T-1 Shift Eyes Real-Time Alignment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Overhauls-ETF-Pricing-T-1-Shift-Eyes-Real-Time-Alignment/698f94307e6478cdfc272f4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Overhauls-ETF-Pricing-T-1-Shift-Eyes-Real-Time-Alignment/698f94307e6478cdfc272f4d</guid><description>India's Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) is set to overhaul exchange-traded fund (ETF) trading mechanics. The regulator has proposed shifting to a T-1 day reference price system, discarding the current T-2 NAV lag, and introducing dynamic price bands to better align ETF trading with underlying asset movements. These changes aim to bolster price discovery, reduce operational friction, and mitigate volatility-induced trading halts in the rapidly expanding Indian ETF market, which managed nearly ₹8.75 lakh crore by fiscal year 2025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:14:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f94307e6478cdfc272f4c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Inox Green Energy: Strategic Shift Fuels Profit Surge, Stock Reaction Muted</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Inox-Green-Energy-Strategic-Shift-Fuels-Profit-Surge-Stock-Reaction-Muted/698f941d7e6478cdfc272f3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Inox-Green-Energy-Strategic-Shift-Fuels-Profit-Surge-Stock-Reaction-Muted/698f941d7e6478cdfc272f3d</guid><description>Inox Green Energy Services Limited posted a robust Q3 FY26 with net profit soaring to ₹24.67 crore, up from ₹5.19 crore year-on-year, fueled by strong O&amp;M execution. Revenue climbed 33.8% to ₹81.79 crore. The company is actively streamlining its business by demerging its power evacuation unit to focus on higher-margin services. Despite these positive results, shares closed slightly lower on Friday, though the stock has outperformed the Nifty 50 over the past year. A capital raise of ₹145 per share during the quarter signals investor confidence amidst a high valuation environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:14:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f941d7e6478cdfc272f3c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>M&amp;M's EBITDA Misses Consensus Amid Growth; El Niño Fears Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandMs-EBITDA-Misses-Consensus-Amid-Growth-El-Niño-Fears-Loom/698f93c27e6478cdfc272e9d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandMs-EBITDA-Misses-Consensus-Amid-Growth-El-Niño-Fears-Loom/698f93c27e6478cdfc272e9d</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra's Q3 FY26 results showed a 19% year-on-year increase in standalone EBITDA to ₹5,290 crore, though this fell 4% short of Bloomberg consensus. Normalised PAT rose 31% to ₹4,000 crore, aided by higher other income, but reported PAT was affected by ₹590 crore in charges for the global farm equipment business. The company highlighted benefits from GST cuts on SUV premiumisation and entry-level cars, alongside strong reception for the XUV7XO. However, concerns over El Niño's potential impact on FY27 tractor demand persist, alongside upcoming regulatory compliance costs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:12:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f93c27e6478cdfc272e9c_1771017313710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HUL Revenue Grows, But Margin Pressure Persists Amid Growth Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Revenue-Grows-But-Margin-Pressure-Persists-Amid-Growth-Push/698f93c17e6478cdfc272e95</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Revenue-Grows-But-Margin-Pressure-Persists-Amid-Growth-Push/698f93c17e6478cdfc272e95</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever (HUL) saw its Q3FY26 revenue rise 2.8% year-on-year, with underlying volumes up 4%. However, EBITDA margins compressed to 23% due to gross margin decline and increased investment. Management reaffirmed 22-23% margin guidance, prioritizing volume-led growth and premiumization, while analysts maintain a cautious 'Hold' rating citing short-term margin pressures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f93c17e6478cdfc272e94_1771017330571.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airbnb Posts 10% Revenue Growth, But Profits Dip Amidst Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Airbnb-Posts-10percent-Revenue-Growth-But-Profits-Dip-Amidst-Investments/698f93447e6478cdfc272bf1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Airbnb-Posts-10percent-Revenue-Growth-But-Profits-Dip-Amidst-Investments/698f93447e6478cdfc272bf1</guid><description>Airbnb reported a 10% increase in full-year 2025 revenue, reaching $12.2 billion, bolstered by strong performance in markets such as India. However, net income saw a 3.8% decline to $2.5 billion, primarily attributed to increased operational expenses and strategic investments. Despite a slight dip in after-hours trading, the company forecasts continued revenue growth for 2026, signaling a focus on expansion over immediate profit maximization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:10:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f93447e6478cdfc272bf0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 10K Cr Fund Targets India's Deep-Tech Ambitions Amid Funding Gaps</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Rs-10K-Cr-Fund-Targets-Indias-Deep-Tech-Ambitions-Amid-Funding-Gaps/698f92b97e6478cdfc272b2b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Rs-10K-Cr-Fund-Targets-Indias-Deep-Tech-Ambitions-Amid-Funding-Gaps/698f92b97e6478cdfc272b2b</guid><description>The Indian government has greenlit a Rs 10,000 crore second tranche for the Startup India Fund of Funds Scheme. This infusion targets early-stage and deep-technology startups, aiming to bolster indigenous innovation and bridge critical funding gaps in capital-intensive sectors. The initiative seeks to address past operational inefficiencies and accelerate India's technological self-reliance amidst a maturing venture capital landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:08:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f92b97e6478cdfc272b2a_1771017077009.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Elegant Floriculture Postpones Q3 Results Amidst Financial 'Variations'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Elegant-Floriculture-Postpones-Q3-Results-Amidst-Financial-Variations/698f92b47e6478cdfc272b22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Elegant-Floriculture-Postpones-Q3-Results-Amidst-Financial-Variations/698f92b47e6478cdfc272b22</guid><description>Elegant Floriculture &amp; Agrotech (India) Limited has postponed its board meeting, originally scheduled for February 13, 2026, to February 14, 2026. The company cited "significant variations" in its un-audited financial results for the period ending December 31, 2025, necessitating further analysis. This delay has raised concerns among investors awaiting clarity on the company's financial performance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:08:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f92b47e6478cdfc272b21.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Naturite Agro Posts Profit After Loss, But Sequential Sales Drop</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Naturite-Agro-Posts-Profit-After-Loss-But-Sequential-Sales-Drop/698f924b7e6478cdfc272a6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Naturite-Agro-Posts-Profit-After-Loss-But-Sequential-Sales-Drop/698f924b7e6478cdfc272a6e</guid><description>Naturite Agro Products Limited has reported a significant turnaround, moving from losses to profitability in the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Year-on-year, revenue surged by over 900% in Q3 and 223% for the nine months, leading to net profits. However, sequential quarterly performance shows a sharp decline in both revenue and profit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:06:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f924b7e6478cdfc272a6d_1771016976433.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kenvi Jewels Profit Jumps, But EPS Plummets; Depreciation Zeroed Out</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kenvi-Jewels-Profit-Jumps-But-EPS-Plummets-Depreciation-Zeroed-Out/698f923c7e6478cdfc2729d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kenvi-Jewels-Profit-Jumps-But-EPS-Plummets-Depreciation-Zeroed-Out/698f923c7e6478cdfc2729d4</guid><description>Kenvi Jewels Limited reported a revenue increase of 12.72% to ₹52.85 Cr and profit after tax (PAT) up 61.88% to ₹0.46 Cr in Q3 FY26. However, basic Earnings Per Share (EPS) saw a sharp decline of 82.61% year-on-year. A significant point of concern is the reported zero depreciation expense for the quarter, an unusual accounting practice.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:06:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f923b7e6478cdfc2729d3_1771017106064.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Personal Loan Surge: Tech Fuels Growth Amidst Rising Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Personal-Loan-Surge-Tech-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Rising-Risks/698f920b7e6478cdfc2729ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Personal-Loan-Surge-Tech-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Rising-Risks/698f920b7e6478cdfc2729ac</guid><description>India's personal loan market is experiencing rapid expansion, driven by technology-led personalization and customer-centric strategies. Assets under management reached ₹15.9 lakh crore as of September 2025, with a 13% year-on-year growth [cite: input]. Advanced analytics and AI enable tailored loan offers, enhancing customer experience and broadening credit inclusion. However, this boom faces headwinds from increasing defaults in unsecured lending, tightening credit filters by lenders, and regulatory scrutiny, signaling a complex future for the sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:05:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f920b7e6478cdfc2729ab.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Finance Secures Top 'AAA' Ratings for ₹57,631 Crore Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Secures-Top-AAA-Ratings-for-57631-Crore-Debt/698f91707e6478cdfc2728ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Secures-Top-AAA-Ratings-for-57631-Crore-Debt/698f91707e6478cdfc2728ba</guid><description>Shriram Finance Limited has received top credit ratings from CARE Ratings, including 'CARE AAA; Stable' for its bank facilities and Non-Convertible Debentures, covering ₹57,631.12 Crore. The 'Stable' outlook signifies the company's robust financial health and low credit risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:02:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f91707e6478cdfc2728b9_1771016872871.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Monsoon Prediction Leap: India's Economy Gains Early Warning System</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Monsoon-Prediction-Leap-Indias-Economy-Gains-Early-Warning-System/698f90e77e6478cdfc2726b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Monsoon-Prediction-Leap-Indias-Economy-Gains-Early-Warning-System/698f90e77e6478cdfc2726b5</guid><description>A February 2026 research paper reveals a novel method to predict disruptive monsoon breaks by tracking dry western winds, offering crucial lead time for India's agricultural sector and water management. This advance aims to mitigate economic shocks from rainfall deficits that have historically impacted GDP and commodity prices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:00:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f90e77e6478cdfc2726b4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RACL Geartech Surges: Q3 Profit Soars 149%, Interim Dividend Declared</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RACL-Geartech-Surges-Q3-Profit-Soars-149percent-Interim-Dividend-Declared/698f906e7e6478cdfc272460</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RACL-Geartech-Surges-Q3-Profit-Soars-149percent-Interim-Dividend-Declared/698f906e7e6478cdfc272460</guid><description>RACL Geartech Ltd. reported a robust financial performance for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. Consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) surged by an impressive 149.1% year-on-year to ₹16.29 crore, while revenue grew 21.7% to ₹137.32 crore. The company's board also approved an interim dividend of ₹1.50 per share and set a budget of ₹565 crore for FY2026-27, alongside a significant capital expenditure plan.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:58:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f906e7e6478cdfc27245f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>USG Tech Solutions Reports Zero Revenue, Losses Persist</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/USG-Tech-Solutions-Reports-Zero-Revenue-Losses-Persist/698f905b7e6478cdfc2723a4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/USG-Tech-Solutions-Reports-Zero-Revenue-Losses-Persist/698f905b7e6478cdfc2723a4</guid><description>USG Tech Solutions has reported zero revenue from operations for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company continues to incur losses, relying solely on other income. Despite reduced expenditures, the consolidated net loss for the quarter was ₹2.14 Lakhs. The board approved the appointment of Mr. Ashish Gupta as an Additional Non-Executive Director.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:58:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f905b7e6478cdfc2723a3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indigo Paints Posts Strong Q3 Growth, Margins Shine Despite Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indigo-Paints-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Margins-Shine-Despite-Costs/698f8fe87e6478cdfc2720e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indigo-Paints-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Margins-Shine-Despite-Costs/698f8fe87e6478cdfc2720e9</guid><description>Indigo Paints announced its Q3 FY26 results, showcasing a 4.7% year-on-year increase in revenue to ₹358.8 crore. The company also reported a strong 19.5% rise in EBITDA to ₹68.3 crore, with EBITDA margins expanding to 19.4%. Profit after tax, excluding an exceptional item, grew 16.4%. The results reflect positive momentum in the decorative paint segment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:56:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f8fe87e6478cdfc2720e8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sawaca Enterprises Q3 Revenue Soars, But Huge Depreciation Sparks Alarm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sawaca-Enterprises-Q3-Revenue-Soars-But-Huge-Depreciation-Sparks-Alarm/698f8f6d7e6478cdfc272071</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sawaca-Enterprises-Q3-Revenue-Soars-But-Huge-Depreciation-Sparks-Alarm/698f8f6d7e6478cdfc272071</guid><description>Sawaca Enterprises Ltd reported a strong 100.4% year-on-year jump in revenue from operations to ₹11.43 crore for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. However, the financial results are overshadowed by an unusually high depreciation charge of ₹637.29 crore for the quarter, a figure disproportionately large compared to the company's total income and profit. This raises serious questions about the accuracy of reported profitability and the company's underlying financial health.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:54:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8f6d7e6478cdfc272070_1771016238268.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEYA INDUSTRIES LTD Faces Insolvency; Auditor Issues Limited Review</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/SEYA-INDUSTRIES-LTD-Faces-Insolvency-Auditor-Issues-Limited-Review/698f8f6a7e6478cdfc272069</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/SEYA-INDUSTRIES-LTD-Faces-Insolvency-Auditor-Issues-Limited-Review/698f8f6a7e6478cdfc272069</guid><description>Seya Industries Ltd has been admitted into the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), marking a severe financial distress. An independent auditor has published a 'Review Report' on its latest financial results, offering limited assurance rather than a full audit opinion. This situation means the company's board is suspended, with an Interim Resolution Professional (IRP) now in charge, signaling significant risk for existing shareholders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:54:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8f6a7e6478cdfc272068_1771016252944.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Senores Pharma Raises ₹95 Cr Via Warrants for Subsidiary Funding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Senores-Pharma-Raises-95-Cr-Via-Warrants-for-Subsidiary-Funding/698f8eff7e6478cdfc271e8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Senores-Pharma-Raises-95-Cr-Via-Warrants-for-Subsidiary-Funding/698f8eff7e6478cdfc271e8f</guid><description>Senores Pharmaceuticals Limited is set to raise approximately ₹95 crore through a preferential issue of 11.7 lakh convertible equity warrants to its promoter and promoter group. The funds are earmarked to provide a loan to its subsidiary, Apnar Pharma Private Limited, for working capital needs. This move follows Senores' acquisition of a 75% stake in Apnar Pharma, aimed at enhancing its manufacturing capabilities and market access. However, the company faces challenges including margin compression and increasing debt.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:52:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8eff7e6478cdfc271e8e_1771016117236.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RACL Geartech Soars: Q3 Profit Jumps 149%, Declares Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/RACL-Geartech-Soars-Q3-Profit-Jumps-149percent-Declares-Dividend/698f8ef27e6478cdfc271e3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/RACL-Geartech-Soars-Q3-Profit-Jumps-149percent-Declares-Dividend/698f8ef27e6478cdfc271e3d</guid><description>RACL Geartech Ltd. reported stellar Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 149% year-on-year to ₹16.29 Cr. Revenue also grew by 21.75%. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹1.50 per share and outlined significant capex plans for FY27.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:52:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8ef27e6478cdfc271e3c_1771016116830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Natural Biocon Posts Zero Revenue in Q3, Reports Net Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Natural-Biocon-Posts-Zero-Revenue-in-Q3-Reports-Net-Loss/698f8e077e6478cdfc271a5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Natural-Biocon-Posts-Zero-Revenue-in-Q3-Reports-Net-Loss/698f8e077e6478cdfc271a5c</guid><description>Natural Biocon (India) Limited has reported a dire third quarter for FY26, with revenue plummeting to ₹0.00 Lakhs, a stark 100% year-on-year drop. This resulted in a net loss of ₹4.27 Lakhs. While the nine-month period saw a revenue decline of 72.31%, profits improved to ₹44.83 Lakhs, driven solely by a significant 32.85% reduction in total expenses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:48:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f8e077e6478cdfc271a5b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sawaca Enterprises Plunges YoY Amidst Accounting Doubts &amp; Operating Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Sawaca-Enterprises-Plunges-YoY-Amidst-Accounting-Doubts-and-Operating-Losses/698f8e037e6478cdfc271a55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Sawaca-Enterprises-Plunges-YoY-Amidst-Accounting-Doubts-and-Operating-Losses/698f8e037e6478cdfc271a55</guid><description>Sawaca Enterprises Limited posted a sharp 51.50% year-over-year revenue decline for Q3 FY26, with profits falling 33.08%. While quarter-on-quarter performance showed a strong rebound, the company faces serious questions regarding data integrity, including a significant reconciliation gap and inconsistent accounting for 'Other Income'. Operating losses persist in key segments, compounding performance worries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:48:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8e037e6478cdfc271a54_1771016043419.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exicom IPO Funds Delayed; Tritium Losses Dent Profits, Shrink Net Worth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Exicom-IPO-Funds-Delayed-Tritium-Losses-Dent-Profits-Shrink-Net-Worth/698f8db37e6478cdfc27197a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Exicom-IPO-Funds-Delayed-Tritium-Losses-Dent-Profits-Shrink-Net-Worth/698f8db37e6478cdfc27197a</guid><description>Exicom Tele-Systems Limited's utilization of IPO funds is facing significant delays, with its manufacturing facility project nine months behind schedule. The company is also grappling with losses from its acquired subsidiary, Tritium, which has led to a widening of PBILDT losses in H1FY26 and a reduction in tangible net worth. While revenue showed growth, profitability remains under pressure, creating investor concerns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:46:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8db37e6478cdfc271979_1771015755776.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prism Medico Revenue Plummets 85%; Major Accounting Anomaly Raises Red Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Prism-Medico-Revenue-Plummets-85percent-Major-Accounting-Anomaly-Raises-Red-Flags/698f8d987e6478cdfc271884</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Prism-Medico-Revenue-Plummets-85percent-Major-Accounting-Anomaly-Raises-Red-Flags/698f8d987e6478cdfc271884</guid><description>Prism Medico And Pharmacy Limited reported a severe 85.86% year-on-year drop in revenue from operations to ₹7.10 Cr for Q3 FY26. The company also disclosed a significant accounting anomaly where 'Total income from operations' (₹71.79 Cr) did not reconcile with the sum of its components. This led to a net loss of ₹1.34 Cr for the quarter, despite a nine-month profit. The discrepancy raises serious concerns about financial transparency.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:46:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8d987e6478cdfc271883_1771015754756.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Veto Switchgears Profit Surges Over 67% on Strong Sales Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Veto-Switchgears-Profit-Surges-Over-67percent-on-Strong-Sales-Growth/698f8d227e6478cdfc271771</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Veto-Switchgears-Profit-Surges-Over-67percent-on-Strong-Sales-Growth/698f8d227e6478cdfc271771</guid><description>Veto Switchgears and Cables Limited has posted impressive financial results for the third quarter of FY26. Standalone net profit soared by 67.26% year-on-year to ₹641.92 Lacs, driven by a 30.01% jump in total income from operations. On a consolidated basis, net profit grew by a significant 72.62% to ₹627.16 Lacs, with income rising 24.45%. The nine-month performance also shows healthy growth in both revenue and profit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:44:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f8d227e6478cdfc271770.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Diana Tea Profits Soar 388% on Strong Sales; Auditors Note Provision Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Diana-Tea-Profits-Soar-388percent-on-Strong-Sales-Auditors-Note-Provision-Issue/698f8caf7e6478cdfc271648</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Diana-Tea-Profits-Soar-388percent-on-Strong-Sales-Auditors-Note-Provision-Issue/698f8caf7e6478cdfc271648</guid><description>Diana Tea Company Limited has reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with net profits surging 388.6% year-on-year to ₹529.93 crore, driven by a strong 25.3% jump in revenue to ₹3,106.72 crore. Despite the impressive performance, auditors noted the company has not made a full provision for a portion of its gratuity liability. The company highlighted the seasonal nature of the tea industry, with results varying quarterly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:42:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8caf7e6478cdfc271647_1771015683848.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shreyas Intermediates Reports Zero Revenue, Posts Wider Quarterly Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Shreyas-Intermediates-Reports-Zero-Revenue-Posts-Wider-Quarterly-Loss/698f8c9c7e6478cdfc2715c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Shreyas-Intermediates-Reports-Zero-Revenue-Posts-Wider-Quarterly-Loss/698f8c9c7e6478cdfc2715c8</guid><description>Shreyas Intermediates Limited has reported zero revenue from operations for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company posted a net loss of ₹39 lakh for the quarter, which widened from ₹24 lakh in the same period last year. While the nine-month loss narrowed to ₹36 lakh from ₹97 lakh, the absence of operational income raises serious concerns about the company's future business continuity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:42:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f8c9c7e6478cdfc2715c7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prostarm Info Systems Surges 110% in Q3, Eyes Growth Turnaround</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Prostarm-Info-Systems-Surges-110percent-in-Q3-Eyes-Growth-Turnaround/698f8c237e6478cdfc271466</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Prostarm-Info-Systems-Surges-110percent-in-Q3-Eyes-Growth-Turnaround/698f8c237e6478cdfc271466</guid><description>Prostarm Info Systems Limited has announced stellar financial results for the third quarter of FY26, with standalone revenue soaring 110.8% year-on-year to ₹159.34 Cr and profit after tax (PAT) jumping 104.9% to ₹15.96 Cr. This marks a significant acceleration compared to the more modest growth seen in the nine-month period, suggesting a strong turnaround quarter for the company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:40:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f8c237e6478cdfc271465.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nirav Commercials Sells Core Business for Tiny Sum, Focuses on Unclear Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nirav-Commercials-Sells-Core-Business-for-Tiny-Sum-Focuses-on-Unclear-Future/698f8baa7e6478cdfc271231</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nirav-Commercials-Sells-Core-Business-for-Tiny-Sum-Focuses-on-Unclear-Future/698f8baa7e6478cdfc271231</guid><description>Nirav Commercials Limited has decided to sell its 'Elesar Focchi' aluminium business to Hind Aluminium Industries, a related party, for ₹1.25 Crores. This unit generated nearly all of the company's revenue (₹9.64 Crores), raising questions about Nirav Commercials' future strategy as it aims to focus on its 'remaining business'. Shareholder approval is required for the deal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:38:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f8baa7e6478cdfc271230.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EMS Limited PAT Plunges 64% YoY Amid Revenue Fall, Shows QoQ Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EMS-Limited-PAT-Plunges-64percent-YoY-Amid-Revenue-Fall-Shows-QoQ-Recovery/698f8b477e6478cdfc27105b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EMS-Limited-PAT-Plunges-64percent-YoY-Amid-Revenue-Fall-Shows-QoQ-Recovery/698f8b477e6478cdfc27105b</guid><description>EMS Limited reported a steep 64.59% year-on-year fall in standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹17.78 Cr for Q3 FY26, with consolidated PAT down 61.91% to ₹19.28 Cr. Annual revenue also declined. However, the company demonstrated a notable quarter-on-quarter improvement in both revenue and PAT. Key events include the acquisition of EMS Industries and formation of a joint venture for a Kolkata river project.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:36:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8b477e6478cdfc27105a_1771015155797.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Savita Oil Tech's Q3 Profit Surges Over 200% YoY, Revenue Grows 13%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Savita-Oil-Techs-Q3-Profit-Surges-Over-200percent-YoY-Revenue-Grows-13percent/698f8abc7e6478cdfc270e9f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Savita-Oil-Techs-Q3-Profit-Surges-Over-200percent-YoY-Revenue-Grows-13percent/698f8abc7e6478cdfc270e9f</guid><description>Savita Oil Technologies has announced a stellar Q3 FY26 performance, with consolidated profit after tax (PAT) soaring by over 200% year-on-year to ₹37.95 crore. Revenue from operations also saw a healthy jump of 13.56% to ₹1,073.62 crore. Despite a slight sequential dip, the company's strong year-on-year growth marks a significant turnaround, and its auditors provided a clean review.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:34:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8abc7e6478cdfc270e9e_1771015176288.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Natural Biocon India Reports Zero Revenue, Posts Quarterly Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Natural-Biocon-India-Reports-Zero-Revenue-Posts-Quarterly-Loss/698f8abb7e6478cdfc270e97</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Natural-Biocon-India-Reports-Zero-Revenue-Posts-Quarterly-Loss/698f8abb7e6478cdfc270e97</guid><description>Natural Biocon (India) Limited has reported a startling financial update, with zero revenue from operations in the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. This resulted in a net loss of ₹0.04 crore for the quarter, a sharp reversal from a profit in the previous year. Year-to-date performance also shows a significant 72.3% drop in revenue and an 88.6% fall in net profit compared to the same period last year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:34:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f8abb7e6478cdfc270e96.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pradhin Falls 96% in Revenue, Auditors Flag Major Red Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pradhin-Falls-96percent-in-Revenue-Auditors-Flag-Major-Red-Flags/698f8a597e6478cdfc270ca5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pradhin-Falls-96percent-in-Revenue-Auditors-Flag-Major-Red-Flags/698f8a597e6478cdfc270ca5</guid><description>Pradhin Limited has reported a catastrophic 96.1% year-on-year fall in revenue for Q3 FY26, plunging to ₹8.00 Cr from ₹205.80 Cr. The company also swung to a loss, with a net loss of ₹0.78 Cr. Compounding these grim financial numbers, the statutory auditors have issued multiple critical qualifications on the company's financial statements, raising serious concerns about accounting practices, asset verification, debt management, and regulatory compliance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:32:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8a597e6478cdfc270ca4_1771015076588.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Virgo Global Loss Widens, CFO Resigns Amid Negative Net Worth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Virgo-Global-Loss-Widens-CFO-Resigns-Amid-Negative-Net-Worth/698f8a447e6478cdfc270be7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Virgo-Global-Loss-Widens-CFO-Resigns-Amid-Negative-Net-Worth/698f8a447e6478cdfc270be7</guid><description>Virgo Global reported a significantly widened net loss of ₹76.13 Lacs in Q3 FY26, driven by a 91.7% YoY and 899% QoQ surge in expenses. The company's net worth has turned negative at ₹25.66 Lacs. Adding to concerns, Whole-Time Director and CFO Umasankar Mylapur Prakash Rao has resigned.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:32:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f8a447e6478cdfc270be6_1771015068273.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shree Tirupati Agro Sees Revenue Jump, But Losses Balloon</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Shree-Tirupati-Agro-Sees-Revenue-Jump-But-Losses-Balloon/698f89cb7e6478cdfc270a64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Shree-Tirupati-Agro-Sees-Revenue-Jump-But-Losses-Balloon/698f89cb7e6478cdfc270a64</guid><description>Shree Tirupati Balajee Agro Trading reported strong revenue growth for Q3 FY26, with standalone sales soaring over 160% YoY. However, this growth came at a steep cost, as net losses widened significantly for both standalone and consolidated operations, driven by high finance costs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f89cb7e6478cdfc270a63_1771014937178.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BBTC Declares Big Dividend, Reappoints MD, Boosts Profits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/BBTC-Declares-Big-Dividend-Reappoints-MD-Boosts-Profits/698f89697e6478cdfc27088a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/BBTC-Declares-Big-Dividend-Reappoints-MD-Boosts-Profits/698f89697e6478cdfc27088a</guid><description>Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation (BBTC) board approved a hefty 850% interim dividend (₹17/share) and reappointed Ness N. Wadia as Managing Director for five years. The company also reported improved financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025, showcasing reduced debt levels and strong profit growth on a standalone basis, despite a slight dip in consolidated earnings per share.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:28:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f89697e6478cdfc270889_1771014690470.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>M M Forgings Profit Plunges 34% as Costs Surge Despite Flat Sales</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/M-M-Forgings-Profit-Plunges-34percent-as-Costs-Surge-Despite-Flat-Sales/698f89587e6478cdfc270803</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/M-M-Forgings-Profit-Plunges-34percent-as-Costs-Surge-Despite-Flat-Sales/698f89587e6478cdfc270803</guid><description>M M Forgings Limited saw its profits tumble by over 34% for the nine months ending December 2025 compared to the previous year. While revenue remained nearly flat, a significant jump in finance costs and operating expenses squeezed profitability. Standalone net profit dropped to ₹65.80 crore from ₹100.06 crore.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:28:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f89587e6478cdfc270802_1771014704323.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Varvee Global Posts Q3 Profit Turnaround, Auditors Raise MAT Credit Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Varvee-Global-Posts-Q3-Profit-Turnaround-Auditors-Raise-MAT-Credit-Concern/698f88ec7e6478cdfc27065f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Varvee-Global-Posts-Q3-Profit-Turnaround-Auditors-Raise-MAT-Credit-Concern/698f88ec7e6478cdfc27065f</guid><description>Varvee Global Limited, formerly Aarvee Denims, has turned profitable in Q3 FY26, posting a net profit of ₹5.35 Cr against a loss last year. Revenue rose 18.2% YoY. However, auditors issued an 'Emphasis of Matter' regarding the recognition of MAT credit as an asset, contingent on future profitability, adding a note of caution for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:26:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f88ec7e6478cdfc27065e_1771014562394.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>