<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:39:59 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Indian QSRs Rally on Earnings, Merger Hopes; Valuations Vary</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-QSRs-Rally-on-Earnings-Merger-Hopes-Valuations-Vary/698462ccbf48f011a29c0c1d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-QSRs-Rally-on-Earnings-Merger-Hopes-Valuations-Vary/698462ccbf48f011a29c0c1d</guid><description>Quick Service Restaurant (QSR) stocks defied a weak market on Thursday, rallying up to 13% following Q3 FY26 earnings reports. Companies like Devyani International, Westlife Foodworld, Sapphire Foods India, and Jubilant FoodWorks saw share price increases, largely attributed to pricing strategies that boosted growth and exceeded margin expectations. The proposed merger between Devyani International and Sapphire Foods India is anticipated to unlock significant synergies. However, beneath the sector-wide uplift, individual company performances reveal a divergence, with some facing declining net profits despite revenue gains, and several entities trading at high or negative P/E multiples.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Stock Surges as QIP, Acquisition Plans Shelved</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PB-Fintech-Stock-Surges-as-QIP-Acquisition-Plans-Shelved/69846299bf48f011a29c0af3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PB-Fintech-Stock-Surges-as-QIP-Acquisition-Plans-Shelved/69846299bf48f011a29c0af3</guid><description>PB Fintech's stock jumped 8.2% on Thursday, February 5, 2026, to ₹1,559.50. The surge followed the cancellation of a board meeting intended to approve a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) and the shelving of acquisition plans. This move, attributed to shareholder feedback, suggests a market preference for current stability and profitability over aggressive expansion initiatives. The company's high valuation and the broader InsurTech sector's growth dynamics provide a complex backdrop for this strategic pause.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Godrej Properties Shares Slip Amidst Revenue Drop, EBITDA Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-Shares-Slip-Amidst-Revenue-Drop-EBITDA-Loss/6984626bbf48f011a29c09f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-Shares-Slip-Amidst-Revenue-Drop-EBITDA-Loss/6984626bbf48f011a29c09f1</guid><description>Godrej Properties Ltd. saw its shares decline on February 4, 2026, following its third-quarter results. While bookings surged 55% to ₹8,421 crore and the company remains on track to meet its full-year guidance of ₹32,500 crore, a stark 48.6% year-on-year drop in revenue to ₹498.4 crore and an EBITDA loss of ₹182.7 crore (compared to a profit of ₹27.7 crore) overshadowed the positive booking momentum. Net profit, however, rose 20% to ₹195.2 crore, but fell short of analyst expectations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:27:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Air India Express Targets Profit Amidst Sector Turbulence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Express-Targets-Profit-Amidst-Sector-Turbulence/69846233bf48f011a29c093c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Express-Targets-Profit-Amidst-Sector-Turbulence/69846233bf48f011a29c093c</guid><description>Air India Express is poised to report its first operating profit since its 2022 privatization, forecasting a turnaround in the second half of FY26. This milestone is attributed to stringent cost controls, improved unit economics, and enhanced operational performance. However, the airline faces intense competition from established players like IndiGo and a challenging broader Indian aviation market projected to incur significant net losses for FY26. Despite ambitious growth plans, AIE's strategic 'value carrier' positioning and overall financial viability remain under scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Marksans Pharma Posts Strong Q3, But Nine-Month Profit Dips Amid Margin Pressure.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Marksans-Pharma-Posts-Strong-Q3-But-Nine-Month-Profit-Dips-Amid-Margin-Pressure/698460fbbf48f011a29c0555</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Marksans-Pharma-Posts-Strong-Q3-But-Nine-Month-Profit-Dips-Amid-Margin-Pressure/698460fbbf48f011a29c0555</guid><description>Marksans Pharma reported a robust Q3 FY26 with a 10.6% YoY revenue jump to ₹754.4 crore and expanded EBITDA margins to 21.3%. However, the nine-month FY26 period showed a slight 0.1% dip in EBITDA and a 7.1% decline in PAT to ₹271.0 crore, signaling margin pressures despite strategic expansion in Europe and Canada.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>360 ONE Launches SIF Fund Amid Regulatory Evolution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/360-ONE-Launches-SIF-Fund-Amid-Regulatory-Evolution/698460ccbf48f011a29c0410</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/360-ONE-Launches-SIF-Fund-Amid-Regulatory-Evolution/698460ccbf48f011a29c0410</guid><description>360 ONE Mutual Fund has launched its DynaSIF Equity Long–Short Fund, its inaugural offering within India's newly established Specialised Investment Fund (SIF) framework. The fund, open from February 6 to February 20, 2026, aims for long-term capital appreciation through selective long and short positions. This move capitalizes on the SIF framework's enhanced flexibility, introduced in 2025 by SEBI, to bridge the gap between traditional mutual funds and alternative investment strategies, amidst growing competition from peers like Quant, SBI, and Edelweiss.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Alembic Pharma Q3: Consolidated PAT Dips, Standalone Growth Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Alembic-Pharma-Q3-Consolidated-PAT-Dips-Standalone-Growth-Soars/698460a3bf48f011a29c0331</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Alembic-Pharma-Q3-Consolidated-PAT-Dips-Standalone-Growth-Soars/698460a3bf48f011a29c0331</guid><description>Alembic Pharmaceuticals reported mixed Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue up 10.84% to ₹1,876 Cr, but PAT fell 3.94% to ₹133 Cr due to exceptional items. Standalone operations excelled, seeing revenue rise 16.79% and PAT surge 33.40%. Margins improved across both segments. A Non-Executive Director appointment was also approved.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BlackBuck Posts Strong Revenue Growth, Turns Profitable in Q3 FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/BlackBuck-Posts-Strong-Revenue-Growth-Turns-Profitable-in-Q3-FY26/6984606dbf48f011a29c01fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/BlackBuck-Posts-Strong-Revenue-Growth-Turns-Profitable-in-Q3-FY26/6984606dbf48f011a29c01fb</guid><description>BlackBuck Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26, with Total Income up 53.12% YoY to ₹188.27 Cr and Revenue from Operations up 50.71% YoY to ₹171.78 Cr. The company achieved a significant profit turnaround, posting ₹31.72 Cr PAT compared to a ₹48.03 Cr loss in Q3 FY25. Adjusted EBITDA grew 51.35% YoY to ₹50.04 Cr. Key operating metrics and growth ventures show strong momentum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Tax Reforms Ease Burden, Risk Unintended Compliance Gaps</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Tax-Reforms-Ease-Burden-Risk-Unintended-Compliance-Gaps/69845fe0bf48f011a29c0094</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Tax-Reforms-Ease-Burden-Risk-Unintended-Compliance-Gaps/69845fe0bf48f011a29c0094</guid><description>Budget 2026 enacts significant tax reforms, moving from a punitive system to one prioritizing correction. Decriminalizing minor procedural errors and replacing discretionary penalties with graded fees under new provisions aims to alleviate compliance stress for businesses and individuals. However, the delicate balance of incentivizing voluntary adherence while preventing strategic avoidance poses a key challenge for fiscal stability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pidilite Industries: Buy Signal Issued With ₹1734 Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pidilite-Industries-Buy-Signal-Issued-With-1734-Target/69845f43bf48f011a29bfe7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pidilite-Industries-Buy-Signal-Issued-With-1734-Target/69845f43bf48f011a29bfe7d</guid><description>Prabhudas Lilladher has maintained a 'BUY' rating on Pidilite Industries, setting a new target price of ₹1734. The brokerage highlights the company's strong volume growth momentum and expanding EBITDA margins, even with increased advertising spend. Pidilite's focus on category development, new segments, and B2B project verticals is expected to drive future expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JK Lakshmi Cement: Margin Dip Overshadows Growth Amid Pricing Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JK-Lakshmi-Cement-Margin-Dip-Overshadows-Growth-Amid-Pricing-Headwinds/69845f32bf48f011a29bfe20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JK-Lakshmi-Cement-Margin-Dip-Overshadows-Growth-Amid-Pricing-Headwinds/69845f32bf48f011a29bfe20</guid><description>JK Lakshmi Cement reported a challenging Q3 FY26, with operating performance impacted by a significant 10% quarter-on-quarter decline in average realizations, pushing EBITDA per tonne to Rs 625. Despite 8% year-on-year volume growth driven by institutional sales, lower prices offset gains. Management projects a price recovery post-December 2025, supported by demand and input cost inflation. The company continues its strategic focus on capacity additions and operational efficiencies, including enhanced green power usage, expected to support long-term margins. Analysts maintain a positive stance, projecting robust EBITDA and volume growth through FY28, while slightly adjusting price targets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Silver Plummets Nearly 10%, Exposing Fragile Investor Confidence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Plummets-Nearly-10percent-Exposing-Fragile-Investor-Confidence/69845f00bf48f011a29bfcff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Plummets-Nearly-10percent-Exposing-Fragile-Investor-Confidence/69845f00bf48f011a29bfcff</guid><description>Silver prices experienced a precipitous drop of nearly 10% on February 5, 2026, erasing recent gains and highlighting a significant bout of market volatility. The decline, attributed to renewed selling pressure and a confluence of geopolitical and macroeconomic factors, saw prices fall to $78.90 per ounce internationally. This sharp reversal signals a fragile investor sentiment, particularly following record outflows from Chinese gold ETFs and concerns over Federal Reserve policy shifts. Despite predictions of a potential long-term bullish trend driven by industrial demand and supply deficits, the immediate market reaction points to a cautious and uncertain outlook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fractal Analytics IPO Priced Lower Amid GPU Woes, Eyes August AI Model Launch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Priced-Lower-Amid-GPU-Woes-Eyes-August-AI-Model-Launch/69845e9abf48f011a29bfb10</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Priced-Lower-Amid-GPU-Woes-Eyes-August-AI-Model-Launch/69845e9abf48f011a29bfb10</guid><description>Fractal Analytics has recalibrated its initial public offering (IPO) price band, aiming to attract investors by leaving 'money on the table.' The enterprise AI firm is also facing delays in its foundation model launch for the IndiaAI Mission, now targeted for August 15, 2026, due to a pending Graphics Processing Unit (GPU) allocation from the government.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:10:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845e9abf48f011a29bfb0f_1770284278044.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Digital Security Imperative Fuels Fintech &amp; Cyber Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Digital-Security-Imperative-Fuels-Fintech-and-Cyber-Growth/69845e88bf48f011a29bfab6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Digital-Security-Imperative-Fuels-Fintech-and-Cyber-Growth/69845e88bf48f011a29bfab6</guid><description>The increasing realization of mobile device vulnerabilities is accelerating demand for robust digital security measures. This heightened consumer awareness is a significant tailwind for the cybersecurity sector and is influencing consumer adoption patterns within fintech, driving a market shift towards more secure platforms and services. Financial institutions face renewed pressure to enhance security protocols and data protection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:10:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845e88bf48f011a29bfab5_1770284266530.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Nears: First Tranche Ready, GCC FTA Talks Gain Momentum</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Deal-Nears-First-Tranche-Ready-GCC-FTA-Talks-Gain-Momentum/69845e6fbf48f011a29bf9e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Deal-Nears-First-Tranche-Ready-GCC-FTA-Talks-Gain-Momentum/69845e6fbf48f011a29bf9e7</guid><description>India is poised to implement the first tranche of its trade deal with the United States within days, signaling imminent tariff reductions. Union Commerce Minister Piyush Goyal announced the progress, targeting a formal agreement by mid-March. Concurrently, India revived talks for a long-pending Free Trade Agreement with the Gulf Cooperation Council, aiming to boost bilateral trade currently valued at $179 billion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:10:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845e6fbf48f011a29bf9e6_1770284125210.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Voltamp Transformers Posts 30% Revenue Surge in Q3, Order Book Bolsters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Voltamp-Transformers-Posts-30percent-Revenue-Surge-in-Q3-Order-Book-Bolsters/69845dfbbf48f011a29bf7dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Voltamp-Transformers-Posts-30percent-Revenue-Surge-in-Q3-Order-Book-Bolsters/69845dfbbf48f011a29bf7dc</guid><description>Voltamp Transformers delivered robust Q3 FY26 results, reporting a 30% year-on-year surge in Net Sales to ₹630.32 Crores. Profit Before Tax (PBT) climbed 27% YoY to ₹129.88 Crores. The company secured fresh orders worth ₹1981 Crores, bolstering its order book which began FY26 at ₹938 Crores. A new EHV transformer facility is on schedule for completion by June 2026. Management highlighted positive infrastructure spending trends but flagged risks from geopolitical tensions, currency volatility, and rising copper prices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:08:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845dfbbf48f011a29bf7db_1770284129315.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Knowledge Realty Trust Posts Strong Q3 Profit, Approves INR 6,953M Distribution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Knowledge-Realty-Trust-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Approves-INR-6953M-Distribution/69845d93bf48f011a29bf631</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Knowledge-Realty-Trust-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Approves-INR-6953M-Distribution/69845d93bf48f011a29bf631</guid><description>Knowledge Realty Trust announced a substantial consolidated Profit Before Tax (PBT) of INR 7,778.93 million for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. The Board also approved a significant distribution of INR 6,953.14 million (INR 1.568 per Unit) for the period. Direct financial comparison with prior periods is limited due to the Trust's recent incorporation on October 10, 2024, and subsequent large-scale acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:06:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845d93bf48f011a29bf630_1770283974547.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Marksans Pharma Q3 Surge: Revenue Jumps 10.6%, Profit Beats Expectations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Marksans-Pharma-Q3-Surge-Revenue-Jumps-106percent-Profit-Beats-Expectations/69845d62bf48f011a29bf4f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Marksans-Pharma-Q3-Surge-Revenue-Jumps-106percent-Profit-Beats-Expectations/69845d62bf48f011a29bf4f0</guid><description>Marksans Pharma reported a robust Q3 FY26 with operating revenue climbing 10.6% YoY to ₹754.4 crore and EBITDA soaring 23.2% YoY to ₹160.7 crore, boosting the EBITDA margin by 217 bps to 21.3%. While nine-month PAT declined 7.1% YoY due to an early fiscal year slowdown and higher costs, the strong sequential improvement in Q3 highlights management's effective strategies. The company targets ₹3,000 crore revenue within a year, driven by global expansion and a focus on the OTC segment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:05:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845d62bf48f011a29bf4ef_1770283841663.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PVR INOX Skyrockets Profit, Slashes Debt in Strong Q3 FY'26 Results</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVR-INOX-Skyrockets-Profit-Slashes-Debt-in-Strong-Q3-FY26-Results/69845d38bf48f011a29bf3b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVR-INOX-Skyrockets-Profit-Slashes-Debt-in-Strong-Q3-FY26-Results/69845d38bf48f011a29bf3b9</guid><description>PVR INOX reported a stellar Q3 FY'26, with revenue climbing 9.7% YoY to INR 19,077 Mn and adjusted EBITDA surging 32.8% to INR 3,435 Mn. PAT turned positive at INR 1,149 Mn, a 68.7% increase YoY. For 9M FY'26, revenue grew 14.2% to INR 52,388 Mn, and PAT turned around from a loss to INR 2,078 Mn. The company significantly deleveraged, cutting net debt by over 60% to INR 3,652 Mn, driven by robust free cash flow. Operational metrics like admits, ATP, and F&amp;B SPH also showed strong growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:04:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845d38bf48f011a29bf3b8_1770283700750.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IMFA Acquires Tata Steel Plant, Q3 Profit Surges Amidst Mixed 9-Month View</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IMFA-Acquires-Tata-Steel-Plant-Q3-Profit-Surges-Amidst-Mixed-9-Month-View/69845d1abf48f011a29bf2ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IMFA-Acquires-Tata-Steel-Plant-Q3-Profit-Surges-Amidst-Mixed-9-Month-View/69845d1abf48f011a29bf2ec</guid><description>Indian Metals &amp; Ferro Alloys (IMFA) reported robust Q3 FY26 year-on-year growth, with revenue up 9.27% to ₹702.83 Cr and PAT soaring 40.29% to ₹130.67 Cr. However, nine-month performance showed a 3.05% PAT decline. The company announced a significant acquisition of Tata Steel's Ferro Alloys Plant in Odisha, subject to approvals. No forward guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:04:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845d1abf48f011a29bf2eb_1770283611668.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India Express FY25 Losses Mount Amidst Group Financial Turmoil</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Express-FY25-Losses-Mount-Amidst-Group-Financial-Turmoil/69845cc0bf48f011a29bf17d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Express-FY25-Losses-Mount-Amidst-Group-Financial-Turmoil/69845cc0bf48f011a29bf17d</guid><description>Air India Express reported a substantial net loss in FY2025, contrary to earlier profit projections. The broader Air India Group also posted widened consolidated losses, weighed down by high costs for fleet modernization, geopolitical headwinds such as the Pakistan airspace ban, and ongoing aircraft delivery delays. Despite aggressive expansion and refurbishment plans, achieving group-wide profitability remains a considerable challenge, further impacting stakeholder Singapore Airlines.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:02:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845cc0bf48f011a29bf17c_1770283495975.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sun Pharma Bets ₹500 Cr on Assam for Domestic Growth &amp; Diversification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sun-Pharma-Bets-500-Cr-on-Assam-for-Domestic-Growth-and-Diversification/69845c9abf48f011a29bf09e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sun-Pharma-Bets-500-Cr-on-Assam-for-Domestic-Growth-and-Diversification/69845c9abf48f011a29bf09e</guid><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries is deploying ₹500 crore to establish a new pharmaceutical manufacturing plant in Assam, a strategic move aimed at bolstering its domestic formulation capacity and diversifying its geographic operational base. The phased project is slated to create over 500 direct jobs and aligns with India's broader objectives for industrial growth and pharmaceutical self-sufficiency. This investment leverages Sun Pharma's extensive global network and deep domestic market penetration, positioning it for continued expansion within the robust Indian pharmaceutical sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:02:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845c9abf48f011a29bf09d_1770283338788.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Voltas Eyes AC Rebound Amidst Margin Squeeze Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Voltas-Eyes-AC-Rebound-Amidst-Margin-Squeeze-Risk/69845c5fbf48f011a29bef4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Voltas-Eyes-AC-Rebound-Amidst-Margin-Squeeze-Risk/69845c5fbf48f011a29bef4f</guid><description>Voltas anticipates a robust double-digit revenue increase in its room air conditioner segment this summer, driven by first-time buyers and India's low AC penetration. However, the company faces significant headwinds from escalating commodity prices and new energy-efficiency norms, potentially squeezing margins despite expected demand recovery. Voltas, the market leader, is navigating fierce competition as it aims to capitalize on the substantial untapped potential in the Indian cooling market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:01:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845c5fbf48f011a29bef4e_1770283230885.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors Launches Range Rover Evoque Assembly in India, Eyes Export Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Launches-Range-Rover-Evoque-Assembly-in-India-Eyes-Export-Growth/69845c3dbf48f011a29bee3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Launches-Range-Rover-Evoque-Assembly-in-India-Eyes-Export-Growth/69845c3dbf48f011a29bee3e</guid><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd. will begin assembling the Range Rover Evoque at its new Panapakkam, Tamil Nadu plant on February 9. This move aims to capture surging domestic luxury car demand and eventually leverage the 250,000-unit capacity plant for exports. The facility is designed to absorb more JLR assembly, currently at Tata's Pune plant, positioning India as a key hub for premium car production and competitive pricing against rivals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:00:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845c3dbf48f011a29bee3d_1770283162741.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PVR INOX Surges on Record Revenue, Profit, and Debt Reduction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVR-INOX-Surges-on-Record-Revenue-Profit-and-Debt-Reduction/69845c16bf48f011a29bed7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVR-INOX-Surges-on-Record-Revenue-Profit-and-Debt-Reduction/69845c16bf48f011a29bed7d</guid><description>PVR INOX posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with adjusted revenue climbing 9.7% YoY to INR 19,077 million and adjusted PAT surging 68.7% to INR 1,149 million. The company benefited from a record-breaking Indian theatrical industry in 2025 and achieved its highest post-pandemic 9-month revenue and PAT. Significant financial discipline led to a 74% reduction in net debt to INR 3,652 million, its lowest since the merger, buoyed by operational cash flow and strategic divestments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:00:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845c16bf48f011a29bed7c_1770282995201.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pharma Eyes NAM Leadership Amid Animal Testing Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Eyes-NAM-Leadership-Amid-Animal-Testing-Debate/69845b8abf48f011a29beb9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Eyes-NAM-Leadership-Amid-Animal-Testing-Debate/69845b8abf48f011a29beb9e</guid><description>Dr. Reddy's Laboratories is spearheading India's ambition to lead in promoting non-animal methodologies (NAMs) for drug discovery, a move supported by a recent report recommending central agencies and multi-stakeholder collaborations. While lauded for potential cost and time savings, particularly for biologics and generics, the report acknowledges that animal testing remains necessary for novel chemical drugs. This aligns with global trends favoring ethical research and regulatory evolution, including the US FDA Modernization Act 2.0, but significant investment and a clear regulatory path are crucial for widespread adoption across all drug types.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Q3 Revenue Surges 10%, But Margins Face Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Q3-Revenue-Surges-10percent-But-Margins-Face-Pressure/69845b61bf48f011a29beaa6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Q3-Revenue-Surges-10percent-But-Margins-Face-Pressure/69845b61bf48f011a29beaa6</guid><description>Max Healthcare's Q3 FY26 revenue jumped 10% YoY to ₹2,608 Cr, with 9-month PAT up 30%. While EBITDA grew 4%, margins slightly compressed. The company is aggressively expanding capacity and pursuing strategic acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:57:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845b61bf48f011a29beaa5_1770282867983.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nava Ltd: Consolidated Revenue Rises 17.6%, PAT Dips 7.8% on Higher Taxes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nava-Ltd-Consolidated-Revenue-Rises-176percent-PAT-Dips-78percent-on-Higher-Taxes/69845b1fbf48f011a29be939</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nava-Ltd-Consolidated-Revenue-Rises-176percent-PAT-Dips-78percent-on-Higher-Taxes/69845b1fbf48f011a29be939</guid><description>Nava Limited reported a 17.6% YoY increase in consolidated revenue to ₹1061.5 Cr for Q3 FY26, driven by mining and power segments. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) declined 7.8% YoY to ₹325.7 Cr, primarily due to a doubling of tax expenses, leading to a margin contraction. Conversely, standalone operations showed robust growth, with revenue up 41.4% YoY and PAT surging 185.6% YoY to ₹47.4 Cr, bolstered by Ferro Alloys and Mining. Key growth drivers include the upcoming commissioning of MEL Phase II and Maamba Solar projects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Q3 PAT Soars 26%, Greenlights ₹10,200 Cr Pune Hospital Plan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Q3-PAT-Soars-26percent-Greenlights-10200-Cr-Pune-Hospital-Plan/69845af3bf48f011a29be829</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Q3-PAT-Soars-26percent-Greenlights-10200-Cr-Pune-Hospital-Plan/69845af3bf48f011a29be829</guid><description>Max Healthcare Institute Limited reported a robust 25.99% year-on-year surge in consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹30,092 lakhs for the quarter ending December 31, 2025. While standalone revenue grew modestly by 1.94% YoY to ₹71,091 lakhs, standalone PAT escalated by 35.23% YoY to ₹18,695 lakhs. The company approved a significant ₹1,02,000 lakhs (₹10,200 Cr) investment for a new ~450-bed super-speciality hospital in Pune and expanded its Dwarka facility services to include ~260 additional beds. Consolidated results were impacted by ₹4,824 lakhs in exceptional items.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:55:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845af3bf48f011a29be828_1770282554485.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Voltamp Transformers Q3 Profit Surges 35%, Labour Law Costs Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Voltamp-Transformers-Q3-Profit-Surges-35percent-Labour-Law-Costs-Emerge/69845ab0bf48f011a29be735</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Voltamp-Transformers-Q3-Profit-Surges-35percent-Labour-Law-Costs-Emerge/69845ab0bf48f011a29be735</guid><description>Voltamp Transformers reported a robust Q3 FY26, with net profit soaring 34.98% year-on-year to ₹9,908.26 Lakhs on a 30.35% revenue increase. Basic EPS rose to ₹97.94. However, net profit margins saw a slight sequential dip, and the company provisioned ₹517.18 Lakhs for implications of new Labour Codes. Nine-month results also show healthy growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:54:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845ab0bf48f011a29be734_1770282415395.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Knowledge Realty Trust posts 21% revenue growth, added to global REIT index</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Knowledge-Realty-Trust-posts-21percent-revenue-growth-added-to-global-REIT-index/69845a8bbf48f011a29be6b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Knowledge-Realty-Trust-posts-21percent-revenue-growth-added-to-global-REIT-index/69845a8bbf48f011a29be6b9</guid><description>Knowledge Realty Trust (KRT) reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue up 21% YoY to ₹11,787 million and Net Operating Income (NOI) growing 19% YoY to ₹10,407 million. The REIT leased 0.6 million sq ft in the quarter, maintaining 92% occupancy. KRT also reduced its average debt cost and was added to the FTSE EPRA Nareit Global REITs index, signaling strong operational performance and positive future prospects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:53:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845a8bbf48f011a29be6b8_1770282412767.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Voltamp Transformers Q3 Profit Surges 35%, Revenue Jumps 30%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Voltamp-Transformers-Q3-Profit-Surges-35percent-Revenue-Jumps-30percent/69845a5bbf48f011a29be5a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Voltamp-Transformers-Q3-Profit-Surges-35percent-Revenue-Jumps-30percent/69845a5bbf48f011a29be5a7</guid><description>Voltamp Transformers posted a strong Q3 FY26, with Net Profit soaring 34.98% YoY to ₹9,908.26 Lakhs on Revenue growth of 30.35% to ₹63,032.32 Lakhs. Basic EPS climbed 34.98% YoY to ₹97.94. For the nine months, Net Profit grew 12.64% YoY. The company also made an additional provision of ₹517.18 Lakhs for consolidated Labour Codes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:52:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845a5bbf48f011a29be5a6_1770282292265.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anthem Biosciences Q3 Slips, Investors Fear Uncertainty on No Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Anthem-Biosciences-Q3-Slips-Investors-Fear-Uncertainty-on-No-Outlook/69845a40bf48f011a29be518</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Anthem-Biosciences-Q3-Slips-Investors-Fear-Uncertainty-on-No-Outlook/69845a40bf48f011a29be518</guid><description>Anthem Biosciences' Q3 FY26 performance took a sharp hit, with revenues down 15% YoY and 25.3% YoY drop in PAT. This marks a stark contrast to its strong nine-month growth. The company reported ₹4,232 Mn revenue and ₹928 Mn PAT for the quarter, impacted by a ₹254 Mn provision for new Labour Codes. Crucially, Anthem provided no forward-looking guidance, leaving investors uncertain about future prospects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Q3 Revenue Up 10%, Margins Squeeze Amid Cost Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Q3-Revenue-Up-10percent-Margins-Squeeze-Amid-Cost-Pressures/6984594bbf48f011a29be2ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Q3-Revenue-Up-10percent-Margins-Squeeze-Amid-Cost-Pressures/6984594bbf48f011a29be2ca</guid><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd. reported a 10% YoY rise in Q3 FY26 gross revenue to ₹2,608 Cr, fueled by a 7% increase in occupied bed days. Network operating EBITDA grew 4% to ₹648 Cr, but margins compressed 120 bps to 26.1% due to revised CGHS tariffs and drug pricing impacts. PAT climbed 9% to ₹344 Cr, aided by strong 9M FY26 performance showing 19% revenue growth and 30% PAT jump. The company plans a ~450-bed hospital in Pune and aims to double bed capacity in five years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:48:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984594bbf48f011a29be2c9_1770282138499.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godrej Properties Books Record Sales, Profit Jumps, Debt Doubles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-Books-Record-Sales-Profit-Jumps-Debt-Doubles/69845919bf48f011a29be1bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-Books-Record-Sales-Profit-Jumps-Debt-Doubles/69845919bf48f011a29be1bf</guid><description>Godrej Properties reported its strongest-ever calendar year 2025 with record bookings of ₹34,171 crore and robust PAT growth of 20%. Q3 FY26 saw a 55% YoY surge in booking value to ₹8,421 crore and improved EBITDA margins to 33.2%. Despite a 17% YoY dip in Q3 total income, net profit climbed 20%. However, net debt more than doubled to ₹6,873 crore, increasing the debt-to-equity ratio to 0.37x, though the company maintains strong credit ratings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:47:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845919bf48f011a29be1be_1770282018709.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent Q3 Surges: ICICI Securities Upgrades Target on Margin Gains, Retains 'Add'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Q3-Surges-ICICI-Securities-Upgrades-Target-on-Margin-Gains-Retains-Add/698458f4bf48f011a29be0b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Q3-Surges-ICICI-Securities-Upgrades-Target-on-Margin-Gains-Retains-Add/698458f4bf48f011a29be0b5</guid><description>Trent Ltd. reported a robust 16% year-on-year revenue growth in Q3 FY26. ICICI Securities maintained its 'Add' rating, citing strong margin expansion driven by operational efficiencies and product mix, despite heightened competition. The brokerage anticipates normalisation in like-for-like growth to mid-single digits, with improved profitability supporting earnings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:46:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698458f4bf48f011a29be0b4_1770281910207.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PVR INOX Q3: Standalone Profit Surges, Consolidated Declines; Sells Subsidiary</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVR-INOX-Q3-Standalone-Profit-Surges-Consolidated-Declines-Sells-Subsidiary/698458d2bf48f011a29be00b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVR-INOX-Q3-Standalone-Profit-Surges-Consolidated-Declines-Sells-Subsidiary/698458d2bf48f011a29be00b</guid><description>PVR INOX Limited reported divergent Q3 FY26 results. Standalone PAT surged 169% YoY to ₹950 million, boosted by an exceptional item. Conversely, consolidated PAT fell 28% YoY to ₹1,057 million, despite a 3% revenue increase. The company also completed the ₹2,268 million disposal of its subsidiary, Zea Maize Private Limited, post-reporting period. No forward-looking guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Marksans Pharma Posts Stellar Q3 Growth, But Consolidated EPS Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Marksans-Pharma-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Growth-But-Consolidated-EPS-Dips/69845882bf48f011a29bdec3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Marksans-Pharma-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Growth-But-Consolidated-EPS-Dips/69845882bf48f011a29bdec3</guid><description>Marksans Pharma reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with standalone revenue soaring 414% and PAT up 433% YoY. Consolidated revenue jumped 276%, with PAT surging 605%. However, a 7% year-to-date dip in consolidated EPS from ₹6.40 to ₹5.95, despite PAT growth, warrants investor scrutiny. The company also established subsidiaries in Europe and Canada. No forward-looking guidance was issued.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:44:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845882bf48f011a29bdec2_1770281777982.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PVR INOX Posts Standalone Loss, Consolidated Profit Dips Amidst Cost Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVR-INOX-Posts-Standalone-Loss-Consolidated-Profit-Dips-Amidst-Cost-Pressures/6984585dbf48f011a29bddf7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVR-INOX-Posts-Standalone-Loss-Consolidated-Profit-Dips-Amidst-Cost-Pressures/6984585dbf48f011a29bddf7</guid><description>PVR INOX Limited has reported a significant standalone net loss of ₹1,541 million for Q3 FY26, a stark contrast to a profit in the prior year, alongside a 6.4% drop in standalone revenue. Consolidated net profit also declined by 27.8% to ₹1,057 million, despite a 5.7% rise in consolidated revenue. The company cited exceptional costs related to new Labour Codes and faces liquidity challenges with low current ratios. Post-period, PVR INOX divested its stake in Zea Maize for ₹2,268 million.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:44:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984585dbf48f011a29bddf6_1770281599713.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Voltamp Transformers Posts 35% Surge in Q3 Net Profit on Strong Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Voltamp-Transformers-Posts-35percent-Surge-in-Q3-Net-Profit-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/69845802bf48f011a29bdc9a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Voltamp-Transformers-Posts-35percent-Surge-in-Q3-Net-Profit-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/69845802bf48f011a29bdc9a</guid><description>Voltamp Transformers Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26, with Net Profit soaring 34.98% year-on-year to ₹9,908.26 Lakhs (₹99.08 Cr equivalent). Revenue from operations surged 30.35% YoY to ₹630.32 Crore. Sequentially, revenue grew 30.63% and net profit climbed 25.65%. The nine-month period saw revenue rise 17.34% and net profit increase 12.64%. The company made an additional provision of ₹5.17 Crore for new Labour Codes, impacting expenses, while PBT margins saw a slight dip to 20.61% from 21.13% in the prior year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 08:42:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69845802bf48f011a29bdc99_1770281467751.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>