<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:30 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Boosts Startup Capital with ₹10,000 Cr Fund</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-Boosts-Startup-Capital-with-10000-Cr-Fund/69900dfe7e6478cdfc278b7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-Boosts-Startup-Capital-with-10000-Cr-Fund/69900dfe7e6478cdfc278b7f</guid><description>The Department for Promotion of Industry and Internal Trade (DPIIT) has allocated another ₹10,000 crore for its Fund of Funds for Startups (FFS 2.0). This significant capital commitment aims to bolster domestic funding pipelines, particularly for ventures in manufacturing and clean technologies, signaling a strategic shift as global venture capital flows become more discerning. The initiative builds upon the success of the original FFS launched in 2016, underscoring a sustained governmental focus on nurturing India's entrepreneurial ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:54:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69900dfe7e6478cdfc278b7e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Productivity Push: Can Execution Bridge Scale vs. Gains?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Productivity-Push-Can-Execution-Bridge-Scale-vs-Gains/69900d757e6478cdfc278b40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Productivity-Push-Can-Execution-Bridge-Scale-vs-Gains/69900d757e6478cdfc278b40</guid><description>India is pivoting from 'growth at scale' to 'productivity growth' for its 'Viksit Bharat @2047' vision, a strategy detailed by KPMG. The plan prioritizes manufacturing depth, MSME competitiveness, and human capital. However, translating capital investment into sustainable productivity gains faces significant challenges, including persistent regulatory complexities, a skills gap, and the need to scale smaller enterprises effectively. While global supply chain diversification offers opportunities, historical reform impacts on manufacturing productivity remain mixed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:51:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69900d757e6478cdfc278b3f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Natco Pharma Gains Generic Semaglutide Nod Amid Patent War</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Natco-Pharma-Gains-Generic-Semaglutide-Nod-Amid-Patent-War/699001577e6478cdfc27807f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Natco-Pharma-Gains-Generic-Semaglutide-Nod-Amid-Patent-War/699001577e6478cdfc27807f</guid><description>Hyderabad-based Natco Pharma has received approval from India's CDSCO to manufacture and market a generic semaglutide injection, with a planned launch in March 2026. This critical diabetes treatment's market entry, however, is shadowed by ongoing patent revocation suits filed by Natco Pharma and Dr. Reddy's Laboratories against originator Novo Nordisk's patent rights. The company's stock closed lower on Friday, reflecting investor caution regarding the legal battles.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:00:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699001577e6478cdfc27807e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerages Pick 10 Stocks for Upside Amidst Market Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerages-Pick-10-Stocks-for-Upside-Amidst-Market-Dip/698fff8e7e6478cdfc27801d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerages-Pick-10-Stocks-for-Upside-Amidst-Market-Dip/698fff8e7e6478cdfc27801d</guid><description>Amidst a market decline, leading brokerages have pinpointed ten Indian companies exhibiting resilience and growth potential. Firms like Motilal Oswal, Citi, Jefferies, Nuvama, and Axis Securities issued 'Buy' ratings, citing strong earnings, capacity expansions, and market share gains. Hindalco Industries, Eicher Motors, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, Apollo Hospitals, Kotak Mahindra Bank, State Bank of India, and others are highlighted for their distinct operational strengths and favorable outlooks, suggesting selective opportunities amidst broader economic headwinds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:52:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698fff8e7e6478cdfc27801c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kotak Takes Helm at GIFT City, Aiming to Rival Global Hubs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kotak-Takes-Helm-at-GIFT-City-Aiming-to-Rival-Global-Hubs/698ff6187e6478cdfc2775a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kotak-Takes-Helm-at-GIFT-City-Aiming-to-Rival-Global-Hubs/698ff6187e6478cdfc2775a5</guid><description>Veteran banker Uday Kotak has been appointed Chairman of GIFT City, marking a significant strategic move to bolster India's financial hub. With his proven track record of building financial institutions, Kotak is expected to accelerate GIFT City's global ambitions, leveraging its cost advantages and government incentives to compete with mature markets like Singapore and Dubai. This appointment underscores India's commitment to positioning GIFT City as a premier international financial services center.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:12:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ff6187e6478cdfc2775a4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tax Shift: Growth Engine or Fiscal Risk?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Shift-Growth-Engine-or-Fiscal-Risk/698fe9ce7e6478cdfc276aaf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Shift-Growth-Engine-or-Fiscal-Risk/698fe9ce7e6478cdfc276aaf</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 accelerates a structural shift from indirect to direct taxes, driven by manufacturing growth and record capital expenditure. While positioning the nation as a global investment hub, this strategy faces scrutiny over the sustainability of direct tax reliance amid global economic uncertainties and potentially stretched market valuations. The report examines the underlying risks and comparative advantages against emerging market peers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:19:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698fe9ce7e6478cdfc276aae.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hybrid Funds: Beyond CAGR, A Critical Metrics Deep Dive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Hybrid-Funds-Beyond-CAGR-A-Critical-Metrics-Deep-Dive/698fe8807e6478cdfc276a4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Hybrid-Funds-Beyond-CAGR-A-Critical-Metrics-Deep-Dive/698fe8807e6478cdfc276a4f</guid><description>While aggressive hybrid funds showcase strong long-term CAGRs, investors must scrutinize metrics beyond headline returns. Factors like expense ratios, risk-adjusted performance via Sharpe ratios, and portfolio turnover reveal significant differences, dictating suitability for varied risk profiles. The current volatile market environment further emphasizes the need for a nuanced approach, favoring funds that balance growth with resilience.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698fe8807e6478cdfc276a4e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Mineral Security: Recycling Unlocks Critical Supply Chains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Mineral-Security-Recycling-Unlocks-Critical-Supply-Chains/698fe2e07e6478cdfc276968</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Mineral-Security-Recycling-Unlocks-Critical-Supply-Chains/698fe2e07e6478cdfc276968</guid><description>India faces systemic critical mineral insecurity, more complex than past oil crises. While a National Critical Minerals Mission and overseas asset acquisition are underway, the nation's vast, informal recycling sector offers a rapid, cost-effective route to resilience, functioning as an efficient 'secondary mine.' This approach leverages domestic labor, bypasses geopolitical mining risks, and complements primary exploration and import strategies, providing a critical advantage against China's dominance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:50:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698fe2e07e6478cdfc276967.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axis Bets Big on IT Amidst AI Sell-off: Four Stocks Eye Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Axis-Bets-Big-on-IT-Amidst-AI-Sell-off-Four-Stocks-Eye-Gains/698fe0fe7e6478cdfc2768f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Axis-Bets-Big-on-IT-Amidst-AI-Sell-off-Four-Stocks-Eye-Gains/698fe0fe7e6478cdfc2768f4</guid><description>Axis Securities has identified HCL Technologies, Tech Mahindra, Persistent Systems, and Coforge as top IT conviction plays, targeting significant upside potential. This bullish stance emerges following a sharp sector-wide sell-off, attributed to AI disruption fears and global economic uncertainties. While AI is seen as a key growth driver, particularly in BFSI and healthcare, investor focus is shifting towards adaptation and sustainable earnings in a high-interest-rate environment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:42:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698fe0fe7e6478cdfc2768f3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Eases Rules, Unlocking Gold Loan NBFC Growth Potential</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Eases-Rules-Unlocking-Gold-Loan-NBFC-Growth-Potential/698fdbd37e6478cdfc27453f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Eases-Rules-Unlocking-Gold-Loan-NBFC-Growth-Potential/698fdbd37e6478cdfc27453f</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is implementing precise regulatory changes, exempting smaller NBFCs from registration and removing prior approval for gold loan NBFC branch expansion. These moves aim to focus supervision on systemic risks and boost credit distribution efficiency, particularly benefiting gold loan financiers like Muthoot Finance and Manappuram Finance. With strong economic growth forecasts and a shift toward secured lending, the gold loan sector is poised for significant expansion, though competition from banks remains a factor.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:20:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698fdbd37e6478cdfc27453e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Finance Reckoning: Productivity Hype Meets Valuation Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AIs-Finance-Reckoning-Productivity-Hype-Meets-Valuation-Jitters/698fdb4d7e6478cdfc274501</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AIs-Finance-Reckoning-Productivity-Hype-Meets-Valuation-Jitters/698fdb4d7e6478cdfc274501</guid><description>Artificial intelligence is a dual-edged sword in financial services. While firms report significant productivity gains and CEOs are optimistic about AI's ROI, the true impact hinges on AI's real-world productivity and integration challenges. This uncertainty, coupled with substantial implementation costs and evolving regulatory landscapes, is causing market volatility and a strategic re-evaluation of sector valuations. The future likely favors firms adept at leveraging AI for efficiency and innovation while navigating these complexities.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:17:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698fdb4d7e6478cdfc274500.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Green Hydrogen Ambition: Hype vs. Execution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Hydrogen-Ambition-Hype-vs-Execution/698fda6f7e6478cdfc2744cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Hydrogen-Ambition-Hype-vs-Execution/698fda6f7e6478cdfc2744cd</guid><description>India's National Green Hydrogen Mission targets 5 million metric tonnes by 2030, backed by over ₹8 lakh crore in projected investments. This national push aims to reduce import dependence and foster domestic capacity in electrolyser manufacturing, creating opportunities across infrastructure, power, refining, and fertilizer sectors. While capital commitments are rising and pilot projects are commencing, the sector remains nascent. Investors face a landscape where core businesses still drive current earnings, and long-term green hydrogen economics hinge on future cost competitiveness and large-scale execution. Companies like L&amp;T, NTPC, JSW Energy, IOC, and GSFC represent diverse entry points into this evolving ecosystem, but significant hurdles persist before hydrogen becomes a primary profit center.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:14:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698fda6f7e6478cdfc2744cc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Honasa Consumer Recovers on Strong Q3, But Valuation Concerns Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Honasa-Consumer-Recovers-on-Strong-Q3-But-Valuation-Concerns-Linger/698fc8287e6478cdfc274271</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Honasa-Consumer-Recovers-on-Strong-Q3-But-Valuation-Concerns-Linger/698fc8287e6478cdfc274271</guid><description>Honasa Consumer, parent of Mamaearth, reported its highest-ever quarterly revenue of ₹601.5 crore and a 93% surge in net profit to ₹50.2 crore for Q3 FY26. This turnaround follows significant operational challenges including a ₹65 crore inventory write-off and negative margins in Q2 FY25 due to a costly distribution restructuring. While recent performance has boosted investor sentiment, the stock remains below its IPO price, and its elevated P/E ratio of approximately 75x TTM highlights persistent valuation concerns amid intense market competition.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:56:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698fc8287e6478cdfc274270.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>