<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Indian Tea Woes: Cost Squeeze Fuels Sector Bifurcation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indian-Tea-Woes-Cost-Squeeze-Fuels-Sector-Bifurcation/6991df362e6a0b8ae17c42fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indian-Tea-Woes-Cost-Squeeze-Fuels-Sector-Bifurcation/6991df362e6a0b8ae17c42fa</guid><description>India's tea sector is under mounting financial pressure as escalating wages, input costs, and labor shortages force estates to sell below cost. Climate variability further erodes yields and quality. While calls for policy reform and support intensify, the industry faces a bifurcated future, with high-quality specialty teas showing resilience against the commoditized segment's struggles.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:59:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991df362e6a0b8ae17c42f9_1771167684224.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mold-Tek Packaging Eyes ₹1000 Cr Revenue; Pharma &amp; Food Drive Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mold-Tek-Packaging-Eyes-1000-Cr-Revenue-Pharma-and-Food-Drive-Growth/6991debf2e6a0b8ae17c42aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mold-Tek-Packaging-Eyes-1000-Cr-Revenue-Pharma-and-Food-Drive-Growth/6991debf2e6a0b8ae17c42aa</guid><description>Mold-Tek Packaging reported a strong Q3 FY26 with sales volumes up 6% and EBITDA growing 14% year-on-year. For the nine months, sales rose 12% and EBITDA jumped 20%. The company is strategically expanding into the Pharma and Food &amp; FMCG segments, targeting over ₹1,000 Crores in revenue by FY27 with improved EBITDA margins. Despite a dip in lubricant volumes, operational efficiencies and new partnerships are key growth drivers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:57:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991debf2e6a0b8ae17c42a9_1771167563645.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Co-op Banks Balk at RBI License: Autonomy Fears Trump Bank Status</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Co-op-Banks-Balk-at-RBI-License-Autonomy-Fears-Trump-Bank-Status/6991dc8e878851adec4d71c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Co-op-Banks-Balk-at-RBI-License-Autonomy-Fears-Trump-Bank-Status/6991dc8e878851adec4d71c4</guid><description>Large urban co-operative credit societies are poised to decline Reserve Bank of India (RBI) licenses for conversion into urban co-operative banks. Societies fear the stringent, dual regulatory oversight from the RBI, in addition to existing state registrars, will impose prohibitive costs and operational complexities. This reluctance stems from a desire to preserve their distinct community-centric governance and localized trust, which they believe would be compromised under formal banking regulations. Recent RBI reforms aimed at strengthening co-operative banks might not be enough to offset these deep-seated concerns about losing operational autonomy.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:47:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991dc8e878851adec4d71c3_1771166954417.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bain Capital Navigates RBI Hurdles for Manappuram Finance Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bain-Capital-Navigates-RBI-Hurdles-for-Manappuram-Finance-Stake/6991dbf6878851adec4d7134</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bain-Capital-Navigates-RBI-Hurdles-for-Manappuram-Finance-Stake/6991dbf6878851adec4d7134</guid><description>Bain Capital's significant investment in Manappuram Finance is proceeding under a conditional approval from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI). The approval mandates Bain to divest its majority stake in Tyger Capital, another NBFC it controls, to comply with regulations against controlling multiple entities in the same financial category. This strategic move signals Bain's focus on Manappuram's strong market position in gold loans and its potential for growth, despite the cost of regulatory compliance and divestment. Analysts see Manappuram as a more attractive proposition compared to Tyger, reflecting a calculated trade-off for capital infusion and market access in India's expanding NBFC sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:45:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991dbf6878851adec4d7133_1771166867740.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CarTrade Tech Leaps Ahead with AI, Posts Record Revenue and Strong Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CarTrade-Tech-Leaps-Ahead-with-AI-Posts-Record-Revenue-and-Strong-Margins/6991db77878851adec4d70c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CarTrade-Tech-Leaps-Ahead-with-AI-Posts-Record-Revenue-and-Strong-Margins/6991db77878851adec4d70c7</guid><description>CarTrade Tech is making a big stride with its new Multi-Agent AI Ecosystem, aimed at revolutionizing customer experience and boosting profits on platforms like CarWale and BikeWale. This follows a stellar Q3 FY26 where the company hit record revenue of ₹228 crore and achieved an impressive 37% EBITDA margin, a significant jump from single digits historically. The AI initiative will deploy specialized agents across its brands to manage transactions, connect buyers and sellers, and simplify vehicle discovery and purchasing, promising to boost transaction speed and customer satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:43:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991db77878851adec4d70c6_1771166723510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BEL Seals French Defence JV for HAMMER Missile Kits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/BEL-Seals-French-Defence-JV-for-HAMMER-Missile-Kits/6991d99d878851adec4d7007</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/BEL-Seals-French-Defence-JV-for-HAMMER-Missile-Kits/6991d99d878851adec4d7007</guid><description>Bharat Electronics Limited (BEL) has received board approval to sign a Joint Venture Agreement (JVA) with France's Safran Electronics and Defence (SED). The JV will establish a 'Center of Excellence' for the manufacturing, supply, maintenance, and repair of Guidance Kits for the HAMMER Weapon System, primarily for the Indian Air Force and Navy. This move is a significant step in India's defence indigenization efforts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:35:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991d99d878851adec4d7006_1771166218551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IPO Surge: 6 Companies Debut Amidst Muted Grey Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Surge-6-Companies-Debut-Amidst-Muted-Grey-Market/6991d70b878851adec4d6f34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Surge-6-Companies-Debut-Amidst-Muted-Grey-Market/6991d70b878851adec4d6f34</guid><description>The Indian primary market is poised for an active week starting February 16, featuring three IPO openings and three new listings, including Gaudium IVF, Fractal Industries, Yashhtej Industries, Marushika Technology, Fractal Analytics, and Aye Finance. Despite a robust pipeline, key mainboard debutants Fractal Analytics and Aye Finance are seeing no premium in the grey market, indicating investor caution amidst AI disruption fears and geopolitical tensions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:24:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991d70b878851adec4d6f33_1771165583101.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Health Push: Scaling Challenges Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Health-Push-Scaling-Challenges-Emerge/6991d583878851adec4d6dd7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Health-Push-Scaling-Challenges-Emerge/6991d583878851adec4d6dd7</guid><description>India is aggressively digitizing rural healthcare with AI, backed by significant government investment and initiatives like Ayushman Bharat. While AI-driven diagnostics and telemedicine are expanding access, the sector's true potential hinges on overcoming challenges in scalability, digital literacy, and fostering deeper private sector involvement to ensure equitable and sustainable healthcare outcomes for its vast rural population.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:17:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991d583878851adec4d6dd6_1771165197859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Record Power Growth: Grid Stability Faces Test Amidst Green Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Record-Power-Growth-Grid-Stability-Faces-Test-Amidst-Green-Surge/6991d566878851adec4d6d9f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Record-Power-Growth-Grid-Stability-Faces-Test-Amidst-Green-Surge/6991d566878851adec4d6d9f</guid><description>India has set an unprecedented record by adding over 52 GW of power generation capacity in the first ten months of FY26, pushing its non-fossil fuel share past 50% ahead of schedule. While this surge, primarily driven by renewables like solar and wind, signifies a monumental stride in its energy transition, it simultaneously magnifies existing vulnerabilities in grid stability and necessitates substantial investment in storage and infrastructure upgrades to manage intermittency and ensure reliable power delivery. The rapid expansion, though record-breaking, highlights an ongoing tension between capacity targets and the practicalities of grid management, demanding a critical reassessment of integration strategies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:17:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991d566878851adec4d6d9e_1771165221627.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Oil Pivot: Strategic Realignment or Costly Gamble?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Oil-Pivot-Strategic-Realignment-or-Costly-Gamble/6991d554878851adec4d6d61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Oil-Pivot-Strategic-Realignment-or-Costly-Gamble/6991d554878851adec4d6d61</guid><description>India's directive to shift from Russian crude oil imports to US and Venezuelan sources signals a strategic geopolitical pivot but introduces considerable economic friction. Moody's Analytics highlights that this transition will inevitably drive up domestic energy prices and strain India's fiscal balance due to extensive fuel subsidies. Refineries face higher processing costs adapting to different crude grades, while the lack of detailed trade agreement terms introduces uncertainty. The move reflects a broader effort to diversify energy sources, though immediate full replacement of Russian supplies is deemed infeasible in the near term.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:16:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6991d554878851adec4d6d60.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Revenue Surges 30%, Settles US Patent Case</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Zydus-Lifesciences-Revenue-Surges-30percent-Settles-US-Patent-Case/6991cfc3878851adec4d6bed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Zydus-Lifesciences-Revenue-Surges-30percent-Settles-US-Patent-Case/6991cfc3878851adec4d6bed</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences posted a strong Q3 FY26, with revenue jumping 30% year-on-year to ₹68.6 billion and EBITDA up 31%. This growth was fueled by significant contributions from recent acquisitions like Amplitude Surgical and Comfort Click, alongside robust performance in its US, India, and international markets. The company also announced a $120 million settlement in its US patent litigation concerning generic Mirabegron, securing continued market access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:53:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991cfc3878851adec4d6bec_1771163723235.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Bets on Proprietary AI World Models</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Mahindra-Bets-on-Proprietary-AI-World-Models/6991c6a40caf1c998745df98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Mahindra-Bets-on-Proprietary-AI-World-Models/6991c6a40caf1c998745df98</guid><description>Tech Mahindra is investing in proprietary AI "world models" designed for complex, contextual simulations in sectors like telecom and healthcare. This initiative anticipates future client demand for highly tailored AI, differentiating the company in the evolving agentic AI landscape. This strategic R&amp;D aims to secure a competitive edge amid industry-wide challenges, including talent deficits and the broader Indian IT sector's navigation of macroeconomic pressures and policy recommendations for AI sovereignty.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:14:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991c6a40caf1c998745df97_1771161390248.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Signature Global Expands with ₹12,500 Cr Projects Amidst Sales Target Revision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-Expands-with-12500-Cr-Projects-Amidst-Sales-Target-Revision/6991c0fb0caf1c998745de1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-Expands-with-12500-Cr-Projects-Amidst-Sales-Target-Revision/6991c0fb0caf1c998745de1e</guid><description>Signature Global is set to launch a branded luxury housing project in Gurugram with an estimated ₹5,000 crore revenue potential and a significant mixed-use commercial development through a ₹7,500 crore joint venture with RMZ Group. This aggressive expansion comes as the company revises its fiscal year sales booking target downwards to ₹10,300 crore, citing a softening housing demand in Gurugram. Construction activities have accelerated, anticipating increased revenue recognition in the current quarter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:50:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991c0fb0caf1c998745de1d_1771159964184.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Embassy REIT's Expansion: Growth Hype Meets Valuation Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-REITs-Expansion-Growth-Hype-Meets-Valuation-Headwinds/6991bfd10caf1c998745dd67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-REITs-Expansion-Growth-Hype-Meets-Valuation-Headwinds/6991bfd10caf1c998745dd67</guid><description>Embassy Office Parks REIT is leveraging a booming Indian office market, characterized by rising rents and tight vacancies, to fund a substantial 7.6 million sq ft expansion pipeline. The REIT reported a 17% YoY revenue increase to ₹1,193 crore and 19% NOI growth to ₹985 crore. However, questions linger regarding its premium valuation, lower occupancy compared to retail peers, and the performance of specific assets, even as analyst sentiment remains cautiously optimistic.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:45:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991bfd10caf1c998745dd66_1771159642196.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-UK Trade Pact Ratification Awaits Parliament; Tariff Cuts Spark Sector Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-UK-Trade-Pact-Ratification-Awaits-Parliament-Tariff-Cuts-Spark-Sector-Debate/6991bb570caf1c998745dbe9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-UK-Trade-Pact-Ratification-Awaits-Parliament-Tariff-Cuts-Spark-Sector-Debate/6991bb570caf1c998745dbe9</guid><description>The India-UK Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement (CETA), signed in July 2025, is targeting an April 2026 rollout, contingent on UK parliamentary ratification. This pact aims to boost bilateral trade beyond the current estimated $56 billion by 2030, offering Indian exporters 99% duty-free access to the UK while phasing down tariffs on key British goods like Scotch whisky and automobiles. A parallel Double Contributions Convention is also set for implementation. Debates in the UK's House of Commons and House of Lords are underway, representing the critical next phase. Chris Bryant, Minister of State, described the agreement as a "momentous achievement."</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:25:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991bb570caf1c998745dbe8_1771158469809.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manappuram Finance: RBI Nod Comes With Regulatory Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-RBI-Nod-Comes-With-Regulatory-Scrutiny/6991bb280caf1c998745dbd2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-RBI-Nod-Comes-With-Regulatory-Scrutiny/6991bb280caf1c998745dbd2</guid><description>Manappuram Finance shares are under observation following the Reserve Bank of India's conditional approval for Bain Capital affiliates to acquire up to 41.66% stake. This marks the transition to a joint promoter structure, with significant regulatory conditions requiring ongoing compliance and strategic planning. Despite the milestone, the stock saw a slight dip, reflecting investor caution regarding the intricate oversight and future operational adjustments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:25:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991bb280caf1c998745dbd1_1771158476851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Centum Electronics Exits Loss-Making Units, Bets Big on India's Defence &amp; Space Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Centum-Electronics-Exits-Loss-Making-Units-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Defence-and-Space-Boom/6991b3260caf1c998745da3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Centum-Electronics-Exits-Loss-Making-Units-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Defence-and-Space-Boom/6991b3260caf1c998745da3d</guid><description>Centum Electronics Limited is undergoing a significant strategic overhaul, exiting its loss-making operations in Canada and initiating restructuring for its French subsidiaries. This move, which includes recognizing substantial impairment charges, aims to sharpen the company's focus on the booming high-reliability Electronics System Design and Manufacturing (ESDM) sector in India, particularly in defence, space, and aerospace. The company expects these actions to strengthen its financial foundation and drive value-accretive growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:51:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991b3260caf1c998745da3c_1771161835526.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Startup Shift: Profitability &amp; Deep Tech Drive New Growth Phase</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Shift-Profitability-and-Deep-Tech-Drive-New-Growth-Phase/6991ac9b0caf1c998745d8a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Shift-Profitability-and-Deep-Tech-Drive-New-Growth-Phase/6991ac9b0caf1c998745d8a3</guid><description>India's startup ecosystem, now the world's third largest, is undergoing a significant evolution. While boasting over 2 lakh recognized startups and approximately 125 unicorns by early 2026, the focus is shifting from sheer scale to sustainable profitability and value creation. New government initiatives like the ₹10,000 crore Startup India Fund of Funds 2.0 aim to bridge capital gaps, particularly for deep tech and companies in emerging regions, signalling a more disciplined investment approach driven by fundamentals, ethical practices, and global competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:23:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991ac9b0caf1c998745d8a2_1771154718106.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fears Trigger IT Sector Sell-off, Indian Markets Face Valuation Reset</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Fears-Trigger-IT-Sector-Sell-off-Indian-Markets-Face-Valuation-Reset/6991aa4b0caf1c998745d774</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Fears-Trigger-IT-Sector-Sell-off-Indian-Markets-Face-Valuation-Reset/6991aa4b0caf1c998745d774</guid><description>Indian equity markets faced sharp volatility, primarily driven by a steep sell-off in technology stocks on rising concerns over artificial intelligence-led disruption. The Nifty IT index plunged over 8% for the week, erasing significant market value. Foreign institutional investors (FIIs) turned net sellers, offloading ₹7,395 crore on February 13 alone, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) provided crucial support. Analysts warn of structural headwinds and potential long-term impacts on the IT sector's traditional outsourcing model, advocating for a selective investment approach.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:13:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991aa4b0caf1c998745d773_1771154141987.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India AI Expo Signals Strategic Pivot to Global Platform Leadership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-AI-Expo-Signals-Strategic-Pivot-to-Global-Platform-Leadership/6991aa420caf1c998745d75d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-AI-Expo-Signals-Strategic-Pivot-to-Global-Platform-Leadership/6991aa420caf1c998745d75d</guid><description>Prime Minister Modi inaugurated the India AI Impact Expo 2026, underscoring India's ambition to transition from a technology services provider to a global leader in developing and exporting AI platforms. The event showcases over 300 pavilions and 600 startups, emphasizing production-grade AI solutions across critical sectors. This strategic pivot aims to leverage India's growing AI ecosystem, address national challenges, and reshape its position in the global technology landscape, moving beyond its traditional role in the IT sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:13:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991aa420caf1c998745d75c_1771154143166.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fears Spark IT Selloff; Indian Market Faces Crucial Levels</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fears-Spark-IT-Selloff-Indian-Market-Faces-Crucial-Levels/6991a96d0caf1c998745d668</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fears-Spark-IT-Selloff-Indian-Market-Faces-Crucial-Levels/6991a96d0caf1c998745d668</guid><description>Indian equity markets, led by the Sensex and Nifty, experienced a significant downturn, exceeding 1% losses for the week. The primary driver was a sharp selloff in the Information Technology (IT) sector, fueled by escalating concerns over artificial intelligence (AI) disrupting traditional business models. Foreign institutional investors (FIIs) maintained their selling stance, exacerbating downward pressure. Macroeconomic factors, including anticipated US Federal Reserve policy shifts and persistent geopolitical tensions, further clouded the market outlook. Despite the broader weakness, some IT stocks like Infosys and Wipro saw intraday rebounds from lower levels.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:09:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991a96d0caf1c998745d667_1771153897337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Focuses on Energy Security, Growth Inputs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Focuses-on-Energy-Security-Growth-Inputs/6991a9550caf1c998745d651</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Focuses-on-Energy-Security-Growth-Inputs/6991a9550caf1c998745d651</guid><description>India and the United States have finalized an interim trade agreement, setting a $500 billion bilateral trade target by 2030. The pact strategically addresses India's rising energy needs, aiming to secure crude oil and other vital resources at competitive prices through diversified sourcing. It also targets growth in sectors like steel, by facilitating coking coal imports, and the IT industry, through access to advanced U.S. technology. Tariff reductions on various goods are designed to invigorate trade flows.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:09:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991a9550caf1c998745d650_1771153929734.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fineotex Revenue Surges 46%, But Margins Squeeze Amid US Buyout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fineotex-Revenue-Surges-46percent-But-Margins-Squeeze-Amid-US-Buyout/6991a67e0caf1c998745d590</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fineotex-Revenue-Surges-46percent-But-Margins-Squeeze-Amid-US-Buyout/6991a67e0caf1c998745d590</guid><description>Fineotex Chemical Limited reported a robust 45.90% year-on-year revenue growth in Q3 FY26, reaching ₹183.71 Cr. However, its profit margins faced significant pressure, with EBITDA margins declining to 18.96% from 27.23% YoY. The company also completed a strategic acquisition of US-based CrudeChem Technologies, aiming for global expansion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 10:57:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991a67e0caf1c998745d58f_1771161924570.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Navigate AI Fears Amid FPI Rebound and Sector Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Navigate-AI-Fears-Amid-FPI-Rebound-and-Sector-Strength/69919b7c0caf1c998745d32f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Navigate-AI-Fears-Amid-FPI-Rebound-and-Sector-Strength/69919b7c0caf1c998745d32f</guid><description>Indian equity markets are grappling with global economic uncertainties and the profound impact of AI-driven disruptions, particularly on the IT sector. However, a significant rebound in foreign portfolio investor (FPI) inflows in early February, fueled by a new US-India trade agreement, is providing a counter-balance. Analysts point to strong fundamentals in domestically oriented sectors like banking, autos, and consumption, suggesting a potential leadership rotation despite broader market caution. Upcoming economic data and US Federal Reserve policy signals will remain key watchpoints.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69919b7c0caf1c998745d32e_1771150379781.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Religare Enterprises Plans Demerger Amid Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Enterprises-Plans-Demerger-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/699195270caf1c998745d0e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Enterprises-Plans-Demerger-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/699195270caf1c998745d0e0</guid><description>Religare Enterprises (REL) will separate its financial services and insurance businesses into two distinct, listed companies, a strategy initiated post-Burman family takeover in early 2025. The insurance arm, Care Health Insurance, will remain with REL, while the financial services division will be housed under Religare Finvest Ltd. (RFL). RFL is slated for listing on BSE and NSE by Q1 FY28, featuring a 1:1 mirror shareholding. This complex restructuring aims to sharpen strategic focus and streamline operations, though historical demerger outcomes are mixed and Religare faces internal financial and valuation questions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:43:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699195270caf1c998745d0df_1771148737867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bath &amp; Body Works India Pivot: Localization Over Replication</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bath-and-Body-Works-India-Pivot-Localization-Over-Replication/699195060caf1c998745d059</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bath-and-Body-Works-India-Pivot-Localization-Over-Replication/699195060caf1c998745d059</guid><description>Bath &amp; Body Works (BBWI) is undergoing a significant strategic shift in India, prioritizing deep localization over its established US model to capture a massive consumer market. The company plans to introduce ~500 sq ft neighborhood stores, targeting Tier 2 and 3 cities, alongside an aggressive multi-channel digital strategy. This move aims to accelerate growth from doubling the business every five years to potentially every three years. While facing intense competition from players like Nykaa and Myntra, BBWI sees India as a critical global growth engine, with over 50% of its India revenue already coming from online channels.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:42:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699195060caf1c998745d058_1771148676481.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FPI Inflows Surge, But IT Sector Weakness Clouds Indian Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FPI-Inflows-Surge-But-IT-Sector-Weakness-Clouds-Indian-Market/699194bb0caf1c998745cff8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FPI-Inflows-Surge-But-IT-Sector-Weakness-Clouds-Indian-Market/699194bb0caf1c998745cff8</guid><description>Foreign Portfolio Investors (FPIs) injected ₹19,675 crore into Indian equities in the first half of February 2026, reversing months of significant outflows. This surge follows a US-India trade deal and easing global economic concerns. However, a severe sell-off in the Information Technology (IT) sector, triggered by advancements in AI, has introduced a sharp divergence, casting a shadow over the broader market's positive momentum. The Nifty IT index plummeted 8.2% in the week ending February 13, 2026, highlighting significant sector-specific headwinds.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:41:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699194bb0caf1c998745cff7_1771148677309.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nippon India Mid Cap Fund: 30-Year Legend Faces Modern Market Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Nippon-India-Mid-Cap-Fund-30-Year-Legend-Faces-Modern-Market-Test/699194b60caf1c998745cfe1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Nippon-India-Mid-Cap-Fund-30-Year-Legend-Faces-Modern-Market-Test/699194b60caf1c998745cfe1</guid><description>The Nippon India Growth Mid Cap Fund, a 30-year industry veteran, has delivered exceptional returns, transforming a ₹10,000 monthly SIP into ₹26 crore and a ₹1 lakh lump sum into ₹4 crore. Despite its stellar historical performance and high-risk adjusted metrics, the fund's significant Assets Under Management (AUM) of ₹41,727 crore and a notable expense ratio of 1.54% warrant close examination against current market conditions and peer performance.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:41:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699194b60caf1c998745cfe0_1771148615520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NALCO-NLCIL Pact: India PSU Banks on Coal for Power Security Amid Green Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NALCO-NLCIL-Pact-India-PSU-Banks-on-Coal-for-Power-Security-Amid-Green-Push/699194b30caf1c998745cfca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NALCO-NLCIL-Pact-India-PSU-Banks-on-Coal-for-Power-Security-Amid-Green-Push/699194b30caf1c998745cfca</guid><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NALCO) has formalized a strategic alliance with NLC India Ltd (NLCIL) via a recent Memorandum of Understanding. This pact centers on developing a 1080-MW thermal captive power project and exploring renewable energy avenues to secure NALCO's long-term energy needs. The collaboration aims to establish a structured framework for power and coal supply, reinforcing NALCO's operational cost stability. This move positions NALCO to leverage established thermal capacity while navigating the industry's accelerating transition towards sustainable energy solutions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:41:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699194b30caf1c998745cfc9_1771148670340.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lodha Developers Buys 80% of Solidrise Realty for ₹294 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Lodha-Developers-Buys-80percent-of-Solidrise-Realty-for-294-Cr/699194af0caf1c998745cfb3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Lodha-Developers-Buys-80percent-of-Solidrise-Realty-for-294-Cr/699194af0caf1c998745cfb3</guid><description>Lodha Developers Ltd. has acquired an 80% stake in Pune-based Solidrise Realty Pvt Ltd (SRPL) for ₹294.07 crore, marking a strategic expansion in the Pune market. This move follows a robust third quarter for Lodha, which reported a consolidated net profit of ₹956.9 crore. The acquisition complements the company's aggressive expansion into new land parcels, aimed at developing projects with an estimated sales value of ₹34,000 crore.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:41:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699194af0caf1c998745cfb2_1771148619404.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Tightens NSOP, Airfield Oversight After Fatal LearJet Crash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Tightens-NSOP-Airfield-Oversight-After-Fatal-LearJet-Crash/699189760caf1c998745ccf0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Tightens-NSOP-Airfield-Oversight-After-Fatal-LearJet-Crash/699189760caf1c998745ccf0</guid><description>Following the fatal January 28 crash of a VSR Ventures LearJet 45 carrying Maharashtra Deputy Chief Minister Ajit Pawar, India's Ministry of Civil Aviation is conducting a comprehensive study of non-scheduled flight operators (NSOPs) and uncontrolled airfields. The Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA) has initiated a special safety audit of major NSOPs and is reviewing over 400 uncontrolled airstrips to implement uniform safety standards. This intensified focus occurs against a backdrop of rapid growth in India's aviation sector, particularly in private aviation, and ongoing concerns over market concentration and systemic risks in commercial air travel.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:53:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699189760caf1c998745ccef_1771145714058.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maharashtra's $1 Trillion Ambition: Growth Drivers Clash with Pace Demands</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Maharashtras-1-Trillion-Ambition-Growth-Drivers-Clash-with-Pace-Demands/699188810caf1c998745cbf6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Maharashtras-1-Trillion-Ambition-Growth-Drivers-Clash-with-Pace-Demands/699188810caf1c998745cbf6</guid><description>Maharashtra aims to become a $1 trillion economy, bolstered by significant foreign direct investment (FDI) and extensive infrastructure development. The state is projected to reach a nominal GSDP near $578 billion in FY26, attracting a substantial portion of India's foreign capital. However, achieving the $1 trillion milestone by 2030 necessitates an unprecedented annual growth rate, potentially requiring 15-17%, a pace significantly higher than current economic expansion. This report analyzes the state's growth engines alongside critical headwinds that could impede its rapid economic ascent.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699188810caf1c998745cbf5_1771145541688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Giants Wilt as Select Banks, Industrials Shine in Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tech-Giants-Wilt-as-Select-Banks-Industrials-Shine-in-Market-Downturn/699188510caf1c998745cbca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tech-Giants-Wilt-as-Select-Banks-Industrials-Shine-in-Market-Downturn/699188510caf1c998745cbca</guid><description>A broad market sell-off last week erased over ₹3 lakh crore from the market capitalizations of India's top listed firms. Technology behemoths Tata Consultancy Services and Infosys were the primary casualties, alongside major lenders and telecom operators. In contrast, State Bank of India, Bajaj Finance, Larsen &amp; Toubro, and ICICI Bank demonstrated resilience, posting valuation gains. This divergence highlights a potential investor rotation amid prevailing market caution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:48:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699188510caf1c998745cbc9_1771145435047.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Religare Demerges: Burman Play Faces Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Demerges-Burman-Play-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/699181780caf1c998745ca40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Demerges-Burman-Play-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/699181780caf1c998745ca40</guid><description>Religare Enterprises' board approved a plan to split its financial services and insurance businesses into two listed entities, aiming to unlock shareholder value and sharpen focus. This move, spearheaded by the Burman family following their takeover in February 2025, will see Religare Finvest (RFL) spun off for financial services, while the company retains Care Health Insurance. Despite management optimism, the demerger faces complex regulatory approvals, potential execution challenges, and questions surrounding its high valuation relative to current earnings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:19:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699181780caf1c998745ca3f_1771143679299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Talent Surge Meets Patent Paradox</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Talent-Surge-Meets-Patent-Paradox/699175750caf1c998745c7c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Talent-Surge-Meets-Patent-Paradox/699175750caf1c998745c7c6</guid><description>India's artificial intelligence sector is surging, driven by exceptional talent penetration and high executive optimism, with BCGX projecting a doubling of the AI talent pool by 2027. However, a stark paradox emerges: despite a large volume of AI patent applications, India's grant ratio remains critically low, hindering true 'sovereign by design' capabilities. This, coupled with a significant workforce skills gap, presents a complex dynamic for the nation's AI-driven economic growth, particularly impacting the potential unlocked for MSMEs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 07:27:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699175750caf1c998745c7c5_1771140583142.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CNH Bets Big on India: Rs 1,800 Cr Boosts Global Strategy Amid US Trade Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CNH-Bets-Big-on-India-Rs-1800-Cr-Boosts-Global-Strategy-Amid-US-Trade-Shift/6991738f0caf1c998745c6df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CNH-Bets-Big-on-India-Rs-1800-Cr-Boosts-Global-Strategy-Amid-US-Trade-Shift/6991738f0caf1c998745c6df</guid><description>CNH India plans a substantial ₹1,800 crore investment over two to three years, focusing on a new greenfield tractor plant to double production capacity to 120,000 units annually. This move capitalizes on a recent India-US trade pact reducing tariffs to 18%, enabling a resumption of full-scale tractor exports to the US. The 'India for Global' strategy positions the country as a key manufacturing hub amid a broader agricultural equipment market growth projection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 07:19:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991738f0caf1c998745c6de_1771140111013.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Charts AI's Future Amidst Global Power Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Charts-AIs-Future-Amidst-Global-Power-Shifts/69916b3a0caf1c998745c4b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Charts-AIs-Future-Amidst-Global-Power-Shifts/69916b3a0caf1c998745c4b3</guid><description>UN Secretary-General António Guterres has endorsed India as the ideal host for the AI Impact Summit 2026, stressing artificial intelligence must serve all humanity, not just superpowers. The summit, February 16-20, aims to unite global leaders and tech CEOs on AI's equitable future. Guterres highlighted India's growing economic influence and its central role in shaping a multipolar world order, positioning the nation at the forefront of discussions on AI's potential and risks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69916b3a0caf1c998745c4b2_1771137968989.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-EU FTA: Strategic Gains Amidst Market Caution and Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Strategic-Gains-Amidst-Market-Caution-and-Global-Headwinds/6991637b0caf1c998745c2bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Strategic-Gains-Amidst-Market-Caution-and-Global-Headwinds/6991637b0caf1c998745c2bf</guid><description>India's Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's recent diplomatic engagements have yielded a finalized India-EU Free Trade Agreement (FTA) and paved the way for increased European bank presence. While lauded as a long-term strategic win, market reaction remains measured, reflecting lingering global uncertainties and implementation challenges. The economic outlook is buoyed by strong GDP projections, yet external factors like US tariffs and internal fiscal metrics present ongoing concerns.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991637b0caf1c998745c2be_1771135998306.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's SIP Trap: Emergency Fund Crisis Fuels Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-SIP-Trap-Emergency-Fund-Crisis-Fuels-Losses/69915f4012665ef560f9b61c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-SIP-Trap-Emergency-Fund-Crisis-Fuels-Losses/69915f4012665ef560f9b61c</guid><description>Indian novice investors are falling into a "SIP trap," prioritizing mutual fund investments over essential emergency funds due to low financial literacy and peer pressure. This leads to high SIP breakage rates and financial distress when unexpected expenses arise. Experts stress a foundational approach, advocating for robust emergency savings before or concurrently with initiating investments to ensure long-term financial well-being and prevent wealth destruction.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 05:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69915f4012665ef560f9b61b_1771134996187.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Escorts Kubota Eyes US Tractor Exports Amid Trade Deal &amp; Global Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Eyes-US-Tractor-Exports-Amid-Trade-Deal-and-Global-Strategy/69915e8d12665ef560f9b457</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Eyes-US-Tractor-Exports-Amid-Trade-Deal-and-Global-Strategy/69915e8d12665ef560f9b457</guid><description>Escorts Kubota sees a significant opportunity to export tractors to the United States following the recent India-US interim trade agreement. This potential expansion aligns with its parent company Kubota Corporation's ambitious 'Mid-Term Business Plan 2030,' which designates India as a critical global hub for R&amp;D, procurement, and production. Despite the promising outlook, the company navigates a competitive landscape, including established players like Mahindra &amp; Mahindra and John Deere, and a domestic market evolving with mechanization trends and affordability challenges. Mixed analyst sentiment and a current P/E ratio of approximately 30.8 suggest a cautious yet opportunistic outlook for the company.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 05:50:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69915e8d12665ef560f9b456_1771134812564.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>