<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:53:28 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Aegis Vopak Q3 Earnings Soar, Unveils $5Bn India Expansion Plan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Aegis-Vopak-Q3-Earnings-Soar-Unveils-5Bn-India-Expansion-Plan/69843c00bf48f011a29b6a01</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Aegis-Vopak-Q3-Earnings-Soar-Unveils-5Bn-India-Expansion-Plan/69843c00bf48f011a29b6a01</guid><description>Aegis Vopak Terminals posted a robust Q3 FY26, with revenue up 22.3% YoY to INR197.5 cr and PAT surging 62.7% YoY to INR61.5 cr. For 9M FY26, profit jumped 90% YoY. The company completed its HALPG acquisition, entering the East Coast market, and detailed a massive $5 billion capex plan by 2030. This includes significant expansions at JNPT, Kandla, Pipavav, and other ports, aiming to nearly double its asset base and capitalize on India's growing energy logistics demand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:43:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69843c00bf48f011a29b6a00_1770273959152.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kotak Mahindra Bank Bets Big on Tech to Forge AI-Powered Banking Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kotak-Mahindra-Bank-Bets-Big-on-Tech-to-Forge-AI-Powered-Banking-Future/69843be8bf48f011a29b6976</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kotak-Mahindra-Bank-Bets-Big-on-Tech-to-Forge-AI-Powered-Banking-Future/69843be8bf48f011a29b6976</guid><description>Kotak Mahindra Bank plans to hire up to 500 engineers to bolster its technology capabilities, aiming to transform into a "technology company with a banking license." This strategic pivot, fueled by investments in AI and automation, follows a period of internal system overhaul after a regulatory embargo. The bank's technology spending now represents approximately 13% of operating expenses, a significant increase aimed at enhancing competitiveness and operational resilience in India's rapidly digitalizing financial sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:42:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69843be8bf48f011a29b6975_1770273868992.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nomura Upgrades Cognizant, Predicts 34% Stock Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nomura-Upgrades-Cognizant-Predicts-34percent-Stock-Surge/69843bc2bf48f011a29b68ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nomura-Upgrades-Cognizant-Predicts-34percent-Stock-Surge/69843bc2bf48f011a29b68ba</guid><description>Nomura reiterates a 'Buy' rating on Nasdaq-listed Cognizant Technology Solutions, forecasting a significant 34% upside. The global brokerage highlights steady execution, improving margins, and robust deal activity. Cognizant's Q4 FY25 results surpassed expectations across revenue, margins, and EPS, driven by North America and financial services. Full-year growth also beat guidance, solidifying its position among IT service providers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:42:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69843bc2bf48f011a29b68b9_1770273819684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cognizant Surges on 2025 Results, Eyes AI Value Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cognizant-Surges-on-2025-Results-Eyes-AI-Value-Gap/69843ae7bf48f011a29b6666</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cognizant-Surges-on-2025-Results-Eyes-AI-Value-Gap/69843ae7bf48f011a29b6666</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Services closed 2025 with impressive financial results, reporting $21.1 billion in revenue and a 16.1% operating margin, driven by a 7.0% year-over-year increase in dollar terms and strategic acquisitions like Belcan. The company secured significant deal wins, including megadeals exceeding $500 million, and projects 4.9% to 7.4% revenue growth for 2026. CEO Ravi Kumar S. highlighted over 4,000 AI engagements and a pivot towards an "AI builder" strategy, while also acknowledging the "AI velocity gap"—the challenge of translating AI infrastructure spending into tangible client business value.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:38:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69843ae7bf48f011a29b6665_1770273678062.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amazon Consolidates Global Seller Services Under Agarwal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazon-Consolidates-Global-Seller-Services-Under-Agarwal/69843ad4bf48f011a29b6602</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazon-Consolidates-Global-Seller-Services-Under-Agarwal/69843ad4bf48f011a29b6602</guid><description>Amazon has expanded the role of SVP Amit Agarwal to encompass its Worldwide Selling Partner Services (SPS), a critical division responsible for over 60% of units sold on the platform. This strategic move integrates Agarwal's oversight of emerging markets, including India and Brazil, with the core seller ecosystem, signaling a push for deeper global integration and higher-margin service revenue. Dharmesh Mehta transitions to a technical advisor role for CEO Andy Jassy. The consolidation aims to bolster Amazon's competitive stance against rivals like Walmart and capitalize on ongoing e-commerce expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:38:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69843ad4bf48f011a29b6601_1770273583328.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Plunge From Records: Market Fears Grip Precious Metals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Plunge-From-Records-Market-Fears-Grip-Precious-Metals/6984396fbf48f011a29b6444</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Plunge-From-Records-Market-Fears-Grip-Precious-Metals/6984396fbf48f011a29b6444</guid><description>Precious metals gold and silver have sharply reversed course, plummeting from record highs witnessed in late January 2026. The drastic sell-off, triggered by factors including a hawkish Federal Reserve nomination and strengthening US dollar, has wiped out significant gains. Gold fell from over $5,500/oz to near $4,400/oz, while silver dropped from over $120/oz to around $71/oz. This correction highlights increased market volatility and uncertainty regarding the sustainability of previous bullish trends.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984396fbf48f011a29b6443_1770273257786.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apollo Tyres Q3 Profit Surges 39.5% on India Strength, Margins Expand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apollo-Tyres-Q3-Profit-Surges-395percent-on-India-Strength-Margins-Expand/6984378ebf48f011a29b629c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apollo-Tyres-Q3-Profit-Surges-395percent-on-India-Strength-Margins-Expand/6984378ebf48f011a29b629c</guid><description>Apollo Tyres reported a strong Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 11.8% YoY to ₹77,431 Mn and PAT soaring 39.5% to ₹4,703 Mn. India operations posted record revenue and a 264% PAT jump. Consolidated EBITDA grew 25.2% with margins expanding 165 bps. Net debt reduced, and FCF was positive. However, YTD FY26 PAT dipped 20.9% due to exceptional items. Management eyes profitable growth and European recovery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:24:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984378ebf48f011a29b629b_1770272723383.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Stocks Tumble on Delivery Delays; HAL Leads Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Stocks-Tumble-on-Delivery-Delays-HAL-Leads-Losses/6984362fbf48f011a29b60ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Stocks-Tumble-on-Delivery-Delays-HAL-Leads-Losses/6984362fbf48f011a29b60ef</guid><description>Defence stocks slumped Thursday, led by Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL), as the crucial LCA Tejas Mk1A delivery faces delays due to pending avionics integration and certification. Other defence counters also saw declines amid profit-booking. The Nifty India Defence Index dropped 2.7%, underperforming the broader Nifty 50.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:18:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984362fbf48f011a29b60ee_1770272519343.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Road Sector Rebound: Valuations Face Margin Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Road-Sector-Rebound-Valuations-Face-Margin-Scrutiny/69843621bf48f011a29b6061</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Road-Sector-Rebound-Valuations-Face-Margin-Scrutiny/69843621bf48f011a29b6061</guid><description>India's road construction sector is navigating a cyclical upswing, bolstered by National Highways Authority of India's (NHAI) strengthened balance sheet and proactive project readiness measures. Analysts note NHAI's debt-to-equity has decreased significantly, unlocking capacity for an ₹8.3 trillion project pipeline through FY28. Despite positive indicators, the sector faces evolving market dynamics, including a shift towards Build-Operate-Transfer (BOT) toll projects and persistent competition, suggesting potential margin pressures despite robust order books.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:18:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69843621bf48f011a29b6060_1770272389839.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW Cement Surges 9% on Q3 Profit Turnaround, Overseas Expansion Fuels Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Cement-Surges-9percent-on-Q3-Profit-Turnaround-Overseas-Expansion-Fuels-Rally/698435a9bf48f011a29b5f27</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Cement-Surges-9percent-on-Q3-Profit-Turnaround-Overseas-Expansion-Fuels-Rally/698435a9bf48f011a29b5f27</guid><description>JSW Cement stock experienced a significant surge, jumping over 9% to reach a two-month high on Thursday. This upward movement followed the company's announcement of a strong turnaround in its third-quarter financial results, shifting from a substantial loss to a healthy profit. The rally was further supported by news of the company's strategic overseas expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:16:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698435a9bf48f011a29b5f26_1770272243876.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT's Real Threat: Muted Growth, Not AI, Fund Manager Warns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-ITs-Real-Threat-Muted-Growth-Not-AI-Fund-Manager-Warns/69843532bf48f011a29b5e17</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-ITs-Real-Threat-Muted-Growth-Not-AI-Fund-Manager-Warns/69843532bf48f011a29b5e17</guid><description>Prashant Paroda, Portfolio Manager at Allspring Global Investment, argues that fears of Artificial Intelligence disrupting Indian IT services are overstated. He identifies muted revenue growth as the sector's primary and more significant risk. This perspective comes as hedge funds aggressively bet against software stocks, exacerbated by recent AI tool launches impacting global tech shares.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:14:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69843532bf48f011a29b5e16_1770272160561.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent's Q3: Expansion Outpaces Profit Growth Amid SSSG Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trents-Q3-Expansion-Outpaces-Profit-Growth-Amid-SSSG-Pressure/69843443bf48f011a29b5cb6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trents-Q3-Expansion-Outpaces-Profit-Growth-Amid-SSSG-Pressure/69843443bf48f011a29b5cb6</guid><description>Trent Ltd. posted a 2.73% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 510.11 crore for Q3 FY26, alongside a 14.78% revenue jump to Rs 5,345.06 crore. This growth was largely fueled by the addition of 65 new stores across its formats. However, pressure on Same-Store Sales Growth (SSSG) and a one-time labor charge led to mixed brokerage sentiment and continued valuation concerns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:10:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69843443bf48f011a29b5cb5_1770272008651.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cancer Costs Soar, Fueling Health Insurance Market Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Cancer-Costs-Soar-Fueling-Health-Insurance-Market-Expansion/698433c9bf48f011a29b5b57</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Cancer-Costs-Soar-Fueling-Health-Insurance-Market-Expansion/698433c9bf48f011a29b5b57</guid><description>Escalating cancer treatment costs in India, now reaching ₹20-30 lakh for advanced cases, are exposing critical gaps in insurance coverage. Care Health Insurance data indicates early-stage treatments cost ₹5-7 lakh. This financial strain is spurring demand for higher sum insured health policies, with a recommended minimum of ₹15-25 lakh. The critical illness insurance market is projected for robust growth, as insurers expand offerings to meet this escalating need. Government initiatives aim to improve affordability, but the industry faces challenges in penetration and managing rising claims. This trend positions the health insurance sector for significant expansion and product evolution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:08:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698433c9bf48f011a29b5b56_1770271767727.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oberoi Realty Wins Rs 5,400 Crore Mumbai Land Bid</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Oberoi-Realty-Wins-Rs-5400-Crore-Mumbai-Land-Bid/69843351bf48f011a29b5a05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Oberoi-Realty-Wins-Rs-5400-Crore-Mumbai-Land-Bid/69843351bf48f011a29b5a05</guid><description>Oberoi Realty has placed the winning bid of Rs 5,400 crore for an 11-acre railway land parcel in Mumbai's Bandra East. The Railway Land Development Authority (RLDA) confirmed the bid opens possibilities for developing approximately 19.50 lakh sq ft. This strategic acquisition marks a significant move for the prominent developer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:06:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69843351bf48f011a29b5a04_1770271649212.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Capital Surge: Retail Boom Meets 'Patient Capital' Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Capital-Surge-Retail-Boom-Meets-Patient-Capital-Ambition/698432dbbf48f011a29b5891</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Capital-Surge-Retail-Boom-Meets-Patient-Capital-Ambition/698432dbbf48f011a29b5891</guid><description>India's economic future is pegged on shifting from short-term volatility to 'patient capital' and mass market participation, a vision articulated by Mukesh Ambani and Larry Fink. The country is experiencing an unprecedented surge in retail investors, with participation growing ninefold over the decade and now accounting for over half of daily transactions. However, significant challenges persist, including low financial literacy rates and substantial household savings locked in unproductive assets like gold, which must be addressed to fully realize India's ambitious growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:04:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698432dbbf48f011a29b5890_1770271537682.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MAS Financial Posts 20.5% PAT Jump; Eyes 25% AUM Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MAS-Financial-Posts-205percent-PAT-Jump-Eyes-25percent-AUM-Growth/698431f1bf48f011a29b56bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MAS-Financial-Posts-205percent-PAT-Jump-Eyes-25percent-AUM-Growth/698431f1bf48f011a29b56bc</guid><description>MAS Financial Services reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated PAT rising 20.55% to INR 97 crore and AUM growing 18.28% to INR 14,641 crore YoY. The company aims for 20-25% AUM growth, fueled by SME and 2-wheeler segments. Strategic tech investments and market expansion are key priorities, though a deliberate slowdown in the CV segment due to quality concerns is noted. An interim dividend of INR 1.25 per share was declared.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:00:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698431f1bf48f011a29b56bb_1770271299620.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCLT Approves Sumuka Agro's Merger With Gujjubhai Foods</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/NCLT-Approves-Sumuka-Agros-Merger-With-Gujjubhai-Foods/698431eabf48f011a29b5654</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/NCLT-Approves-Sumuka-Agros-Merger-With-Gujjubhai-Foods/698431eabf48f011a29b5654</guid><description>Sumuka Agro Industries Limited announced that the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), Mumbai Bench, has sanctioned its Scheme of Merger by Absorption with Gujjubhai Foods Private Limited. The order, pronounced on February 4, 2026, marks a significant step towards consolidation. The company is now proceeding to file certified copies of the order with the Registrar of Companies (RoC) to officially effectuate the merger.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:00:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698431eabf48f011a29b5653_1770271318418.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Energy Solutions Hits 1 Crore Smart Meter Milestone, Surpassing Guidance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Adani-Energy-Solutions-Hits-1-Crore-Smart-Meter-Milestone-Surpassing-Guidance/69843083bf48f011a29b5450</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Adani-Energy-Solutions-Hits-1-Crore-Smart-Meter-Milestone-Surpassing-Guidance/69843083bf48f011a29b5450</guid><description>Adani Energy Solutions Limited (AESL) has achieved a significant milestone, installing 1 crore electricity smart meters across India, approximately 24 months after commencing its journey and surpassing its own guidance. This rapid deployment, averaging 25,000 meters daily, positions AESL as a key player in modernizing India's power distribution under the RDSS. The company has a mandate to install 2.5 crore smart meters and plans to deliver the next crore in the upcoming fiscal year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:54:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69843083bf48f011a29b544f_1770270973437.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Associated Alcohols Q3: Revenue Dips 20%, Profit Climbs 5% on Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Associated-Alcohols-Q3-Revenue-Dips-20percent-Profit-Climbs-5percent-on-Margin-Gains/6984300abf48f011a29b5330</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Associated-Alcohols-Q3-Revenue-Dips-20percent-Profit-Climbs-5percent-on-Margin-Gains/6984300abf48f011a29b5330</guid><description>Associated Alcohols &amp; Breweries saw Q3 FY26 revenue decline 20% YoY to ₹2,604 million, hit by lower IMFL licensed volumes and ethanol sales. However, Profit After Tax (PAT) grew 5% to ₹273 million, driven by a 400 bps EBITDA margin expansion to 16% due to cost efficiencies and premium product focus. New capacity additions and premium launches are underway.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:52:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984300abf48f011a29b532f_1770270876091.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent's Margin Surge Fuels Re-rating Potential Amidst Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trents-Margin-Surge-Fuels-Re-rating-Potential-Amidst-Growth/69842ea0bf48f011a29b51c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trents-Margin-Surge-Fuels-Re-rating-Potential-Amidst-Growth/69842ea0bf48f011a29b51c4</guid><description>Trent Limited reported Q3 FY26 results that surpassed expectations, primarily through substantial EBITDA margin expansion. While revenue growth of 14.8% year-on-year moderated due to festive timing shifts, the company's operational efficiencies and cost leverage drove its operating profit margin to 20.23%, a significant increase of 203 basis points year-on-year. This performance, coupled with a substantial underperformance in its stock price over the preceding quarters, sets the stage for a potential re-rating.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:46:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842ea0bf48f011a29b51c3_1770270494949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hexaware Shares Plunge 10% on Weak Q4 Results, Outlook Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexaware-Shares-Plunge-10percent-on-Weak-Q4-Results-Outlook-Concerns/69842bd1bf48f011a29b4bc0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexaware-Shares-Plunge-10percent-on-Weak-Q4-Results-Outlook-Concerns/69842bd1bf48f011a29b4bc0</guid><description>Hexaware Technologies saw its shares plummet nearly 10% after a disappointing fourth-quarter performance. Revenue declined sequentially, and margins missed expectations, raising concerns despite management's optimism about an improving demand environment and AI strategy. The company forecasts a weaker first quarter in 2026 before a second-half rebound.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:34:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842bd1bf48f011a29b4bbf_1770269741911.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metal Stocks Plunge 7% as Profit Booking, Stronger Dollar Hit Shares</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Metal-Stocks-Plunge-7percent-as-Profit-Booking-Stronger-Dollar-Hit-Shares/69842b5ebf48f011a29b4a2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Metal-Stocks-Plunge-7percent-as-Profit-Booking-Stronger-Dollar-Hit-Shares/69842b5ebf48f011a29b4a2c</guid><description>Indian metal stocks experienced a sharp sell-off on February 5, with the Nifty Metal index declining nearly 3%. This downturn was driven by aggressive profit-booking following a recent rally, the strengthening U.S. dollar which pressured commodity prices, and a significant drop in gold and silver futures. Hindustan Zinc shares were particularly hard-hit, falling approximately 7%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:32:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842b5ebf48f011a29b4a2b_1770269621876.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent Beats Profit Estimates Amidst Moderate Growth, Expansion Fuels Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Beats-Profit-Estimates-Amidst-Moderate-Growth-Expansion-Fuels-Outlook/69842b5abf48f011a29b4a13</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Beats-Profit-Estimates-Amidst-Moderate-Growth-Expansion-Fuels-Outlook/69842b5abf48f011a29b4a13</guid><description>Trent Limited exceeded profit expectations in Q3 FY26, driven by significant margin expansion through cost efficiencies and operating leverage, even as revenue growth moderated to 16% year-on-year. The company aggressively expanded its store network, adding 65 new outlets across Westside and Zudio. Despite sector headwinds and high valuations, Trent maintains a positive medium-term outlook, signaling resilience and strategic positioning for future re-rating.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:32:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842b5abf48f011a29b4a12_1770269695426.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HAL Confirms LCA Mk1A Deliveries On Track, Meets FY Guidance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HAL-Confirms-LCA-Mk1A-Deliveries-On-Track-Meets-FY-Guidance/69842ae5bf48f011a29b4433</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HAL-Confirms-LCA-Mk1A-Deliveries-On-Track-Meets-FY-Guidance/69842ae5bf48f011a29b4433</guid><description>Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL) has clarified the status of its Light Combat Aircraft (LCA) Mk1A program, confirming that five aircraft are fully prepared for delivery with contracted capabilities. An additional nine aircraft have been manufactured and completed flight testing, pending engine supply from GE. HAL assured stakeholders it is on track to meet its projected financial guidance for the current Financial Year, buoyed by a positive outlook on GE engine deliveries and continuous dialogue with the Indian Air Force.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:30:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842ae5bf48f011a29b4432_1770269561180.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Warburg Pincus to Boost India Investments: Succession &amp; Global Ambitions Drive Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Warburg-Pincus-to-Boost-India-Investments-Succession-and-Global-Ambitions-Drive-Strategy/6984297cbf48f011a29b427d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Warburg-Pincus-to-Boost-India-Investments-Succession-and-Global-Ambitions-Drive-Strategy/6984297cbf48f011a29b427d</guid><description>Warburg Pincus plans significant investment increases in India, tapping into succession planning for family-owned businesses and facilitating international expansion for Indian firms. India now stands as the firm's second-largest market globally behind the US, reflecting a deepening commitment amid a maturing private equity landscape and strong economic tailwinds. The strategy aligns with broader Asia-Pacific trends of control-oriented buyouts and capital reallocation towards dynamic emerging markets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:24:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984297cbf48f011a29b427c_1770269164073.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Terrain Fashions Swings to Q3 Profit, Loss Narrows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indian-Terrain-Fashions-Swings-to-Q3-Profit-Loss-Narrows/69842888bf48f011a29b40ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indian-Terrain-Fashions-Swings-to-Q3-Profit-Loss-Narrows/69842888bf48f011a29b40ec</guid><description>Indian Terrain Fashions Limited posted a strong Q3 FY26 turnaround, achieving a net profit of ₹2.56 Cr against a prior-year loss. Revenue grew 4.66% year-on-year to ₹101.40 Cr. The nine-month net loss significantly narrowed to ₹4.01 Cr. However, an exceptional item of ₹0.58 Cr for gratuity provisioning due to new labor codes signals potential future cost implications for the apparel firm.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:20:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842888bf48f011a29b40eb_1770268943395.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSP Projects Hits Record Revenue; Order Book Guidance Revised Down</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PSP-Projects-Hits-Record-Revenue-Order-Book-Guidance-Revised-Down/698426aabf48f011a29b3f59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PSP-Projects-Hits-Record-Revenue-Order-Book-Guidance-Revised-Down/698426aabf48f011a29b3f59</guid><description>PSP Projects Ltd. reported its best-ever quarterly revenue of INR 771 crore, up 24% YoY, with PAT surging 159% to INR 16 crore. Order inflow soared 151% to INR 957 crore, boosting the order book to INR 9,178 crore. However, FY26 order book guidance was revised downwards to INR 11,000-12,000 crore. A one-time INR 8 crore employee benefit expense impacted EBITDA margins, which stood at 6.73%. Management targets INR 4,000-4,500 crore revenue in FY27.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:12:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698426aabf48f011a29b3f58_1770268430857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Faces CCI Probe: Operational Woes Threaten Market Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Faces-CCI-Probe-Operational-Woes-Threaten-Market-Dominance/69842559bf48f011a29b3cfe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Faces-CCI-Probe-Operational-Woes-Threaten-Market-Dominance/69842559bf48f011a29b3cfe</guid><description>InterGlobe Aviation Ltd. (IndiGo) shares declined on Thursday as the Competition Commission of India (CCI) initiated a probe into the airline for alleged abuse of its dominant market position. The investigation stems from over 4,200 flight cancellations in December 2025, attributed to scheduling challenges post new pilot duty regulations. This operational disruption saw IndiGo's market share dip, creating openings for competitors like Air India Group, while the airline faces significant regulatory scrutiny and financial penalties.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:06:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842559bf48f011a29b3cfd_1770268227497.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Bull Market Endures $7 Trillion Sell-Off; UBS Eyes $6200</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Bull-Market-Endures-7-Trillion-Sell-Off-UBS-Eyes-6200/69842550bf48f011a29b3c76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Bull-Market-Endures-7-Trillion-Sell-Off-UBS-Eyes-6200/69842550bf48f011a29b3c76</guid><description>Gold demonstrated remarkable resilience following a historic market correction on January 30, 2026, which saw prices plummet by up to 12% and erase trillions in value. Analysts at UBS, alongside other institutions like JP Morgan and Deutsche Bank, maintain a bullish stance, projecting gold to reach $6,200 per ounce by mid-2026. This outlook is underpinned by persistent geopolitical risks, anticipated central bank easing, and strong underlying investor demand, suggesting the recent volatility was primarily driven by leveraged positions unwinding rather than a fundamental shift. Silver, however, faces a more uncertain path, characterized by significant price swings and a cautious analyst consensus.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:06:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842550bf48f011a29b3c75_1770268122644.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Stocks Hit 52-Week Highs Amid Geopolitical Spikes, Analysts Urge Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-Stocks-Hit-52-Week-Highs-Amid-Geopolitical-Spikes-Analysts-Urge-Caution/698424cdbf48f011a29b3b15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-Stocks-Hit-52-Week-Highs-Amid-Geopolitical-Spikes-Analysts-Urge-Caution/698424cdbf48f011a29b3b15</guid><description>The BSE Oil &amp; Gas index reached a new 52-week high of 29,447.10, significantly outperforming a declining Sensex by gaining over 1% intraday. State-owned entities like ONGC and Oil India saw substantial monthly price increases, attributed to rising crude oil prices influenced by US-Iran tensions and inventory data. However, a cautious outlook prevails for the medium to long term due to demand concerns, despite bullish short-term technicals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:04:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698424cdbf48f011a29b3b14_1770268017081.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ElevenLabs Secures $500M, Hits $11B Valuation in AI Audio Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ElevenLabs-Secures-500M-Hits-11B-Valuation-in-AI-Audio-Surge/69842457bf48f011a29b39a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ElevenLabs-Secures-500M-Hits-11B-Valuation-in-AI-Audio-Surge/69842457bf48f011a29b39a8</guid><description>Artificial intelligence audio firm ElevenLabs secured $500 million in a Series D round, catapulting its valuation to $11 billion. The funding surge, led by Sequoia Capital, reflects strong enterprise adoption of its voice AI platform, Eleven Agents. Capital will fuel expansion and advanced model research.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:02:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842457bf48f011a29b39a7_1770267879069.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver ETFs Plunge 16%, Gold ETFs Slip 5% Amid Futures Drop</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-ETFs-Plunge-16percent-Gold-ETFs-Slip-5percent-Amid-Futures-Drop/698423d9bf48f011a29b3893</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-ETFs-Plunge-16percent-Gold-ETFs-Slip-5percent-Amid-Futures-Drop/698423d9bf48f011a29b3893</guid><description>Precious metals faced a sharp sell-off on February 5, with silver ETFs tumbling up to 16% and gold ETFs dropping around 5%. This decline followed a rebound in earlier sessions, driven by profit-taking and anticipation of key US economic data. While futures markets saw significant drops, analysts maintain a long-term bullish outlook citing central bank demand and supply deficits.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:00:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698423d9bf48f011a29b3892_1770267729182.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Volatility: Tariff Easing Wars with Geopolitical Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Volatility-Tariff-Easing-Wars-with-Geopolitical-Fears/69842363bf48f011a29b37ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Volatility-Tariff-Easing-Wars-with-Geopolitical-Fears/69842363bf48f011a29b37ae</guid><description>Gold futures on MCX and Comex experienced significant volatility on February 5, 2026, driven by conflicting economic and geopolitical forces. A landmark reduction in US tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 50% was met with ongoing geopolitical tensions, including the downing of an Iranian drone. This created a tug-of-war between factors that should reduce safe-haven demand and those that increase it, leading to price swings and a complex outlook for the precious metal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:58:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842363bf48f011a29b37ad_1770267605896.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent's Divided Analyst Views Signal Valuation Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Trents-Divided-Analyst-Views-Signal-Valuation-Jitters/6984218fbf48f011a29b35dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Trents-Divided-Analyst-Views-Signal-Valuation-Jitters/6984218fbf48f011a29b35dc</guid><description>Trent posted a 16% YoY revenue rise to ₹5,259 crore and a 36% net profit jump to ₹640 crore in Q3 FY26. However, analyst sentiment is split: Motilal Oswal reiterates 'Buy' with a ₹5,200 target, citing cost controls and expansion, while Nuvama Institutional Equities cuts its target to ₹4,543 and maintains 'Hold' due to negative like-for-like sales. The stock's recent 30% annual decline underscores this valuation tension.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:50:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984218fbf48f011a29b35db_1770267277154.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lilly Surges on Obesity Dominance, Outpacing Novo Nordisk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lilly-Surges-on-Obesity-Dominance-Outpacing-Novo-Nordisk/69842184bf48f011a29b3515</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lilly-Surges-on-Obesity-Dominance-Outpacing-Novo-Nordisk/69842184bf48f011a29b3515</guid><description>Eli Lilly &amp; Co. projected robust sales growth, driven by its leading obesity drugs, contrasting sharply with rival Novo Nordisk's sales decline forecast. Lilly's shares climbed as its strong guidance, extended patent protection for key drugs like Mounjaro and Zepbound, and diversified pipeline position it favorably against Novo Nordisk's narrower focus and looming generic competition. The company also anticipates FDA approval for its oral weight-loss pill, further solidifying its market lead.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:50:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842184bf48f011a29b3514_1770267119886.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Concord Control Wins ₹185 Crore Indian Railways Order for KAVACH 4.0</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Concord-Control-Wins-185-Crore-Indian-Railways-Order-for-KAVACH-40/69842094bf48f011a29b330f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Concord-Control-Wins-185-Crore-Indian-Railways-Order-for-KAVACH-40/69842094bf48f011a29b330f</guid><description>Concord Control Systems Limited has bagged a significant ₹185.09 crore order from Indian Railways for the advanced KAVACH 4.0 Automatic Train Protection system. The contract, to be executed within 12 months, underscores the company's technological prowess in railway safety solutions. This win is expected to bolster Concord Control's growth trajectory and reinforce its strategic position in India's railway modernization efforts, aligning with the Gati Shakti initiative.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:46:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69842094bf48f011a29b330e_1770266869496.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Concord Control Systems Wins Rs 185 Cr Indian Railways KAVACH Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Concord-Control-Systems-Wins-Rs-185-Cr-Indian-Railways-KAVACH-Order/69841fa1bf48f011a29b3178</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Concord-Control-Systems-Wins-Rs-185-Cr-Indian-Railways-KAVACH-Order/69841fa1bf48f011a29b3178</guid><description>Concord Control Systems Limited secured a major Rs 185.09 Crore order from Indian Railways for KAVACH 4.0 Loco equipment. Executed over 12 months, the deal strengthens the company's presence in railway signalling and safety systems. Progota India Private Limited, an associate, will aid in execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:42:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841fa1bf48f011a29b3177_1770266650875.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GRM Overseas Posts Stellar Q3, Eyes Rs 3,500 Cr Revenue by FY28</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GRM-Overseas-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Eyes-Rs-3500-Cr-Revenue-by-FY28/69841eb2bf48f011a29b2fe1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GRM-Overseas-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Eyes-Rs-3500-Cr-Revenue-by-FY28/69841eb2bf48f011a29b2fe1</guid><description>GRM Overseas Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated total income climbing 28.9% YoY to Rs 492.6 Crores and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 42.8% YoY to Rs 19.3 Crores. For the nine-month period, revenue grew 11.3% and PAT rose 30.3%. The company unveiled aggressive FY28 targets, aiming for Rs 2,000 Crores in India business and Rs 1,500 Crores internationally, bolstered by packaged food expansion and acquisition of a 44% stake in Rage Coffee.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:38:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841eb2bf48f011a29b2fe0_1770266380862.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GRM Overseas Q3 Profit Soars 43%, Revenue Jumps 29% on Strong Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GRM-Overseas-Q3-Profit-Soars-43percent-Revenue-Jumps-29percent-on-Strong-Demand/69841d5dbf48f011a29b2941</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GRM-Overseas-Q3-Profit-Soars-43percent-Revenue-Jumps-29percent-on-Strong-Demand/69841d5dbf48f011a29b2941</guid><description>GRM Overseas reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 28.9% YoY to ₹492.6 Crores and PAT surging 42.8% YoY to ₹19.3 Crores. EBITDA grew 34.1% to ₹31.3 Crores with margins expanding. For the nine months, revenue rose 11.3% and PAT by 30.3%. Management cited strong demand in international basmati and domestic branded segments, projecting continued growth driven by market expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:32:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841d5dbf48f011a29b2940_1770266131717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aster DM Healthcare, QCIL Merger Forms Top 3 Indian Hospital Chain With Strong Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aster-DM-Healthcare-QCIL-Merger-Forms-Top-3-Indian-Hospital-Chain-With-Strong-Growth/69841d4abf48f011a29b2897</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aster-DM-Healthcare-QCIL-Merger-Forms-Top-3-Indian-Hospital-Chain-With-Strong-Growth/69841d4abf48f011a29b2897</guid><description>Aster DM Healthcare and Quality Care India Limited (QCIL) have announced merger progress, creating one of India's top three hospital chains, 'Aster DM Quality Care Limited', with over 10,625 beds. The proforma combined entity reported a robust 15% year-on-year revenue growth to INR 2,366 crore and a 22% jump in Operating EBITDA to INR 503 crore in Q3FY26, with margins improving to 21%. The transaction is cash neutral and projected to be EPS accretive.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:32:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841d4abf48f011a29b2896_1770266070232.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>