<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:59:22 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Pfizer India's Margin Leap Fuels Rally; Sustainability Questioned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pfizer-Indias-Margin-Leap-Fuels-Rally-Sustainability-Questioned/698ad431757d40c7818532e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pfizer-Indias-Margin-Leap-Fuels-Rally-Sustainability-Questioned/698ad431757d40c7818532e7</guid><description>Pfizer Ltd shares climbed over 10% on Tuesday, February 10, after reporting robust Q3FY26 results. The company posted a 20% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹645.03 crore and a significant operating margin expansion to 35.4%, leading to a 13% net profit rise to ₹143.71 crore. While management points to key brands and operational efficiency for future growth, the sustainability of these elevated margins amidst competitive pressures and evolving regulatory landscapes remains a key focus for investors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:46:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ad431757d40c7818532e6_1770706068898.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T Wins 'Significant' Dubai Road Project Worth ₹1,000-2,500 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/LandT-Wins-Significant-Dubai-Road-Project-Worth-1000-2500-Cr/698ad3ed757d40c781853100</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/LandT-Wins-Significant-Dubai-Road-Project-Worth-1000-2500-Cr/698ad3ed757d40c781853100</guid><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro's Transportation Infrastructure business has secured a 'significant' contract for road improvements on Latifa Bint Hamdan Street in Dubai, UAE. The project, valued between ₹1,000 to ₹2,500 Crore, involves widening the carriageway and constructing a major interchange. Scheduled for completion in 36 months, this win enhances L&amp;T's order book and provides revenue visibility for the next three years, underscoring its global EPC capabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:45:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ad3ed757d40c7818530ff_1770706227563.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Bullion Market in Crisis: Volatility Shatters Trust, Demand Evaporates</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indian-Bullion-Market-in-Crisis-Volatility-Shatters-Trust-Demand-Evaporates/698ad3d4757d40c78185303c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indian-Bullion-Market-in-Crisis-Volatility-Shatters-Trust-Demand-Evaporates/698ad3d4757d40c78185303c</guid><description>India's precious metals sector faces a systemic crisis driven by unprecedented price volatility in gold and silver. Business activity has ground to a halt in key hubs like Rajkot, a major silver trading center, with demand evaporating and nearly 1.5 lakh workers impacted by job cuts. An estimated 44 trading firms face insolvency, burdened by ₹3,500 crore in unsettled dues. This financial distress cascades through a supply chain traditionally reliant on trust, as payment delays become the norm. Soaring raw material costs and mounting losses on pre-rally priced orders have crippled manufacturers, while consumers find even silver prohibitively expensive, leading to deferred purchases and reduced demand for adornment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:44:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ad3d4757d40c78185303b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Corona Remedies Surges 15% Revenue, Beats Guidance on Strategic Acquisitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Corona-Remedies-Surges-15percent-Revenue-Beats-Guidance-on-Strategic-Acquisitions/698ad3b8757d40c781852f2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Corona-Remedies-Surges-15percent-Revenue-Beats-Guidance-on-Strategic-Acquisitions/698ad3b8757d40c781852f2a</guid><description>CORONA Remedies Limited reported a robust Q3 FY'26, with revenue climbing 15% YoY to ₹342 crores and PAT rising 24% YoY to ₹56 crores. The company exceeded its guidance for the nine-month period, achieving 16% revenue growth and 31% PAT growth, driven by strategic brand acquisitions like the Bayer portfolio and new product launches. Management reiterated a positive outlook, targeting continued mid-teen revenue and high-teen PAT growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:44:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ad3b8757d40c781852f29_1770705944175.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Overhaul: Insurance Stocks Face Reckoning as New Tech Threatens Core Models</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Overhaul-Insurance-Stocks-Face-Reckoning-as-New-Tech-Threatens-Core-Models/698ad251757d40c781852d0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Overhaul-Insurance-Stocks-Face-Reckoning-as-New-Tech-Threatens-Core-Models/698ad251757d40c781852d0a</guid><description>The insurance brokerage sector experienced a significant market re-evaluation on February 9, 2026, following the launch of Insurify's AI shopping agent. This event, compounded by other AI advancements from companies like Anthropic, triggered billions in market cap losses for firms such as Willis Towers Watson and Aon. The market's perception of AI has shifted from a productivity tool to a direct revenue competitor, impacting valuations across human-led service industries. Willis Towers Watson fell 8% and Aon dropped over 9% amid heightened trading volumes, reflecting deep investor concern about AI's long-term impact on intermediary roles and traditional business models.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:38:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ad251757d40c781852d09_1770705650940.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Mutual Fund Selection Evolves Beyond Past Returns in 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Mutual-Fund-Selection-Evolves-Beyond-Past-Returns-in-2026/698ad1de757d40c781852b20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Mutual-Fund-Selection-Evolves-Beyond-Past-Returns-in-2026/698ad1de757d40c781852b20</guid><description>The Indian mutual fund industry's selection paradigm is shifting in 2026. Investors are moving past solely historical returns and star ratings towards a more analytical approach. This requires understanding alignment with policy-driven themes like those from Budget 2025-26, scrutinizing investment styles, and evaluating portfolio construction, risk management, and the impact of growing AUM. Sustained SIP inflows of ₹31,002 crore in December 2025 indicate robust domestic participation, yet normalized return expectations necessitate a deeper due diligence process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:36:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ad1de757d40c781852b1f_1770705483441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MF Investing Fails to Predict Returns; Outliers Shine</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/MF-Investing-Fails-to-Predict-Returns-Outliers-Shine/698ad163757d40c78185297d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/MF-Investing-Fails-to-Predict-Returns-Outliers-Shine/698ad163757d40c78185297d</guid><description>A six-year analysis from FY21 to FY26 reveals a near-zero correlation between mutual fund (MF) shareholding increases and subsequent stock returns, suggesting institutional conviction is not a reliable predictor of market performance. This disconnect is starkly illustrated by GE Vernova T&amp;D India, which achieved strong price appreciation backed by genuine earnings growth, and Gokaldas Exports, where valuation expansion alone drove significant stock gains despite negative earnings. The findings challenge conventional investor wisdom, emphasizing the need to look beyond MF flows for investment opportunities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:34:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ad163757d40c78185297c_1770705365322.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shanti Gold Q3 Revenue Leaps 124%, But 9-Month Margins Narrow</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shanti-Gold-Q3-Revenue-Leaps-124percent-But-9-Month-Margins-Narrow/698ad071757d40c7818527aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shanti-Gold-Q3-Revenue-Leaps-124percent-But-9-Month-Margins-Narrow/698ad071757d40c7818527aa</guid><description>Shanti Gold International Limited has reported a significant surge in its third quarter performance for FY2025-26. Revenue from operations soared 124% year-on-year to ₹3670 crore. Profit After Tax (PAT) also grew robustly by 138% YoY to ₹1101 crore, with PAT margins improving to 30.00% from 28.24%. The company's Earnings Per Share (EPS) more than doubled to ₹3.03. However, for the nine-month period, while revenue grew 66% YoY to ₹8651 crore, PAT saw a more moderate increase of 37% YoY to ₹2095 crore, and PAT margins contracted to 24.22% from 29.46% last year. The company recently completed its IPO in August 2025.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:30:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ad071757d40c7818527a9_1770705126980.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Electrosteel Castings Posts Q3 Loss, Eyes Recovery on JJM Spending &amp; Valve Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Electrosteel-Castings-Posts-Q3-Loss-Eyes-Recovery-on-JJM-Spending-and-Valve-Growth/698acf88757d40c78185258c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Electrosteel-Castings-Posts-Q3-Loss-Eyes-Recovery-on-JJM-Spending-and-Valve-Growth/698acf88757d40c78185258c</guid><description>Electrosteel Castings reported a Q3 FY26 consolidated loss of ₹22 crores, impacted by a 31% YoY drop in DI/CI pipe volumes due to delayed government spending on the Jal Jeevan Mission (JJM). Revenue fell to ₹1,526 crores. However, net debt was reduced by ₹455 crores to ₹812 crores. Management anticipates a market rebound from Q2 FY27, citing increased JJM budget and growth prospects from its acquired Italian valve manufacturer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:26:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698acf88757d40c78185258b_1770704842604.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Valiant Comm's GPS Tech Passes Indian Army Jamming &amp; Spoofing Tests</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valiant-Comms-GPS-Tech-Passes-Indian-Army-Jamming-and-Spoofing-Tests/698acf0a757d40c78185243b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valiant-Comms-GPS-Tech-Passes-Indian-Army-Jamming-and-Spoofing-Tests/698acf0a757d40c78185243b</guid><description>Valiant Communications Limited's VCL-2156 Dual-Band GPS and NavIC NTP Time Server has successfully completed rigorous field evaluation with the Indian Armed Forces. The indigenous system demonstrated robust resilience against sophisticated GNSS signal jamming and spoofing threats, ensuring secure and accurate timing synchronization essential for defence operations and critical infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:24:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698acf0a757d40c78185243a_1770704732275.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jain Resource Recycling Surges on Growth, Eyes Mideast Expansion; Debt Climbs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jain-Resource-Recycling-Surges-on-Growth-Eyes-Mideast-Expansion-Debt-Climbs/698ace1b757d40c781852292</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jain-Resource-Recycling-Surges-on-Growth-Eyes-Mideast-Expansion-Debt-Climbs/698ace1b757d40c781852292</guid><description>Jain Resource Recycling reported a robust 38% YoY revenue surge to ₹6,438 crore for 9M FY26, with EBITDA soaring 65% and PAT up 65%. The company is aggressively expanding, eyeing a Middle East stake and a new copper recycling JV, alongside forward integration into value-added copper products. However, net borrowings rose significantly, pushing the Net Debt to Equity ratio to 31.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:20:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ace1b757d40c781852291_1770704505082.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US-India AI Pact: Reshaping Global Tech Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-India-AI-Pact-Reshaping-Global-Tech-Dominance/698acd2f757d40c7818520f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-India-AI-Pact-Reshaping-Global-Tech-Dominance/698acd2f757d40c7818520f2</guid><description>The India AI Impact Summit 2026 convenes a significant US business delegation, spearheaded by USISPF, to advance US-India AI collaboration. A new AI Board Task Force, co-chaired by industry leaders, aims to accelerate ethical AI adoption across both nations. This strategic alliance, involving tech titans from both countries, is poised to shape global AI development, foster competitive ecosystems, and establish benchmarks for trustworthy technology, impacting nearly two billion people.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:16:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698acd2f757d40c7818520f1_1770704294822.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SILA Acquires SMS FS for ₹270 Cr, Eyes Tech-Led FM Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SILA-Acquires-SMS-FS-for-270-Cr-Eyes-Tech-Led-FM-Dominance/698acc4f757d40c781851f2d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SILA-Acquires-SMS-FS-for-270-Cr-Eyes-Tech-Led-FM-Dominance/698acc4f757d40c781851f2d</guid><description>SILA has acquired SMS Integrated Facility Services for ₹270 crore, a move designed to consolidate its position in India's burgeoning facility management (FM) market. The transaction aims to leverage SILA's strategy of building a scaled, technology-led business services platform, expanding its reach to over 125 cities and a workforce exceeding 50,000 employees. This consolidation is strategically timed to capitalize on the robust growth in India's commercial real estate sector, which is increasingly demanding sophisticated, integrated facility management solutions beyond traditional manpower services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:12:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698acc4f757d40c781851f2c_1770704126648.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crystal Crop Protection Invests ₹100 Crore in New Gujarat Agrochemical Plant</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Crystal-Crop-Protection-Invests-100-Crore-in-New-Gujarat-Agrochemical-Plant/698acc38757d40c781851ded</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Crystal-Crop-Protection-Invests-100-Crore-in-New-Gujarat-Agrochemical-Plant/698acc38757d40c781851ded</guid><description>Agrochemical firm Crystal Crop Protection has acquired 31.06 acres in Jhagadia, Gujarat, for a new manufacturing facility. The company plans to invest ₹100 crore over three years to build a fully automated plant for agrochemical formulations and technical products. This expansion aims to meet growing domestic demand and tap into export opportunities in Asia and Africa.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:12:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698acc38757d40c781851dec_1770704066482.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Equity Outflows: Geopolitics, Valuations Drive Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/India-Equity-Outflows-Geopolitics-Valuations-Drive-Caution/698acbc9757d40c781851c88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/India-Equity-Outflows-Geopolitics-Valuations-Drive-Caution/698acbc9757d40c781851c88</guid><description>Indian equity mutual funds experienced a 14.35% drop in January 2026 inflows to Rs 240.29 billion, extending a two-month decline. Foreign portfolio investors divested $3.95 billion, driven by geopolitical tensions and US tariff threats. Despite a stable domestic macroeconomic outlook and favorable interest rates, India's high P/E ratio relative to emerging market peers amplified investor caution, contributing to its underperformance against broader EM fund flow trends.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:10:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698acbc9757d40c781851c87_1770703946366.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kalyan Jewellers Surges 90% PAT on Strong Q3, E-commerce Turns Profitable</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kalyan-Jewellers-Surges-90percent-PAT-on-Strong-Q3-E-commerce-Turns-Profitable/698aca59757d40c781851a75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kalyan-Jewellers-Surges-90percent-PAT-on-Strong-Q3-E-commerce-Turns-Profitable/698aca59757d40c781851a75</guid><description>Kalyan Jewellers India Limited reported a spectacular Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue jumping 42% YoY to ₹10,343 crore and Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 90% YoY to ₹416 crore. The company's e-commerce arm, Candere, achieved PAT positivity, recording 117% revenue growth for the quarter. The nine-month period saw consolidated revenue rise 35% to ₹25,468 crore and PAT climb 79% to ₹941 crore. Management expressed optimism for continued strong performance through the wedding season and positive Q4 trends, backed by aggressive expansion plans in India and the Middle East.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:04:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aca59757d40c781851a74_1770703581130.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aarti Industries Q3 Revenue Jumps 11%, Taps Global Trade Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aarti-Industries-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-11percent-Taps-Global-Trade-Shifts/698ac968757d40c7818518b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aarti-Industries-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-11percent-Taps-Global-Trade-Shifts/698ac968757d40c7818518b4</guid><description>Aarti Industries reported an 11% quarter-on-quarter revenue increase to Rs. 2,492 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by volume growth and higher capacity utilization. EBITDA also rose 11% to Rs. 323 crore. Despite Rs. 15 crore in exceptional expenses, PAT climbed 25% QoQ to Rs. 133 crore. The company achieved its highest-ever export share at 65%, benefiting from global trade realignments like the India-EU FTA, China's 'anti-involution' strategy, and the US-India trade deal. Strategic focus shifts towards advanced materials, with significant CAPEX planned for FY26.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:00:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac968757d40c7818518b3_1770703285621.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>WeWork India, Turner International Ink Major Mumbai Managed Office Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/WeWork-India-Turner-International-Ink-Major-Mumbai-Managed-Office-Deal/698ac8f3757d40c781851741</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/WeWork-India-Turner-International-Ink-Major-Mumbai-Managed-Office-Deal/698ac8f3757d40c781851741</guid><description>WeWork India has significantly expanded its collaboration with Turner International India, launching a new 46,000 sq. ft. managed office in Airoli, Mumbai, designed to house over 650 professionals. This substantial growth from their initial 2022 partnership underscores the increasing enterprise confidence in flexible workspaces as strategic enablers for business expansion and operational efficiency.

The custom-built facility blends Turner's global standards with WeWork's agile design, reflecting a broader trend of large corporations leveraging flexible office solutions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:58:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac8f3757d40c781851740_1770703215210.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gulf Oil Lubricants Declares Dividend, Revenue Up, But PAT Dips on Exceptional Item</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Gulf-Oil-Lubricants-Declares-Dividend-Revenue-Up-But-PAT-Dips-on-Exceptional-Item/698ac788757d40c781851553</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Gulf-Oil-Lubricants-Declares-Dividend-Revenue-Up-But-PAT-Dips-on-Exceptional-Item/698ac788757d40c781851553</guid><description>Gulf Oil Lubricants India Limited reported a 10.55% year-on-year increase in consolidated revenue from operations for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹1,017.55 Crores. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) attributable to owners declined 22.00% YoY to ₹76.44 Crores, impacted by an exceptional item of ₹22.78 Crores related to new government labour codes. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹21 per equity share and approved acquiring an additional 14.18% stake in its subsidiary, Tirex Transmission Private Limited, raising its shareholding to 65.18%. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, revenue grew 12.03% YoY to ₹3,000.78 Crores, while PAT saw a marginal decrease of 3.65% YoY to ₹2,578.83 Crores.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:52:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac788757d40c781851552_1770702859746.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pfizer Shares Surge 11% on Strong Q3 Results, New Migraine Drug Boosts Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pfizer-Shares-Surge-11percent-on-Strong-Q3-Results-New-Migraine-Drug-Boosts-Outlook/698ac714757d40c7818513bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pfizer-Shares-Surge-11percent-on-Strong-Q3-Results-New-Migraine-Drug-Boosts-Outlook/698ac714757d40c7818513bb</guid><description>Pfizer's stock climbed over 11% following strong third-quarter earnings. The pharmaceutical giant reported an 11% year-over-year increase in net profit and a 20% jump in revenue, driven by robust operational performance and the India launch of a new migraine treatment, Rimegepant ODT. The company anticipates significant market penetration in the growing anti-migraine segment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:50:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac714757d40c7818513ba_1770702724894.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Insurers' Divergent Paths: Growth Shifts, Valuations Diverge, Regulatory Fog</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Insurers-Divergent-Paths-Growth-Shifts-Valuations-Diverge-Regulatory-Fog/698ac69a757d40c78185125e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Insurers-Divergent-Paths-Growth-Shifts-Valuations-Diverge-Regulatory-Fog/698ac69a757d40c78185125e</guid><description>January life insurance results reveal a reshuffling of leadership, with Axis Max Life posting robust gains while HDFC Life and SBI Life experienced a slowdown. This divergence occurs as insurer valuations converge, limiting immediate upside potential. Meanwhile, PB Fintech faces significant headwinds from proposed regulatory caps on insurance commissions, a concern exacerbated by its already stretched valuation multiples and a history of similar market reactions. The broader Indian insurance sector, however, anticipates steady growth through 2030, driven by expanding distribution and rising demand, though regulatory adjustments loom.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:48:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac69a757d40c78185125d_1770702681882.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Energy Dominance Play: Lavrov Slams 'Coercive' Tactics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Energy-Dominance-Play-Lavrov-Slams-Coercive-Tactics/698ac626757d40c78185110c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Energy-Dominance-Play-Lavrov-Slams-Coercive-Tactics/698ac626757d40c78185110c</guid><description>Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov has accused the United States of employing 'coercive' economic tactics, including sanctions and prohibitions, to prevent India and other nations from purchasing affordable Russian oil while pushing them towards higher-priced U.S. liquefied natural gas (LNG). This geopolitical maneuvering occurs as India reaffirms its commitment to 'national interest' in its energy procurement, prioritizing availability and fair pricing. The global energy market faces heightened volatility, with Brent crude trading around $68.86 and WTI near $64.19, influenced by sanctions on Russian oil and broader supply-demand dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:46:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac626757d40c78185110b_1770702519604.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Mandates SIM-Binding for Apps Amidst Scam Crackdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Mandates-SIM-Binding-for-Apps-Amidst-Scam-Crackdown/698ac5ab757d40c781850f6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Mandates-SIM-Binding-for-Apps-Amidst-Scam-Crackdown/698ac5ab757d40c781850f6a</guid><description>The Department of Telecommunications (DoT) has directed over-the-top (OTT) communication platforms, including WhatsApp, to implement SIM-binding. This regulatory shift, prompted by the Supreme Court's suo motu case on digital arrest scams, aims to bolster security by continuously linking user accounts to active SIM cards. The initiative is part of a broader strategy involving new legislation and technological interventions to combat escalating cyber fraud. However, concerns linger regarding implementation feasibility, privacy, and the actual effectiveness of such measures against sophisticated criminal networks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:44:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ac5ab757d40c781850f69.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Prices Dip 0.64% as Fed Rate Cut Bets Firm, India Rates High</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Dip-064percent-as-Fed-Rate-Cut-Bets-Firm-India-Rates-High/698ac52f757d40c781850dea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Dip-064percent-as-Fed-Rate-Cut-Bets-Firm-India-Rates-High/698ac52f757d40c781850dea</guid><description>Gold prices in India saw a 0.64% decline on February 10, 2026, with 24K gold trading at ₹157,350 per 10 grams. This dip aligns with global trends influenced by reinforced expectations of US Federal Reserve rate cuts and a weaker dollar. Despite the fall, Indian gold prices remain significantly higher than those in Dubai.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:42:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac52f757d40c781850de9_1770702355814.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Tumbles: Speculative Surge Unwinds Amidst Fed Cues</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Tumbles-Speculative-Surge-Unwinds-Amidst-Fed-Cues/698ac4cf757d40c781850bf3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Tumbles-Speculative-Surge-Unwinds-Amidst-Fed-Cues/698ac4cf757d40c781850bf3</guid><description>Silver prices in India dropped 1.84% on February 10, 2026, with 1 gram trading at ₹258, following a sharp retreat from recent highs. This decline underscores the speculative nature of the preceding rally, described as a 'blow-off' by US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent. International spot silver also fell, mirroring weakness in gold, platinum, and palladium. Investors are now closely monitoring delayed US jobs and inflation data for clues on Federal Reserve monetary policy, with expectations of rates remaining steady in March. The pullback highlights the market's sensitivity to macroeconomic signals and investor positioning shifts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:40:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac4cf757d40c781850bf2_1770702226790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSE Surges on Q3 Beat; High Valuation, Long-Term Gaps Cloud Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/BSE-Surges-on-Q3-Beat-High-Valuation-Long-Term-Gaps-Cloud-Outlook/698ac4b8757d40c781850b1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/BSE-Surges-on-Q3-Beat-High-Valuation-Long-Term-Gaps-Cloud-Outlook/698ac4b8757d40c781850b1c</guid><description>Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) shares jumped following better-than-expected Q3 FY26 results, driven by strong revenue growth and expanding market share in index options. Net profit surged 174% to ₹601.8 crore on revenue up 62% to ₹1,244.1 crore. Leading brokerages reiterated 'Buy' ratings with raised targets, citing operational momentum. However, significant concerns persist regarding the stock's premium valuation and long-term strategic growth drivers beyond FY29.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:40:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac4b8757d40c781850b1b_1770702139074.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auto Dealers Bullish: Budget Fuels Strong Growth Outlook for Next 3 Months</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Dealers-Bullish-Budget-Fuels-Strong-Growth-Outlook-for-Next-3-Months/698ac440757d40c78185098a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Dealers-Bullish-Budget-Fuels-Strong-Growth-Outlook-for-Next-3-Months/698ac440757d40c78185098a</guid><description>Indian auto dealers express optimism for the next three months, citing a growth-focused Budget and policy stability. January retail sales surged across all major segments—passenger vehicles, two-wheelers, three-wheelers, and commercial vehicles—registering significant year-on-year increases driven by rural liquidity and sustained demand.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:38:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac440757d40c781850989_1770701995216.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AstraZeneca Pharma India Gets CDSCO Nod for Cancer Drug Imfinzi</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/AstraZeneca-Pharma-India-Gets-CDSCO-Nod-for-Cancer-Drug-Imfinzi/698ac34f757d40c7818503e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/AstraZeneca-Pharma-India-Gets-CDSCO-Nod-for-Cancer-Drug-Imfinzi/698ac34f757d40c7818503e9</guid><description>AstraZeneca Pharma India has received CDSCO approval to import and distribute Durvalumab (Imfinzi) for a new indication: first-line treatment of advanced endometrial cancer. This expands market access for the drug in India, pending further statutory approvals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:34:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac34f757d40c7818503e8_1770701788548.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nazara Revenue Tumbles 24% on Divestment, Profit Jumps; Growth Drivers Strong</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Nazara-Revenue-Tumbles-24percent-on-Divestment-Profit-Jumps-Growth-Drivers-Strong/698ac263757d40c78184fe7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Nazara-Revenue-Tumbles-24percent-on-Divestment-Profit-Jumps-Growth-Drivers-Strong/698ac263757d40c78184fe7a</guid><description>Nazara Technologies reported a 24.1% year-on-year revenue drop in Q3 FY'26 to INR 406 crore, largely due to the deconsolidation of its NODWIN Esports business. However, EBITDA soared 29.4% to INR 67.8 crore, with margins expanding to 16.7% by focusing on high-margin, IP-based gaming. The nine-month period showed robust 29.7% revenue growth and a 73% EBITDA jump. Key segments posted strong gains, while Adtech shifted towards higher-margin offerings. Management eyes global expansion via scalable IP and strategic M&amp;A, supported by a strong INR 700 crore net cash position.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:30:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac263757d40c78184fe79_1770701561972.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW Steel Beats Earnings Despite January Production Dip; Sector Outlook Bright</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/JSW-Steel-Beats-Earnings-Despite-January-Production-Dip-Sector-Outlook-Bright/698ac18d757d40c78184fbf3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/JSW-Steel-Beats-Earnings-Despite-January-Production-Dip-Sector-Outlook-Bright/698ac18d757d40c78184fbf3</guid><description>JSW Steel's January crude steel production fell 2% year-on-year to 2.475 million tonnes, primarily due to planned upgrades at its Vijayanagar Blast Furnace 3 and an outage at its US operations. This operational slowdown contrasts sharply with a strong December quarter performance, where net profit significantly surpassed expectations, and consolidated sales volumes hit an all-time high. The Indian steel sector anticipates an uptrend in early 2026, bolstered by government safeguard duties and resilient domestic demand, even as global prices face pressure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:26:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac18d757d40c78184fbf2_1770701401534.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSE Earnings Shine Amid STT Hike; EMS, Textiles Sector Outlook Mixed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/BSE-Earnings-Shine-Amid-STT-Hike-EMS-Textiles-Sector-Outlook-Mixed/698ac180757d40c78184fb3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/BSE-Earnings-Shine-Amid-STT-Hike-EMS-Textiles-Sector-Outlook-Mixed/698ac180757d40c78184fb3e</guid><description>BSE reported its highest quarterly revenue, defying Securities Transaction Tax (STT) hike concerns as transaction growth and client additions bolster performance. The electronics manufacturing services (EMS) sector is poised for order inflows, driven by significant government budget allocations. Integrated textile players appear better positioned amidst rising global competition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:26:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac180757d40c78184fb3d_1770701448883.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RailTel Shares Surge 8% on ₹4,550 Crore Railway Order Bonanza</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/RailTel-Shares-Surge-8percent-on-4550-Crore-Railway-Order-Bonanza/698ac170757d40c78184fa49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/RailTel-Shares-Surge-8percent-on-4550-Crore-Railway-Order-Bonanza/698ac170757d40c78184fa49</guid><description>RailTel Corporation of India Ltd shares climbed nearly 8% Tuesday after securing a substantial ₹4,550 crore order from West Central Railway. The contract mandates execution over 960 days, concluding by September 24, 2028. This surge follows a 2.53% rise on Monday. Despite a 4% dip in net profit to ₹62.4 crore for Q3 FY26, the company reported a strong 19% revenue growth to ₹913.4 crore.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:26:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac170757d40c78184fa48_1770701319328.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Rally's Fragile Core: Markets Brace for Reality Check</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Rallys-Fragile-Core-Markets-Brace-for-Reality-Check/698ac102757d40c78184f8aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Rallys-Fragile-Core-Markets-Brace-for-Reality-Check/698ac102757d40c78184f8aa</guid><description>Global markets are showing increasing fragility, with enthusiasm for Artificial Intelligence driving rallies that may outpace underlying economic fundamentals. Analysts warn that narrative-driven momentum, exemplified by massive AI capital expenditure pledges, could face a sharp correction. While some markets, like India, show robust domestic drivers and positive analyst outlooks, the broader landscape is characterized by elevated valuations and a potential disconnect between technological promise and sustainable earnings. Investors are cautioned to be wary of prolonged speculative trends, drawing parallels to historical market exuberances that eventually succumbed to fundamental realities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:24:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac102757d40c78184f8a9_1770701216198.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Bonds Tax Rule Shift: SGBs Tumble, ETFs Emerge as New Favorite</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Bonds-Tax-Rule-Shift-SGBs-Tumble-ETFs-Emerge-as-New-Favorite/698ac0a1757d40c78184f742</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Bonds-Tax-Rule-Shift-SGBs-Tumble-ETFs-Emerge-as-New-Favorite/698ac0a1757d40c78184f742</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 has rewritten Sovereign Gold Bond (SGB) tax rules, impacting investors who buy bonds on the secondary market. Gains from these purchases will no longer be tax-exempt at maturity. This led to an immediate 8-10% drop in listed SGB prices. Experts suggest Gold ETFs and Fund of Funds may now offer a more attractive risk-return profile due to better liquidity and simpler tax treatment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:22:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac0a1757d40c78184f741_1770701097145.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>M1xchange Hits ₹1 Lakh Cr Milestone Amidst TReDS Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/M1xchange-Hits-1-Lakh-Cr-Milestone-Amidst-TReDS-Boom/698ac088757d40c78184f619</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/M1xchange-Hits-1-Lakh-Cr-Milestone-Amidst-TReDS-Boom/698ac088757d40c78184f619</guid><description>M1xchange achieved a record ₹1 lakh crore in transaction throughput within 10 months of FY2025-26, becoming the first Trade Receivables Discounting System (TReDS) platform to hit this mark in a single financial year. This milestone underscores the rapid growth in digital invoice discounting, fueled by robust MSME adoption and supportive government initiatives. Over 70,000 MSMEs and 5,000 corporate buyers engage on the platform, facilitated by over 70 banks and NBFCs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:22:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac088757d40c78184f618_1770701082330.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks Rise on FIIs &amp; Capex; IT Sector Faces AI Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Stocks-Rise-on-FIIs-and-Capex-IT-Sector-Faces-AI-Headwinds/698ac00f757d40c78184f477</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Stocks-Rise-on-FIIs-and-Capex-IT-Sector-Faces-AI-Headwinds/698ac00f757d40c78184f477</guid><description>Indian stock markets extended their gains for a second day, driven by returning foreign institutional investors (FIIs) and robust private capital expenditure (capex) growth. While financials show promise, the IT sector is under pressure from AI advancements, and small-cap stocks face risks despite recent corrections. FIIs injected approximately ₹4,900.17 crore month-to-date, buoyed by a recent India-US trade deal. Private sector capex plans surged 41% in H1 FY26, signaling a strengthening investment cycle. However, the IT industry confronts significant headwinds from AI automation tools, leading to sharp stock declines and market value erosion. Small-cap indices have seen a notable downturn in 2025, with analysts cautioning against stretched valuations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:20:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ac00f757d40c78184f476_1770700967582.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Faces US OFAC Probe Over Iran-Linked Transactions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Adani-Enterprises-Faces-US-OFAC-Probe-Over-Iran-Linked-Transactions/698abfa4757d40c78184f2d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Adani-Enterprises-Faces-US-OFAC-Probe-Over-Iran-Linked-Transactions/698abfa4757d40c78184f2d2</guid><description>Adani Enterprises Limited (AEL) is proactively engaging with the U.S. Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) regarding allegations of transactions possibly involving Iran. AEL received a Request for Information (RFI) from OFAC as part of a civil investigation. The company stated that the LPG segment, implicated in the allegations, constituted a minor 1.46% of its FY24-25 revenue and has ceased all LPG imports out of caution. AEL asserts no financial implications are expected and is fully cooperating.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:18:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698abfa4757d40c78184f2d1_1770700873933.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KPI Green Energy Wins Rs 300MW Adani Order for Khavda Renewable Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Wins-Rs-300MW-Adani-Order-for-Khavda-Renewable-Project/698abf90757d40c78184f1ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Wins-Rs-300MW-Adani-Order-for-Khavda-Renewable-Project/698abf90757d40c78184f1ec</guid><description>KPI Green Energy Limited announced securing new orders worth 300 MWac from Adani Group entities for the Khavda Hybrid Renewable Power Project in Gujarat. This win boosts KPI's cumulative order book from Adani for Khavda to 834 MWac. The company views this as validation of its execution capabilities for large-scale renewable projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:18:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698abf90757d40c78184f1eb_1770700865452.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Tech's WATTSync Meets India's Battery ID Rules, Global Standards</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tata-Techs-WATTSync-Meets-Indias-Battery-ID-Rules-Global-Standards/698abf18757d40c78184f05a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tata-Techs-WATTSync-Meets-Indias-Battery-ID-Rules-Global-Standards/698abf18757d40c78184f05a</guid><description>Tata Technologies' WATTSync platform is now fully equipped to meet India's upcoming Battery Aadhaar digital identity and traceability mandates for electric vehicle (EV) batteries. The system also aligns with global standards like the EU Battery Regulation, enabling seamless generation of India's 21-character Battery Pack Aadhaar Number (BPAN). This positions Tata Technologies as a key partner in developing trusted, sustainable, and future-ready battery ecosystems through enhanced lifecycle traceability and circular economy enablement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:16:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698abf18757d40c78184f059_1770700710936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Life Insurers: Growth Slows, LIC Gains Share Amid Mixed Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indian-Life-Insurers-Growth-Slows-LIC-Gains-Share-Amid-Mixed-Outlook/698abea1757d40c78184eead</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indian-Life-Insurers-Growth-Slows-LIC-Gains-Share-Amid-Mixed-Outlook/698abea1757d40c78184eead</guid><description>India's life insurance sector experienced a 9% YoY retail APE growth moderation in January 2026. Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) outperformed private insurers, achieving 15% growth aided by a low base, while private players managed only 7% growth. Despite this, robust group business contributed to a 13% overall industry APE increase. LIC's retail APE share expanded to 29.4%. Key private players showed divergent trends, with Axis Max Life surging 29%, SBI Life growing 4%, and HDFC Life declining 7%. Analysts anticipate continued FY26 growth of 10-11% for the industry, with private insurers projected to lead. Margin sustainability and competitive pressures remain key monitoring points for the sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:14:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698abea1757d40c78184eeac_1770700593971.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>