<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:55:51 +0000</pubDate><item><title>HFIL Resolves Bank Debt, Eyes Growth as Tariffs Ease</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/HFIL-Resolves-Bank-Debt-Eyes-Growth-as-Tariffs-Ease/69929fde2e6a0b8ae17c9487</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/HFIL-Resolves-Bank-Debt-Eyes-Growth-as-Tariffs-Ease/69929fde2e6a0b8ae17c9487</guid><description>Himalaya Food International's Q3 FY26 results were impacted by US tariffs, though YoY performance saw an improvement. The company successfully extended its One-Time Settlement (OTS) for ₹43 Crores of debt, depositing ₹21.5 Crores. Strategies to boost liquidity include asset sales and attracting strategic investors, anticipating future tariff reductions to revive its order book and drive growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:41:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69929fde2e6a0b8ae17c9486_1771217004668.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pennar Industries Sees Strong Growth Fueled by Acquisitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pennar-Industries-Sees-Strong-Growth-Fueled-by-Acquisitions/69929f662e6a0b8ae17c9432</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pennar-Industries-Sees-Strong-Growth-Fueled-by-Acquisitions/69929f662e6a0b8ae17c9432</guid><description>Pennar Industries has posted a solid Q3 FY26 with revenue up 13.30% year-on-year to ₹959 crore. Profit after tax rose 10.14% to ₹33.55 crore. This growth is driven by the acquisition of Ascent Structural assets and strong performance in its Structural Engineering division. The company also saw a 16.74% revenue jump for the first nine months of FY26. While debt levels remain significant, operating cash flow has improved.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:39:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69929f662e6a0b8ae17c9431_1771216881324.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SRM Contractors Posts 53% Revenue Jump on Strong Q3, Eyes Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SRM-Contractors-Posts-53percent-Revenue-Jump-on-Strong-Q3-Eyes-Expansion/69929e792e6a0b8ae17c939b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SRM-Contractors-Posts-53percent-Revenue-Jump-on-Strong-Q3-Eyes-Expansion/69929e792e6a0b8ae17c939b</guid><description>SRM Contractors reported a robust Q3 FY26, with revenue soaring 53.69% year-on-year to ₹231.21 Cr. Profit after tax grew 50% to ₹24 Cr. The company also announced the acquisition of a 51% stake in Maccaferri Infrastructure and provided positive guidance for FY26, expecting revenue between ₹800-900 Cr.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:35:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69929e792e6a0b8ae17c939a_1771216616566.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>R M Drip Enters Smart Irrigation, Eyes Tech-Led Growth &amp; Recurring Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/R-M-Drip-Enters-Smart-Irrigation-Eyes-Tech-Led-Growth-and-Recurring-Revenue/69929e1a2e6a0b8ae17c9334</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/R-M-Drip-Enters-Smart-Irrigation-Eyes-Tech-Led-Growth-and-Recurring-Revenue/69929e1a2e6a0b8ae17c9334</guid><description>R M Drip &amp; Sprinklers Systems Limited is making a significant strategic move into the smart irrigation automation segment through a technology partnership. This pivot aims to transform the company's business model from hardware-centric to an integrated hardware and software platform, unlocking new revenue streams from mobile apps, analytics, and subscriptions. The company expects this new segment to contribute around 5% of revenue by FY27 and grow rapidly thereafter, leveraging government initiatives and its extensive dealer network. This move is projected to enhance long-term revenue visibility, improve margins, and boost scalability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:33:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69929e1a2e6a0b8ae17c9333_1771216493409.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric's Margin Surge Masks Revenue Plunge Amid Fierce EV Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-Margin-Surge-Masks-Revenue-Plunge-Amid-Fierce-EV-Race/69929d0f2e6a0b8ae17c922d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-Margin-Surge-Masks-Revenue-Plunge-Amid-Fierce-EV-Race/69929d0f2e6a0b8ae17c922d</guid><description>Ola Electric Mobility Ltd. saw its valuation plummet by nearly 7% following a stark 55% year-on-year revenue decline in Q3 FY26. The electric vehicle maker reported a consolidated net loss of ₹487 crore, down from ₹564 crore a year prior, with scooter sales falling to 32,680 units from 84,029. Despite the operational downturn, Ola Electric announced a record consolidated gross margin of 34.3%, a significant 15.7 percentage point increase year-on-year, attributed to a 'structural reset' and cost-cutting measures. However, analysts like Emkay Global Financial Services have downgraded the stock to 'Sell', slashing its target price to ₹20 and warning of prolonged turnaround challenges and survival risks amid intensifying competition from players like Ather Energy. The company's current market capitalization stands at ₹13,519.00 crore.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:29:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69929d0f2e6a0b8ae17c922c_1771216315444.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GMR Airports: Profitability Surge Amidst Growth Pains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/GMR-Airports-Profitability-Surge-Amidst-Growth-Pains/69929cb42e6a0b8ae17c9165</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/GMR-Airports-Profitability-Surge-Amidst-Growth-Pains/69929cb42e6a0b8ae17c9165</guid><description>GMR Airports surged on robust Q3 EBITDA growth driven by tariff resets and non-aero revenue expansion. Despite turning operationally profitable, net profit declined YoY due to one-time expenses. Analysts maintain a strong buy consensus with upward price targets, yet the stock exhibits bearish technical signals and faces structural concerns regarding its balance sheet and competitive positioning.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:27:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69929cb42e6a0b8ae17c9164_1771216186468.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lupin's Q3 Surge Faces Analyst Skepticism Amidst Future Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupins-Q3-Surge-Faces-Analyst-Skepticism-Amidst-Future-Risks/69929ca62e6a0b8ae17c9149</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupins-Q3-Surge-Faces-Analyst-Skepticism-Amidst-Future-Risks/69929ca62e6a0b8ae17c9149</guid><description>Lupin's Q3 FY26 earnings showcased a significant 37% year-over-year profit jump to ₹1,175.5 crore and revenue growth to ₹7,167.52 crore, driven by a record $350 million in US sales and a decade-high Ebitda margin. Despite this performance, analyst sentiment remains divided. While some see a 'Neutral' outlook with price targets around ₹2,360, others maintain a 'Reduce' rating with a target of ₹2,037, citing risks from potential product revenue loss and long commercialization timelines for complex assets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:27:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69929ca62e6a0b8ae17c9148_1771216153804.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Jet Healthcare Downgraded: Execution Woes Spark Valuation Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Downgraded-Execution-Woes-Spark-Valuation-Fears/69929c9a2e6a0b8ae17c9132</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Downgraded-Execution-Woes-Spark-Valuation-Fears/69929c9a2e6a0b8ae17c9132</guid><description>Blue Jet Healthcare shares plummeted Monday following a downgrade by JPMorgan, which cited weak execution in contrast media and API segments, alongside competitive threats and a stalled pipeline. The brokerage slashed earnings estimates and its target multiple, reflecting concerns over high product concentration and shifting client dynamics. Despite a recent profit surge in the December quarter, revenue declined, and margins compressed significantly.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:27:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69929c9a2e6a0b8ae17c9131_1771216167712.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lenskart's AI Engine Fuels Growth, But Valuation Scrutiny Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskarts-AI-Engine-Fuels-Growth-But-Valuation-Scrutiny-Mounts/69929bbf2e6a0b8ae17c8faa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskarts-AI-Engine-Fuels-Growth-But-Valuation-Scrutiny-Mounts/69929bbf2e6a0b8ae17c8faa</guid><description>Lenskart reported a substantial surge in Q3 FY26 earnings, with net profit jumping over 70 times year-on-year to ₹131 crore and revenue climbing 38.3% to ₹2,307.7 crore. This performance is largely attributed to the company's deep integration of artificial intelligence across its operations, from store analytics and location intelligence to logistics and customer service. The AI-first strategy, bolstered by advancements in generative AI, has enabled significant operating leverage, allowing for a doubling of store openings year-over-year without a commensurate rise in costs. The company's aggressive expansion, with 41% of new stores in Tier 2 and beyond, further solidifies its market position. Lenskart's stock has reacted positively, trading at approximately $5.12 with a market cap of $8.85 billion as of February 9, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:23:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69929bbf2e6a0b8ae17c8fa9_1771215963509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai Metro Car Depot Land Dispute Resolved</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbai-Metro-Car-Depot-Land-Dispute-Resolved/69929bb42e6a0b8ae17c8f93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbai-Metro-Car-Depot-Land-Dispute-Resolved/69929bb42e6a0b8ae17c8f93</guid><description>The Bombay High Court has dismissed challenges to the Kanjurmarg land handover for the Mumbai Metro Line 6 car depot. This action vacates interim orders, enabling the ₹6,716 crore project to advance after prolonged legal battles. The court affirmed the petitioner lacked standing post-lease termination. The project, vital for decongesting Mumbai, is nearing completion stages, with significant funds already invested, targeting a December 2026 launch. This resolves a key hurdle for critical urban infrastructure development.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:23:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69929bb42e6a0b8ae17c8f92.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Luggage Firm VIP Industries Downgraded Amidst Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Luggage-Firm-VIP-Industries-Downgraded-Amidst-Margin-Squeeze/69929ba72e6a0b8ae17c8f79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Luggage-Firm-VIP-Industries-Downgraded-Amidst-Margin-Squeeze/69929ba72e6a0b8ae17c8f79</guid><description>Prabhudas Lilladher downgraded VIP Industries to 'Reduce' with a ₹352 target, citing a 9.4% revenue decline and 29.5% gross margin due to inventory provisions. Persistent competitive pressures, a high 40x FY28E earnings multiple, and already-priced-in turnaround benefits drive the downgrade. Significant EPS estimate cuts for FY27/FY28 underscore the challenges ahead.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:23:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69929ba72e6a0b8ae17c8f78_1771215914696.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Unlocks M&amp;A Finance, Boosts Retail Credit Amidst Risk Controls</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Unlocks-MandA-Finance-Boosts-Retail-Credit-Amidst-Risk-Controls/69929a5a2e6a0b8ae17c8e82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Unlocks-MandA-Finance-Boosts-Retail-Credit-Amidst-Risk-Controls/69929a5a2e6a0b8ae17c8e82</guid><description>Effective April 1, 2026, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has finalized new capital market exposure guidelines, empowering banks to finance up to 75% of corporate acquisition costs and significantly increasing individual lending limits against securities. These measures aim to invigorate M&amp;A activity and market liquidity. However, stringent eligibility criteria for borrowers, capped debt-to-equity ratios, and a strict 40% overall capital market exposure limit for banks are in place to mitigate systemic risk. The changes represent a strategic shift towards facilitating growth alongside enhanced prudential oversight.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:17:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69929a5a2e6a0b8ae17c8e81_1771215594560.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Collateral Overhaul Reshapes Broker &amp; Exchange Economics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Collateral-Overhaul-Reshapes-Broker-and-Exchange-Economics/699298622e6a0b8ae17c8d94</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Collateral-Overhaul-Reshapes-Broker-and-Exchange-Economics/699298622e6a0b8ae17c8d94</guid><description>Effective April 1, 2026, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has mandated a 'full collateral' rule for banks financing capital market intermediaries, significantly increasing liquidity requirements for brokers. The RBI has also barred banks from financing proprietary trading desks, a move expected to curb market turnover. While banks face limited impact due to low capital market exposure, brokerage firms like Angel One, Motilal Oswal, and Groww, along with exchanges such as BSE and MCX, are poised for substantial operational and revenue adjustments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:09:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699298622e6a0b8ae17c8d93_1771215085882.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Astra Microwave's Margin Boost: Orders Up, But Valuation Concerns Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Astra-Microwaves-Margin-Boost-Orders-Up-But-Valuation-Concerns-Linger/699297762e6a0b8ae17c8cf9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Astra-Microwaves-Margin-Boost-Orders-Up-But-Valuation-Concerns-Linger/699297762e6a0b8ae17c8cf9</guid><description>Astra Microwave Products (ASTRAMICRO) has demonstrated robust EBITDA growth in Q3 FY26, driven by expanded margins to 31.7% despite flat year-on-year revenue growth. The company maintains its revenue guidance for FY26 and anticipates strong order inflows for FY27, supporting near-term visibility. However, the stock's current valuation, trading at approximately 29 times its fiscal 2028 estimated earnings, presents a point of concern for investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:05:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699297762e6a0b8ae17c8cf8_1771214847018.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Shares Tumble on Brutal Q3 Results, Analyst Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Shares-Tumble-on-Brutal-Q3-Results-Analyst-Sell-Off/699295282e6a0b8ae17c8c17</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Shares-Tumble-on-Brutal-Q3-Results-Analyst-Sell-Off/699295282e6a0b8ae17c8c17</guid><description>Ola Electric Mobility Ltd. shares plunged Monday, February 16, following a stark Q3 FY26 earnings report marked by a 55% year-over-year revenue drop and a 38% sequential decline in volumes. Brokerage Emkay Global slashed its rating to 'Sell' and price target by 60% to ₹20, citing significant market share erosion and increasing debt. While gross margins improved, the company's financial performance contrasts sharply with booming growth from competitors like Ather Energy, TVS Motor, and Bajaj Auto.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:55:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699295282e6a0b8ae17c8c16_1771214272053.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Risk-Based Insurance Premiums to Reshape Indian Banking</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Risk-Based-Insurance-Premiums-to-Reshape-Indian-Banking/6992942e2e6a0b8ae17c8a7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Risk-Based-Insurance-Premiums-to-Reshape-Indian-Banking/6992942e2e6a0b8ae17c8a7d</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) will implement a risk-based pricing framework for deposit insurance premiums starting April 1, 2026. This significant shift replaces the long-standing flat rate, meaning banks with stronger financial health and better risk management will pay lower premiums, while riskier institutions will face increased costs. The move aims to foster greater financial discipline, enhance the resilience of the deposit insurance fund, and recalibrate competitive dynamics across the Indian banking sector. Depositor protection limits remain unchanged.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:51:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992942e2e6a0b8ae17c8a7c_1771214013282.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Azad Engineering Sees BUY Upgrade Amid INR 65 Bn Order Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Azad-Engineering-Sees-BUY-Upgrade-Amid-INR-65-Bn-Order-Surge/6992942b2e6a0b8ae17c8a66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Azad-Engineering-Sees-BUY-Upgrade-Amid-INR-65-Bn-Order-Surge/6992942b2e6a0b8ae17c8a66</guid><description>Azad Engineering secured a BUY rating with a INR 1,900 target price from Choice Institutional Equities, fueled by a substantial INR 65 billion order book. The company is expanding its global OEM relationships in aerospace and turbines, expecting volume-driven earnings leverage by FY28. However, analysts noted moderated near-term growth expectations, prompting a valuation multiple adjustment. Its strong export orientation and benefits from geopolitical trade shifts are key advantages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:51:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992942b2e6a0b8ae17c8a65_1771213993252.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Astra Microwave: Order Surge vs. Flat Sales &amp; Execution Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astra-Microwave-Order-Surge-vs-Flat-Sales-and-Execution-Risks/699294292e6a0b8ae17c8a4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astra-Microwave-Order-Surge-vs-Flat-Sales-and-Execution-Risks/699294292e6a0b8ae17c8a4f</guid><description>Astra Microwave Products Ltd. posted robust Q3 FY26 EBITDA growth and maintained revenue guidance, underpinned by a strong order book projected to yield ₹550-600 crore in Q4 FY26. However, flat year-on-year revenue growth and a recent technical downgrade to "Sell" by MarketsMOJO, coupled with a P/E near 54x trailing earnings, highlight execution risks and potentially stretched valuations. The company's strategic push into new defense technologies faces scrutiny against a backdrop of sector-wide opportunities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699294292e6a0b8ae17c8a4e_1771214023904.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Private Capital Revival for Highway Projects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Eyes-Private-Capital-Revival-for-Highway-Projects/699293bb2e6a0b8ae17c897b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Eyes-Private-Capital-Revival-for-Highway-Projects/699293bb2e6a0b8ae17c897b</guid><description>India is renewing efforts to attract private investment into its highway construction sector, a market that saw investors retreat over a decade ago due to revenue risks and bureaucratic delays. New rules are being finalized to offer developers revenue protection and directly invite global funds. The government aims to award projects worth 1 trillion rupees ($11 billion) by fiscal year 2027 and increase private capital's share to 25% of development next year, up from current low single digits. This initiative is part of a broader strategy to boost corporate participation in infrastructure, modernize logistics, and enhance national competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:49:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699293bb2e6a0b8ae17c897a_1771213897017.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW MG Motor Invests $440M Amidst Profit Woes and EV Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-MG-Motor-Invests-440M-Amidst-Profit-Woes-and-EV-Race/699293b62e6a0b8ae17c8964</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-MG-Motor-Invests-440M-Amidst-Profit-Woes-and-EV-Race/699293b62e6a0b8ae17c8964</guid><description>JSW MG Motor plans a significant $440 million investment to expand its Indian manufacturing capacity and pivot its product lineup heavily towards hybrid and electric vehicles. This strategic move aims to boost annual plant capacity to 300,000 units and introduce three to four new models this year. However, the initiative is undertaken against a backdrop of doubled losses in FY2025, reaching $121 million, and a competitive Indian automotive market increasingly focused on new energy vehicles.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:49:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699293b62e6a0b8ae17c8963_1771213903224.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Summit Signals Global South Power Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Summit-Signals-Global-South-Power-Shift/699292c72e6a0b8ae17c883d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Summit-Signals-Global-South-Power-Shift/699292c72e6a0b8ae17c883d</guid><description>The India AI Impact Summit 2026 has commenced, marking a significant push for the Global South in the AI arena. Hosting world leaders and tech titans, the event focuses on AI's role in governance and sustainable development. The summit aims to shape global policy, foster innovation, and accelerate AI adoption across vital sectors, potentially redefining the future investment landscape for artificial intelligence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:45:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699292c72e6a0b8ae17c883c_1771213665582.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Keystone Realtors Wins Rs 1,775 Cr Mumbai Redevelopment Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Keystone-Realtors-Wins-Rs-1775-Cr-Mumbai-Redevelopment-Project/699292c02e6a0b8ae17c8823</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Keystone-Realtors-Wins-Rs-1775-Cr-Mumbai-Redevelopment-Project/699292c02e6a0b8ae17c8823</guid><description>Keystone Realtors Limited, through its Rustomjee Group brand, has been appointed as the developer for a large society redevelopment project in Andheri (East), Mumbai. The project, involving eight housing societies, has an estimated Gross Development Value (GDV) of approximately Rs. 1,775 Crores and spans over 20,500 sq meters, promising significant free sale potential.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699292c02e6a0b8ae17c8822_1771213611118.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>du Bets on SING Cable for Regional Digital Sovereignty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/du-Bets-on-SING-Cable-for-Regional-Digital-Sovereignty/699291d12e6a0b8ae17c8743</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/du-Bets-on-SING-Cable-for-Regional-Digital-Sovereignty/699291d12e6a0b8ae17c8743</guid><description>Emirates Integrated Telecommunications Company (du) is making a significant investment to land and operate the Singapore-India-Gulf (SING) subsea cable system, connecting the UAE to key Asian markets. This initiative is designed to bolster the UAE's position as a global data hub and enhance digital infrastructure resilience. With an expected capacity of tens of terabits per second and a target service date of 2030, the SING cable aims to provide low-latency, high-capacity connectivity, crucial for emerging AI workloads and cloud services, while crucially diversifying data routes away from vulnerable traditional paths.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:41:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699291d12e6a0b8ae17c8742_1771213459221.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EaseMyTrip Plans Big Capital Raise for Growth &amp; Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/EaseMyTrip-Plans-Big-Capital-Raise-for-Growth-and-Expansion/6992906a2e6a0b8ae17c869e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/EaseMyTrip-Plans-Big-Capital-Raise-for-Growth-and-Expansion/6992906a2e6a0b8ae17c869e</guid><description>Online travel company EaseMyTrip is looking to raise up to ₹500 crore through equity shares and other securities. The funds are earmarked for strengthening its core business, expanding into high-potential segments like hotels and holidays, and investing in technology. The company aims to build an integrated travel ecosystem and focus on sustainable growth and value creation for shareholders.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:35:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992906a2e6a0b8ae17c869d_1771213086652.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Apple Tariffs: Safeguard Efficacy Under Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Apple-Tariffs-Safeguard-Efficacy-Under-Scrutiny/69928d9f2e6a0b8ae17c85b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Apple-Tariffs-Safeguard-Efficacy-Under-Scrutiny/69928d9f2e6a0b8ae17c85b0</guid><description>India's apple import duties have been lowered, sparking fears among domestic growers in Jammu &amp; Kashmir and Himachal Pradesh about price erosion and competition from subsidized foreign fruit. While the government has implemented a Minimum Import Price (MIP) and quotas, the effectiveness of these safeguards and transparency in their enforcement are now the critical factors determining market impact. This situation highlights ongoing tensions between agricultural trade liberalization and the imperative to protect local farmer livelihoods and the broader Indian agri-sector's economic stability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:23:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69928d9f2e6a0b8ae17c85af_1771212315897.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Whirlpool India Gains Share Amidst Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Whirlpool-India-Gains-Share-Amidst-Risks/69928ca92e6a0b8ae17c84c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Whirlpool-India-Gains-Share-Amidst-Risks/69928ca92e6a0b8ae17c84c8</guid><description>Whirlpool of India navigated a challenging demand environment in Q3 FY26, posting a 4% revenue increase driven by market share gains in washing machines and cost efficiencies. However, this performance occurs against a backdrop of significant uncertainty, marked by the parent company's ongoing stake reduction, persistent currency depreciation risks impacting input costs, and strategic divergence from competitors like LG Electronics. While operational metrics improved, reported profits were impacted by one-off provisions, and investor sentiment remains cautious due to the overhang from the promoter's divestment plans and a failed private equity sale.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:19:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69928ca92e6a0b8ae17c84c7_1771212158153.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Desco Infratech Secures ₹40 Cr Orders, Expands Into Power &amp; Renewables</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Desco-Infratech-Secures-40-Cr-Orders-Expands-Into-Power-and-Renewables/69928c302e6a0b8ae17c8468</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Desco-Infratech-Secures-40-Cr-Orders-Expands-Into-Power-and-Renewables/69928c302e6a0b8ae17c8468</guid><description>Desco Infratech Limited has secured two significant purchase orders totalling ₹40.43 crore from KP Group entities, Sun Drops Energia Limited and KP Energy Limited. These orders for solar and power infrastructure signify a strategic move by Desco Infratech to diversify its business beyond City Gas Distribution (CGD) and strengthen its presence in the burgeoning renewable energy sector, leveraging its existing execution expertise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69928c302e6a0b8ae17c8467_1771211997318.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Logistics &amp; FMCG: Delhivery, Britannia in Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Logistics-and-FMCG-Delhivery-Britannia-in-Focus/69928a542e6a0b8ae17c8398</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Logistics-and-FMCG-Delhivery-Britannia-in-Focus/69928a542e6a0b8ae17c8398</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services has identified Delhivery and Britannia Industries as prime stock picks for the trading week commencing February 16, 2026. The brokerage anticipates significant upside potential, projecting a 36% rise for Delhivery to ₹570 and a 20% increase for Britannia Industries to ₹7150. These recommendations are underpinned by strategic initiatives and robust financial performances reported in the third quarter of fiscal year 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:09:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69928a542e6a0b8ae17c8397_1771211474044.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's SIFs: Sebi's Calculated Play on Investor Sophistication</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-SIFs-Sebis-Calculated-Play-on-Investor-Sophistication/699286e42e6a0b8ae17c81de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-SIFs-Sebis-Calculated-Play-on-Investor-Sophistication/699286e42e6a0b8ae17c81de</guid><description>The Indian Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has launched Specialized Investment Funds (SIFs), a new category designed to offer sophisticated investors greater portfolio flexibility than traditional mutual funds. With a minimum investment of ₹10 lakh, SIFs allow for strategies like unhedged shorting, a significant departure from standard schemes. Critically, SEBI's framework prioritizes distributor competency through mandatory derivatives certification, signaling a move toward market integrity over rapid asset growth. Early data confirms a nascent market, underscoring SEBI's cautious, calibrated approach to introducing complex investment vehicles.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:54:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699286e42e6a0b8ae17c81dd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC Demands Overhaul as Digital Fraud Hits ₹52K Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SC-Demands-Overhaul-as-Digital-Fraud-Hits-52K-Cr/699286992e6a0b8ae17c8162</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SC-Demands-Overhaul-as-Digital-Fraud-Hits-52K-Cr/699286992e6a0b8ae17c8162</guid><description>India's digital fraud epidemic has prompted an unprecedented Supreme Court warning, with over ₹52,000 crore lost to scams between April 2021 and November 2025. The apex court has mandated the RBI and MHA to implement robust, technology-driven solutions within a month, highlighting fragmented enforcement and insufficient bank monitoring as critical failures. This intervention signals a shift towards greater accountability for financial institutions and emphasizes the urgent need for advanced AI-driven fraud detection and enhanced inter-agency coordination to protect the nation's rapidly expanding digital economy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:53:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699286992e6a0b8ae17c8161_1771210592979.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Road Neglect: Fatalities Rise Amidst Infrastructure Spending Myopia</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Road-Neglect-Fatalities-Rise-Amidst-Infrastructure-Spending-Myopia/699286932e6a0b8ae17c814a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Road-Neglect-Fatalities-Rise-Amidst-Infrastructure-Spending-Myopia/699286932e6a0b8ae17c814a</guid><description>India is grappling with a dramatic surge in pothole-related road fatalities, which climbed by over 53% between 2020 and 2024, claiming 9,438 lives. This crisis is exacerbated by a systemic policy imbalance that prioritizes expansive new highway construction over essential maintenance, leading to a substantial economic drain estimated at 3-5% of GDP annually due to road crashes and traffic congestion. Despite significant capital expenditure on new projects, dedicated funding for road upkeep remains critically low, creating a dangerous deficit in asset preservation and long-term national competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:53:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699286932e6a0b8ae17c8149_1771210521520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Navigate Data-Driven Volatility Amid Mixed Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Navigate-Data-Driven-Volatility-Amid-Mixed-Outlook/699286302e6a0b8ae17c80c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Navigate-Data-Driven-Volatility-Amid-Mixed-Outlook/699286302e6a0b8ae17c80c4</guid><description>Gold prices saw a marginal dip while silver experienced significant volatility on Monday, February 16, 2026. Investors are consolidating recent gains as key US economic data, including Q4 GDP and PCE inflation, are scrutinized for Federal Reserve policy direction. While gold benefits from safe-haven demand and strong central bank accumulation, silver's dual role as an industrial and precious metal exposes it to sector-specific pressures and risks of price-driven substitution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:51:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699286302e6a0b8ae17c80c3_1771210558385.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Banks Face Funding Squeeze as Credit Outpaces Deposits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Face-Funding-Squeeze-as-Credit-Outpaces-Deposits/699282d92e6a0b8ae17c7e77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Face-Funding-Squeeze-as-Credit-Outpaces-Deposits/699282d92e6a0b8ae17c7e77</guid><description>Indian banks are experiencing a significant tightening of liquidity as credit growth consistently outpaces deposit mobilization, pushing incremental credit-deposit ratios to historic highs. This trend, particularly evident by January-end 2026, forces lenders to rely more on costlier wholesale funding and household savings. While loan demand remains strong, this imbalance poses risks of margin compression and sustainability challenges for rapid credit expansion, as seen in increased Certificate of Deposit rates and cautious analyst outlooks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:37:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699282d92e6a0b8ae17c7e76_1771209578700.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Tariff Cuts Clouded by Costly Energy Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariff-Cuts-Clouded-by-Costly-Energy-Pivot/699282d52e6a0b8ae17c7e60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariff-Cuts-Clouded-by-Costly-Energy-Pivot/699282d52e6a0b8ae17c7e60</guid><description>The United States has significantly reduced tariffs on Indian goods, lowering the base rate from 50% to 18%. However, this trade agreement is overshadowed by critical ambiguities regarding India's energy security. New Delhi has not definitively committed to halting Russian oil imports, prioritizing affordable energy despite US pressure and the potentially high costs associated with sourcing alternatives like US and Venezuelan crude. This energy dilemma introduces substantial risk, complicating the net benefit of the tariff relief.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:37:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699282d52e6a0b8ae17c7e5f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India PE Buys Control, Faces Exit Market Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-PE-Buys-Control-Faces-Exit-Market-Headwinds/699282ce2e6a0b8ae17c7e46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-PE-Buys-Control-Faces-Exit-Market-Headwinds/699282ce2e6a0b8ae17c7e46</guid><description>The private equity landscape in India is undergoing a significant transformation, with investors increasingly prioritizing majority and controlling stakes, a shift away from traditional minority investments. This 'buyout' strategy is being propelled by substantial foreign capital and a notable evolution in founder attitudes. However, this aggressive pursuit of control comes with heightened operational risks and faces headwinds from a competitive exit environment, primarily driven by strong public market performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:37:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699282ce2e6a0b8ae17c7e45_1771209594008.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Bank, Max Health: Technical Rallies Face Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/ICICI-Bank-Max-Health-Technical-Rallies-Face-Valuation-Scrutiny/69927f1d2e6a0b8ae17c7c74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/ICICI-Bank-Max-Health-Technical-Rallies-Face-Valuation-Scrutiny/69927f1d2e6a0b8ae17c7c74</guid><description>ICICI Bank and Max Health are exhibiting bullish technical patterns, prompting buy recommendations. However, a deeper analysis reveals differing risk profiles. ICICI Bank trades at a relatively standard valuation for its segment, supported by analyst optimism. Max Health, on the other hand, presents a higher valuation hurdle, suggesting its technical ascent may be vulnerable to broader market sentiment and sector-specific headwinds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:21:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69927f1d2e6a0b8ae17c7c73_1771208597687.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indus Towers: Catalysts Shine, But Vi's Shadow Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Indus-Towers-Catalysts-Shine-But-Vis-Shadow-Looms/69927f152e6a0b8ae17c7c59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Indus-Towers-Catalysts-Shine-But-Vis-Shadow-Looms/69927f152e6a0b8ae17c7c59</guid><description>Indus Towers remains a focus for analysts, with Citi maintaining a 'Buy' and ₹540 price target, citing key catalysts like Vodafone Idea's debt closure and AGR reassessment. However, the stock's performance is intrinsically tied to Vi's uncertain financial recovery, a fact underscored by mixed analyst sentiment and recent price target divergences. Bharti Airtel's continued stake-building offers support, but the broader sector outlook, while growing, faces complexities from tenant financial health.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:21:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69927f152e6a0b8ae17c7c58_1771208608356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Gems &amp; Jewellery Exports Stabilize Amidst US Slump, Diversification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Gems-and-Jewellery-Exports-Stabilize-Amidst-US-Slump-Diversification/69927ead2e6a0b8ae17c7bb1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Gems-and-Jewellery-Exports-Stabilize-Amidst-US-Slump-Diversification/69927ead2e6a0b8ae17c7bb1</guid><description>India's gem and jewellery exports held steady at $23.19 billion for April-January 2025-26, a slight 0.64% dip in dollar terms. This stability masks a significant 45% collapse in shipments to the crucial US market, countered by robust growth in UAE (+23.7%), Hong Kong (+33.5%), and Australia/France (+36% each). While diamonds face pressure from lab-grown competition and weakened demand, jewellery segments, particularly silver and gold, demonstrate resilience. The proposed India-US trade framework offers a potential pathway to recovery.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:19:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69927ead2e6a0b8ae17c7bb0_1771208505244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs Spotlights Diverse Growth Bets Amid Market Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Goldman-Sachs-Spotlights-Diverse-Growth-Bets-Amid-Market-Shifts/69927ea22e6a0b8ae17c7b9a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Goldman-Sachs-Spotlights-Diverse-Growth-Bets-Amid-Market-Shifts/69927ea22e6a0b8ae17c7b9a</guid><description>Goldman Sachs has presented a high-conviction list of stocks, signaling a strategic blend of high-growth technology and more stable sectors. The firm's analysis highlights companies poised for share price appreciation, suggesting a carefully constructed portfolio designed to navigate a complex market environment characterized by technological disruption and evolving economic conditions. This selection includes semiconductor giant Nvidia, pharmaceutical firm Teva Pharmaceutical Industries, consumer staple Philip Morris International, financial intelligence provider S&amp;P Global, and alternative asset manager Apollo Global Management, indicating a broad-based confidence across diverse market segments. The rationale appears to center on companies with robust earnings outlooks and strong market positioning, capable of delivering value irrespective of broader macroeconomic headwinds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:19:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69927ea22e6a0b8ae17c7b99_1771208475594.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashoka Buildcon: Global Projects Boost Profit, Debt Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ashoka-Buildcon-Global-Projects-Boost-Profit-Debt-Looms/69927d312e6a0b8ae17c7a55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ashoka-Buildcon-Global-Projects-Boost-Profit-Debt-Looms/69927d312e6a0b8ae17c7a55</guid><description>Ashoka Buildcon secured substantial infrastructure projects in Liberia, India, and Saudi Arabia, valued at over $95 million equivalent from international contracts alone. These wins follow a remarkable 222.6% surge in quarterly net profit to Rs 2,111.41 crore. The company's expanding global footprint and robust order book signal growth potential, yet its high debt levels and the complexities of executing in new international markets present significant challenges for sustained profitability and investor returns.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:13:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69927d312e6a0b8ae17c7a54_1771208191391.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>