<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:43:38 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Remsons' Order Boom Meets Market Skepticism Amid Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Remsons-Order-Boom-Meets-Market-Skepticism-Amid-Expansion/698d9e37211323ff9f630999</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Remsons-Order-Boom-Meets-Market-Skepticism-Amid-Expansion/698d9e37211323ff9f630999</guid><description>Remsons Industries reported a 25% net profit increase for the December quarter, bolstered by significant order wins totaling over ₹360 crore from Stellantis and a leading commercial vehicle OEM, alongside new manufacturing capacity. Despite these achievements, the company's stock dipped 2% on February 12, 2026, reflecting market apprehension about execution risks and broader sector challenges. Remsons faces a P/E valuation that appears attractive relative to peers, yet its stock has underperformed the industry over the past year, signaling investor caution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Hotels Approves Merger, PVR INOX Boosts Profit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Gujarat-Hotels-Approves-Merger-PVR-INOX-Boosts-Profit/698d9dea211323ff9f630805</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Gujarat-Hotels-Approves-Merger-PVR-INOX-Boosts-Profit/698d9dea211323ff9f630805</guid><description>Gujarat Hotels Limited will merge its wholly-owned subsidiary, Inox Infrastructure Limited, a strategic move to streamline operations. The company reported a substantial year-on-year surge in both standalone and consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) for Q3 FY26. This jump was primarily driven by a significant increase in profit share from its associate, PVR INOX Limited, and the reversal of prior-year deferred tax charges, rather than operational revenue growth. Key leadership changes were also approved, including a new Chairman and Managing Director. No future guidance was issued.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Hits Record Revenue, EV Push Drives Strong Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Hits-Record-Revenue-EV-Push-Drives-Strong-Growth/698d9ddd211323ff9f630785</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Hits-Record-Revenue-EV-Push-Drives-Strong-Growth/698d9ddd211323ff9f630785</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp reported its highest-ever quarterly revenue of INR 12,328 Crores in Q3 FY'26, surging 21% year-on-year. EBITDA climbed 23% to INR 1,810 Crores, with normalized PAT up 20% to INR 1,489 Crores. The company highlights robust growth across ICE and EV segments, expanding market share in entry and scooter categories, and strong performance in global markets. Management anticipates double-digit industry growth for Q4 FY'26, while acknowledging potential moderation in H2 FY'27.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Marriott's India Surge: Expansion Drives Stock, But At What Price?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Marriotts-India-Surge-Expansion-Drives-Stock-But-At-What-Price/698d9d3b211323ff9f630598</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Marriotts-India-Surge-Expansion-Drives-Stock-But-At-What-Price/698d9d3b211323ff9f630598</guid><description>Marriott International reported significant expansion in 2025, with India contributing 42% of signed rooms in Asia-Pacific (excluding China). The company inked 99 deals in India, adding over 12,000 rooms. This performance pushed Marriott's stock to an all-time high near $359.35 in early February 2026. However, the rapid growth strategy, heavily reliant on brand affiliations and property conversions, is occurring as Marriott trades at a P/E ratio of approximately 34-38x, a premium compared to some major competitors, raising questions about the long-term sustainability and margin impact of its valuation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Aramco Hits 70% Local Content, Pivoting to Industrial Powerhouse</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Aramco-Hits-70percent-Local-Content-Pivoting-to-Industrial-Powerhouse/698d9cd9211323ff9f6304a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Aramco-Hits-70percent-Local-Content-Pivoting-to-Industrial-Powerhouse/698d9cd9211323ff9f6304a6</guid><description>Saudi Aramco has reached a 70% local content milestone in its supply chain through the In-Kingdom Total Value Add (iktva) program. Launched in 2015, iktva has generated over $280 billion for Saudi Arabia's GDP and created more than 200,000 jobs. The company aims for 75% local content by 2030, reinforcing its role as a diversified industrial and economic engine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Astra Microwave Products Surges QoQ Profit; New CFO Appointed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astra-Microwave-Products-Surges-QoQ-Profit-New-CFO-Appointed/698d9cab211323ff9f6303d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astra-Microwave-Products-Surges-QoQ-Profit-New-CFO-Appointed/698d9cab211323ff9f6303d2</guid><description>Astra Microwave Products Limited posted robust sequential profit growth for Q3 FY26, with standalone PAT up 87.78% QoQ and consolidated PAT up 95.84% QoQ. The company also announced the appointment of Srinivasarao Devathi as its new Chief Financial Officer, succeeding Rahul Rungta. A significant warrant allotment, aiming to raise up to Rs. 173.99 Crores, was also approved, bolstering its financial position.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Whirlpool India Posts Strong Q3 EBITDA Growth, Secures 30-Year Brand Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Whirlpool-India-Posts-Strong-Q3-EBITDA-Growth-Secures-30-Year-Brand-Deal/698d9c49211323ff9f630155</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Whirlpool-India-Posts-Strong-Q3-EBITDA-Growth-Secures-30-Year-Brand-Deal/698d9c49211323ff9f630155</guid><description>Whirlpool India delivered a robust Q3 FY26, with standalone EBITDA surging 47% year-on-year to ₹65.3 Cr, driven by cost productivity and premium product sales. Revenue grew 4% to ₹1,624 Cr, boosted by market share gains and AC business expansion. The company also secured a critical 30-year brand rights agreement with Whirlpool Corporation and increased its stake in Elica India to ~97%. Despite one-time wage code provisions impacting reported PBT, Whirlpool India anticipates profit improvement and a market recovery in the second half of the fiscal year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:24:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sukhjit Starch Q3 Profit Plunges 71%, Revenue Drops 7.5% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Sukhjit-Starch-Q3-Profit-Plunges-71percent-Revenue-Drops-75percent-YoY/698d9bc0211323ff9f62ff3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Sukhjit-Starch-Q3-Profit-Plunges-71percent-Revenue-Drops-75percent-YoY/698d9bc0211323ff9f62ff3f</guid><description>Sukhjit Starch &amp; Chemicals reported a dismal Q3 FY26 with standalone net profit dropping 62.59% YoY to ₹4.04 crore and consolidated profit plummeting 70.97% to ₹3.13 crore. Revenue also saw a decline, with standalone sales down 7.89% to ₹343.86 crore. The nine-month performance mirrored this trend, showing significant year-on-year contractions in both top and bottom lines. The company's auditors noted that interim financials of three subsidiaries were not reviewed, though deemed immaterial.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>West Coast Paper Mills Q3 Profits Plunge 56% Amidst Import Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/West-Coast-Paper-Mills-Q3-Profits-Plunge-56percent-Amidst-Import-Woes/698d9b74211323ff9f62fe74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/West-Coast-Paper-Mills-Q3-Profits-Plunge-56percent-Amidst-Import-Woes/698d9b74211323ff9f62fe74</guid><description>West Coast Paper Mills reported a sharp 56.14% year-on-year decline in consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹29.58 Cr for Q3 FY26, despite a 3.34% rise in consolidated revenue to ₹1049.78 Cr. Standalone PAT plummeted 67% YoY. Management highlighted industry challenges from rising imports and pricing pressures affecting realizations, while expressing confidence in a future stabilization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>West Coast Paper Mills Profit Plunges 54% YoY Amid Import Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/West-Coast-Paper-Mills-Profit-Plunges-54percent-YoY-Amid-Import-Pressures/698d9b66211323ff9f62fdb0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/West-Coast-Paper-Mills-Profit-Plunges-54percent-YoY-Amid-Import-Pressures/698d9b66211323ff9f62fdb0</guid><description>West Coast Paper Mills reported a sharp 54% year-on-year decline in consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹29.58 Crores. Standalone PAT saw an even steeper 68% fall to ₹18.61 Crores. Management attributed the challenging quarter to rising imports and competitive pricing, which impacted revenue realizations. A planned maintenance shutdown also affected production. Despite these headwinds, the company anticipates stabilization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Suzlon Surges on Record Deliveries, But Q3 Margins Dip Amid EPC Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Suzlon-Surges-on-Record-Deliveries-But-Q3-Margins-Dip-Amid-EPC-Shift/698d9b61211323ff9f62fd89</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Suzlon-Surges-on-Record-Deliveries-But-Q3-Margins-Dip-Amid-EPC-Shift/698d9b61211323ff9f62fd89</guid><description>Suzlon Energy posted a record Q3 FY26 with 617 MW deliveries, highest ever in India, boosting its order book to 6.4 GW. 9-month revenues climbed 58% YoY to ₹11,211 Cr and EBITDA surged 77% to ₹2,058 Cr. While WTG EBITDA margins saw a Q3 dip due to a shift towards lower-margin EPC projects (now 27% of revenue), management remains confident in achieving 60% FY26 growth, leveraging AI, exports, and a new project development vertical.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NATCO Pharma's Q3 PAT Rises 14% YoY, But QoQ Revenue Plummets 52%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/NATCO-Pharmas-Q3-PAT-Rises-14percent-YoY-But-QoQ-Revenue-Plummets-52percent/698d9acb211323ff9f62fc55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/NATCO-Pharmas-Q3-PAT-Rises-14percent-YoY-But-QoQ-Revenue-Plummets-52percent/698d9acb211323ff9f62fc55</guid><description>NATCO Pharma reported a mixed bag for Q3FY26. While consolidated revenue grew 8.34% YoY to ₹705.4 crore and PAT increased 14.27% YoY to ₹151.3 crore, the company saw a significant 51.79% sequential drop in revenue and a 70.80% fall in PAT from Q2FY26. This decline was attributed to a sharp drop in 'Formulations export' revenue. The acquisition of a stake in South Africa's Adcock Ingram is impacting financials with amortisation costs. Strategic moves include evaluating an Agro Chemicals business demerger and incorporating a new Chilean subsidiary.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sukhjit Starch Profit Plummets 62% Amid Revenue Drop</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Sukhjit-Starch-Profit-Plummets-62percent-Amid-Revenue-Drop/698d9a7e211323ff9f62fb43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Sukhjit-Starch-Profit-Plummets-62percent-Amid-Revenue-Drop/698d9a7e211323ff9f62fb43</guid><description>Sukhjit Starch &amp; Chemicals reported a severe profit decline for Q3 FY26, with standalone net profit plummeting 62.6% year-on-year to ₹4.04 Crores on a 7.9% revenue drop to ₹343.86 Crores. Consolidated profit fared worse, tumbling 71.0% to ₹3.13 Crores. The nine-month period also saw significant contraction in both revenue and profit, highlighting substantial margin pressures and a concerning trend for the agro-processing firm.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Stallion India Raises Rs 364 Cr Via Rights Issue Amidst Trading Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Stallion-India-Raises-Rs-364-Cr-Via-Rights-Issue-Amidst-Trading-Scrutiny/698d9a61211323ff9f62fa5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Stallion-India-Raises-Rs-364-Cr-Via-Rights-Issue-Amidst-Trading-Scrutiny/698d9a61211323ff9f62fa5f</guid><description>Stallion India Fluorochemicals has announced a Rs 364 crore rights issue to fund a new R-32 Gas Manufacturing Plant. The company will offer 3.67 crore shares at Rs 99 each, opening February 20, 2026. However, the stock's trading under Periodic Call Auction due to Additional Surveillance Measure (ASM) LT – Stage 1 and Trade-for-Trade (T/T+1) segment signals heightened regulatory monitoring and potential market volatility, posing risks for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>UPI Powers Malaysian Payments: India-Malaysia Cross-Border Deal Struck</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UPI-Powers-Malaysian-Payments-India-Malaysia-Cross-Border-Deal-Struck/698d99b2211323ff9f62f5fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UPI-Powers-Malaysian-Payments-India-Malaysia-Cross-Border-Deal-Struck/698d99b2211323ff9f62f5fa</guid><description>NPCI International Payments Limited (NIPL) has partnered with Payments Network Malaysia Sdn Bhd (PayNet) to integrate India's UPI payment system with Malaysia's DuitNow QR. This phased rollout will allow Indian travelers to use UPI apps for payments in Malaysia and later enable Malaysian travelers to use DuitNow apps in India, enhancing cross-border transactions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BFSI Bullish Call: Axis Sees Up to 20% Upside in 4 Financials</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/BFSI-Bullish-Call-Axis-Sees-Up-to-20percent-Upside-in-4-Financials/698d99a7211323ff9f62f573</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/BFSI-Bullish-Call-Axis-Sees-Up-to-20percent-Upside-in-4-Financials/698d99a7211323ff9f62f573</guid><description>Axis Securities identifies four financial firms—State Bank of India, Federal Bank, Shriram Finance, and Ujjivan Small Finance Bank—as top picks, forecasting up to 20% share price gains. These stocks exhibit strong technical uptrends, trading above key moving averages. The brokerage cites broad-based growth, revised guidance, and improving asset quality as drivers, underpinning a positive outlook for the BFSI sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lumax Auto Technologies Surges on Strong Consolidated Growth, Standalone PAT Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Lumax-Auto-Technologies-Surges-on-Strong-Consolidated-Growth-Standalone-PAT-Dips/698d98b6211323ff9f62ee83</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Lumax-Auto-Technologies-Surges-on-Strong-Consolidated-Growth-Standalone-PAT-Dips/698d98b6211323ff9f62ee83</guid><description>Lumax Auto Technologies reported a strong third quarter for FY26, with consolidated revenue jumping 40.3% year-on-year to ₹1,27,066.24 Lakhs and consolidated PAT soaring 92.9% to ₹10,806.30 Lakhs. Margins also improved significantly. However, standalone PAT declined 50.9% to ₹1,088.87 Lakhs, impacted by an exceptional item of ₹903.10 Lakhs related to new Labour Codes. The company approved a ₹30 Crore channel financing guarantee from ICICI Bank. Management did not provide future guidance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Airlines Clash With Regulators Over Cabin Crew Fatigue Rules</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Airlines-Clash-With-Regulators-Over-Cabin-Crew-Fatigue-Rules/698d98b4211323ff9f62ee7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Airlines-Clash-With-Regulators-Over-Cabin-Crew-Fatigue-Rules/698d98b4211323ff9f62ee7c</guid><description>Indian airlines are pushing back against proposed stricter cabin crew fatigue rules, warning of significant disruptions and long-term growth impacts. The Federation of Indian Airlines, representing major carriers, seeks to dilute draft norms that would increase rest periods and mandate single hotel rooms for crew. These changes, aimed at enhancing safety, could impose operational and cost pressures on airlines already navigating a complex market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ganesh Housing Posts Robust 82% EBITDA Margin, Maintains Debt-Free Status</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ganesh-Housing-Posts-Robust-82percent-EBITDA-Margin-Maintains-Debt-Free-Status/698d9840211323ff9f62ecc0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ganesh-Housing-Posts-Robust-82percent-EBITDA-Margin-Maintains-Debt-Free-Status/698d9840211323ff9f62ecc0</guid><description>Ganesh Housing Limited reported Q3 FY26 revenues of ₹92 crore and EBITDA of ₹72 crore, achieving an impressive 82.3% EBITDA margin, with PAT at ₹54 crore. The company highlighted a moderation from an exceptional FY25 base due to land monetization, characterizing FY26 as an execution-led year. Maintaining its debt-free status for over three years, Ganesh Housing benefits from significant financial flexibility. Key projects like Million Minds Tech building are nearing full lease, while Malabar Retreat sees strong booking progress. The company remains optimistic about Ahmedabad's real estate market growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:07:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pearl Global Sees Record Revenue; Trade Deals Boost Textile Giant's Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Pearl-Global-Sees-Record-Revenue-Trade-Deals-Boost-Textile-Giants-Outlook/698d97ae211323ff9f62e89a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Pearl-Global-Sees-Record-Revenue-Trade-Deals-Boost-Textile-Giants-Outlook/698d97ae211323ff9f62e89a</guid><description>Pearl Global Industries reported a record Q3 FY'26 revenue of INR 1,170 crores, a significant 14.4% year-on-year increase. Nine-month FY'26 revenue grew 13.2% to INR 3,711 crores, with Profit After Tax up 14% to INR 189 crores. The company's outlook is strong, bolstered by favorable trade agreements, ongoing capacity expansions in Bangladesh, and a recent credit rating upgrade to A+ stable by ICRA.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:04:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Airports Bets on 8.45% Bonds Amid Group Debt Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Airports-Bets-on-845percent-Bonds-Amid-Group-Debt-Push/698d97a1211323ff9f62e84a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Airports-Bets-on-845percent-Bonds-Amid-Group-Debt-Push/698d97a1211323ff9f62e84a</guid><description>Adani Airport Holdings Limited (AAHL) is securing Rs 1,500 crore through three-year bonds yielding 8.45% with quarterly interest payments. This move consolidates six key airports under a restricted group, capping further indebtedness while aiming to double passenger capacity by FY30. The issuance occurs within a wider Adani Group strategy of significant domestic debt market engagement, though group-level regulatory attention introduces a complex risk backdrop.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:04:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Flipkart Eyes Food Delivery: IPO-Bound E-Com Giant Tests New Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Flipkart-Eyes-Food-Delivery-IPO-Bound-E-Com-Giant-Tests-New-Market/698d970d211323ff9f62e593</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Flipkart-Eyes-Food-Delivery-IPO-Bound-E-Com-Giant-Tests-New-Market/698d970d211323ff9f62e593</guid><description>Walmart-owned Flipkart is preparing a pilot for online food delivery in Bengaluru by May-June, signaling a strategic diversification ahead of its IPO. The move aims to leverage Flipkart's extensive logistics network and deepen consumer engagement in a habit-forming sector, while also exploring integration with the Open Network for Digital Commerce (ONDC). This venture enters a market dominated by Zomato and Swiggy, where past competitors have struggled, highlighting significant entry barriers and intense competition. Flipkart's strategy appears to be a calculated approach to bolster its ecosystem and growth narrative for potential investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Singapore's FDI Lead Faces Macroeconomic Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Singapores-FDI-Lead-Faces-Macroeconomic-Scrutiny/698d963bba46a4833be18ed0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Singapores-FDI-Lead-Faces-Macroeconomic-Scrutiny/698d963bba46a4833be18ed0</guid><description>Singapore cemented its position as India's leading FDI source, injecting nearly $15 billion in FY24-25 and reinforcing a seven-year trend. The Comprehensive Economic Cooperation Agreement (CECA) underpins this robust economic corridor. However, persistent global economic uncertainty and exchange rate volatility present potential headwinds for future capital flows, even as Indian firms leverage Singapore as a regional launchpad.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Choksi Asia PAT Jumps 922% on 41% Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Choksi-Asia-PAT-Jumps-922percent-on-41percent-Revenue-Growth/698d93e0ba46a4833be18bed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Choksi-Asia-PAT-Jumps-922percent-on-41percent-Revenue-Growth/698d93e0ba46a4833be18bed</guid><description>Choksi Asia Limited reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with Net Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 922.6% year-on-year to ₹212.82 Lakhs, driven by a 41.3% rise in revenue to ₹1,225.74 Lakhs. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, PAT grew 83.7% YoY. The results reflect amalgamation impacts and new Labour Codes, with the company operating solely in the NDT sector. No forward guidance or balance sheet details were provided.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Alliance Metaliks Plunges on Soaring Losses, Auditor Flags Going Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Alliance-Metaliks-Plunges-on-Soaring-Losses-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern/698d93d6ba46a4833be18b76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Alliance-Metaliks-Plunges-on-Soaring-Losses-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern/698d93d6ba46a4833be18b76</guid><description>Alliance Integrated Metaliks Limited reported a significant net loss of ₹2354.20 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, worsening from the prior year. For the nine months, losses ballooned to ₹6800.17 Lakhs. The company's auditor has raised doubts about its ability to continue as a going concern due to a severely eroded net worth, now a debit balance of ₹33,159.36 Lakhs. Furthermore, the Directorate of Enforcement has provisionally attached company properties and promoter shares, adding another layer of risk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:48:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698d93d6ba46a4833be18b75.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan Acquires Luxembourg Entities, Secures ₹415 Crore Funding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Acquires-Luxembourg-Entities-Secures-415-Crore-Funding/698d92f9ba46a4833be18a8b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Acquires-Luxembourg-Entities-Secures-415-Crore-Funding/698d92f9ba46a4833be18a8b</guid><description>Anupam Rasayan India Ltd. is expanding its global footprint by acquiring two Luxembourg-based entities, Doriath and Batam. The company will raise ₹415 crore through credit facilities and External Commercial Borrowing (ECB) to fund the acquisitions and establish a corporate presence in Luxembourg. Significant security interests have been created to back these facilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Axentra Corp Plunges into Deep Losses With Zero Operational Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Axentra-Corp-Plunges-into-Deep-Losses-With-Zero-Operational-Revenue/698d9243ba46a4833be187a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Axentra-Corp-Plunges-into-Deep-Losses-With-Zero-Operational-Revenue/698d9243ba46a4833be187a8</guid><description>Axentra Corp Limited has posted alarming unaudited financial results for Q3 FY26, reporting zero revenue from operations and a net loss of ₹4.71 Cr. The company's total revenue of ₹8.20 Cr was solely derived from 'Other Income'. This marks a significant downturn from a profitable FY25. Adding to concerns, the Managing Director has resigned, with a new MD appointed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mold-Tek Technologies Posts Stellar Q3 YoY Growth, Driven by US Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mold-Tek-Technologies-Posts-Stellar-Q3-YoY-Growth-Driven-by-US-Acquisition/698d9207ba46a4833be1871a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mold-Tek-Technologies-Posts-Stellar-Q3-YoY-Growth-Driven-by-US-Acquisition/698d9207ba46a4833be1871a</guid><description>Mold-Tek Technologies Ltd. has announced strong unaudited financial results for Q3 FY26, showcasing a significant 56.75% year-on-year increase in consolidated revenue to ₹5,266.70 Lakhs and a remarkable 617.54% surge in consolidated PAT to ₹388.85 Lakhs. The acquisition of Beryl Project Engineering LLC in the US contributed positively, adding USD 1.39 Million to revenue. Despite a slight QoQ dip in standalone revenue, management remains optimistic about future performance, citing improved execution, sustained order inflows, and strategic focus on automation and segment recovery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HAL Q3 Beat: Profit Soars, But Margin Nuances Raise Eyebrows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/HAL-Q3-Beat-Profit-Soars-But-Margin-Nuances-Raise-Eyebrows/698d919cba46a4833be18619</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/HAL-Q3-Beat-Profit-Soars-But-Margin-Nuances-Raise-Eyebrows/698d919cba46a4833be18619</guid><description>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd. (HAL) announced robust third-quarter results, with net profit surging 30.3% year-on-year to ₹1,867 crore, exceeding analyst expectations. Revenue also saw a healthy 10.7% increase. Despite this top-line and bottom-line strength, the market is scrutinizing minor margin misses against forecasts and elevated valuation metrics, alongside recent analyst downgrades and program exclusion reports.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Exits Mali Lithium Deal Over Security, Russian Ties</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Exits-Mali-Lithium-Deal-Over-Security-Russian-Ties/698d9120ba46a4833be18430</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Exits-Mali-Lithium-Deal-Over-Security-Russian-Ties/698d9120ba46a4833be18430</guid><description>India has pulled out of a crucial lithium exploration project in Mali, citing escalating security risks and the project's association with Russia's Rosatom. The decision by Khanij Bidesh India Ltd (KABIL) and NLC India Ltd aims to protect investments in the volatile West African nation. This move signals New Delhi's cautious approach to securing vital minerals for its electric vehicle ambitions amidst geopolitical instability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GFL Turns Profitable: Board OKs Merger, New MD Appointment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GFL-Turns-Profitable-Board-OKs-Merger-New-MD-Appointment/698d90caba46a4833be182d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GFL-Turns-Profitable-Board-OKs-Merger-New-MD-Appointment/698d90caba46a4833be182d6</guid><description>GFL Limited has reported a significant turnaround in its financial performance for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company posted improved revenues and substantial PAT growth YoY on both standalone and consolidated bases. Key corporate actions include the approval of a draft scheme for the merger of its wholly-owned subsidiary, Inox Infrastructure Limited, and leadership changes with the appointment of Mrs. Ishita Jain and Mr. Pavan Kumar Jain as Chairman and Managing Director.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Inox Clean Energy Expands to Africa, Bets on Secured Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Inox-Clean-Energy-Expands-to-Africa-Bets-on-Secured-Infrastructure/698d90bcba46a4833be18289</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Inox-Clean-Energy-Expands-to-Africa-Bets-on-Secured-Infrastructure/698d90bcba46a4833be18289</guid><description>Inox Clean Energy Services Ltd. and RJ Corp have formed a joint venture to enter Africa's renewable energy sector, acquiring Skypower Services MENA Ltd. The partnership aims to commission 570 MW of solar capacity in its first phase, supported by sovereign-backed power purchase agreements and pre-secured infrastructure. This strategic move is part of Inox Clean Energy's broader global expansion, targeting 2.5 GW in Africa by FY29, while navigating the continent's dynamic, yet challenging, energy market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Welspun Living Profit Plummets 99.9%, Debt Falls Amidst Trade Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Welspun-Living-Profit-Plummets-999percent-Debt-Falls-Amidst-Trade-Headwinds/698d9024ba46a4833be17f99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Welspun-Living-Profit-Plummets-999percent-Debt-Falls-Amidst-Trade-Headwinds/698d9024ba46a4833be17f99</guid><description>Welspun Living reported a devastating Q3 FY26, with Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeting 99.9% year-on-year to a mere ₹0.2 Cr, down from ₹121 Cr. Consolidated revenue declined 9.9% to ₹2,277 Cr, and EBITDA margins compressed significantly to 7.7% from 12.6%. Despite the steep profitability drop, the company managed to reduce its Net Debt by ₹326 Cr YoY to ₹1,332 Cr. Management cited challenging conditions but expressed optimism on trade tailwinds and sustainability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>3M India Posts Net Loss on One-Off Charges Despite Strong Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/3M-India-Posts-Net-Loss-on-One-Off-Charges-Despite-Strong-Revenue-Growth/698d8fdeba46a4833be17eca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/3M-India-Posts-Net-Loss-on-One-Off-Charges-Despite-Strong-Revenue-Growth/698d8fdeba46a4833be17eca</guid><description>3M India swung to a net loss of ₹62.05 crore in Q3 FY26, a stark reversal from a ₹113.77 crore profit last year, driven by ₹214.04 crore in exceptional items including a ₹74.57 crore charge for new labor codes and ₹139.47 crore for Advance Pricing Agreement (APA) related tax expenses. Despite this, total income from operations grew 12.7% YoY to ₹1,237.50 crore, and EBITDA surged 40.5% YoY to ₹240 crore, with all business segments reporting sales growth. The company also announced the retirement of Managing Director Ramesh Ramadurai, effective March 31, 2026, and the appointment of Aseem Kuldip Joshi as his successor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Expands Global Footprint, Eyes EV Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ashok-Leyland-Expands-Global-Footprint-Eyes-EV-Growth/698d8f9eba46a4833be17eb6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ashok-Leyland-Expands-Global-Footprint-Eyes-EV-Growth/698d8f9eba46a4833be17eb6</guid><description>Ashok Leyland is accelerating its international growth strategy by establishing an assembly unit in Saudi Arabia and forming a strategic partnership in Indonesia for electric buses and defense vehicles. This expansion, coupled with a ₹600 crore commitment to its e-mobility platform, complements a record Q3 FY26 performance featuring ₹11,534 crore revenue and ₹796 crore net profit. The moves aim to capitalize on emerging market demand and address capacity constraints at its UAE plant.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ritco Logistics: Revenue Surges, But Consolidated Profit Dips Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ritco-Logistics-Revenue-Surges-But-Consolidated-Profit-Dips-Sharply/698d8f64ba46a4833be17e59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ritco-Logistics-Revenue-Surges-But-Consolidated-Profit-Dips-Sharply/698d8f64ba46a4833be17e59</guid><description>Ritco Logistics reported a robust Q3 FY26, with consolidated total income soaring 25.31% YoY to ₹394.01 Cr. Standalone performance showed strong growth in EBITDA and net profit. However, consolidated net profit declined 5.12% YoY to ₹9.64 Cr, despite revenue gains, indicating potential cost pressures. The digital division, TrucksUp, saw a remarkable 73.45% QoQ income jump.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>UP Budget: ₹9.13L Cr Bets on Capex, Digital Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UP-Budget-913L-Cr-Bets-on-Capex-Digital-Push/698d8f2bba46a4833be17dc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UP-Budget-913L-Cr-Bets-on-Capex-Digital-Push/698d8f2bba46a4833be17dc3</guid><description>Uttar Pradesh presented its largest-ever state budget, a ₹9.13 lakh crore outlay for FY26-27, marking a 12-13% increase. The fiscal plan signals a strategic emphasis on capital expenditure, allocating ₹1.78 lakh crore (19.5% of the total) to drive infrastructure and asset creation. A significant boost to technology, including ₹2,000 crore for IT and Electronics, alongside a focus on AI, underscores the state's ambition to foster a digital economy and enhance job prospects. This budget aims to sustain economic momentum, citing a projected GSDP of ₹30.25 lakh crore and declining unemployment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Om Infra Q3 Profit Down 33%; 9M Revenue Up 77%; FY26 Guidance Puzzles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Om-Infra-Q3-Profit-Down-33percent-9M-Revenue-Up-77percent-FY26-Guidance-Puzzles/698d8dc6ba46a4833be178d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Om-Infra-Q3-Profit-Down-33percent-9M-Revenue-Up-77percent-FY26-Guidance-Puzzles/698d8dc6ba46a4833be178d5</guid><description>Om Infra Limited reported a challenging third quarter (Q3 FY26) with Net Sales down 37.1% YoY to ₹340 Cr and PAT falling 33.3% to ₹14 Cr, impacted by margin contraction. However, the nine-month period (9M FY26) showcased robust growth, with Net Sales up 77.6% to ₹961 Cr and EBITDA surging 138.9%. The company maintains a strong order book of ₹2,236 Cr, including significant Jal Jeevan Mission projects, and has guided for FY26 revenue of ₹500-550 Cr, a figure lower than 9M FY26 achieved revenue, raising investor questions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Shyam Telecom Faces Insolvency Fears on Auditor's Grave Warnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Shyam-Telecom-Faces-Insolvency-Fears-on-Auditors-Grave-Warnings/698d8dafba46a4833be178ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Shyam-Telecom-Faces-Insolvency-Fears-on-Auditors-Grave-Warnings/698d8dafba46a4833be178ce</guid><description>Shyam Telecom Limited's Q3 FY26 results are overshadowed by its auditor's stark warning of "material uncertainty" regarding its ability to continue as a going concern. The company's net worth is fully eroded, and liabilities exceed assets, signaling severe financial distress. Revenue from operations plunged YoY, while net losses widened significantly in nine months, painting a grim picture for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Capillary Tech Surges on Revenue Growth, AI Push; PAT Dips Amid One-Offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Capillary-Tech-Surges-on-Revenue-Growth-AI-Push-PAT-Dips-Amid-One-Offs/698d8dacba46a4833be178c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Capillary-Tech-Surges-on-Revenue-Growth-AI-Push-PAT-Dips-Amid-One-Offs/698d8dacba46a4833be178c7</guid><description>Capillary Technologies India Limited posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue climbing 16% YoY to ₹184 cr and Adjusted EBITDA rising 24% with improved margins. While one-time expenses led to a PAT decline, normalized PAT remained flat, and 9M PAT surged significantly. The company highlighted strong Net Retention Rate (NRR) of 111% and significant investments in AI innovation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 08:22:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d8dacba46a4833be178c6_1770884976767.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>