<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:27 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Market: Select Sectors Outperform Sluggish Economy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Market-Select-Sectors-Outperform-Sluggish-Economy/69a2acfbfa7d0695d1b0191d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Market-Select-Sectors-Outperform-Sluggish-Economy/69a2acfbfa7d0695d1b0191d</guid><description>Despite a perceived sluggish Indian market, Sohum Asset Managers' CIO is overweighting domestic themes including telecom, NBFCs, industrials, and cement, citing early recovery signs in commercial vehicles and steady credit growth. While underweight on banking, the strategy embraces IT giants and mid-caps, alongside infrastructure and defense plays, navigating a complex economic backdrop where targeted sectorial strength may diverge from broader index performance. Aggregate Nifty 50 earnings saw 7% growth in Q3 FY26, with Nifty 500 companies showing a more robust 19% year-on-year increase, highlighting a potential divergence in performance across market segments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:53:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2acfbfa7d0695d1b0191c_1772268913949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zenith Exports Fined By NSE, BSE For Compliance Lapses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Zenith-Exports-Fined-By-NSE-BSE-For-Compliance-Lapses/69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Zenith-Exports-Fined-By-NSE-BSE-For-Compliance-Lapses/69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017c9</guid><description>Zenith Exports Limited faces penalties from both NSE and BSE, totaling ₹7,90,600 (including GST), for non-compliance with SEBI's Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements (LODR) for the quarter ending December 2025. The company must pay the fine within 15 days or face potential trading restrictions, promoter shareholding freeze, or even suspension.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017c8_1772268444528.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goa Carbon Gets NGT Favourable Order for Goa Plant; Pollution Case Dismissed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Goa-Carbon-Gets-NGT-Favourable-Order-for-Goa-Plant-Pollution-Case-Dismissed/69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Goa-Carbon-Gets-NGT-Favourable-Order-for-Goa-Plant-Pollution-Case-Dismissed/69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017b3</guid><description>Goa Carbon Limited has received a favourable final order from the National Green Tribunal (NGT) dismissing a case alleging environmental pollution and health issues at its Goa plant. The tribunal found the applicant's medical reports insufficient and noted the company's compliance, removing a significant regulatory overhang. The company stated there will be no financial impact from this order.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ab10fa7d0695d1b017b2_1772268410861.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silicon Rental H1 FY26 Revenue ₹61.6 Cr; EBIDTA ₹20.2 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silicon-Rental-H1-FY26-Revenue-616-Cr-EBIDTA-202-Cr/69a2a2a1fa7d0695d1b013f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silicon-Rental-H1-FY26-Revenue-616-Cr-EBIDTA-202-Cr/69a2a2a1fa7d0695d1b013f9</guid><description>Silicon Rental Solutions Limited presented its H1 FY26 performance, showing ₹61.6 crore revenue and ₹20.2 crore EBIDTA. The company is pivoting to a full-stack tech rental model, expanding into AI and robotics, and launching a 'CoE-as-a-Service' for educational institutions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:09:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2a2a1fa7d0695d1b013f8_1772266285383.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MapmyIndia Data Reveals India Retail Shift to Tier 3-5 Cities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MapmyIndia-Data-Reveals-India-Retail-Shift-to-Tier-3-5-Cities/69a2a229fa7d0695d1b0136a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MapmyIndia-Data-Reveals-India-Retail-Shift-to-Tier-3-5-Cities/69a2a229fa7d0695d1b0136a</guid><description>A new report, co-powered by MapmyIndia's data, shows India's retail sector is decentralizing. Tier 3-5 cities are growing significantly faster than metros, driven by rising consumer spending and aspirations. MapmyIndia's location intelligence is crucial for retailers to navigate this evolving landscape.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:07:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2a229fa7d0695d1b01369_1772266329938.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRFC Tokyo Roadshow Targets Japanese Investors for Funding Diversification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IRFC-Tokyo-Roadshow-Targets-Japanese-Investors-for-Funding-Diversification/69a2a13dfa7d0695d1b0129f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IRFC-Tokyo-Roadshow-Targets-Japanese-Investors-for-Funding-Diversification/69a2a13dfa7d0695d1b0129f</guid><description>Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) held a two-day External Commercial Borrowing (ECB) roadshow in Tokyo, February 26-27, 2026. The initiative aimed to engage Japanese regional investors, diversify funding sources, and optimize borrowing costs, highlighting IRFC's credit profile and its crucial role in financing India's railway infrastructure expansion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:03:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2a13dfa7d0695d1b0129e_1772266119397.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fund Influx Meets Tobacco Tax Shock: Elitecon Valuation Questioned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Fund-Influx-Meets-Tobacco-Tax-Shock-Elitecon-Valuation-Questioned/69a29fd7fa7d0695d1b011a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Fund-Influx-Meets-Tobacco-Tax-Shock-Elitecon-Valuation-Questioned/69a29fd7fa7d0695d1b011a7</guid><description>Mauritius-based Minerva Ventures Fund has acquired an 8.58% stake in Elitecon International Limited via warrants and open market purchases. This investment enters a sector facing a harsh regulatory environment in 2026, with significant tax hikes set to increase costs and potentially compress margins. Elitecon's reported explosive growth contrasts sharply with its exceedingly high valuation multiples and recent stock volatility, prompting scrutiny over sustainability. Competitor valuations are notably lower, and analyst sentiment leans cautiously pessimistic due to sector-wide headwinds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:57:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29fd7fa7d0695d1b011a6_1772265744483.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Laxmipati Engineering Seeks ₹25 Cr RPT Approval; Vote March 2-31</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Laxmipati-Engineering-Seeks-25-Cr-RPT-Approval-Vote-March-2-31/69a29df0fa7d0695d1b01085</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Laxmipati-Engineering-Seeks-25-Cr-RPT-Approval-Vote-March-2-31/69a29df0fa7d0695d1b01085</guid><description>Laxmipati Engineering Works Limited is seeking shareholder approval for a material related party transaction (RPT) with Laxmipati Apparel Private Limited. The proposed job work and fabrication services deal is valued up to ₹25 Crore annually, representing 49.90% of the company's turnover. Shareholders will vote via postal ballot and remote e-voting from March 2 to March 31, 2026. The Board has recommended approval, citing it as an ordinary course of business.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:49:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29df0fa7d0695d1b01084_1772265203244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PE Firms Exit Vishal Mega Mart; Shares Slide Post Block Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PE-Firms-Exit-Vishal-Mega-Mart-Shares-Slide-Post-Block-Deal/69a29c8efa7d0695d1b00f7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PE-Firms-Exit-Vishal-Mega-Mart-Shares-Slide-Post-Block-Deal/69a29c8efa7d0695d1b00f7d</guid><description>Samayat Services LLP, backed by Kedaara Capital and Partners Group, divested nearly 14% of its stake in Vishal Mega Mart (VMM) for ₹7,635 crore. The sale reduced its holding to 40.13% from 54.09%. Prominent institutional investors, including the Singapore government, Monetary Authority of Singapore, and HDFC Mutual Fund, collectively acquired over 6.3% of VMM. The market reacted negatively, with VMM shares falling 7.59% to ₹117.85 on the NSE. This divestment follows a similar large stake sale in June last year.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:43:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29c8efa7d0695d1b00f7c_1772264739176.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Tumbles 3% as Geopolitical Shockwaves Hit Crypto</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Tumbles-3percent-as-Geopolitical-Shockwaves-Hit-Crypto/69a29677fa7d0695d1b00ca4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Tumbles-3percent-as-Geopolitical-Shockwaves-Hit-Crypto/69a29677fa7d0695d1b00ca4</guid><description>Bitcoin experienced a swift 3% decline, nearing $63,000, following U.S. and Israeli military actions against Iran. This sharp weekend sell-off demonstrates Bitcoin's function as a real-time barometer for geopolitical risk, reacting instantaneously due to its continuous trading cycle, unlike traditional markets. The move underscores increasing correlations between digital assets and global instability, impacting investor sentiment and liquidity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:17:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29677fa7d0695d1b00ca3_1772263203336.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Almondz Global Securities seeks EOGM nod for ₹13.26 cr preferential issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Almondz-Global-Securities-seeks-EOGM-nod-for-1326-cr-preferential-issue/69a29671fa7d0695d1b00c8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Almondz-Global-Securities-seeks-EOGM-nod-for-1326-cr-preferential-issue/69a29671fa7d0695d1b00c8d</guid><description>Almondz Global Securities Ltd. has called an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EOGM) on March 27, 2026, to seek shareholder approval for a preferential issue. The company plans to raise ₹13.26 crore by issuing 80 lakh convertible warrants at ₹16.58 each. Proceeds will bolster working capital, fund proprietary trading, and support general corporate needs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29671fa7d0695d1b00c8c_1772263125073.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ETFs vs. Mutual Funds: Indian Investor Behavior Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/ETFs-vs-Mutual-Funds-Indian-Investor-Behavior-Shifts/69a29539fa7d0695d1b00b6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/ETFs-vs-Mutual-Funds-Indian-Investor-Behavior-Shifts/69a29539fa7d0695d1b00b6e</guid><description>India's investment landscape sees a dichotomy: Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) attract with lower fees and transparency, while mutual funds, amplified by the ubiquitous Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) culture, foster crucial behavioral discipline. Recent data shows passive fund AUM nearing 17% of total industry assets, yet the psychological friction provided by mutual funds, especially during market volatility, offers a unique protective layer for retail investors. This structural advantage, combined with consistent inflows, suggests mutual funds, despite higher costs, may maintain relevance for wealth accumulation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:11:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29539fa7d0695d1b00b6d_1772262845200.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kopran Secures NSE Nod for Merger with Kopran Labs; NCLT Next</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Kopran-Secures-NSE-Nod-for-Merger-with-Kopran-Labs-NCLT-Next/69a2948ffa7d0695d1b00af2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Kopran-Secures-NSE-Nod-for-Merger-with-Kopran-Labs-NCLT-Next/69a2948ffa7d0695d1b00af2</guid><description>Kopran Limited has advanced its proposed merger with Kopran Laboratories Limited, receiving a "no objection" observation letter from the National Stock Exchange (NSE). This procedural milestone enables the company to proceed with submitting the amalgamation scheme to the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), paving the way for integration.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 07:09:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2948ffa7d0695d1b00af1_1772262861197.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Balkrishna Industries NCD Rating: CRISIL Assigns 'AA+/Stable' to ₹750 Cr Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balkrishna-Industries-NCD-Rating-CRISIL-Assigns-AAStable-to-750-Cr-Issue/69a291c0fa7d0695d1b00989</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balkrishna-Industries-NCD-Rating-CRISIL-Assigns-AAStable-to-750-Cr-Issue/69a291c0fa7d0695d1b00989</guid><description>Balkrishna Industries Limited (BIL) has secured a 'CRISIL AA+/Stable' credit rating for its proposed ₹750 crore Non-Convertible Debenture (NCD) issuance. This rating signifies a high degree of safety and very low credit risk, enhancing investor confidence in the company's ability to meet its financial obligations. The rating is crucial for the company's fundraising strategy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:57:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a291c0fa7d0695d1b00988_1772261998989.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Concord Control Systems bags Rs 53.73 Cr KAVACH order from Indian Railways</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Concord-Control-Systems-bags-Rs-5373-Cr-KAVACH-order-from-Indian-Railways/69a29059fa7d0695d1b00856</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Concord-Control-Systems-bags-Rs-5373-Cr-KAVACH-order-from-Indian-Railways/69a29059fa7d0695d1b00856</guid><description>Concord Control Systems Limited announced a significant Rs. 53.73 Crore order for KAVACH 4.0 equipment from Indian Railways, to be executed within 12 months. This win strengthens the company's position in critical railway safety systems and is expected to boost its order book and revenue trajectory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a29059fa7d0695d1b00855_1772261592859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Balkrishna Industries Ratings Reaffirmed at Crisil AA+/A1+ by CRISIL</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Balkrishna-Industries-Ratings-Reaffirmed-at-Crisil-AAA1-by-CRISIL/69a28fdffa7d0695d1b007b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Balkrishna-Industries-Ratings-Reaffirmed-at-Crisil-AAA1-by-CRISIL/69a28fdffa7d0695d1b007b8</guid><description>CRISIL Ratings has reaffirmed Balkrishna Industries Limited's (BIL) long-term rating at 'Crisil AA+/Stable' for bank facilities and 'Crisil A1+' for short-term bank facilities and its Rs 500 Crore Commercial Paper. This reaffirmation indicates sustained financial stability and a low credit risk, assuring lenders and investors of the company's ability to meet its obligations. However, the company must avail proposed facilities within 180 days of the rating letter date, or a fresh revalidation will be required.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:49:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28fdffa7d0695d1b007b7_1772261487496.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UBS Pivots: US Equities Downgraded as EM &amp; Cyclicals Gain Traction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/UBS-Pivots-US-Equities-Downgraded-as-EM-and-Cyclicals-Gain-Traction/69a28fb9fa7d0695d1b00788</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/UBS-Pivots-US-Equities-Downgraded-as-EM-and-Cyclicals-Gain-Traction/69a28fb9fa7d0695d1b00788</guid><description>UBS has strategically shifted its stance on U.S. equities, downgrading the asset class to 'benchmark' due to elevated valuations, diminishing buyback support, and dollar-related risks. The firm reiterates a high-conviction overweight on emerging markets (EM), citing accelerating global growth, more attractive valuations, and improved operational leverage. This move signals a potential rotation favoring cyclical regions and sectors outside the U.S. as capital flows increasingly diversify.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:48:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28fb9fa7d0695d1b00787_1772261590146.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ramkrishna Forgings Subsidiaries Amalgamation Receives NCLT Approval</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ramkrishna-Forgings-Subsidiaries-Amalgamation-Receives-NCLT-Approval/69a28eeffa7d0695d1b006a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ramkrishna-Forgings-Subsidiaries-Amalgamation-Receives-NCLT-Approval/69a28eeffa7d0695d1b006a0</guid><description>The National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), Kolkata Bench, has approved the amalgamation of Ramkrishna Forgings Limited's subsidiaries, Mal Metalliks Private Limited and Multitech Auto Private Limited, with Ramkrishna Casting Solutions Limited (formerly JMT Auto Limited). This strategic move, effective from January 1, 2024, aims to enhance administrative control, reduce costs, and strengthen the company's financial structure for greater operational efficiency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:45:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28eeffa7d0695d1b0069f_1772261213208.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>d-Matrix Challenges GPU Giants in AI Inference Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/d-Matrix-Challenges-GPU-Giants-in-AI-Inference-Race/69a28da2fa7d0695d1b00535</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/d-Matrix-Challenges-GPU-Giants-in-AI-Inference-Race/69a28da2fa7d0695d1b00535</guid><description>Silicon Valley firm d-Matrix is emerging as a significant contender in the AI inference hardware market, directly challenging incumbent GPU manufacturers like Nvidia. By focusing on a specialized architecture built around SRAM and in-memory compute, d-Matrix claims its solutions offer substantial improvements in cost-effectiveness, power efficiency, and speed for running trained AI models at scale. With substantial funding and strategic backing, the company aims to democratize AI access by making inference operations economically viable for a broader range of enterprises, positioning itself as a critical enabler against market speculation and high operational costs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:39:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28da2fa7d0695d1b00534_1772261126823.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Bets on HPV Vaccine: Merck's China Woes vs. Domestic Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Bets-on-HPV-Vaccine-Mercks-China-Woes-vs-Domestic-Rise/69a28d16fa7d0695d1b0045d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Bets-on-HPV-Vaccine-Mercks-China-Woes-vs-Domestic-Rise/69a28d16fa7d0695d1b0045d</guid><description>India has initiated a nationwide Human Papillomavirus (HPV) Vaccination Programme targeting 1.15 crore girls annually. The program initially utilizes Merck's Gardasil vaccine but signals a strong push for domestic manufacturing, with Serum Institute of India's Cervavac poised to play a significant role. This initiative arrives as Merck faces declining Gardasil sales in China, creating a complex global market dynamic and highlighting India's growing pharmaceutical self-sufficiency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:37:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28d16fa7d0695d1b0045c_1772260758202.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BF Utilities Q3 Profit Jumps 22% Amid Auditor's Adverse Conclusion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Q3-Profit-Jumps-22percent-Amid-Auditors-Adverse-Conclusion/69a28d10fa7d0695d1b00446</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Q3-Profit-Jumps-22percent-Amid-Auditors-Adverse-Conclusion/69a28d10fa7d0695d1b00446</guid><description>BF Utilities reported a consolidated net profit of ₹102.76 crore for Q3 FY26, a 22.43% increase year-on-year, with revenue up 12.60%. However, the results are overshadowed by an adverse conclusion from statutory auditors regarding compliance with accounting standards. Significant concerns remain over a ₹500 crore arbitration liability, unresolved advances, and accounting non-compliance, casting a shadow over the reported financial performance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:37:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28d10fa7d0695d1b00445_1772260948553.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Precious Metals Rally: Tax Complexities Overshadow Stellar Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Rally-Tax-Complexities-Overshadow-Stellar-Gains/69a28c1ffa7d0695d1b0035d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Rally-Tax-Complexities-Overshadow-Stellar-Gains/69a28c1ffa7d0695d1b0035d</guid><description>Gold and silver have delivered exceptional returns in recent years, with significant appreciation in 2025 and early 2026. However, the surge is met by increasingly complex tax implications across various investment vehicles, including ETFs, funds of funds, Sovereign Gold Bonds, and physical assets. Recent budget changes have introduced new tax liabilities, particularly for secondary market SGB transactions, demanding a strategic re-evaluation of investment approaches.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:33:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28c1ffa7d0695d1b0035c_1772260727241.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indonesia Halts Tata, Mahindra Truck Deal Amidst Local Industry Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indonesia-Halts-Tata-Mahindra-Truck-Deal-Amidst-Local-Industry-Push/69a28baefa7d0695d1b002fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indonesia-Halts-Tata-Mahindra-Truck-Deal-Amidst-Local-Industry-Push/69a28baefa7d0695d1b002fc</guid><description>Indonesia has halted a significant order for 105,000 trucks from Indian manufacturers Tata Motors and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra. This decision follows strong pushback from local policymakers and industry associations concerned about undermining domestic industrialization and job creation. The pause is pending further government and legislative discussions, signaling a potential shift in procurement strategy to favor local production capacity, estimated at one million pickup trucks annually.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28baefa7d0695d1b002fb_1772260393068.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Caplin Point Unit Gets USFDA Nod for $26M Desmopressin Injection</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Caplin-Point-Unit-Gets-USFDA-Nod-for-26M-Desmopressin-Injection/69a28951fa7d0695d1b0019d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Caplin-Point-Unit-Gets-USFDA-Nod-for-26M-Desmopressin-Injection/69a28951fa7d0695d1b0019d</guid><description>Caplin Point Laboratories' subsidiary, Caplin Steriles, has secured final USFDA approval for its Desmopressin Acetate Injection USP. This generic drug, used for haemophilia and diabetes insipidus, targets a US market with $26 million in sales. The approval is a significant step for Caplin Steriles, opening access to the lucrative US market and expected to boost revenue for the parent company.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:21:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28951fa7d0695d1b0019c_1772259802464.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OpenAI Lands DoD Classified AI Deal as Anthropic Faces Ban</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/OpenAI-Lands-DoD-Classified-AI-Deal-as-Anthropic-Faces-Ban/69a288c4fa7d0695d1b00111</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/OpenAI-Lands-DoD-Classified-AI-Deal-as-Anthropic-Faces-Ban/69a288c4fa7d0695d1b00111</guid><description>OpenAI's agreement to deploy AI on US Department of Defense classified networks marks a significant expansion, occurring as President Trump orders a halt to Anthropic's government use, citing national security risks. This move sharpens the competitive edge in defense AI, with OpenAI securing a strategic partnership while grappling with stringent ethical safeguards. The landscape sees valuations soaring for private AI firms, fueling a global race for AI supremacy in military applications.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:18:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a288c4fa7d0695d1b00110_1772259806276.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Meta Navigates Privacy Shift: DPDP Act Triggers New Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Meta-Navigates-Privacy-Shift-DPDP-Act-Triggers-New-Scrutiny/69a2874efa7d0695d1afffe5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Meta-Navigates-Privacy-Shift-DPDP-Act-Triggers-New-Scrutiny/69a2874efa7d0695d1afffe5</guid><description>Meta Platforms (META) is navigating a significant regulatory pivot. India's Digital Personal Data Protection Act (DPDP) enables direct privacy enforcement, moving scrutiny beyond competition law's dominance arguments that previously framed cases like WhatsApp's 2021 policy update. This shift, coupled with global regulatory actions like EU fines totaling over €1.5 billion, pressures Meta's targeted advertising model. With a market cap of $1.64 trillion and a P/E ratio around 27.4, Meta's stock ($657.01) is under watch as it adapts to stricter data governance and user consent mandates, while competitors like Apple adopt more privacy-centric approaches.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:12:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2874efa7d0695d1afffe4_1772259434283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Products A/S Acquires India's Techcom Precision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Products-AS-Acquires-Indias-Techcom-Precision/69a286fbfa7d0695d1afff91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Products-AS-Acquires-Indias-Techcom-Precision/69a286fbfa7d0695d1afff91</guid><description>Steel Products A/S, a Danish industrial conglomerate, has completed the 100% acquisition of Techcom Precision India Private Limited. This strategic move signifies the Danish firm's entry into India's precision manufacturing market, leveraging Techcom's capabilities. ALMT Legal advised Steel Products A/S, while Rubicon Law LLC represented Techcom Precision India. The transaction underscores a growing trend of Danish industrial players expanding their presence in India's dynamic economy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a286fbfa7d0695d1afff90_1772259196891.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Bank Eyes Up to 2% More Stake in ICICI Pru Life</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Bank-Eyes-Up-to-2percent-More-Stake-in-ICICI-Pru-Life/69a2860afa7d0695d1affea1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Bank-Eyes-Up-to-2percent-More-Stake-in-ICICI-Pru-Life/69a2860afa7d0695d1affea1</guid><description>ICICI Bank's Board has greenlit the acquisition of an additional stake, potentially up to 2.0%, in its subsidiary, ICICI Prudential Life Insurance. This strategic move aims to solidify the Bank's majority shareholding, particularly against dilution risks from stock-based compensation plans at the life insurance arm. Regulatory approvals are now the key next step.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:07:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2860afa7d0695d1affea0_1772258926636.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Secures USFDA Nod for Key Generics; Combined Sales $23.2M</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Secures-USFDA-Nod-for-Key-Generics-Combined-Sales-232M/69a2824dfa7d0695d1affd1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Secures-USFDA-Nod-for-Key-Generics-Combined-Sales-232M/69a2824dfa7d0695d1affd1f</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences has received final USFDA approvals for Ivermectin Tablets USP (3 mg) and Dapsone Tablets USP (25 mg and 100 mg). These approvals grant market access in the United States for prescription medications used to treat parasitic worm infections and leprosy, respectively. The combined annual sales for these formulations were reported at $23.2 million. Manufacturing will be at Zydus's Ahmedabad facilities, with Viona Pharmaceuticals Inc. handling distribution. This marks a step in expanding its US generic drug portfolio.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:51:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2824dfa7d0695d1affd1e_1772257972179.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Xflow Secures $16.6M Series A for Cross-Border Payment Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Xflow-Secures-166M-Series-A-for-Cross-Border-Payment-Expansion/69a27f7bfa7d0695d1affbef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Xflow-Secures-166M-Series-A-for-Cross-Border-Payment-Expansion/69a27f7bfa7d0695d1affbef</guid><description>Xflow Payments India Pvt. Ltd. has closed a $16.6 million Series A funding round led by General Catalyst, with participation from PayPal Ventures and existing investors including Stripe and Lightspeed. The company achieved an $85 million valuation with this round, bringing its total funding to over $32 million. This capital infusion, coupled with final PA-CB regulatory authorization for both imports and exports, positions Xflow to scale its cross-border payment solutions for Indian businesses. The funding follows a reported tenfold growth in 2025, serving nearly 15,000 clients.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:39:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a27f7bfa7d0695d1affbee_1772257271288.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cognizant's Resurgence: AI Fuels Growth, But Valuation Nears Peers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cognizants-Resurgence-AI-Fuels-Growth-But-Valuation-Nears-Peers/69a27ea2fa7d0695d1affaf0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cognizants-Resurgence-AI-Fuels-Growth-But-Valuation-Nears-Peers/69a27ea2fa7d0695d1affaf0</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions closed 2025 with a robust 6.4% revenue growth in constant currency, reaching $21.1 billion, and expanded operating margins to 16.1%. CEO Ravi Kumar S.'s strategy, focused on AI-driven 'mega-deals' and operational efficiency, has reversed earlier challenges. For 2026, the company projects revenue growth of 4.0-6.5% in constant currency and margin expansion. This performance places it favorably against competitors like Infosys and HCLTech, though its valuation metrics are now converging.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:35:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a27ea2fa7d0695d1affaef_1772257095696.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEC Mandates Rapid Insider Trade Reporting for Foreign Execs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SEC-Mandates-Rapid-Insider-Trade-Reporting-for-Foreign-Execs/69a27785fa7d0695d1aff805</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SEC-Mandates-Rapid-Insider-Trade-Reporting-for-Foreign-Execs/69a27785fa7d0695d1aff805</guid><description>Effective March 18, 2026, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will enforce new regulations requiring executives and directors of foreign private issuers to promptly disclose their company stock transactions. This mandate, originating from the Holding Foreign Insiders Accountable Act, aligns reporting standards with those for U.S. executives, targeting insider trading concerns and aiming to protect American investors. The move signifies increased regulatory scrutiny for global companies operating within U.S. capital markets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:05:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a27785fa7d0695d1aff804_1772255410716.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Minerva Ventures Buys 8.58% Stake in Elitecon International</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Minerva-Ventures-Buys-858percent-Stake-in-Elitecon-International/69a27692fa7d0695d1aff720</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Minerva-Ventures-Buys-858percent-Stake-in-Elitecon-International/69a27692fa7d0695d1aff720</guid><description>Minerva Ventures Fund has acquired a substantial 8.5761% stake in Elitecon International Limited, comprising 137,088,605 shares. The investment, made through warrants and open market operations on February 27, 2026, signifies growing institutional interest in the tobacco and agro commodities player. This move could influence Elitecon's strategic direction.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:01:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a27692fa7d0695d1aff71f_1772254968721.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Power: ICRA Reaffirms 'AA; Stable' on ₹69,000 Crore Facilities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-ICRA-Reaffirms-AA-Stable-on-69000-Crore-Facilities/69a273c3fa7d0695d1aff5cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-ICRA-Reaffirms-AA-Stable-on-69000-Crore-Facilities/69a273c3fa7d0695d1aff5cf</guid><description>ICRA has reaffirmed Adani Power's 'ICRA AA; Stable' rating on its ₹58,000 crore bank facilities and assigned the same rating to ₹11,000 crore of proposed Non-Convertible Debentures. This brings the total rated credit facilities to ₹69,000 crore, underscoring the company's market leadership and strong operational efficiency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:49:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a273c3fa7d0695d1aff5ce_1772254458216.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Inflation Shock Rocks Markets; Fed Policy Dilemma Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Inflation-Shock-Rocks-Markets-Fed-Policy-Dilemma-Intensifies/69a271e8fa7d0695d1aff4cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Inflation-Shock-Rocks-Markets-Fed-Policy-Dilemma-Intensifies/69a271e8fa7d0695d1aff4cc</guid><description>A surprising jump in January Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) inflation has intensified Federal Reserve policy concerns, sending shockwaves through financial markets. The core PCE price index accelerated to 3.1% year-over-year, defying expectations of a continued disinflationary trend. This latest inflation print, coupled with ongoing debates about Artificial Intelligence's long-term impact on the labor market, creates a complex and uncertain outlook for interest rates and economic growth in 2026. The upcoming jobs report will be closely watched for further clues on the economy's resilience.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:41:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a271e8fa7d0695d1aff4cb_1772253792730.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CBI Probe Launched: Forged NOCs Spark Regulatory Overhaul Fears in Fuel Retail</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/CBI-Probe-Launched-Forged-NOCs-Spark-Regulatory-Overhaul-Fears-in-Fuel-Retail/69a27142fa7d0695d1aff3f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/CBI-Probe-Launched-Forged-NOCs-Spark-Regulatory-Overhaul-Fears-in-Fuel-Retail/69a27142fa7d0695d1aff3f1</guid><description>The Madras High Court has mandated a CBI investigation into a widespread racket involving forged No Objection Certificates (NOCs) used to secure explosive licenses for petrol stations across Tamil Nadu. This directive follows the court's finding that the state police investigation inadequately addressed the role of beneficiaries, who allegedly paid substantial sums for fraudulent documents. The probe signifies heightened regulatory oversight, potentially leading to stricter compliance requirements, license reviews, and increased operational risks for fuel retail operators and investors in the sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:38:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a27142fa7d0695d1aff3f0_1772253616370.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Tax Regime Shifts Focus from Tax Savings to Goals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-New-Tax-Regime-Shifts-Focus-from-Tax-Savings-to-Goals/69a270f2fa7d0695d1aff39c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-New-Tax-Regime-Shifts-Focus-from-Tax-Savings-to-Goals/69a270f2fa7d0695d1aff39c</guid><description>India's shift to a new tax regime has significantly altered the investment calculus for Public Provident Fund (PPF) and Equity Linked Savings Schemes (ELSS). With the removal of Section 80C deductions, the primary appeal of these instruments now rests on their inherent investment merits rather than tax advantages. This transition mandates a strategic re-evaluation, prioritizing goal-based planning and capital appreciation over mere tax arbitrage.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:37:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a270f2fa7d0695d1aff39b_1772253547535.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SpaceX Eyes Record IPO: Valuation Soars Amidst Visionary Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SpaceX-Eyes-Record-IPO-Valuation-Soars-Amidst-Visionary-Ambitions/69a2681efa7d0695d1aff067</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SpaceX-Eyes-Record-IPO-Valuation-Soars-Amidst-Visionary-Ambitions/69a2681efa7d0695d1aff067</guid><description>SpaceX is on track for a confidential IPO filing in March 2026, targeting a June listing with a valuation north of $1.75 trillion, potentially raising $50 billion. This would shatter existing records, with funds earmarked for Starship development, orbital AI data centers, and lunar base construction. Major financial institutions are slated to manage the offering, while a dual-class share structure is under consideration to maintain insider control. This move signals a significant shift in the space industry's public market presence, though questions linger regarding the sustainability of its lofty valuation against developmental risks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 03:59:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2681efa7d0695d1aff066_1772251275628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GDP Surge: New Math, Sectoral Splits, and Investor Realities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Surge-New-Math-Sectoral-Splits-and-Investor-Realities/69a263b2fa7d0695d1afeec5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Surge-New-Math-Sectoral-Splits-and-Investor-Realities/69a263b2fa7d0695d1afeec5</guid><description>India's economy grew 7.8% in Q3 FY26, bolstered by a revised GDP calculation framework with a 2022-23 base year. Manufacturing output surged 13.3%, with services expanding 9.5%, underscoring the economy's resilience. However, agriculture growth slowed to 1.4%, highlighting a widening sectoral divergence. This methodological overhaul, incorporating GST and administrative data, enhances accuracy but requires reassessment of historical performance, with FY24 growth now revised down to 7.2%. Consumer spending (8.7%) remains a key driver, while investment eased, indicating a recalibration of growth engines.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 03:40:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a263b2fa7d0695d1afeec4_1772250127907.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Lombard Rating Outlook Revised to Positive by AM Best</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/ICICI-Lombard-Rating-Outlook-Revised-to-Positive-by-AM-Best/69a261effa7d0695d1afeddb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/ICICI-Lombard-Rating-Outlook-Revised-to-Positive-by-AM-Best/69a261effa7d0695d1afeddb</guid><description>AM Best has upgraded the outlook on ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company's Financial Strength Rating (FSR) and Long-Term Issuer Credit Rating (ICR) to Positive from Stable. The company's ratings remain affirmed at B++ (Good) and "bbb+" (Good) respectively, with the India National Scale Rating (NSR) holding at aaa.IN (Exceptional). This move reflects AM Best's confidence in ICICI Lombard's robust capital generation and prudent capital management, which are expected to further strengthen its balance sheet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 03:33:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a261effa7d0695d1afedda_1772249690309.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>