<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:46:17 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Cyber Scammers Exploit Tax Refund Anxiety Amidst Rising Fraud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Cyber-Scammers-Exploit-Tax-Refund-Anxiety-Amidst-Rising-Fraud/699a7e96814271922101ff38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Cyber-Scammers-Exploit-Tax-Refund-Anxiety-Amidst-Rising-Fraud/699a7e96814271922101ff38</guid><description>Sophisticated scams are preying on taxpayer anxiety regarding income tax refunds. Fraudsters deploy fake messages and websites to steal sensitive information, leading to significant financial losses. Despite improved refund processing times by the Income Tax Department, the evolving tactics of cybercriminals necessitate heightened vigilance from citizens and continuous adaptation of government cybersecurity measures.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 03:57:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a7e96814271922101ff37_1771732757620.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Fraud: Rs 590 Cr Lost, Controls Scrutinized</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Rs-590-Cr-Lost-Controls-Scrutinized/699a778a814271922101fd95</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Rs-590-Cr-Lost-Controls-Scrutinized/699a778a814271922101fd95</guid><description>IDFC First Bank disclosed a significant internal breach involving unauthorized and fraudulent activities totaling Rs 590 crore, linked to Haryana government accounts at its Chandigarh branch. The incident, discovered starting February 18, 2026, has led to the suspension of four employees and the initiation of a forensic audit. This development casts a shadow over the bank's internal control mechanisms and operational integrity, prompting closer examination by investors and regulators.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a778a814271922101fd94_1771730950086.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Luxury Asset Correction: India's Growth Contrasts Global Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Luxury-Products/Luxury-Asset-Correction-Indias-Growth-Contrasts-Global-Slump/699a7712814271922101fd34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Luxury-Products/Luxury-Asset-Correction-Indias-Growth-Contrasts-Global-Slump/699a7712814271922101fd34</guid><description>The global luxury asset market, including prestige watches, rare whiskies, and fine wines, is experiencing a post-pandemic slowdown with prices falling 10-20% from peaks due to market normalization and reduced demand in key Western markets. Concurrently, India is witnessing significant growth in Swiss watch exports, rising over 35.5% in the first ten months of 2025, indicating a local expansion amidst a global correction. This divergence highlights a market bifurcation favoring assets with enduring cultural or technical value over those inflated by hype. Major luxury conglomerates like LVMH and Richemont reported revenue declines in 2025, reflecting the broader global trend, though both demonstrated resilience in profitability and cash flow. Swiss watch exports overall saw a 1.7% decrease in value for 2025, contrasting sharply with India's specific market surge.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 03:25:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a7712814271922101fd33_1771730891509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Drone Firms: Valuation vs. Reality Amidst Defence Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Drone-Firms-Valuation-vs-Reality-Amidst-Defence-Boom/699a6725814271922101f9b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Drone-Firms-Valuation-vs-Reality-Amidst-Defence-Boom/699a6725814271922101f9b2</guid><description>India's burgeoning drone sector sees Paras Defence and Space Technologies and Zen Technologies report strong Q3 FY26 results driven by defence orders. Paras Defence's revenue grew 24% and profit 21%, while Zen Technologies saw revenue up 16.8% and profit 38%. However, differing valuations, operational efficiencies, and mixed analyst outlooks create a complex investment narrative, especially as the broader defence sector faces valuation scrutiny post-Budget.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:17:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a6725814271922101f9b1_1771726841359.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Nuclear Boom: Investors bet on shaky giants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Nuclear-Boom-Investors-bet-on-shaky-giants/699a6721814271922101f99b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Nuclear-Boom-Investors-bet-on-shaky-giants/699a6721814271922101f99b</guid><description>India's SHANTI Act ends a 60-year state monopoly on atomic energy, paving the way for a projected ₹2 lakh crore industry aimed at achieving 100 GW by 2047. Prominent investors Mukul Agrawal and Ashish Kacholia are positioning themselves, backing companies from infrastructure giants like HCC to specialized component makers like Walchandnagar Industries, though many beneficiaries grapple with significant financial headwinds and valuation concerns.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a6721814271922101f99a_1771726832760.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Ethanol Glut: Policy Gap Fuels Farmer Distress</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Ethanol-Glut-Policy-Gap-Fuels-Farmer-Distress/699a4a13814271922101f48c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Ethanol-Glut-Policy-Gap-Fuels-Farmer-Distress/699a4a13814271922101f48c</guid><description>India's ethanol sector is crippled by a massive supply surplus, with installed capacity vastly exceeding demand for the E20 petrol blending mandate. This policy-driven imbalance strains the entire value chain, impacting farmers and leading to underutilization of distilleries. As the industry awaits clarity on higher blending targets, the complex technical challenges of integrating ethanol into diesel, India's dominant fuel, loom large. Companies like IOC and BPCL face pressure to absorb excess supply while navigating uncertain policy shifts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:13:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a4a13814271922101f48b_1771719387196.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>