<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:21 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Muthoot Finance: Rally Outpaces Gold, Analysts See Downside</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Rally-Outpaces-Gold-Analysts-See-Downside/698eab2a119a61fe896f0939</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Rally-Outpaces-Gold-Analysts-See-Downside/698eab2a119a61fe896f0939</guid><description>Muthoot Finance delivered robust Q3 FY26 results, driven by 50% year-over-year gold loan growth and improved asset quality. However, the company's stock has surged 90% in the past year, significantly outperforming gold's 70% rise and Nifty's 9%. This rally, coupled with gold price volatility, has led to a rating downgrade to 'Equal-weight' by some analysts, with recent price targets suggesting a potential downside. While the company benefits from strong structural demand for gold loans and favorable regulatory shifts, its valuation and the speculative nature of its recent stock performance warrant scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HAL Stock: Order Book Fuels Growth, But Execution Hurdles Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HAL-Stock-Order-Book-Fuels-Growth-But-Execution-Hurdles-Loom/698eab26119a61fe896f0931</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HAL-Stock-Order-Book-Fuels-Growth-But-Execution-Hurdles-Loom/698eab26119a61fe896f0931</guid><description>Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL) posted a robust 29.6% year-on-year net profit surge to ₹1,867 crore in Q3 FY26, supported by an 10.7% revenue increase to ₹7,699 crore. A massive order book of ₹2.5 lakh crore offers visibility through 2032. However, significant headwinds persist, including critical engine supply delays for the Tejas Mk1A fighter program and geopolitical complexities surrounding its partnership with Russia’s United Aircraft Corporation for SJ100 aircraft manufacturing. The company's diversification into the civil sector, while ambitious, introduces new competitive dynamics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>EaseMyTrip Buys AB Finance Via Discounted Share Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/EaseMyTrip-Buys-AB-Finance-Via-Discounted-Share-Issue/698eaaaa119a61fe896f0894</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/EaseMyTrip-Buys-AB-Finance-Via-Discounted-Share-Issue/698eaaaa119a61fe896f0894</guid><description>Easy Trip Planners Limited is set to acquire AB Finance Private Limited by issuing new shares at INR 9.19 each. The company has completed SEBI's mandatory valuation and disclosure requirements for this preferential issuance, which exceeds 5% of its post-issue share capital. This strategic move aims to expand the company's financial services arm.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:38:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eaaaa119a61fe896f0893.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Skid: AI Fears Spark IT Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Skid-AI-Fears-Spark-IT-Sell-Off/698ea8d4119a61fe896efdbd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Skid-AI-Fears-Spark-IT-Sell-Off/698ea8d4119a61fe896efdbd</guid><description>Indian equity markets witnessed a steep sell-off on February 13, 2026, with the Sensex falling 683.72 points to 82,991.20 and the Nifty 50 dropping 207.15 points to 25,600.05. This downturn was primarily fueled by growing concerns over artificial intelligence's disruptive potential, leading to a significant sell-off in the heavily weighted Information Technology sector. Global market weakness and fading optimism regarding near-term interest rate cuts also contributed to the negative sentiment, overshadowing India's otherwise robust economic growth outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lupin's Profit Hit by US Litigation Despite Strong Sales</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupins-Profit-Hit-by-US-Litigation-Despite-Strong-Sales/698ea859119a61fe896efd0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupins-Profit-Hit-by-US-Litigation-Despite-Strong-Sales/698ea859119a61fe896efd0b</guid><description>Lupin Limited's Q3FY26 results showcased a 28% year-on-year revenue surge to ₹7,167.5 crore and an 87% EBITDA jump to ₹2,261.9 crore, driven by record US sales of $350 million and robust emerging market growth. However, net profit declined sequentially by 20.5% to ₹1,180.5 crore, impacted by ₹426.57 crore in exceptional items including provisions for US litigation and settlements. Despite operational strengths, Morgan Stanley maintained an 'Equal-weight' rating, highlighting investor focus on the profitability headwinds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mamaearth Parent Surges on Record Quarter Amidst Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mamaearth-Parent-Surges-on-Record-Quarter-Amidst-Valuation-Scrutiny/698ea858119a61fe896efd03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mamaearth-Parent-Surges-on-Record-Quarter-Amidst-Valuation-Scrutiny/698ea858119a61fe896efd03</guid><description>Honasa Consumer, the parent of Mamaearth, saw its shares climb on Friday, February 13, following a reported record quarter marked by a 16% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹601.5 crore and a dramatic EBITDA margin expansion to 10.9%. Underlying volume growth surged 30.2%. Despite robust operational figures and a constructive management outlook, analyst sentiment remains divided. Jefferies maintains a 'Buy' with a ₹500 target, while HSBC retains a 'Reduce' rating at ₹260, citing growth on a low base. The stock, trading at a P/E of approximately 72-74x, remains below its IPO price of ₹324, indicating lingering investor caution on long-term growth sustainability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Unlocks 100% FDI in Insurance Amid Sweeping Law Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Unlocks-100percent-FDI-in-Insurance-Amid-Sweeping-Law-Overhaul/698ea76e119a61fe896efc0f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Unlocks-100percent-FDI-in-Insurance-Amid-Sweeping-Law-Overhaul/698ea76e119a61fe896efc0f</guid><description>India has enacted the "Sabka Bima Sabki Raksha" (Amendment of Insurance Laws) Act, 2025, bringing significant changes to its insurance sector. The landmark legislation permits 100% foreign direct investment under the automatic route, removes the mandatory joint venture requirement, and substantially enhances the regulatory and enforcement powers of the Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority of India (IRDAI). Reforms also streamline share transfer approvals and explicitly allow mergers with non-insurance entities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PFC Finances Hybrid Power Hub with Storage Integration</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/PFC-Finances-Hybrid-Power-Hub-with-Storage-Integration/698ea766119a61fe896efc07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/PFC-Finances-Hybrid-Power-Hub-with-Storage-Integration/698ea766119a61fe896efc07</guid><description>Power Finance Corporation (PFC) has sanctioned a ₹2,046.24 crore term loan for ACME Urja One Private Limited's 380 MW hybrid renewable energy project in Andhra Pradesh and Madhya Pradesh. This financing supports a significant component of solar, wind, and battery energy storage systems (BESS), underscoring a move towards reliable, dispatchable renewable power and enhanced grid stability. The project comprises 406 MWp/280 MW solar capacity with 600 MWh BESS in Andhra Pradesh and 64 MW wind capacity with 40 MWh BESS in Madhya Pradesh. Shardul Amarchand Mangaldas &amp; Co advised PFC on the transaction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NSE Hits 25 Cr Accounts: Record Growth, Rising Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/NSE-Hits-25-Cr-Accounts-Record-Growth-Rising-Risks/698ea5ff119a61fe896efa7e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/NSE-Hits-25-Cr-Accounts-Record-Growth-Rising-Risks/698ea5ff119a61fe896efa7e</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange of India has crossed a significant milestone, registering over 25 crore trading accounts by February 2026. This rapid expansion, adding 10 crore accounts in just 16 months, highlights accelerating investor participation driven by digitization, fintech, and rising confidence. Maharashtra leads with 4.2 crore accounts. While this surge democratizes capital markets and enhances liquidity, it also amplifies concerns over market volatility, potential speculative trading, and the imperative for robust financial literacy and regulatory oversight to ensure sustainable wealth creation. The Nifty 50 and Nifty 500 delivered strong annualized returns over the past five years, further fueling household investment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Silver Plunges as Margin Hikes Fuel Volatility Amid Fed Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Plunges-as-Margin-Hikes-Fuel-Volatility-Amid-Fed-Uncertainty/698ea5fd119a61fe896efa76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Plunges-as-Margin-Hikes-Fuel-Volatility-Amid-Fed-Uncertainty/698ea5fd119a61fe896efa76</guid><description>Silver experienced a sharp, &gt;10% decline on February 12, 2026, reversing gains amid extreme volatility. This sell-off was amplified by CME Group's margin hike on silver futures, exacerbating price swings. Investors are closely monitoring upcoming US inflation data and Federal Reserve signals, which have tempered expectations for immediate interest rate cuts and bolstered the US dollar, pressuring precious metals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance AI Bet: Revenue Surge Meets Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finance-AI-Bet-Revenue-Surge-Meets-Margin-Squeeze/698ea588119a61fe896efa37</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finance-AI-Bet-Revenue-Surge-Meets-Margin-Squeeze/698ea588119a61fe896efa37</guid><description>Bajaj Finance's aggressive AI strategy is yielding substantial business gains, with Vice Chairman Rajeev Jain reporting ₹1,600 crore generated from analyzing 20 million customer calls. The company plans to scale this to 100 million calls in the upcoming fiscal year, leveraging AI for enhanced customer engagement and revenue. However, this significant investment occurs against a backdrop of tightening profit margins and a high debt-to-equity ratio, raising questions about the long-term efficiency and sustainability of its ambitious AI expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IT Stocks Tumble on AI Fears; Valuations Face Reset</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-Tumble-on-AI-Fears-Valuations-Face-Reset/698ea536119a61fe896ef983</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-Tumble-on-AI-Fears-Valuations-Face-Reset/698ea536119a61fe896ef983</guid><description>Indian IT giants Infosys, TCS, and Tech Mahindra experienced a sharp sell-off on February 12, 2026, as Artificial Intelligence's impact on traditional outsourcing models intensified investor concerns. The broader market saw significant losses, with the Sensex dropping 559 points and investor wealth shrinking by approximately ₹2.5 lakh crore. TCS's market valuation dipped below the ₹10 lakh crore mark, highlighting the profound shift underway.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Faze Three Revenue Soars 28%, But Tariffs Squeeze Profits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Faze-Three-Revenue-Soars-28percent-But-Tariffs-Squeeze-Profits/698ea41c119a61fe896ef81f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Faze-Three-Revenue-Soars-28percent-But-Tariffs-Squeeze-Profits/698ea41c119a61fe896ef81f</guid><description>Faze Three Limited reported a strong 28.68% year-on-year revenue jump to ₹229.3 Cr in the third quarter ending December 31, 2025. However, profitability faced pressure, with EBITDA falling 4.24% and PAT declining 28.09%. This margin compression was attributed to trade policy volatility and US tariffs. Despite these challenges, the company anticipates continued high growth in the next fiscal year, supported by trade deals, and plans incremental expansion investments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:10:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ea41c119a61fe896ef81e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Finance Board Approves MUFG Nominees for Director Posts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Board-Approves-MUFG-Nominees-for-Director-Posts/698ea2b7119a61fe896ef5f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Board-Approves-MUFG-Nominees-for-Director-Posts/698ea2b7119a61fe896ef5f9</guid><description>Shriram Finance Limited's Board of Directors has deemed nominees from MUFG Bank, Mr. Morihiko Fuji and Mr. Shinichi Fujinami, as 'fit and proper' for appointment as Additional Non-Executive and Non-Independent Directors. This key step is contingent upon the successful completion of MUFG Bank's proposed acquisition of a 20% stake in Shriram Finance and subsequent approval from the Reserve Bank of India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:04:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ea2b7119a61fe896ef5f8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BDL Stock: Export Ambitions Mask Execution Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/BDL-Stock-Export-Ambitions-Mask-Execution-Risks/698ea2b2119a61fe896ef5f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/BDL-Stock-Export-Ambitions-Mask-Execution-Risks/698ea2b2119a61fe896ef5f0</guid><description>Bharat Dynamics Ltd (BDL) stock presents a complex picture. While recent order inflows and ambitious export targets suggest growth potential, a significant Q3 revenue and profit decline highlights execution challenges. The company's aggressive capacity expansion and global footprint goals, coupled with current valuations, warrant a deeper examination beyond immediate tactical opportunities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Muthoot Finance: Record Q3 Results Face Market Skepticism Amid Sector Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Record-Q3-Results-Face-Market-Skepticism-Amid-Sector-Headwinds/698ea157119a61fe896ef424</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Record-Q3-Results-Face-Market-Skepticism-Amid-Sector-Headwinds/698ea157119a61fe896ef424</guid><description>Muthoot Finance reported record loan assets under management (AUM) of ₹1.64 trillion, up 48% year-on-year, and a consolidated profit after tax (PAT) of ₹7,209 crore for the nine months ending December 31, 2025. Despite these strong figures and a 98% year-on-year rise in Q3 PAT to ₹27 billion, the stock experienced a 5% pre-open decline. While brokerages like Jefferies and CLSA maintain positive ratings, citing operating leverage and supportive gold prices, market participants are scrutinizing sequential net interest margin (NIM) compression and a dip in gold tonnage, alongside broader Non-Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI Accuses Chinese Rival of AI Model Theft</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAI-Accuses-Chinese-Rival-of-AI-Model-Theft/698ea114119a61fe896ef3d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAI-Accuses-Chinese-Rival-of-AI-Model-Theft/698ea114119a61fe896ef3d0</guid><description>OpenAI has alerted U.S. lawmakers to alleged 'distillation' tactics by Chinese AI startup DeepSeek, accusing the company of illicitly replicating advanced AI models. This accusation highlights the escalating geopolitical tensions in the AI race, where intellectual property acquisition and rapid development by Chinese firms pose significant challenges to U.S. technological dominance. The practice of AI model distillation, while a legitimate efficiency technique, is presented here as a method for competitive shortcutting, intensifying concerns over fairness and national security in the global AI landscape. Major U.S. AI players like NVIDIA, Alphabet, and Microsoft remain key figures amidst this intensifying competition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:57:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindalco: Novelis Debt Surge Masks Strong India Ops &amp; Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindalco-Novelis-Debt-Surge-Masks-Strong-India-Ops-and-Margins/698ea0da119a61fe896ef3bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindalco-Novelis-Debt-Surge-Masks-Strong-India-Ops-and-Margins/698ea0da119a61fe896ef3bc</guid><description>Hindalco Industries Ltd. saw its shares decline as concerns mounted over its subsidiary Novelis's escalating debt, projected to reach $8 billion. This leverage issue, coupled with near-term earnings pressure from operational disruptions like the Oswego plant fires, has overshadowed the company's otherwise resilient operational performance. Hindalco's Indian business reported record profits, and its upstream aluminium segment boasts world-class EBITDA margins, suggesting a potential disconnect between short-term headwinds and long-term structural strengths. The current valuation metrics also point towards fair pricing, potentially offering an investment opportunity for those looking beyond immediate challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NATCO Pharma Gets US FDA VAI Report for Chennai API Unit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/NATCO-Pharma-Gets-US-FDA-VAI-Report-for-Chennai-API-Unit/698e9fe4119a61fe896ef2f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/NATCO-Pharma-Gets-US-FDA-VAI-Report-for-Chennai-API-Unit/698e9fe4119a61fe896ef2f2</guid><description>NATCO Pharma has received a Voluntary Action Indicated (VAI) report from the U.S. FDA for its API unit in Manali, Chennai. The inspection, held in November 2025, resulted in seven observations. This classification indicates that while issues were found, they are not severe enough for immediate enforcement, and the company is expected to address them voluntarily. This news comes amidst NATCO's history of U.S. FDA scrutiny, including a warning letter for another facility in early 2024.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:52:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e9fe4119a61fe896ef2f1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Analyst Rally Masks Sector Risks for Indian Firms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Analyst-Rally-Masks-Sector-Risks-for-Indian-Firms/698e9db1119a61fe896ef149</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Analyst-Rally-Masks-Sector-Risks-for-Indian-Firms/698e9db1119a61fe896ef149</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra (M&amp;M) is lauded for UV leadership and projected EBITDA growth, while Hindalco Industries faces scrutiny over its plant commissioning timeline amidst operational fires. Divi's Laboratories is recognized for strong EBITDA gains and future product visibility. Lenskart is noted for exceptional growth and margin expansion. Ashok Leyland is poised for CV cycle revival. However, deeper analysis reveals potential margin compression, execution risks, and competitive intensity across these diverse sectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HUL Stock Dips Despite Demerger Gain; Operational Growth Lags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Stock-Dips-Despite-Demerger-Gain-Operational-Growth-Lags/698e9d1c119a61fe896ef058</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Stock-Dips-Despite-Demerger-Gain-Operational-Growth-Lags/698e9d1c119a61fe896ef058</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever's Q3 FY26 net profit more than doubled to ₹7,075 crore, largely driven by an ice cream business demerger gain. However, underlying operational profit grew only 1% to ₹2,570 crore on a 5.7% revenue increase, while the stock declined 2.1%. Investors are scrutinizing margin pressures from input costs and a rich valuation, despite positive sector-wide demand recovery. HUL's market capitalization stands at approximately ₹5.78 trillion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Transrail Lighting Lands ₹2,350 Cr Orders, Bolstering FY26 Inflows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Transrail-Lighting-Lands-2350-Cr-Orders-Bolstering-FY26-Inflows/698e9c9d119a61fe896eefc7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Transrail-Lighting-Lands-2350-Cr-Orders-Bolstering-FY26-Inflows/698e9c9d119a61fe896eefc7</guid><description>Transrail Lighting Limited has secured new domestic EPC orders worth ₹2,350 crore, primarily in the Transmission &amp; Distribution (T&amp;D) segment. These wins, alongside other segments, significantly boost its cumulative order inflows for FY26 to over ₹7,980 crore. Management expresses confidence in sustaining growth momentum, backed by a strong bidding pipeline exceeding ₹800 crore in L1 positions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e9c9d119a61fe896eefc6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Radhagobind Commercial Faces Forensic Audit Amidst Insolvency Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Radhagobind-Commercial-Faces-Forensic-Audit-Amidst-Insolvency-Crisis/698e9a43119a61fe896ee385</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Radhagobind-Commercial-Faces-Forensic-Audit-Amidst-Insolvency-Crisis/698e9a43119a61fe896ee385</guid><description>Radhagobind Commercial Limited is set to hold its 4th Committee of Creditors (COC) meeting on February 14, 2026. A key agenda item is the appointment of forensic auditors, signalling a deep dive into the company's past financial dealings. The company is currently undergoing the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) following a loan default.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:28:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e9a43119a61fe896ee384.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apple Stock Plummets 5% on AI Delay, News App Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apple-Stock-Plummets-5percent-on-AI-Delay-News-App-Scrutiny/698e99eb119a61fe896ee359</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apple-Stock-Plummets-5percent-on-AI-Delay-News-App-Scrutiny/698e99eb119a61fe896ee359</guid><description>Apple's stock experienced its worst trading session in nearly a year, shedding 5% and erasing year-to-date gains as reports surfaced of significant delays to its AI-powered Siri upgrade. This downturn was compounded by Federal Trade Commission scrutiny of Apple News's content curation policies, raising concerns about political bias. The sell-off occurred despite Apple exceeding Q1 earnings expectations, highlighting market sensitivity to execution risks and regulatory challenges within the broader AI-driven tech sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Fears Trigger IT Sell-off Amidst Mixed Q3 Earnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AI-Fears-Trigger-IT-Sell-off-Amidst-Mixed-Q3-Earnings/698e99e3119a61fe896ee351</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AI-Fears-Trigger-IT-Sell-off-Amidst-Mixed-Q3-Earnings/698e99e3119a61fe896ee351</guid><description>Indian equity markets anticipate a downbeat opening, mirroring global anxieties over AI's disruptive potential, which has severely impacted IT stocks. While several sectors reported varied Q3 financial outcomes, the sharp decline in Infosys and Wipro's American Depositary Receipts highlights a growing divergence in market sentiment. Companies in pharmaceuticals, FMCG, and mining are demonstrating resilience, contrasting with the pronounced vulnerability within the technology sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Global EV Sales Dip 3%; Policy Shifts Fuel Regional Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Global-EV-Sales-Dip-3percent-Policy-Shifts-Fuel-Regional-Divergence/698e9909119a61fe896ee294</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Global-EV-Sales-Dip-3percent-Policy-Shifts-Fuel-Regional-Divergence/698e9909119a61fe896ee294</guid><description>Global electric vehicle registrations declined 3% in January 2026, primarily driven by policy shifts and tax changes in China and the U.S. North America experienced a sharp 33% decrease, while China saw a 20% contraction. Conversely, Europe and the rest of the world posted growth, albeit at a slower pace for Europe. The rising popularity of hybrid vehicles presents a complex dynamic for pure EV adoption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:22:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ATLAS Company Misses Q3 Results Amidst Board Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/ATLAS-Company-Misses-Q3-Results-Amidst-Board-Crisis/698e942c119a61fe896ede9f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/ATLAS-Company-Misses-Q3-Results-Amidst-Board-Crisis/698e942c119a61fe896ede9f</guid><description>ATLAS Company has informed the BSE that it cannot approve its unaudited standalone financial results for the third quarter of FY26 by the February 14 deadline. The company cites a severe governance crisis, with all directors having ceased their roles, leading to a non-compliant Board and Audit Committee. An application is now before the NCLT to appoint new directors, delaying the financial reporting until statutory requirements are met.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:02:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e942c119a61fe896ede9e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bangladesh Election Introduces Economic Uncertainty, Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Bangladesh-Election-Introduces-Economic-Uncertainty-Market-Volatility/698e93d1119a61fe896ede6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Bangladesh-Election-Introduces-Economic-Uncertainty-Market-Volatility/698e93d1119a61fe896ede6e</guid><description>Bangladesh's recent elections and political transition have amplified economic uncertainty, projecting a volatile outlook for regional markets. Key indicators like GDP growth forecasts show divergence among international bodies, while inflation remains stubbornly high. Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) has seen a notable decline, particularly in new equity, raising concerns about future capital inflows. The vital garment sector, the nation's primary export earner, faces headwinds from tariffs and domestic instability. Geopolitical competition, especially from China's significant investment, and evolving trade dynamics with India and the US add further complexity to Bangladesh's economic future. The banking sector's fragility and the impending loss of LDC status present significant risks that demand structural reforms beyond electoral outcomes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Tax Courts Prioritize Substance Over Form in Treaties</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/India-Tax-Courts-Prioritize-Substance-Over-Form-in-Treaties/698e93cc119a61fe896ede62</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/India-Tax-Courts-Prioritize-Substance-Over-Form-in-Treaties/698e93cc119a61fe896ede62</guid><description>Supreme Court Justice R. Mahadevan stressed the need for "substance over form" in tax treaty interpretation, particularly for foreign entities, to prevent tax avoidance disguised as genuine investment. This judicial pivot, highlighted by recent rulings like the Tiger Global-Flipkart deal, signals increased scrutiny on cross-border investment structures and their compliance with international tax agreements, potentially affecting future foreign direct investment flows into India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Coinbase Earnings: Diversification Fails to Shield from Crypto Winter</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coinbase-Earnings-Diversification-Fails-to-Shield-from-Crypto-Winter/698e935f119a61fe896eddc0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coinbase-Earnings-Diversification-Fails-to-Shield-from-Crypto-Winter/698e935f119a61fe896eddc0</guid><description>Coinbase Global Inc. plunged into a $667 million net loss for the fourth quarter, with revenue dropping over 20% to $1.8 billion as cryptocurrency trading dried up. The exchange's stock, down 37% year-to-date, showed little sustained reaction to the results. This performance highlights the persistent vulnerability of Coinbase's business model to crypto market cycles, despite recent efforts to diversify revenue streams beyond spot trading. Competitors like Gemini and Robinhood are also signaling distress, underscoring the industry-wide impact of the ongoing 'crypto winter'.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Q3 Earnings Climax: Sectoral Divergence Signals Market Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Q3-Earnings-Climax-Sectoral-Divergence-Signals-Market-Shift/698e92ce119a61fe896edd80</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Q3-Earnings-Climax-Sectoral-Divergence-Signals-Market-Shift/698e92ce119a61fe896edd80</guid><description>India's December quarter earnings season culminates today with over thirty companies reporting across pharmaceuticals, metals, energy, IT, and consumer sectors. Investors scrutinize diverse performance metrics and management commentary for forward guidance, potentially uncovering divergent sector trends and underlying market sentiment shifts. The sheer volume of announcements necessitates a deeper analysis beyond headline figures to identify sector-specific strengths and emerging risks in the current economic climate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Xiaomi YU7 Outsales Tesla Model Y in China EV Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Xiaomi-YU7-Outsales-Tesla-Model-Y-in-China-EV-Race/698e9254119a61fe896edced</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Xiaomi-YU7-Outsales-Tesla-Model-Y-in-China-EV-Race/698e9254119a61fe896edced</guid><description>Xiaomi's YU7 SUV emerged as China's top-selling vehicle in January 2026, delivering 37,869 units and surpassing Tesla's Model Y by a significant margin. This marks a critical shift in the competitive electric vehicle landscape, with Tesla's domestic sales declining while its Shanghai plant increasingly serves as an export hub. The overall Chinese new energy vehicle market experienced its first year-on-year contraction in two years, influenced by tax policy changes and subsidy expirations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Forge: Analyst Rift Over Q3 Signals Divergent Market View</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Forge-Analyst-Rift-Over-Q3-Signals-Divergent-Market-View/698e924e119a61fe896edce5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Forge-Analyst-Rift-Over-Q3-Signals-Divergent-Market-View/698e924e119a61fe896edce5</guid><description>Bharat Forge posted robust Q3 FY26 results with consolidated net profit up 28% year-on-year to ₹273 crore on revenue growth of 25% to ₹4,343 crore. However, the company faced margin compression and a decline in standalone performance due to exceptional costs. This performance has triggered a sharp divergence among analysts, with Jefferies upgrading to 'Buy' citing improving operational outlook and defense strength, while Citi maintains a 'Sell' rating due to weaker export revenues and high valuations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Rebound Amid Fed Policy Crosscurrents, Indian ETFs Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rebound-Amid-Fed-Policy-Crosscurrents-Indian-ETFs-Surge/698e9242119a61fe896edcc0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rebound-Amid-Fed-Policy-Crosscurrents-Indian-ETFs-Surge/698e9242119a61fe896edcc0</guid><description>Precious metals regained ground Friday after a significant sell-off on Thursday, driven by stronger-than-expected US January jobs data which tempered expectations for immediate Federal Reserve rate cuts. Nonfarm payrolls rose by 130,000, and the unemployment rate dipped to 4.3%, reinforcing concerns of prolonged higher interest rates. Concurrently, Indian investors are demonstrating a pronounced shift towards regulated gold and silver ETFs, seeking transparency and safety amid market volatility. This trend is amplified by platforms utilizing the Open Network for Digital Commerce (ONDC), signaling evolving investment behavior in a complex macroeconomic environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Fear Fuels IT Sell-off; Broader Indian Market Shows Resilience</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fear-Fuels-IT-Sell-off-Broader-Indian-Market-Shows-Resilience/698e908e119a61fe896edbcc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fear-Fuels-IT-Sell-off-Broader-Indian-Market-Shows-Resilience/698e908e119a61fe896edbcc</guid><description>Indian equity markets are poised for a negative opening, mirroring global technology sell-offs driven by intensified artificial intelligence disruption concerns. This sell-off has led to significant market capitalisation erosion, particularly within the IT sector. However, sustained foreign and domestic institutional investment in non-IT segments is providing a crucial buffer, suggesting a phase of cautious consolidation rather than broad-based market damage. Derivative data indicates a tightly defined trading range, with defined resistance and support levels shaping near-term price action.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI pilots e-Rupee for KCC, eyes rural credit transformation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/RBI-pilots-e-Rupee-for-KCC-eyes-rural-credit-transformation/698e8f0d119a61fe896edae0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/RBI-pilots-e-Rupee-for-KCC-eyes-rural-credit-transformation/698e8f0d119a61fe896edae0</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has unveiled draft directions to overhaul the Kisan Credit Card (KCC) scheme, proposing the integration of the e-Rupee for farm credit. This initiative aims to enhance flexibility and safeguards for small farmers through digital channels like UPI and programmable currency features. The proposals also introduce enhanced borrower protections, including interest rate caps and relaxed collateral rules, redefining KCC as a six-year composite credit facility for diverse agricultural needs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's New CPI Series: A Moderate Facade or Shifting Inflationary Reality?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-CPI-Series-A-Moderate-Facade-or-Shifting-Inflationary-Reality/698e8e91119a61fe896eda2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-CPI-Series-A-Moderate-Facade-or-Shifting-Inflationary-Reality/698e8e91119a61fe896eda2a</guid><description>India's National Statistics Office has unveiled a new Consumer Price Index (CPI) series, recalibrating the base year to 2024 and reducing food and beverage weights to 36.75% from 45.86%. January retail inflation registered at 2.75% under this updated framework, contrasting with the 1.33% reported in December under the old series. However, a stark surge in silver jewelry prices, up nearly 160%, alongside significant gains in gold, points to a potential divergence between headline inflation and broader economic sentiment, possibly masked by the methodological shift. Analysts suggest this recalibration may temper future inflation forecasts, while acknowledging the continued upward pressure from precious metals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Technical Buys: Tata Power, Manappuram Face Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Technical-Buys-Tata-Power-Manappuram-Face-Valuation-Scrutiny/698e8e8e119a61fe896eda21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Technical-Buys-Tata-Power-Manappuram-Face-Valuation-Scrutiny/698e8e8e119a61fe896eda21</guid><description>Bajaj Broking has identified Tata Power and Manappuram Finance as top stock picks, citing technical indicators suggesting potential upward movement over a three-month horizon. However, a deeper financial assessment reveals significant valuation concerns and operational challenges for both companies, contrasting sharply with their optimistic technical outlooks. Manappuram Finance trades at a considerable premium to its peers, while Tata Power contends with plant-specific losses and high leverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IndiGo's Fleet Ambition Faces Air India's Resurgence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-Fleet-Ambition-Faces-Air-Indias-Resurgence/698e8b47119a61fe896eb40f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-Fleet-Ambition-Faces-Air-Indias-Resurgence/698e8b47119a61fe896eb40f</guid><description>IndiGo CEO Pieter Elbers reaffirmed ambitious fleet expansion targets from 440 to over 600 aircraft by 2030. However, this strategy unfolds against a backdrop of a resurgent Air India, presenting a stark contrast to previous market dominance. This dynamic shift suggests intensified competition and a potential reassessment of IndiGo's competitive posture in one of the world's fastest-growing air travel markets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Shriram Properties Settles Bengal Land Dispute, Unlocking Township Potential</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Shriram-Properties-Settles-Bengal-Land-Dispute-Unlocking-Township-Potential/698e8acc119a61fe896eb3d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Shriram-Properties-Settles-Bengal-Land-Dispute-Unlocking-Township-Potential/698e8acc119a61fe896eb3d4</guid><description>Shriram Properties has resolved a decade-long land dispute with the Bengal government, involving the settlement of a ₹240 crore liability and the cession of 42.37 acres. This pivotal agreement enables expedited development of its 314-acre Uttarpara township project near Kolkata. The resolution removes a significant overhang, allowing the company to focus on developing 5-6 million sq ft of its own projects and monetize remaining land parcels, potentially reviving stalled partnership discussions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>