<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:45:18 +0000</pubDate><item><title>SC Demands SIT in RCOM Fraud Probe, Anil Ambani Faces Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SC-Demands-SIT-in-RCOM-Fraud-Probe-Anil-Ambani-Faces-Scrutiny/6982e794f5a3f0ebac991af5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SC-Demands-SIT-in-RCOM-Fraud-Probe-Anil-Ambani-Faces-Scrutiny/6982e794f5a3f0ebac991af5</guid><description>The Supreme Court has ordered the Enforcement Directorate (ED) to form a Special Investigation Team (SIT) to expedite the probe into allegations of a massive ₹1.78 lakh crore bank fraud involving Reliance Communications (RCOM) and Anil Ambani. The court expressed dissatisfaction with the investigation's pace by the ED and CBI, demanding faster resolution and periodic updates. Anil Ambani's counsel provided an undertaking that he would not leave the country. The CBI is also directed to investigate potential collusion by bank officials. This escalation intensifies scrutiny on the Anil Ambani group, which is already under extensive ED action with over ₹12,000 crore in assets attached across group entities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:34:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982e794f5a3f0ebac991af4_1770186844914.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Services Boom Fuels Netflix Growth: Local Strategy Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Services-Boom-Fuels-Netflix-Growth-Local-Strategy-Key/6982e6c7f5a3f0ebac9917fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Services-Boom-Fuels-Netflix-Growth-Local-Strategy-Key/6982e6c7f5a3f0ebac9917fb</guid><description>India's services sector is experiencing robust expansion, evidenced by a January Services PMI of 58.5, driven by strong new orders and improved business sentiment. This macroeconomic strength, coupled with easing inflation, provides a favorable backdrop for digital services. Netflix, with its decade-long commitment to localized content and pricing strategies in India, is well-positioned to capitalize on this growth, despite a competitive market. The company's current valuation and analyst consensus suggest confidence in its future prospects within this key emerging market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:32:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982e6c7f5a3f0ebac9917fa_1770186730422.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Nuclear Surge: Growth for L&amp;T, NTPC, Tata Power Amidst Capital Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Nuclear-Surge-Growth-for-LandT-NTPC-Tata-Power-Amidst-Capital-Hurdles/6982e775f5a3f0ebac991a4e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Nuclear-Surge-Growth-for-LandT-NTPC-Tata-Power-Amidst-Capital-Hurdles/6982e775f5a3f0ebac991a4e</guid><description>India's ambitious nuclear power expansion, aiming for over 22,000 MW by 2032 and 100 GW by 2047, is driving significant opportunities for engineering giant Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T), power producer NTPC, and utility firm Tata Power. Bolstered by government policy, including extended duty exemptions for nuclear projects, these companies are positioned to benefit from the shift towards clean, baseload energy. However, the sector's inherent capital intensity, long project timelines, and complex regulatory environment present substantial execution risks that could temper aggressive growth projections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India-China Trade Hits Record $155B Amid Deficit Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-China-Trade-Hits-Record-155B-Amid-Deficit-Concerns/6982e6a6f5a3f0ebac99170f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-China-Trade-Hits-Record-155B-Amid-Deficit-Concerns/6982e6a6f5a3f0ebac99170f</guid><description>Bilateral trade between India and China surged to a record $155.6 billion in 2025, marking a 12% year-on-year increase following the easing of post-Galwan tensions and improved diplomatic engagement. This growth, however, is overshadowed by India's widening trade deficit, which hit a new high of $116.12 billion, underscoring continued reliance on Chinese manufactured goods and creating an asymmetric economic relationship. While diplomatic efforts aim to foster mutual benefit, the structural imbalance remains a critical factor for investors monitoring the region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:29:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982e6a6f5a3f0ebac99170e_1770186567194.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PFC Q3 Results: Dividend Focus Amidst Valuation Puzzle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFC-Q3-Results-Dividend-Focus-Amidst-Valuation-Puzzle/6982e591f5a3f0ebac9913d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFC-Q3-Results-Dividend-Focus-Amidst-Valuation-Puzzle/6982e591f5a3f0ebac9913d6</guid><description>Power Finance Corporation Ltd. is poised to unveil its third-quarter and nine-month financial results for FY26 on February 5th. The board will also consider a third interim dividend for the fiscal year. Shareholders are scrutinizing these announcements to gauge performance momentum, dividend potential, and the company's valuation relative to its peers and the broader non-banking financial company (NBFC) sector, especially following recent mixed stock performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:28:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982e591f5a3f0ebac9913d5_1770186487145.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US-India Trade Truce: 18% Tariff Cut Signals Strategic Rebalance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-India-Trade-Truce-18percent-Tariff-Cut-Signals-Strategic-Rebalance/6982e688f5a3f0ebac991647</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-India-Trade-Truce-18percent-Tariff-Cut-Signals-Strategic-Rebalance/6982e688f5a3f0ebac991647</guid><description>The United States and India finalized a trade agreement on February 4, 2026, reducing tariffs on Indian goods to 18% and eliminating a 25% penalty on Russian oil purchases. This accord, emerging after significant diplomatic engagement, aims to reset bilateral ties. It highlights India's strategic objective to balance US economic requirements with its pursuit of geopolitical autonomy and diversified trade partnerships. The deal is anticipated to sustain substantial US investment in critical Indian sectors like AI and electronics.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Overhauls Bank Supervision, Prioritizing Business Models &amp; Cyber Defense</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Overhauls-Bank-Supervision-Prioritizing-Business-Models-and-Cyber-Defense/6982e51bf5a3f0ebac99126d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Overhauls-Bank-Supervision-Prioritizing-Business-Models-and-Cyber-Defense/6982e51bf5a3f0ebac99126d</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is revamping its lender supervision framework, moving beyond traditional ratio analysis to a deeper scrutiny of banks' business models. This strategic shift, driven by the sector's rapid expansion and escalating digital threats, includes a significant increase in hiring cybersecurity specialists. The initiative aims to proactively identify vulnerabilities, learning from past governance failures and adapting to the complexities of modern financial operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982e51bf5a3f0ebac99126c_1770186324206.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCLTech's Aerospace Bet: HAESL Deal Fuels Niche Specialization</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTechs-Aerospace-Bet-HAESL-Deal-Fuels-Niche-Specialization/6982e33ff5a3f0ebac990f65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTechs-Aerospace-Bet-HAESL-Deal-Fuels-Niche-Specialization/6982e33ff5a3f0ebac990f65</guid><description>HCLTech Ltd. has been selected by Hong Kong Aero Engine Services Limited (HAESL) for a comprehensive digital transformation of its aviation maintenance, repair, and overhaul (MRO) operations. This strategic partnership deploys HCLTech's iMRO/4 solution integrated with SAP S/4HANA to modernize HAESL's engine maintenance execution. The deal aims to enhance real-time data visibility, improve efficiency, and ensure global aviation standard compliance, reinforcing HCLTech's position in the specialized aerospace sector. Despite a 6% sequential revenue increase and improved margins reported for Q3FY26, the company's shares saw a notable dip following the announcement, reflecting broader market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:24:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982e33ff5a3f0ebac990f64_1770186283953.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Cut Sparks Textile Stock Rally, Analyst Caution Remains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/US-Tariff-Cut-Sparks-Textile-Stock-Rally-Analyst-Caution-Remains/6982e2c9f5a3f0ebac990de0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/US-Tariff-Cut-Sparks-Textile-Stock-Rally-Analyst-Caution-Remains/6982e2c9f5a3f0ebac990de0</guid><description>Indian textile stocks experienced a significant rally, with shares like Gokaldas Exports and Indo Count Industries climbing up to 20% and 44% over two trading sessions. This surge followed the United States' announcement to reduce tariffs on Indian textile exports from 50% to 18%. Analysts at ICICI Securities and others see this as a multi-year advantage, enhancing earnings and export potential, especially as India gains a competitive edge over other Asian nations. However, lingering uncertainties and the need for margin expansion beyond tariff arbitrage are key considerations for sustained growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982e2c9f5a3f0ebac990ddf_1770186101890.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dalio's Capital War Warning: How Geopolitics Weaponizes Finance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Dalios-Capital-War-Warning-How-Geopolitics-Weaponizes-Finance/6982e251f5a3f0ebac990be1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Dalios-Capital-War-Warning-How-Geopolitics-Weaponizes-Finance/6982e251f5a3f0ebac990be1</guid><description>Legendary investor Ray Dalio has articulated a stark warning, stating the global economy is on the verge of a capital war. This scenario, where money and capital markets are increasingly weaponized through sanctions, trade embargoes, and debt manipulation, is fueled by escalating geopolitical friction and policy uncertainty. As nations navigate these turbulent waters, European investors are reportedly re-evaluating their significant holdings in U.S. Treasurys. Amidst this rising systemic risk, gold's role as a long-term diversifier and inflation hedge remains a central theme for investors and central banks alike.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:18:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982e251f5a3f0ebac990be0_1770185936165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>USFDA Warns Cohance Lifesciences Nacharam Plant; Minimal Financial Blow Expected</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/USFDA-Warns-Cohance-Lifesciences-Nacharam-Plant-Minimal-Financial-Blow-Expected/6982e173f5a3f0ebac990a16</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/USFDA-Warns-Cohance-Lifesciences-Nacharam-Plant-Minimal-Financial-Blow-Expected/6982e173f5a3f0ebac990a16</guid><description>Cohance Lifesciences Limited has received a USFDA Warning Letter for its Finished Dosage Formulations (FDF) manufacturing facility in Nacharam, Hyderabad. This follows an inspection that classified the site as Official Action Indicated (OAI). The company stated that revenues from this facility represent less than 2% of its consolidated revenues in FY2025, with EBITDA contribution below 1%, minimizing the expected financial impact. Cohance Lifesciences is committed to addressing the USFDA's concerns promptly and maintaining high quality standards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:18:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982e173f5a3f0ebac990a15_1770185912427.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sigachi MD Gets Bail in 54-Death Plant Blast Case</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sigachi-MD-Gets-Bail-in-54-Death-Plant-Blast-Case/6982e09af5a3f0ebac99078b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sigachi-MD-Gets-Bail-in-54-Death-Plant-Blast-Case/6982e09af5a3f0ebac99078b</guid><description>Sigachi Industries Limited's Managing Director &amp; CEO, Mr. Amit Raj Sinha, has been granted bail by the Hon'ble High Court of Telangana. This development follows his arrest in connection with the tragic industrial accident on June 30, 2025, which claimed 54 lives and injured many. The company expressed solidarity with affected families and reiterated its commitment to cooperating with investigations and reinforcing safety systems. The bail was granted after the charge sheet was filed, noting the completion of the investigation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:14:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982e09af5a3f0ebac99078a_1770185624223.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bartronics India Surges 289% QoQ Revenue on Agri-Tech Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Bartronics-India-Surges-289percent-QoQ-Revenue-on-Agri-Tech-Push/6982e06ff5a3f0ebac99069e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Bartronics-India-Surges-289percent-QoQ-Revenue-on-Agri-Tech-Push/6982e06ff5a3f0ebac99069e</guid><description>Bartronics India posted a robust Q3 FY26, with revenue soaring 289% quarter-on-quarter to ₹48.34 crore, driven by its financial inclusion base and early gains from agri-trade and agri-tech initiatives. Net profit climbed 144% QoQ to ₹2.45 crore. For the nine months ended FY26, revenue grew 123% YoY to ₹69.57 crore, and net profit surged 381% YoY to ₹3.90 crore. Strategic expansions include an MoU with AYOU for agri-produce sourcing and a collaboration with Origo for post-harvest infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:13:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982e06ff5a3f0ebac99069d_1770185634906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nirav Commercials Sells Entire Business for ₹1.25 Cr to Related Party</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nirav-Commercials-Sells-Entire-Business-for-125-Cr-to-Related-Party/6982dff3f5a3f0ebac99056e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nirav-Commercials-Sells-Entire-Business-for-125-Cr-to-Related-Party/6982dff3f5a3f0ebac99056e</guid><description>Nirav Commercials Limited is divesting its entire Aluminium business, 'Elesar Focchi', to Hind Aluminium Industries Limited, a related party, for ₹1.25 Crores. This unit represented 100% of the company's revenue, with its last audited net worth at ₹972.64 Lakhs and income at ₹3047.45 Lakhs as of March 31, 2025. The transaction signifies a complete strategic overhaul for Nirav Commercials, with future business plans currently undisclosed, raising questions about the rationale and valuation of this material related party deal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:10:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dff3f5a3f0ebac99056d_1770185431412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Clean Science Revenue Dives 21% Amid China Pressure, Margins Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Clean-Science-Revenue-Dives-21percent-Amid-China-Pressure-Margins-Squeeze/6982dfc4f5a3f0ebac99040b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Clean-Science-Revenue-Dives-21percent-Amid-China-Pressure-Margins-Squeeze/6982dfc4f5a3f0ebac99040b</guid><description>Clean Science and Technology reported a challenging Q3 FY26 with standalone revenue dropping 21% year-on-year to INR 180 crore, driven by muted customer offtake and pricing pressures, exacerbated by increased Chinese capacity. EBITDA and PAT margins saw compression. Despite a healthy INR 450 crore cash pile and the upcoming commissioning of new Hydroquinone and Catechol plants, management anticipates persistent market headwinds for at least two more quarters, avoiding specific forward guidance. The company declared an interim dividend of INR 2 per share.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:08:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dfc4f5a3f0ebac99040a_1770185335982.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Next 50 Rejig Signals CV Sector Surge Amidst Capital Flows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Nifty-Next-50-Rejig-Signals-CV-Sector-Surge-Amidst-Capital-Flows/6982e26af5a3f0ebac990c77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Nifty-Next-50-Rejig-Signals-CV-Sector-Surge-Amidst-Capital-Flows/6982e26af5a3f0ebac990c77</guid><description>The upcoming Nifty Next 50 index rebalancing is expected to drive substantial passive inflows, with Tata Motors Commercial Vehicles emerging as a key candidate. This potential inclusion highlights a positive turnaround in the commercial vehicle cycle, contrasting with the projected outflows for other entities. The shift reflects a broader sectoral rotation and influences market liquidity, with specific capital flows estimated for potential entrants and exits. Analysts maintain a cautiously optimistic view on Tata Motors CV, supported by sector-specific growth drivers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bartronics India Surges on Strong Q3 Growth, Agri-Tech Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Bartronics-India-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Growth-Agri-Tech-Expansion/6982df87f5a3f0ebac990256</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Bartronics-India-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Growth-Agri-Tech-Expansion/6982df87f5a3f0ebac990256</guid><description>Bartronics India reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with revenue soaring 289% QoQ to ₹48.34 crore and net profit up 144%. Nine-month figures show 123% revenue and 381% profit growth YoY. The company is aggressively expanding into agri-trade and agri-tech through strategic MoUs and collaborations, leveraging its rural network. Management emphasizes disciplined execution for long-term value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:06:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982df87f5a3f0ebac990255_1770185188169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nuvama Sees 58% Upside in 8 Indian Stocks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Nuvama-Sees-58percent-Upside-in-8-Indian-Stocks/6982dfa2f5a3f0ebac99030e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Nuvama-Sees-58percent-Upside-in-8-Indian-Stocks/6982dfa2f5a3f0ebac99030e</guid><description>Brokerage Nuvama has reaffirmed a positive outlook on eight Indian companies, issuing 'Buy' ratings with significant upside potential. Despite near-term pressures like margin contraction and operational challenges affecting some firms, Nuvama's analysis highlights intact long-term business fundamentals. The brokerage's targets suggest potential gains ranging from 34% to 69% for the selected stocks across various sectors including agri-commodities, consumer goods, real estate, capital goods, and financial services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:06:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dfa2f5a3f0ebac99030d_1770185172660.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aster DM Healthcare: Prabhudas Lilladher Reiterates Buy, Sets Rs 715 Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aster-DM-Healthcare-Prabhudas-Lilladher-Reiterates-Buy-Sets-Rs-715-Target/6982e15df5a3f0ebac990999</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aster-DM-Healthcare-Prabhudas-Lilladher-Reiterates-Buy-Sets-Rs-715-Target/6982e15df5a3f0ebac990999</guid><description>Prabhudas Lilladher initiated a 'BUY' rating on Aster DM Healthcare with a Rs 715 target price. The brokerage highlighted strong growth for Quality Care India (QCIL) and positive post-merger synergies following the approved combination of Aster DM Healthcare and QCIL, positioning them as India's third-largest healthcare chain. While Q3 EBITDA fell short of estimates, analysts anticipate robust growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:04:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Capacit'e Infraprojects Lands ₹445 Crore Noida Project Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capacite-Infraprojects-Lands-445-Crore-Noida-Project-Order/6982defff5a3f0ebac9900d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capacite-Infraprojects-Lands-445-Crore-Noida-Project-Order/6982defff5a3f0ebac9900d6</guid><description>Capacit'e Infraprojects Limited has announced securing a Letter of Intent (LOI) from Great Value Realty Limited for civil and structural works at their Ekanam Project in Noida. The contract is valued at approximately ₹445 Crore, excluding GST. Managing Director Rahul Katyal expressed confidence in the company's capabilities and welcomed the new client, emphasizing timely and quality delivery. The company confirmed the order is not a related party transaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:04:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982defff5a3f0ebac9900d5_1770185038648.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Services PMI Hits 2-Month High Amid Demand Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Services-PMI-Hits-2-Month-High-Amid-Demand-Growth/6982de8bf5a3f0ebac98ff4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Services-PMI-Hits-2-Month-High-Amid-Demand-Growth/6982de8bf5a3f0ebac98ff4d</guid><description>India's services sector activity accelerated in January, with the Purchasing Managers' Index (PMI) reaching 58.5, its highest in two months, fueled by a steady inflow of new domestic and international orders. Business confidence also improved to a three-month peak, supported by efficiency gains and new client wins. However, job creation stayed marginal despite increased workloads, and while input costs rose at their fastest rate since September 2025, output charges increased only moderately, suggesting firms are managing cost pressures without significant price hikes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:04:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982de8bf5a3f0ebac98ff4c_1770184998492.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AGI Greenpac: Q3 Earnings Dip Amidst Major Expansion Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AGI-Greenpac-Q3-Earnings-Dip-Amidst-Major-Expansion-Drive/6982dd98f5a3f0ebac98fd28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AGI-Greenpac-Q3-Earnings-Dip-Amidst-Major-Expansion-Drive/6982dd98f5a3f0ebac98fd28</guid><description>AGI Greenpac posted a 5.4% revenue increase for 9M FY26 to ₹1,923 crore, though EBITDA saw a slight YoY dip to ₹484 crore. Q3 revenue stood at ₹634 crore, with PAT at ₹71 crore, including ₹5.09 crore in exceptional items. Management cited subdued beer segment demand and pricing adjustments for margin pressure. Despite these near-term headwinds, the company is aggressively pursuing growth with a ₹1,100-₹1,200 crore CAPEX plan for FY27, expansion into aluminum beverage cans, and a new Greenfield plant targeting commissioning in March 2027.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:00:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dd98f5a3f0ebac98fd27_1770184844588.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chalet Hotels Q3 Beats Estimates; IDBI Capital Holds 'Hold' Amid Hospitality Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Chalet-Hotels-Q3-Beats-Estimates-IDBI-Capital-Holds-Hold-Amid-Hospitality-Strength/6982dd40f5a3f0ebac98fc2f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Chalet-Hotels-Q3-Beats-Estimates-IDBI-Capital-Holds-Hold-Amid-Hospitality-Strength/6982dd40f5a3f0ebac98fc2f</guid><description>Chalet Hotels Ltd. reported a strong Q3 FY26, exceeding IDBI Capital's expectations. The brokerage noted robust Indian hospitality demand driven by disposable incomes, travel trends, and MICE activity. Average daily rates saw healthy double-digit growth, particularly in key cities. Chalet's new Athiva Khandala resort brand also performed well, achieving sold-out days.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:58:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dd40f5a3f0ebac98fc2e_1770184715909.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gabriel India: High Growth &amp; Premium Valuation Face Market Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Gabriel-India-High-Growth-and-Premium-Valuation-Face-Market-Test/6982dd2ff5a3f0ebac98fb56</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Gabriel-India-High-Growth-and-Premium-Valuation-Face-Market-Test/6982dd2ff5a3f0ebac98fb56</guid><description>Gabriel India posted a robust Q3FY26 with 16% revenue growth to ₹1,178 crore and 20% EBITDA increase, driven by strong automotive demand. The company is expanding into high-potential areas like sunroofs, solar dampers, and EV components, alongside strategic acquisitions and joint ventures. However, its current valuation, trading at over 30x FY27 earnings, is significantly higher than industry averages, suggesting growth is already priced in and posing a risk if future targets are missed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dd2ff5a3f0ebac98fb55_1770184671945.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metro Brands Surges Past ₹800 Cr Revenue Milestone; Eyes 30% EBITDA Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Metro-Brands-Surges-Past-800-Cr-Revenue-Milestone-Eyes-30percent-EBITDA-Growth/6982dd21f5a3f0ebac98fa9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Metro-Brands-Surges-Past-800-Cr-Revenue-Milestone-Eyes-30percent-EBITDA-Growth/6982dd21f5a3f0ebac98fa9b</guid><description>Metro Brands Limited crossed a significant revenue milestone, reporting over ₹800 crore in Q3 FY26, a 15% year-on-year (YoY) increase. The company also saw an 18% YoY jump in EBITDA, maintaining strong 33% margins, and a 33% YoY surge in Profit After Tax (PAT) to 16% margin. Digital commerce grew 24% to account for 12% of revenue. Management is optimistic about sustaining double-digit growth, aiming for 30% EBITDA and 15% PAT margins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:55:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dd21f5a3f0ebac98fa9a_1770184531743.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Surge on MCX; Demand, Dollar Drive Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Surge-on-MCX-Demand-Dollar-Drive-Rally/6982dc39f5a3f0ebac98f797</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Surge-on-MCX-Demand-Dollar-Drive-Rally/6982dc39f5a3f0ebac98f797</guid><description>Indian gold and silver prices rallied sharply on Wednesday, with April gold contracts climbing ₹7,000 to ₹1.60 lakh per 10 grams and March silver jumping over ₹16,000 to ₹2.84 lakh per kg on the MCX. The surge was fueled by firm global markets, a softer US dollar, and renewed domestic buying. Analysts point to bargain hunting after recent corrections, improved sentiment from potential India-EU trade progress, and robust physical demand from China ahead of Lunar New Year holidays as key drivers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:53:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dc39f5a3f0ebac98f796_1770184418315.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mankind Pharma Shares Tumble 4% Despite Profit Rise on Growth Worries</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Mankind-Pharma-Shares-Tumble-4percent-Despite-Profit-Rise-on-Growth-Worries/6982dc62f5a3f0ebac98f839</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Mankind-Pharma-Shares-Tumble-4percent-Despite-Profit-Rise-on-Growth-Worries/6982dc62f5a3f0ebac98f839</guid><description>Mankind Pharma shares tumbled nearly 4% on Wednesday. Despite reporting an 11.5% rise in revenue and a profit increase to ₹414 crore, analysts flagged concerns over subdued organic growth and execution challenges within key segments. The stock's decline highlights investor apprehension about the company's near-term growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:51:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dc62f5a3f0ebac98f838_1770184280121.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: Resilience Mandate Sparks Market Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Resilience-Mandate-Sparks-Market-Jitters/6982dbbef5a3f0ebac98f654</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Resilience-Mandate-Sparks-Market-Jitters/6982dbbef5a3f0ebac98f654</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 anchors on a three-kartavya framework, prioritizing economic growth, national capacity, and equitable development. While outlining substantial capital expenditure of ₹12.2 lakh crore and targeted sectoral initiatives in semiconductors, biopharma, and MSMEs, the immediate market reaction on February 1, 2026, was a sharp decline. The BSE Sensex and NSE Nifty50 saw significant drops, largely attributed to an increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options trading, overshadowing the long-term growth narrative and resilience focus.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dbbef5a3f0ebac98f653_1770184160166.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bartronics India Transforms: Agri-Tech Push Fuels Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Bartronics-India-Transforms-Agri-Tech-Push-Fuels-Revenue-Surge/6982db3ef5a3f0ebac98f4d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Bartronics-India-Transforms-Agri-Tech-Push-Fuels-Revenue-Surge/6982db3ef5a3f0ebac98f4d4</guid><description>Bartronics India Limited (BIL) has reported a robust Q3 FY26, with revenue surging 5.5 times year-on-year to ₹4,834 Lakh. For the nine months ending December 31, 2025 (9M FY26), revenue jumped 123% to ₹6,957 Lakh, while net profit soared 381% to ₹390 Lakh. This exceptional growth is driven by its expanding financial inclusion business and early monetization from its strategic push into agri-tech and agri-trade, spearheaded by 'Project Avio'. The company aims to build a comprehensive rural operating system, targeting USD 1 billion in Gross Merchandise Value (GMV) through rural commerce.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:48:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982db3ef5a3f0ebac98f4d3_1770184110046.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asia Pacific Power Demand to Surge 790 TWh in 2026 on Data Center Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Asia-Pacific-Power-Demand-to-Surge-790-TWh-in-2026-on-Data-Center-Boom/6982dadaf5a3f0ebac98f3d9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Asia-Pacific-Power-Demand-to-Surge-790-TWh-in-2026-on-Data-Center-Boom/6982dadaf5a3f0ebac98f3d9</guid><description>Asia Pacific's power demand is set to surge by 790 terawatt hours (TWh) in 2026, accounting for 85% of global growth. Data centers are the primary driver, reversing demand declines in markets like Japan. Policy shifts in China and India, alongside supply chain constraints for gas turbines, will reshape the region's energy landscape.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:48:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dadaf5a3f0ebac98f3d8_1770183968525.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PCBL Chemical Downgraded to HOLD, Target Slashed to Rs 302</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/PCBL-Chemical-Downgraded-to-HOLD-Target-Slashed-to-Rs-302/6982dacef5a3f0ebac98f33f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/PCBL-Chemical-Downgraded-to-HOLD-Target-Slashed-to-Rs-302/6982dacef5a3f0ebac98f33f</guid><description>Prabhudas Lilladher has downgraded PCBL Chemical to a 'HOLD' rating, setting a new target price of Rs 302. The downgrade reflects concerns over cheaper imports and a weak demand environment, which have impacted the company's revenue and profitability. Fourth-quarter fiscal year 2026 results showed a significant year-on-year decline in both carbon black volumes and realizations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:44:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982dacef5a3f0ebac98f33e_1770183873582.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Avanti Feeds Surges to 8-Year High on US Tariff Cut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Avanti-Feeds-Surges-to-8-Year-High-on-US-Tariff-Cut/6982dcacf5a3f0ebac98f97d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Avanti-Feeds-Surges-to-8-Year-High-on-US-Tariff-Cut/6982dcacf5a3f0ebac98f97d</guid><description>Avanti Feeds shares reached an eight-year peak, surging over 35% in two trading sessions following the Indo-US trade agreement. The deal dramatically reduces US import tariffs on Indian goods, from up to 50% to 18%, significantly enhancing the competitive position of Indian shrimp exports which comprise nearly half of Avanti Feeds' international sales. This tariff relief is expected to improve margins and drive volume growth in the crucial US market, contrasting with recent export challenges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Artemis Medicare Expands Capacity, Analyst Sees 60%+ Upside</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Artemis-Medicare-Expands-Capacity-Analyst-Sees-60percent-Upside/6982da52f5a3f0ebac98edae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Artemis-Medicare-Expands-Capacity-Analyst-Sees-60percent-Upside/6982da52f5a3f0ebac98edae</guid><description>Artemis Medicare Services is set to more than double its bed capacity from approximately 700 to 2,000. Choice Institutional Equities forecasts robust growth with revenue, EBITDA, and PAT CAGRs of 26.1%, 28.9%, and 31.3% respectively from FY25-28E. The brokerage maintains a 'BUY' rating and a target price of INR 325 per share, valuing the company on an 18x EV/EBITDA multiple.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:43:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982da52f5a3f0ebac98edad_1770183806311.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Accretion Nutraveda Lists 48% Above IPO, Edging Past Grey Market Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Accretion-Nutraveda-Lists-48percent-Above-IPO-Edging-Past-Grey-Market-Hopes/6982da0bf5a3f0ebac98ebf4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Accretion-Nutraveda-Lists-48percent-Above-IPO-Edging-Past-Grey-Market-Hopes/6982da0bf5a3f0ebac98ebf4</guid><description>Accretion Nutraveda shares opened at ₹191 on February 4th, a 48% surge from its ₹129 IPO price on the BSE SME platform. The healthcare firm raised ₹24.7 crore through its offering, which was subscribed 1.77 times. Proceeds are earmarked for machinery, working capital, and general corporate needs. Despite a strong market debut, the listing premium slightly trailed pre-listing grey market expectations, reflecting a segment of the market favouring caution amidst a dynamic SME IPO environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:41:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982da0bf5a3f0ebac98ebf3_1770183676771.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NMIA Phase 2: Adani's Airport Expansion Fuels Funding Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NMIA-Phase-2-Adanis-Airport-Expansion-Fuels-Funding-Scrutiny/6982d9f9f5a3f0ebac98eb53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NMIA-Phase-2-Adanis-Airport-Expansion-Fuels-Funding-Scrutiny/6982d9f9f5a3f0ebac98eb53</guid><description>Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA) is set to commence Phase 2 development post-monsoon, targeting a capacity of 60-65 million passengers annually by 2029-2030 with the addition of a second runway and terminal. This aggressive expansion by Adani Airport Holdings Ltd (AAHL) necessitates substantial capital, with ₹20,000 crore earmarked for Phase 2 and a broader ₹1 lakh crore investment planned across AAHL's portfolio. While credit ratings have improved, the sheer scale of these projects raises questions about funding sustainability and execution timelines within a fluctuating aviation market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982d9f9f5a3f0ebac98eb52_1770183589734.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Deep Dive: Banks Face New Scrutiny on Business Models</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Deep-Dive-Banks-Face-New-Scrutiny-on-Business-Models/6982d9ddf5a3f0ebac98eace</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Deep-Dive-Banks-Face-New-Scrutiny-on-Business-Models/6982d9ddf5a3f0ebac98eace</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is revamping its bank oversight, moving beyond traditional ratio analysis to a deeper examination of financial institutions' business models. This proactive shift targets emerging risks in India's rapidly expanding financial system, particularly digital threats and past governance failures. The overhaul includes hiring cybersecurity specialists and intensifying scrutiny across all supervised entities, signaling a new era of regulatory engagement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:38:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982d9ddf5a3f0ebac98eacd_1770183449548.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gabriel India's Growth Traps: High Valuation Meets Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gabriel-Indias-Growth-Traps-High-Valuation-Meets-Margin-Squeeze/6982d993f5a3f0ebac98e920</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gabriel-Indias-Growth-Traps-High-Valuation-Meets-Margin-Squeeze/6982d993f5a3f0ebac98e920</guid><description>Gabriel India posted a 16% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹1,178 crore in Q3 FY26. However, this top-line growth was overshadowed by a 9.0% decline in net profit to ₹547 million, signaling margin compression. The company is actively pursuing multiple growth avenues including the acquisition of Marelli Motherson's assets, a joint venture in fasteners, and expansion into sunroof and solar segments. Despite these strategic moves, the stock trades at a high P/E ratio of approximately 50x-60x, raising concerns about its stretched valuation and the execution risks associated with its ambitious expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:37:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982d993f5a3f0ebac98e91f_1770183458193.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra Lands Record Indonesian LCV Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-Lands-Record-Indonesian-LCV-Order/6982d977f5a3f0ebac98e421</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-Lands-Record-Indonesian-LCV-Order/6982d977f5a3f0ebac98e421</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra has secured its largest-ever export order, agreeing to supply 35,000 Scorpio Pik Up light commercial vehicles to Indonesia in 2026. This significant deal with state-owned Agrinas Pangan Nusantara is tied to Indonesia's Koperasi Desa/Kelurahan Merah Putih (KDKMP) program, aiming to bolster rural logistics and cooperative development. The 35,000-unit order surpasses Mahindra's entire export volume for fiscal year 2025, signaling a major strategic push into the Southeast Asian market and reinforcing its global LCV footprint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:34:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982d977f5a3f0ebac98e420_1770183239418.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI 'SaaSapocalypse' Hits Infosys, Wipro, Tech Stocks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-SaaSapocalypse-Hits-Infosys-Wipro-Tech-Stocks/6982d964f5a3f0ebac98e34c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-SaaSapocalypse-Hits-Infosys-Wipro-Tech-Stocks/6982d964f5a3f0ebac98e34c</guid><description>Indian IT giants Infosys and Wipro experienced sharp declines in their American Depositary Receipts (ADRs) on Tuesday, falling over 5%, following the release of Anthropic's advanced AI automation tool. This development, sparking fears of a 'SaaSapocalypse,' triggered broader market apprehension, with major US IT firms like Accenture and Cognizant dropping up to 10%. The AI agent's capabilities to automate legal and workflow tasks directly challenge traditional software-as-a-service business models, accelerating investor concerns about AI-driven disruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:33:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982d964f5a3f0ebac98e34b_1770183191562.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Recovers Sharply Amid Volatility; Caution Lingers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Recovers-Sharply-Amid-Volatility-Caution-Lingers/6982d888f5a3f0ebac98e09d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Recovers-Sharply-Amid-Volatility-Caution-Lingers/6982d888f5a3f0ebac98e09d</guid><description>Silver surged 5.28% on February 4, 2026, reclaiming ₹28,153 per kilogram following a severe 40% sell-off in late January. The recovery was propelled by easing market volatility and geopolitical tensions, alongside persistent supply deficits and industrial demand. However, a cautious sentiment prevails, with analysts emphasizing short-term catalysts and forecasting choppy trading, suggesting it remains too early for sustained bullish exposure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:30:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982d888f5a3f0ebac98e09c_1770183024963.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>