<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 18:26:32 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Micron's India Plant: Geopolitical Play Amidst Supply Chain Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microns-India-Plant-Geopolitical-Play-Amidst-Supply-Chain-Risks/69a32a95fa7d0695d1b1a7c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microns-India-Plant-Geopolitical-Play-Amidst-Supply-Chain-Risks/69a32a95fa7d0695d1b1a7c4</guid><description>Micron Technology's new ATMP facility in Sanand, Gujarat, signals a strategic move for the US-India partnership and a recalibration of global semiconductor supply chains. US Ambassador Sergio Gor lauded India's 'essential' role as a secure alternative, particularly with ongoing geopolitical realignments and initiatives like Pax Silica aimed at diversifying manufacturing away from concentrated Asian hubs. This significant $2.75 billion investment underscores India's growing appeal, evidenced by over $19 billion in approved semiconductor projects. However, Micron navigates a complex environment marked by intense competition, evolving market demands, and persistent legal and executive-level scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 17:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>OPEC+ May Boost Output As Geopolitical Tensions Flare</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/OPEC-May-Boost-Output-As-Geopolitical-Tensions-Flare/69a325e6fa7d0695d1b17f53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/OPEC-May-Boost-Output-As-Geopolitical-Tensions-Flare/69a325e6fa7d0695d1b17f53</guid><description>OPEC+ nations are reportedly contemplating a substantial increase in oil output, potentially reaching 411,000 barrels per day, significantly more than initially proposed. This consideration comes as geopolitical tensions escalate between the U.S. and Iran, following reported strikes on Saturday. In anticipation of potential supply disruptions, key Middle Eastern producers like Saudi Arabia and the UAE have already ramped up their oil exports. The group is scheduled to meet Sunday to finalize production targets, which would mark the end of a three-month pause in output hikes. Crude prices have surged, with Brent nearing $73 a barrel, driven by these supply fears.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 17:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks: AI Threat Triggers SIP Rout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-AI-Threat-Triggers-SIP-Rout/69a3247dfa7d0695d1b17187</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-AI-Threat-Triggers-SIP-Rout/69a3247dfa7d0695d1b17187</guid><description>Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) returns for Indian IT-focused mutual funds have plunged into negative territory for the first time since early 2020, a stark contrast to the broader market's resilience. The Nifty IT index is down over 20% in February, driven by fears that artificial intelligence will structurally disrupt the sector's traditional outsourcing model. Valuations are under pressure, with analysts warning of significant further derating amid slowing global tech spending and a shift towards AI-driven services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 17:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Proterial India Entry: Amorphous Steel Fuels Grid Modernization</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Proterial-India-Entry-Amorphous-Steel-Fuels-Grid-Modernization/69a31fcdfa7d0695d1b11010</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Proterial-India-Entry-Amorphous-Steel-Fuels-Grid-Modernization/69a31fcdfa7d0695d1b11010</guid><description>Proterial is investing $80 million to establish India's first amorphous electrical steel manufacturing facility in Andhra Pradesh, set to commence operations in October 2026. This strategic move addresses the nation's complete import dependence on the material, vital for high-efficiency power transformers. The facility aims to produce 30,000 tonnes annually, significantly improving transformer efficiency and reducing standby power loss. This aligns with India's surging electricity demand, driven by industrial expansion and the booming data center sector, and is supported by the government's Speciality Steel PLI scheme. The joint venture with Shirdi Sai Electricals Ltd (SSEL) positions Proterial to capture a growing market.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 17:03:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Geopolitical Storm Threatens India's Economic Resilience</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Storm-Threatens-Indias-Economic-Resilience/69a31df0fa7d0695d1b0c261</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Storm-Threatens-Indias-Economic-Resilience/69a31df0fa7d0695d1b0c261</guid><description>Escalating US-Iran hostilities inject significant volatility into India's economic outlook. The success story of the India-UAE Comprehensive Economic Partnership Agreement faces uncertainty, while potential oil price spikes to $120 per barrel threaten to derail inflation control and widen the current account deficit. Sectors reliant on crude inputs are vulnerable, and a historically sensitive rupee faces further depreciation risks, complicating India's otherwise robust growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 16:55:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a31df0fa7d0695d1b0c260_1772297943308.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fino Bank CEO Arrest: Tax Evasion Probe Hits Fintech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Bank-CEO-Arrest-Tax-Evasion-Probe-Hits-Fintech/69a31144fa7d0695d1b05161</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Bank-CEO-Arrest-Tax-Evasion-Probe-Hits-Fintech/69a31144fa7d0695d1b05161</guid><description>The Directorate General of GST Intelligence (DGGI) has arrested Fino Payments Bank's MD &amp; CEO, Rishi Gupta, in a significant probe into alleged multi-crore Goods and Services Tax evasion. The investigation centers on banned online money gaming operations and the alleged use of shell entities and payment aggregators to funnel illicit funds. While Fino Payments Bank maintains its operations are unaffected, the incident raises concerns about systemic risks within the digital payment ecosystem and intensifies regulatory scrutiny on fintech infrastructure providers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a31144fa7d0695d1b05160_1772294615812.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Turmoil Sparks Airline Profit Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Geopolitical-Turmoil-Sparks-Airline-Profit-Squeeze/69a310d3fa7d0695d1b050f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Geopolitical-Turmoil-Sparks-Airline-Profit-Squeeze/69a310d3fa7d0695d1b050f4</guid><description>Escalating Middle East tensions have led to widespread flight cancellations and airspace closures, directly impacting Indian carriers. SpiceJet and IndiGo faced operational disruptions, with indirect cost increases from rerouting and volatile fuel prices. The geopolitical shock exacerbates existing financial vulnerabilities within the Indian aviation sector, casting a shadow over near-term profitability forecasts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:59:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a310d3fa7d0695d1b050f3_1772294718246.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EV Two-Wheeler Boom: Legacy Brands Overtake Startups</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/EV-Two-Wheeler-Boom-Legacy-Brands-Overtake-Startups/69a30fdefa7d0695d1b05036</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/EV-Two-Wheeler-Boom-Legacy-Brands-Overtake-Startups/69a30fdefa7d0695d1b05036</guid><description>Electric two-wheeler (E2W) registrations in February 2026 reached 1.05 lakh units, a 36% year-on-year increase. TVS Motor retained leadership with 61% growth, while Hero MotoCorp more than tripled its volumes. Bajaj Auto saw a 12% increase. Conversely, Ola Electric experienced a stark 55% volume decline and a significant drop in market share. This performance divergence underscores a market consolidation favoring established manufacturers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:55:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a30fdefa7d0695d1b05035_1772294756648.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Apple Supply Chain Ambition: A Multi-Decade Ecosystem Challenge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Apple-Supply-Chain-Ambition-A-Multi-Decade-Ecosystem-Challenge/69a30a2ffa7d0695d1b04dd7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Apple-Supply-Chain-Ambition-A-Multi-Decade-Ecosystem-Challenge/69a30a2ffa7d0695d1b04dd7</guid><description>Patrick McGee, author of 'Apple's China Playbook,' asserts that India's ambition to rival China in Apple's supply chain is a multi-decade endeavor. The focus must shift from mere export numbers to building a dense manufacturing ecosystem, as India remains heavily reliant on imported components, limiting domestic value addition. Competitors like Vietnam offer simpler trade structures and established export models, while China's sheer scale of industrial automation presents a formidable benchmark. Replicating China's integrated industrial clusters requires decades of coordinated effort and significant investment, a challenge compounded by global geopolitical realignments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:30:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a30a2ffa7d0695d1b04dd6_1772293442159.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-EU Trade Deal: MFN Linked to Student Mobility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-EU-Trade-Deal-MFN-Linked-to-Student-Mobility/69a307e6fa7d0695d1b04c98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-EU-Trade-Deal-MFN-Linked-to-Student-Mobility/69a307e6fa7d0695d1b04c98</guid><description>The provisional India-EU Free Trade Agreement establishes a five-year Most Favoured Nation (MFN) provision for services trade, committing both parties to mutual preferential treatment. Crucially, the extension of these benefits beyond the initial term is directly linked to India's progress on facilitating student entry and stay in the EU, alongside the finalization of social security agreements. While the deal opens markets and boosts trade volumes, the EU's Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (CBAM) remains a significant external risk, potentially offsetting tariff gains for Indian exporters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:21:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a307e6fa7d0695d1b04c97_1772292378463.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Humanoid Robot Race: Speed vs. Software Savvy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Chinas-Humanoid-Robot-Race-Speed-vs-Software-Savvy/69a306f1fa7d0695d1b04be6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Chinas-Humanoid-Robot-Race-Speed-vs-Software-Savvy/69a306f1fa7d0695d1b04be6</guid><description>China's humanoid robot sector is surging, dominating global installations with key players like Agibot and Unitree. Bolstered by strong manufacturing and government backing, companies are scaling production rapidly, targeting IPOs and significant valuations. However, the industry's pivot from flashy demos to practical, operation-driven adoption exposes critical gaps in AI sophistication and software reliability, suggesting hardware prowess may be outpacing intelligent autonomy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a306f1fa7d0695d1b04be5_1772291947010.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prediction Markets Under Fire Amidst $1.2M Iran Strike Betting Windfall</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Prediction-Markets-Under-Fire-Amidst-12M-Iran-Strike-Betting-Windfall/69a302bcfa7d0695d1b04a0d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Prediction-Markets-Under-Fire-Amidst-12M-Iran-Strike-Betting-Windfall/69a302bcfa7d0695d1b04a0d</guid><description>Six Polymarket accounts netted approximately $1.2 million by correctly predicting a U.S. strike on Iran on February 28, 2026. The profitable trades, executed by newly created wallets funded just prior to the event, have amplified regulatory concerns regarding insider trading on prediction markets. This incident occurs as platforms like Kalshi face enforcement actions, and the CFTC reiterates its authority over event contracts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:59:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a302bcfa7d0695d1b04a0c_1772290867712.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Groww's AI Strategy: Ecosystem Play Amidst Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Growws-AI-Strategy-Ecosystem-Play-Amidst-Market-Volatility/69a3014ffa7d0695d1b048d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Growws-AI-Strategy-Ecosystem-Play-Amidst-Market-Volatility/69a3014ffa7d0695d1b048d5</guid><description>Groww is launching GR-1, an opt-in AI investing assistant emphasizing personalized, guarded insights rather than autonomous trading. This initiative underscores its broader strategy to build a robust financial ecosystem supported by infrastructure resilience, aiming to navigate market volatility and regulatory complexities while capitalizing on surging retail investor interest in India. The focus on responsible AI and platform stability aims to foster trust and differentiation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:53:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3014ffa7d0695d1b048d4_1772290969293.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Persistent Systems Expands to China with New Shanghai Entity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Persistent-Systems-Expands-to-China-with-New-Shanghai-Entity/69a2ff72fa7d0695d1b047d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Persistent-Systems-Expands-to-China-with-New-Shanghai-Entity/69a2ff72fa7d0695d1b047d7</guid><description>Persistent Systems has expanded its global operational footprint by establishing a Wholly Owned Foreign Enterprise (WFOE) in Shanghai, China. The new entity, Persistent Systems (Shanghai) Co. Ltd., received its business license on February 28, 2026. This move signifies the company's strategic intent to deepen its presence in the significant Chinese market and diversify its international revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:45:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ff72fa7d0695d1b047d6_1772290010142.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SATTE 2026: India Bets Big on Tourism's Trillion-Dollar Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SATTE-2026-India-Bets-Big-on-Tourisms-Trillion-Dollar-Future/69a2fa46fa7d0695d1b0459e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SATTE-2026-India-Bets-Big-on-Tourisms-Trillion-Dollar-Future/69a2fa46fa7d0695d1b0459e</guid><description>The SATTE 2026 exhibition in Delhi highlighted India's ambitious tourism expansion plans, targeting a $125 billion market by 2026 and a $3 trillion GDP contribution by 2047. With over 2,000 exhibitors, the event showcased increased government focus on raising tourism's economic share, alongside significant advancements in aviation, technology, and the burgeoning MICE and wedding tourism sectors. While projections are bullish, achieving these goals hinges on navigating competitive global markets, executing infrastructure projects, and embedding sustainable practices.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:23:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2fa46fa7d0695d1b0459d_1772288961822.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan Encumbers TANFAC Stake for USD 20M Financing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Encumbers-TANFAC-Stake-for-USD-20M-Financing/69a2f68efa7d0695d1b043e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Encumbers-TANFAC-Stake-for-USD-20M-Financing/69a2f68efa7d0695d1b043e4</guid><description>Anupam Rasayan India Ltd has placed a non-disposal undertaking on 25.73 lakh shares of TANFAC Industries, representing 25.80% of its holding and total capital. This encumbrance, effective February 20, 2026, serves as security for a USD 20 million offshore debt instrument, highlighting strategic financing moves by the specialty chemical firm.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:07:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2f68efa7d0695d1b043e3_1772287928327.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan Pledges 25.80% TANFAC Stake for USD 30M ECB</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Pledges-2580percent-TANFAC-Stake-for-USD-30M-ECB/69a2f59afa7d0695d1b0431d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Pledges-2580percent-TANFAC-Stake-for-USD-30M-ECB/69a2f59afa7d0695d1b0431d</guid><description>Anupam Rasayan India Ltd. has encumbered 25.80% of its stake in TANFAC Industries Ltd., representing 25,73,081 equity shares, as security for a USD 30 million external commercial borrowing facility. This move restricts its ability to sell these shares, impacting potential strategic flexibility and raising concerns about future liquidity or default scenarios.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2f59afa7d0695d1b0431c_1772287711998.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Middle East Tensions Force Indian Airlines Into Costly Reroutes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Middle-East-Tensions-Force-Indian-Airlines-Into-Costly-Reroutes/69a2f428fa7d0695d1b041e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Middle-East-Tensions-Force-Indian-Airlines-Into-Costly-Reroutes/69a2f428fa7d0695d1b041e2</guid><description>New Delhi's Ministry of Civil Aviation has reviewed preparedness for Middle East air disruptions, directing airlines and airports to ensure safety and operational continuity. This proactive measure aims to mitigate risks from escalating regional tensions and airspace restrictions. However, the underlying impact on Indian carriers involves significant increases in operational costs due to extended flight paths and volatile fuel prices, straining already tight margins.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:56:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2f428fa7d0695d1b041e1_1772287127711.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel Wins Tax Case, Secures ₹215 Cr Relief on Corus Acquisition Interest</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Tata-Steel-Wins-Tax-Case-Secures-215-Cr-Relief-on-Corus-Acquisition-Interest/69a2f2ddfa7d0695d1b040df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Tata-Steel-Wins-Tax-Case-Secures-215-Cr-Relief-on-Corus-Acquisition-Interest/69a2f2ddfa7d0695d1b040df</guid><description>Tata Steel Limited has secured a favourable order from the Income Tax Appellate Tribunal (ITAT), resolving a tax dispute related to interest expenditure on its 2007 Corus acquisition. This ruling reduces the company's aggregate tax exposure by approximately ₹215 crore, easing contingent liabilities and bringing greater financial clarity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:51:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2f2ddfa7d0695d1b040de_1772286984343.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DMR Engineering Adds 6 New Business Areas, Appoints Non-Executive Director</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DMR-Engineering-Adds-6-New-Business-Areas-Appoints-Non-Executive-Director/69a2f251fa7d0695d1b04053</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DMR-Engineering-Adds-6-New-Business-Areas-Appoints-Non-Executive-Director/69a2f251fa7d0695d1b04053</guid><description>DMR Engineering Limited's Board of Directors has approved significant amendments to its main objects clause to include six new business areas: Engineering Consulting, EPC services, Power Trading, Renewable Energy (RE) Generation, Energy Storage, and Transmission. The company also appointed Mr. Man Mohan Madan as an additional Non-executive Director. These strategic moves, aimed at expanding its operational scope, are subject to shareholder and statutory approvals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2f251fa7d0695d1b04052_1772287241762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hilton Metal Forging plans ₹28 Cr rights issue to cut debt, boost working capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hilton-Metal-Forging-plans-28-Cr-rights-issue-to-cut-debt-boost-working-capital/69a2eff9fa7d0695d1b03ec1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hilton-Metal-Forging-plans-28-Cr-rights-issue-to-cut-debt-boost-working-capital/69a2eff9fa7d0695d1b03ec1</guid><description>Hilton Metal Forging Limited has announced a rights issue to raise up to ₹27.97 crore. The funds are earmarked for significant debt reduction, including ₹10 crore prepayments to SBI and ₹8 crore for promoter loans, alongside working capital needs. This move aims to strengthen its balance sheet and improve financial leverage.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:39:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2eff9fa7d0695d1b03ec0_1772286604668.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel arm NINL faces ₹587 Cr Odisha Govt Notice; disputes liability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Tata-Steel-arm-NINL-faces-587-Cr-Odisha-Govt-Notice-disputes-liability/69a2ee92fa7d0695d1b03df3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Tata-Steel-arm-NINL-faces-587-Cr-Odisha-Govt-Notice-disputes-liability/69a2ee92fa7d0695d1b03df3</guid><description>Tata Steel's subsidiary, NINL, has received a Show Cause Notice (SCN) from the Odisha government demanding ₹587.86 crore. The notice alleges a shortfall in additional charges on iron ore dispatch between February 2022 and March 2025. NINL disputes the claim, asserting its mining operations are not covered by the cited law and it is not liable. The company plans to formally respond and explore legal avenues.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ee92fa7d0695d1b03df2_1772286138144.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Slides as Risk Asset Realignment Accelerates</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Slides-as-Risk-Asset-Realignment-Accelerates/69a2ed2afa7d0695d1b03c96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Slides-as-Risk-Asset-Realignment-Accelerates/69a2ed2afa7d0695d1b03c96</guid><description>Bitcoin is experiencing its most significant losing streak since 2018, with February marking a near 20% decline and year-to-date losses surpassing 25%. The cryptocurrency is exhibiting unusual underperformance relative to resilient equities and the surging gold market. Analysts suggest this isn't mere cyclical weakness but a broader "structural regime shift" in how risk assets are valued amidst heightened global uncertainty and tightening financial conditions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:27:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ed2afa7d0695d1b03c95_1772285399548.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BharatRohan Signs POC For Solar Asset Drone Monitoring In Gujarat</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BharatRohan-Signs-POC-For-Solar-Asset-Drone-Monitoring-In-Gujarat/69a2ed27fa7d0695d1b03c7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BharatRohan-Signs-POC-For-Solar-Asset-Drone-Monitoring-In-Gujarat/69a2ed27fa7d0695d1b03c7f</guid><description>BharatRohan Airborne Innovations is set to deploy its UAV technology for solar asset monitoring in Gujarat under a POC agreement with KPI Green OMS Private Limited. Operations are slated to begin within 20 days, marking a strategic expansion for the drone solutions provider into the renewable energy sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:27:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ed27fa7d0695d1b03c7e_1772285357046.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haryana Digitizes Land Purchase for Mega Urban Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Haryana-Digitizes-Land-Purchase-for-Mega-Urban-Expansion/69a2ec79fa7d0695d1b03b8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Haryana-Digitizes-Land-Purchase-for-Mega-Urban-Expansion/69a2ec79fa7d0695d1b03b8f</guid><description>The Haryana government is launching a significant land procurement initiative using the digital 'e-Bhoomi' portal, acquiring approximately 17,358 acres in Gurgaon and 4,500 acres in Faridabad. This consent-based, voluntary process aims to develop planned residential, commercial, and institutional sectors, marking a departure from traditional land acquisition methods and potentially accelerating urban expansion across the state. The initiative is part of a broader target to procure 1.7 lakh acres statewide, with landowners having until April 30, 2026, to submit their land details online.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:24:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ec79fa7d0695d1b03b8e_1772285351191.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rail Push: BEML Contracts Fuel Domestic Ambition Amidst Project Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Rail-Push-BEML-Contracts-Fuel-Domestic-Ambition-Amidst-Project-Headwinds/69a2ec38fa7d0695d1b03b2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Rail-Push-BEML-Contracts-Fuel-Domestic-Ambition-Amidst-Project-Headwinds/69a2ec38fa7d0695d1b03b2c</guid><description>India is set to acquire 16 more domestically manufactured bullet trains, with BEML securing key manufacturing orders. These trains will operate on the Mumbai-Ahmedabad High-Speed Rail (MAHSR) corridor, alongside two Japanese Shinkansen sets arriving by 2029-30. The MAHSR project, funded significantly by JICA loans totaling nearly ₹59,396 crore, continues to navigate land acquisition challenges and substantial costs, estimated at ₹1.1-1.25 lakh crore. BEML's order bolsters India's indigenous rolling stock capabilities, aiming to capture a larger share of the global rail equipment market, which is projected to exceed $95 billion by 2032.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:23:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ec38fa7d0695d1b03b2b_1772285106015.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alphabet Valuation Under AI Spotlight: High Expectations Face CapEx Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Valuation-Under-AI-Spotlight-High-Expectations-Face-CapEx-Surge/69a2ebc1fa7d0695d1b03ab6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Valuation-Under-AI-Spotlight-High-Expectations-Face-CapEx-Surge/69a2ebc1fa7d0695d1b03ab6</guid><description>Alphabet's valuation has surged approximately 80% in the past year, driven by AI advancements, robust Search revenue growth of 17% in Q4 FY2025, and a 48% acceleration in Google Cloud. With FY2025 revenues hitting $402.8 billion and net income at $132.2 billion, the market is pricing in future AI-led expansion. However, projected 2026 capital expenditures of $175-$185 billion signal significant investment needs, prompting scrutiny on whether this expense translates into durable growth against elevated expectations and increased competitive pressures.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:21:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ebc1fa7d0695d1b03ab5_1772285055166.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Leap: AI Fraud Surge Outpaces Financial Literacy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Digital-Leap-AI-Fraud-Surge-Outpaces-Financial-Literacy/69a2e622fa7d0695d1b037dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Digital-Leap-AI-Fraud-Surge-Outpaces-Financial-Literacy/69a2e622fa7d0695d1b037dc</guid><description>India's digital financial sector is experiencing a tenfold surge in fraud over three years, fueled by advanced AI techniques like deepfakes and voice cloning. Panellists at the Network 18 Rising Bharat Summit highlighted that while digital opportunities in investments, credit, and payments are expanding rapidly, financial literacy has not kept pace, creating vulnerabilities. Regulators like SEBI and RBI are implementing measures, including app verification tools and compensation frameworks, but sophisticated cybercriminals, increasingly operating from international hubs, pose a significant threat to market integrity and investor trust.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:57:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2e622fa7d0695d1b037db_1772283756643.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Groww Pivots Upmarket: AI, Wealth &amp; Bonds Drive New Growth Phase</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Groww-Pivots-Upmarket-AI-Wealth-and-Bonds-Drive-New-Growth-Phase/69a2e621fa7d0695d1b037c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Groww-Pivots-Upmarket-AI-Wealth-and-Bonds-Drive-New-Growth-Phase/69a2e621fa7d0695d1b037c5</guid><description>Groww is aggressively expanding beyond its core offerings, launching new platforms like Prime and W for affluent and HNI investors, alongside AI-powered tools (GR1, CII) and a professional trading platform, '915'. This strategic move into wealth management, advanced trading, and fixed-income instruments aims to capture higher-value market segments. With over 18 million users and a recent pre-IPO funding round valuing it near $7 billion, Groww is positioning itself for significant revenue growth beyond its established retail base.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:57:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2e621fa7d0695d1b037c4_1772283581582.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Arbitration Gap: Trust Deficit Costs Global Hub Status</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Arbitration-Gap-Trust-Deficit-Costs-Global-Hub-Status/69a2e533fa7d0695d1b03674</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Arbitration-Gap-Trust-Deficit-Costs-Global-Hub-Status/69a2e533fa7d0695d1b03674</guid><description>Chief Justice of India Surya Kant identified a critical trust deficit as the primary barrier preventing Indian institutions from attracting international arbitration disputes. Despite legislative and judicial reforms, the CJI stated that parties continue to favor overseas arbitration seats due to perceived shortcomings in arbitrator neutrality, procedural integrity, and award enforceability. This lack of confidence means India is failing to capitalize on its potential as a global dispute resolution hub, impacting commercial certainty and economic competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:53:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2e533fa7d0695d1b03673_1772283327700.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India M&amp;A: Legal Ambiguity Stifles Investment Despite Arbitration Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/India-MandA-Legal-Ambiguity-Stifles-Investment-Despite-Arbitration-Push/69a2e533fa7d0695d1b0365d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/India-MandA-Legal-Ambiguity-Stifles-Investment-Despite-Arbitration-Push/69a2e533fa7d0695d1b0365d</guid><description>India's mergers and acquisitions sector saw robust private equity and venture capital deal value of approximately $36.8 billion in 2025. However, a significant "uncertainty premium" is emerging due to inconsistent judicial interpretations on arbitration enforceability. This ambiguity, amplified by a preference for offshore arbitration seats and contrasting court decisions, risks deterring foreign investment, impacting deal valuations, and hindering India's ambition to be a premier M&amp;A and arbitration hub.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:53:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2e533fa7d0695d1b0365c_1772283408636.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anzen India Energy Buys 11 Solar Firms, Debt Securities; Expands Renewables</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Anzen-India-Energy-Buys-11-Solar-Firms-Debt-Securities-Expands-Renewables/69a2e516fa7d0695d1b03617</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Anzen-India-Energy-Buys-11-Solar-Firms-Debt-Securities-Expands-Renewables/69a2e516fa7d0695d1b03617</guid><description>Anzen India Energy Yield Plus Trust has significantly bolstered its renewable energy portfolio by acquiring 74% equity shares in 11 solar energy companies from Edelweiss Infrastructure Yield Plus. The trust also acquired debt securities in Solaire Surya Urja Private Limited (SSUPL) and is set to complete the equity acquisition of SSUPL shortly. This move signals aggressive expansion in India's burgeoning solar power sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:52:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2e516fa7d0695d1b03616_1772283426499.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahanagar Gas: Deepak Gupta to Chair from March 1; Shareholder Nod Pending</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mahanagar-Gas-Deepak-Gupta-to-Chair-from-March-1-Shareholder-Nod-Pending/69a2e350fa7d0695d1b034a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mahanagar-Gas-Deepak-Gupta-to-Chair-from-March-1-Shareholder-Nod-Pending/69a2e350fa7d0695d1b034a2</guid><description>Mahanagar Gas Limited (MGL) announced a significant leadership change with Shri Sandeep Kumar Gupta stepping down as Director and Chairman on March 1, 2026. The company has approved Shri Deepak Gupta as the new Chairman and an Additional Director, also effective March 1, 2026. This transition follows the withdrawal of nomination for the outgoing chairman by GAIL (India) Limited and is subject to shareholder approval.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2e350fa7d0695d1b034a1_1772283010998.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Finsec Promoters Pledge Entire 56% Stake; Margin Call Risk Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Finsec-Promoters-Pledge-Entire-56percent-Stake-Margin-Call-Risk-Soars/69a2e16ffa7d0695d1b033a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Finsec-Promoters-Pledge-Entire-56percent-Stake-Margin-Call-Risk-Soars/69a2e16ffa7d0695d1b033a3</guid><description>India Finsec Limited's promoter group has pledged its entire holding of 16,342,062 equity shares, equating to 55.98% of the company's total share capital. This significant encumbrance, created on February 24, 2026, is primarily for securing intra-day margin from brokers like Motilal Oswal Financial Services and for personal use. The move exposes the promoters to substantial risk from potential margin calls and raises concerns about their financial flexibility.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:37:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2e16ffa7d0695d1b033a2_1772282325203.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bluegod Entertainment to Raise ₹31.63 Cr Via Rights Issue; Signs Sports IP Term Sheet</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Bluegod-Entertainment-to-Raise-3163-Cr-Via-Rights-Issue-Signs-Sports-IP-Term-Sheet/69a2ddb0fa7d0695d1b031f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Bluegod-Entertainment-to-Raise-3163-Cr-Via-Rights-Issue-Signs-Sports-IP-Term-Sheet/69a2ddb0fa7d0695d1b031f2</guid><description>Bluegod Entertainment Limited will raise ₹31.63 crore through a Rights Issue at ₹3.00 per share. The company also executed a Term Sheet for the assignment of Intellectual Property rights related to Legends League Cricket, while deciding against acquiring a team in the league. This marks a strategic recalibration after a recent acquisition of LLC licensing rights.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:21:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2ddb0fa7d0695d1b031f1_1772281370970.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>March Stock Picks: Seasonality vs. Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/March-Stock-Picks-Seasonality-vs-Volatility/69a2d97afa7d0695d1b0304e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/March-Stock-Picks-Seasonality-vs-Volatility/69a2d97afa7d0695d1b0304e</guid><description>Despite historical March seasonal strength, Pidilite Industries, Cummins India, and AIA Engineering face headwinds. Persistent inflation, geopolitical tensions, and company-specific challenges like export declines and margin pressures introduce significant volatility, questioning the reliability of past performance as a forward indicator for March 2026. Investors must scrutinize these factors beyond simple seasonal patterns.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2d97afa7d0695d1b0304d_1772280308200.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Hype vs. Enterprise Reality: India Poised to Outperform</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Hype-vs-Enterprise-Reality-India-Poised-to-Outperform/69a2d692fa7d0695d1b02e98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Hype-vs-Enterprise-Reality-India-Poised-to-Outperform/69a2d692fa7d0695d1b02e98</guid><description>Jefferies' global equity strategist Chris Wood suggests investors are overestimating AI's consumer profitability, likening its capital intensity to airlines. While consumer AI lacks clear monetization, enterprise adoption presents opportunities for Indian IT services firms, positioning them as AI integrators. Wood identifies U.S. private equity and credit markets as a bubble, heavily exposed to leveraged software buyouts. In contrast, India's market shows resilience, driven by strong domestic flows and extended consolidation, suggesting potential for relative outperformance during global tech or credit-induced corrections. Despite AI's disruptive potential for software and IT services, a nuanced view suggests enterprise AI utility and India's domestic demand may offer a more stable growth narrative.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:50:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2d692fa7d0695d1b02e97_1772279535895.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Teeters as Bearish Futures Signal Deep Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Teeters-as-Bearish-Futures-Signal-Deep-Concern/69a2d01afa7d0695d1b02b27</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Teeters-as-Bearish-Futures-Signal-Deep-Concern/69a2d01afa7d0695d1b02b27</guid><description>Bitcoin consolidated near $63,000-$68,000, grappling with a sharp decline in perpetual futures funding rates to -6%. This indicates aggressive bearish positioning, with traders paying a premium to short the asset. Over $500 million in crypto positions were liquidated in 24 hours, predominantly long. While this could fuel a short squeeze, the persistence of such negative sentiment, coupled with lower funding rates for Ethereum and weaker performance in Solana, raises questions about underlying market conviction.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2d01afa7d0695d1b02b26_1772277913521.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Airspace Curbs: Mideast Tensions Ground Carriers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Airspace-Curbs-Mideast-Tensions-Ground-Carriers/69a2cfbdfa7d0695d1b02a93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Airspace-Curbs-Mideast-Tensions-Ground-Carriers/69a2cfbdfa7d0695d1b02a93</guid><description>Indian carriers IndiGo, Air India, and SpiceJet have suspended flights to the Middle East amid escalating geopolitical tensions and dynamic airspace restrictions. These cancellations impose significant revenue losses and elevate operational costs due to rerouting and extended flight times. The situation strains the already fragile financial health of the Indian aviation sector, which is navigating substantial debt, volatile fuel prices, and currency risks. For carriers like SpiceJet, already facing financial headwinds, these disruptions compound existing challenges, while even market leader IndiGo faces profit margin pressures.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:21:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2cfbdfa7d0695d1b02a92_1772277788841.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Middle East Conflict Grounds Flights, Squeezing Airline Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Middle-East-Conflict-Grounds-Flights-Squeezing-Airline-Margins/69a2cfb8fa7d0695d1b02a7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Middle-East-Conflict-Grounds-Flights-Squeezing-Airline-Margins/69a2cfb8fa7d0695d1b02a7b</guid><description>Following strikes on Iran, airlines are suspending flights and rerouting operations, leading to increased fuel consumption and operational expenses. Major carriers like Lufthansa, Air France-KLM, and Wizz Air face immediate disruption, impacting their stock performance as oil prices surge. The sector, already navigating post-pandemic recovery, is now exposed to heightened geopolitical risk premiums and uncertain demand, prompting investor caution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:21:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2cfb8fa7d0695d1b02a7a_1772277846499.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>