<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>CHG bets on Nadav Greenberg to reinvent Mediterranean cuisine in NYC</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/CHG-bets-on-Nadav-Greenberg-to-reinvent-Mediterranean-cuisine-in-NYC/698b7b85767901642cf1b2c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/CHG-bets-on-Nadav-Greenberg-to-reinvent-Mediterranean-cuisine-in-NYC/698b7b85767901642cf1b2c1</guid><description>Catch Hospitality Group (CHG) has unveiled Or'esh, a bold new modern Mediterranean concept in SoHo, featuring Michelin-starred Chef Nadav Greenberg, formerly of Shmoné. CHG aims to 'reinvent the category' through Greenberg's artistic, ingredient-driven approach centered on a custom charcoal grille. The 80-seat venue boasts a maximalist design by Rockwell Group, intentionally separating ambiance from overt regional cues to let the cuisine command attention. This strategic launch leverages CHG's proven track record in creating high-impact dining experiences, positioning Or'esh to challenge established players in New York's saturated upscale dining scene.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Udhyam Debt Launches: BlackSoil Capital Eyes MSME Credit Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Udhyam-Debt-Launches-BlackSoil-Capital-Eyes-MSME-Credit-Gap/698b757121f404cb59e9ae31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Udhyam-Debt-Launches-BlackSoil-Capital-Eyes-MSME-Credit-Gap/698b757121f404cb59e9ae31</guid><description>BlackSoil Capital has rebranded its acquisition, Caspian Debt, to Udhyam Debt, sharpening its focus on India's micro, small, and medium enterprises (MSMEs). The division has initiated operations with ₹35 crore deployed across five growth-stage companies, including Freshbus and Neeman's. This strategic move aims to leverage Caspian's underwriting expertise with BlackSoil's scale and risk discipline to address the vast MSME credit deficit in India, estimated between $200 billion and $350 billion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Net Zero Gambit: $14T Overhaul Amidst Coal's Enduring Shadow</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Net-Zero-Gambit-14T-Overhaul-Amidst-Coals-Enduring-Shadow/698b752221f404cb59e9acd6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Net-Zero-Gambit-14T-Overhaul-Amidst-Coals-Enduring-Shadow/698b752221f404cb59e9acd6</guid><description>India's ambitious 'Viksit Bharat' and Net Zero by 2070 goals, detailed in a NITI Aayog study, mandate a monumental $14.23 trillion power sector transformation. This involves an aggressive pivot from coal to over 80% renewables and significant nuclear expansion, but the transition faces formidable challenges. Continued coal dependence, immense grid modernization needs, substantial financing gaps, and supply chain vulnerabilities underscore the complex, high-stakes energy overhaul ahead.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jyoti CNC Automation: Q3 Revenue Jumps 28%, But Debt &amp; Margins Raise Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jyoti-CNC-Automation-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-28percent-But-Debt-and-Margins-Raise-Concerns/698b74fb21f404cb59e9abdb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jyoti-CNC-Automation-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-28percent-But-Debt-and-Margins-Raise-Concerns/698b74fb21f404cb59e9abdb</guid><description>Jyoti CNC Automation unveiled robust Q3 FY26 results, posting a 28.1% YoY revenue surge to ₹575.9 Cr and a 37.3% EBITDA jump. Capacity expansions in France and new product launches fueled this growth, backed by a healthy ₹4,585 Cr order book. However, PAT margins contracted by 250 bps YoY to 15.4% amid higher finance costs, while debt-to-equity climbed to 0.7x, indicating a shift to net debt. Investors note negative operating cash flows and significant ongoing CapEx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:12:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b74fb21f404cb59e9abda_1770747222266.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Surge Meets Critical Security Gap: A High-Stakes Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Surge-Meets-Critical-Security-Gap-A-High-Stakes-Race/698b74b321f404cb59e9aad1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Surge-Meets-Critical-Security-Gap-A-High-Stakes-Race/698b74b321f404cb59e9aad1</guid><description>India ranks second globally in enterprise AI/ML transactions, driven by digital transformation and heavy investment. However, a Zscaler report reveals critical security deficits, including rapid AI system vulnerabilities and data loss risks, as adversarial AI capabilities escalate. This imbalance presents substantial challenges for businesses and highlights an urgent need for advanced cyber defenses in India's booming AI sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:10:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b74b321f404cb59e9aad0_1770747158449.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tobacco Board lobbies FM on Tax Hike; Illicit Trade Risks Escalate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Tobacco-Board-lobbies-FM-on-Tax-Hike-Illicit-Trade-Risks-Escalate/698b749c21f404cb59e9aa2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Tobacco-Board-lobbies-FM-on-Tax-Hike-Illicit-Trade-Risks-Escalate/698b749c21f404cb59e9aa2c</guid><description>The Tobacco Board has formally petitioned India's Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman to reconsider the recent steep excise duty hike on cigarettes. Citing severe distress across the tobacco value chain, particularly for millions of farmers, the board warns of a significant rise in illicit cigarette trade. This appeal, led by a senior political figure, highlights a growing tension between government revenue targets and the socio-economic stability of the tobacco sector. The potential for uncontrolled black market growth, coupled with farmer livelihoods at risk, presents a complex policy challenge.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sigma Advanced Systems Bets Big on Systems Integration with AS Strategic Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Sigma-Advanced-Systems-Bets-Big-on-Systems-Integration-with-AS-Strategic-Acquisition/698b748221f404cb59e9a94c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Sigma-Advanced-Systems-Bets-Big-on-Systems-Integration-with-AS-Strategic-Acquisition/698b748221f404cb59e9a94c</guid><description>Hyderabad-based Sigma Advanced Systems has acquired Delhi-based AS Strategic for an estimated Rs 30 crore, signaling a significant strategic shift. This move is designed to propel Sigma into a higher-value aerospace and defence systems integration role, complementing its recent acquisition of UK firm Nasmyth. The integration aims to create a vertically integrated platform with direct access to European defence programs and leverage AS Strategic's existing order book exceeding Rs 315 crore for 2026. Sigma plans to bring AS Strategic's outsourced manufacturing in-house, a move intended to boost margins and enhance operational control.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:10:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b748221f404cb59e9a94b_1770747094248.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCLT Directs Shareholder Meet for India Radiators-Mercantile Ventures Merger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCLT-Directs-Shareholder-Meet-for-India-Radiators-Mercantile-Ventures-Merger/698b714221f404cb59e9a6e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCLT-Directs-Shareholder-Meet-for-India-Radiators-Mercantile-Ventures-Merger/698b714221f404cb59e9a6e9</guid><description>The National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), Chennai Bench, has ordered a meeting of India Radiators Limited (IRL) equity shareholders on March 13, 2026, to approve its amalgamation with Mercantile Ventures Limited (MVL). This crucial step follows IRL's negative net worth of ₹37.03 lakhs for FY25, contrasting sharply with MVL's substantial net worth of ₹32,827.06 lakhs. The proposed scheme involves a share exchange ratio of 10 MVL shares for every 36 IRL shares, with management citing cost efficiencies, operational synergies, and the commercial development of IRL's land bank as primary drivers for the merger.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Servier Launches Global Single-Pill Platform in India with €15M Investment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Servier-Launches-Global-Single-Pill-Platform-in-India-with-15M-Investment/698b713821f404cb59e9a67f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Servier-Launches-Global-Single-Pill-Platform-in-India-with-15M-Investment/698b713821f404cb59e9a67f</guid><description>French pharmaceutical giant Servier is establishing a global single-pill combination platform, GATINN, in India with a €15 million investment. The India-based hub will spearhead development, manufacturing, and export of these simplified medications, aiming to boost patient adherence for cardiometabolic and venous diseases worldwide. This strategic move leverages India's manufacturing prowess.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>R Systems Posts Strong FY25 Growth, Bolsters AI with Novigo Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/R-Systems-Posts-Strong-FY25-Growth-Bolsters-AI-with-Novigo-Acquisition/698b706b21f404cb59e9a544</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/R-Systems-Posts-Strong-FY25-Growth-Bolsters-AI-with-Novigo-Acquisition/698b706b21f404cb59e9a544</guid><description>R Systems International reported robust FY2025 financial results, with revenue up 12.4% YoY to Rs 19,582 million and adjusted PAT growing 24.6% to Rs 1,936 million. Q4 FY2025 saw similar strong momentum. The strategic acquisition of Novigo Solutions for Rs 4,000 million significantly bolsters its automation and Agentic AI capabilities, positioning the company for AI-led growth. Improved liquidity and shareholder equity further underscore financial strength.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>VIP Industries Bets on CSK Tie-Up Amidst Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VIP-Industries-Bets-on-CSK-Tie-Up-Amidst-Losses/698b705321f404cb59e9a45a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VIP-Industries-Bets-on-CSK-Tie-Up-Amidst-Losses/698b705321f404cb59e9a45a</guid><description>VIP Industries, through its Skybags brand, has partnered with Chennai Super Kings for the IPL 2026 season, launching an official licensed range. This move signals a strategic push into the sports category and a broader effort to revitalize the mass-market brand. The company, currently facing financial challenges including significant losses and a high debt-to-equity ratio, is emphasizing premiumization across its portfolio. This initiative, accelerated by private equity firm Multiples' entry, aims to counter competition from agile D2C brands and capture a larger share in the expanding Indian luggage market by increasing average selling prices and product relevance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:52:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b705321f404cb59e9a459_1770746077773.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>STT Hike Sparks Volatility; India's Growth Story Unfazed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/STT-Hike-Sparks-Volatility-Indias-Growth-Story-Unfazed/698b6fd421f404cb59e9a2fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/STT-Hike-Sparks-Volatility-Indias-Growth-Story-Unfazed/698b6fd421f404cb59e9a2fd</guid><description>The Indian market experienced an initial negative reaction to the recent Securities Transaction Tax (STT) hike, designed to curb speculation in derivatives. While High-Frequency Traders (HFTs) face increased costs, the nation's robust economic growth prospects, projected to contribute 17% to global GDP in 2026, are expected to drive market resilience and attract foreign investment back. Despite a challenging 2025 where Indian equities underperformed global peers, a valuation correction and ongoing structural strengths position India as a compelling, albeit premium, investment destination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:50:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6fd421f404cb59e9a2fc_1770745913934.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chambal Fertilisers Surges on Revenue Growth, Margin Pressure Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Chambal-Fertilisers-Surges-on-Revenue-Growth-Margin-Pressure-Looms/698b6c1124fc81b37934f232</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Chambal-Fertilisers-Surges-on-Revenue-Growth-Margin-Pressure-Looms/698b6c1124fc81b37934f232</guid><description>Chambal Fertilisers and Chemicals Limited (CFCL) reported a robust 20% YoY increase in consolidated operating income to ₹58,983 million for Q3 FY26, with net profit rising 10% to ₹5,864 million. The nine-month period saw a similar trend with revenue up 27% and profit up 17%. However, EBITDA margins compressed year-on-year for both periods, a point of concern. The company highlighted progress on its crucial Technical Ammonium Nitrate (TAN) project, nearing completion, and successful launches of five new products in Crop Protection Chemicals and Speciality Nutrients. Explicit forward-looking guidance was absent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:34:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6c1124fc81b37934f231_1770744917057.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wall Street Ignores Consumer Cracks for Fed Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Wall-Street-Ignores-Consumer-Cracks-for-Fed-Hopes/698b6bb624fc81b37934f119</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Wall-Street-Ignores-Consumer-Cracks-for-Fed-Hopes/698b6bb624fc81b37934f119</guid><description>U.S. equities flirted with record levels on Tuesday, February 10, 2026, as traders boosted bets on Federal Reserve interest rate cuts following a disappointing retail sales report. However, mixed corporate earnings, with Hasbro surging on strong gaming results and Coca-Cola slipping on revenue misses, highlight a market increasingly selective amidst economic crosscurrents. Weak consumer demand signals and company-specific challenges are being largely discounted in favor of monetary policy expectations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:32:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6bb624fc81b37934f118_1770744856702.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>XLRI Bags ₹1.1 Crore Top Offer as Placements Conclude</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/XLRI-Bags-11-Crore-Top-Offer-as-Placements-Conclude/698b6b9724fc81b37934f036</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/XLRI-Bags-11-Crore-Top-Offer-as-Placements-Conclude/698b6b9724fc81b37934f036</guid><description>XLRI has concluded its 2024-26 batch placements, securing a top international offer of ₹1.1 crore and a highest domestic offer of ₹59 lakh. Across its Jamshedpur and Delhi-NCR campuses, 145 recruiters extended over 576 domestic and two international offers, with an average salary of ₹31.40 lakh per annum. Consulting, BFSI, and sales &amp; marketing emerged as the dominant domains for roles offered.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:32:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6b9724fc81b37934f035_1770744790282.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Trade Pressure Risks India's Digital Sovereignty, Energy Choices</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Trade-Pressure-Risks-Indias-Digital-Sovereignty-Energy-Choices/698b6b2424fc81b37934eeeb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Trade-Pressure-Risks-Indias-Digital-Sovereignty-Energy-Choices/698b6b2424fc81b37934eeeb</guid><description>As bilateral trade talks intensify, the US is pressing India to eliminate digital services taxes and commit to prohibiting duties on electronic transmissions, potentially compromising India's fiscal sovereignty and domestic digital industry. Simultaneously, the U.S. has linked tariff rollbacks to India's cessation of Russian oil purchases, intertwining energy security with trade concessions. Experts warn these demands could erode India's regulatory autonomy and create long-term disadvantages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:30:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6b2424fc81b37934eeea_1770744981585.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Realigns Trade &amp; Energy: Tariffs Cut Amid Geopolitical Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Realigns-Trade-and-Energy-Tariffs-Cut-Amid-Geopolitical-Shifts/698b6aac757d40c7818b5eac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Realigns-Trade-and-Energy-Tariffs-Cut-Amid-Geopolitical-Shifts/698b6aac757d40c7818b5eac</guid><description>India has finalized a landmark interim trade agreement with the United States, slashing reciprocal tariffs on its goods to 18% from 50%, and secured a Free Trade Agreement with the European Union. These moves coincide with a strategic recalibration of its crude oil imports, prioritizing affordability and security by diversifying away from Russian supplies towards new sources like the US and Venezuela. The nation is actively leveraging its energy procurement to bolster its position in a protectionist global trade environment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:28:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6aac757d40c7818b5eab_1770744561466.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Healthcare's Digital Paradox: Adoption Surges, Efficiency Lags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Healthcares-Digital-Paradox-Adoption-Surges-Efficiency-Lags/698b6a5c757d40c7818b5d88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Healthcares-Digital-Paradox-Adoption-Surges-Efficiency-Lags/698b6a5c757d40c7818b5d88</guid><description>India's healthcare sector has embraced digital transformation, with nearly all hospitals adopting foundational systems like HIS and two-thirds implementing EMRs. However, this widespread adoption is juxtaposed by critically low automation levels, with less than 25% utilizing technologies like RPA, leading to persistent manual workloads and operational inefficiencies. Integration challenges remain, as only about a third of facilities achieve full system interoperability. Despite these hurdles, hospitals are planning increased digital investments, signaling a strategic shift towards optimizing existing systems and governance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Modern Insulators posts 166% PAT surge; flagged for large interest-free loans, tax anomaly</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Modern-Insulators-posts-166percent-PAT-surge-flagged-for-large-interest-free-loans-tax-anomaly/698b6a32757d40c7818b5c52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Modern-Insulators-posts-166percent-PAT-surge-flagged-for-large-interest-free-loans-tax-anomaly/698b6a32757d40c7818b5c52</guid><description>Modern Insulators Ltd. reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with standalone PAT soaring 166.58% YoY to ₹2,466.33 Lacs, driven by a 60% revenue jump. However, the results are overshadowed by significant interest-free unsecured loans totalling ₹7,234 Lacs to an entity for proposed amalgamation and ₹1,678 Lacs to a subsidiary. Furthermore, a tax provision absence of ₹269.81 Lacs in the quarter, linked to the amalgamation, artificially boosted profits, while the NCLT order on the scheme adds complexity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Modern Insulators Q3 Earnings Soar; Amalgamation Update Sparks Interest.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Modern-Insulators-Q3-Earnings-Soar-Amalgamation-Update-Sparks-Interest/698b69bc757d40c7818b56c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Modern-Insulators-Q3-Earnings-Soar-Amalgamation-Update-Sparks-Interest/698b69bc757d40c7818b56c2</guid><description>Modern Insulators Ltd. reported a robust Q3 FY26 with standalone revenue up 60% YoY to ₹19,939 Lacs and PAT surging 166.6% to ₹2,466 Lacs. Consolidated figures mirrored this growth. The company is also advancing its proposed amalgamation with Modern Denim Limited, noting tax provisions and reviewing an NCLT order.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:24:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b69bc757d40c7818b56c1_1770744492493.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Laxmi India Finance Posts 64% PAT Jump, Hit by Loan Stress</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Laxmi-India-Finance-Posts-64percent-PAT-Jump-Hit-by-Loan-Stress/698b693f757d40c7818b5532</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Laxmi-India-Finance-Posts-64percent-PAT-Jump-Hit-by-Loan-Stress/698b693f757d40c7818b5532</guid><description>Laxmi India Finance Ltd. reported a robust 64.32% year-on-year jump in net profit to ₹10.04 crore for Q3 FY26. Total income grew 29.28% YoY. However, the company flagged a one-time stress event in its Direct Assignment loan pool, impacting reported asset quality and profitability. Underlying performance, excluding this event, shows significantly stronger metrics, with PAT at ₹38.22 crore for 9M FY26. Management assures focus on capital buffers, margins, and risk oversight.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:22:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b693f757d40c7818b5531_1770744384324.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>STL Networks Secures INR 206 Cr NICSI Order for Network Equipment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/STL-Networks-Secures-INR-206-Cr-NICSI-Order-for-Network-Equipment/698b68e4757d40c7818b53b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/STL-Networks-Secures-INR-206-Cr-NICSI-Order-for-Network-Equipment/698b68e4757d40c7818b53b7</guid><description>STL Networks has clinched a substantial purchase order worth INR 206.49 Crores from NICSI for network equipment under the NKN initiative. The deal includes a 12-week implementation phase followed by a 5-year warranty and AMC. The company confirmed no promoter interest in NICSI, ensuring a clean transaction. This order significantly bolsters STL's backlog and positions it for key national infrastructure projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Russia's Oil Revenue Crisis: Discounts Surge Amid Shifting Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Russias-Oil-Revenue-Crisis-Discounts-Surge-Amid-Shifting-Markets/698b68cb757d40c7818b52d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Russias-Oil-Revenue-Crisis-Discounts-Surge-Amid-Shifting-Markets/698b68cb757d40c7818b52d4</guid><description>Despite stable crude shipment volumes around 3.33 million barrels per day, Russia's oil revenue has collapsed, hitting a five-year low in January. This is driven by steeper discounts on Urals crude, weaker global prices, and a strengthening ruble, which erodes the rouble-equivalent value of export earnings. Shipments to India have fallen sharply, while an increasing number of tankers are rerouting towards China. Russia's crude output has declined for a second month, signaling production challenges exacerbated by the need for deep discounts to maintain export flows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NBFC Consolidation: Piramal, Tata Motors Surrender Licenses Amid RBI Rule Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFC-Consolidation-Piramal-Tata-Motors-Surrender-Licenses-Amid-RBI-Rule-Shifts/698b686f757d40c7818b515a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFC-Consolidation-Piramal-Tata-Motors-Surrender-Licenses-Amid-RBI-Rule-Shifts/698b686f757d40c7818b515a</guid><description>Piramal Enterprises and Tata Motors Finance have surrendered their NBFC registration certificates to the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) post-merger. This follows the RBI's February 6 announcement proposing exemptions from registration for 'Type I NBFCs' (asset size under ₹1,000 crore, no public funds/customer interface). These actions signal sector-wide consolidation driven by regulatory pressures and strategic realignment. Piramal Enterprises' P/E ratio hovers around 36.8, while Tata Motors (parent of Tata Motors Finance) shows a P/E of 6.14 as of February 2026, indicating diverse valuations within the broader financial services landscape.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:18:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b686f757d40c7818b5159.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Britannia Profit Surges Past Sales, Margins Expand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannia-Profit-Surges-Past-Sales-Margins-Expand/698b6853757d40c7818b502f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannia-Profit-Surges-Past-Sales-Margins-Expand/698b6853757d40c7818b502f</guid><description>Britannia Industries posted a consolidated Q3 FY26 net profit of ₹680 crore, a 17% year-on-year increase that outpaced its 8.2% revenue growth to ₹4,970 crore. EBITDA climbed 16% to ₹980 crore, with margins widening to 19.7% from 18.4%, signaling effective cost management. The results were achieved amidst a leadership transition, with Rakshit Hargave taking the helm as MD &amp; CEO on December 15, succeeding Varun Berry. Hargave attributed the profit-revenue divergence to healthier growth trends and price stabilization post-GST. The company has seen significant stock appreciation over the past year, trading at a premium valuation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:18:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6853757d40c7818b502e_1770744245036.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Michael Burry Warns Alphabet's 100-Year Bond Echoes Motorola's Fall</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Michael-Burry-Warns-Alphabets-100-Year-Bond-Echoes-Motorolas-Fall/698b67f2757d40c7818b4eb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Michael-Burry-Warns-Alphabets-100-Year-Bond-Echoes-Motorolas-Fall/698b67f2757d40c7818b4eb2</guid><description>Michael Burry, famed for predicting the 2008 crisis, is sounding the alarm on Alphabet's unprecedented 100-year bond issuance. He draws a stark parallel to Motorola's 1997 bond issuance, a move that preceded the tech giant's significant decline. Burry warns that long-term debt commitments may trap companies, risking future dominance as seen in Motorola's fate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:16:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b67f2757d40c7818b4eb1_1770743866054.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Laxmi India Finance IPO Funds Confirmed Used Amidst 42% Stock Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Laxmi-India-Finance-IPO-Funds-Confirmed-Used-Amidst-42percent-Stock-Plunge/698b67dc757d40c7818b4d9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Laxmi-India-Finance-IPO-Funds-Confirmed-Used-Amidst-42percent-Stock-Plunge/698b67dc757d40c7818b4d9e</guid><description>Laxmi India Finance Limited's Monitoring Agency Report confirms its IPO proceeds of Rs. 165.17 crore were utilized as disclosed, primarily for lending. Despite this, the company's stock has plunged 42% post-IPO, signaling significant investor concerns over valuation and future prospects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Laxmi India Finance Surges 63% Profit, Utilizes IPO Funds for Lending Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Laxmi-India-Finance-Surges-63percent-Profit-Utilizes-IPO-Funds-for-Lending-Growth/698b671e757d40c7818b16c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Laxmi-India-Finance-Surges-63percent-Profit-Utilizes-IPO-Funds-for-Lending-Growth/698b671e757d40c7818b16c9</guid><description>Laxmi India Finance Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26 with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 63.58% year-on-year to ₹100.62 Cr. Revenue from Operations grew 24.32% YoY to ₹719.86 Cr. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, PAT increased 36.42% YoY to ₹292.41 Cr. The company has significantly utilized its IPO proceeds towards onward lending and appointed a new Chief Technology Officer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:13:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b671e757d40c7818b16c8_1770743911744.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma: US FDA Issues Form 483 With 9 Procedural Observations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-US-FDA-Issues-Form-483-With-9-Procedural-Observations/698b6705757d40c7818b159c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-US-FDA-Issues-Form-483-With-9-Procedural-Observations/698b6705757d40c7818b159c</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma Limited's Unit-VII in Jedcherla, Telangana, has concluded a US FDA inspection, resulting in a Form 483 with nine procedural observations. The company stated these are not expected to impact financial or operational activities and committed to submitting a timely response, assuring adherence to quality standards.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:12:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6705757d40c7818b159b_1770743695555.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Standard Chartered Fuels India's Green Leap Amid Financing Gaps</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Standard-Chartered-Fuels-Indias-Green-Leap-Amid-Financing-Gaps/698b66eb757d40c7818b1481</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Standard-Chartered-Fuels-Indias-Green-Leap-Amid-Financing-Gaps/698b66eb757d40c7818b1481</guid><description>Standard Chartered is aggressively positioning itself to finance India's ambitious net-zero goals, pledging to mobilize $300 billion by 2030. Despite strong corporate intent in India's energy transition, a significant gap persists in the adoption of sustainable finance tools. The bank's commitment, bolstered by recent income generation and strategic partnerships, aims to bridge this gap, even as competitors recalibrate their climate targets. This strategic focus comes as India's green finance market expands, driven by e-mobility and renewable energy investments, though challenges in capital access and policy stability remain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:12:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b66eb757d40c7818b1480_1770743761547.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Biopharma Push: Budget 2026 Sparks Value Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Biopharma-Push-Budget-2026-Sparks-Value-Shift/698b667c757d40c7818b0ae1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Biopharma-Push-Budget-2026-Sparks-Value-Shift/698b667c757d40c7818b0ae1</guid><description>The Indian Union Budget 2026 earmarks ₹10,000 crore for the 'Biopharma Shakti' initiative, signaling a decisive pivot from volume-driven generic drug production to value-added biologics and advanced therapies. This strategic allocation aims to transform India into a global biopharmaceutical manufacturing and innovation hub. Complementary initiatives include enhanced healthcare infrastructure spending exceeding ₹1,06,530 crore, bolstered digital health frameworks, and regulatory reforms targeting accelerated approvals. The move is poised to reshape India's role in global supply chains and catalyze domestic R&amp;D.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:10:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b667c757d40c7818b0ae0_1770743652541.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ESAB India Declares Rs 25 Dividend Amidst 11.5% Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ESAB-India-Declares-Rs-25-Dividend-Amidst-115percent-Revenue-Growth/698b6605757d40c7818b094c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ESAB-India-Declares-Rs-25-Dividend-Amidst-115percent-Revenue-Growth/698b6605757d40c7818b094c</guid><description>ESAB India announced robust Q3 FY26 results, with a 11.5% YoY increase in total income to Rs. 37,990 Lakhs and a 6.5% rise in net profit to Rs. 4,300 Lakhs. For the nine months, net profit surged 27.5%. The company also declared a second interim dividend of Rs. 25 per share. A Rs. 1,365 Lakhs exceptional charge impacted Q3 PAT margin, which fell slightly to 11.32% from 11.85% YoY.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:08:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6605757d40c7818b094b_1770743591263.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Regaal Resources Faces ₹14.9 Cr Tax Demand, Makes ₹6.66 Cr Provision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Regaal-Resources-Faces-149-Cr-Tax-Demand-Makes-666-Cr-Provision/698b6580757d40c7818aef6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Regaal-Resources-Faces-149-Cr-Tax-Demand-Makes-666-Cr-Provision/698b6580757d40c7818aef6a</guid><description>Regaal Resources Limited disclosed receiving a significant ₹14.90 Crore tax demand notice from the Joint Commissioner of State Tax, Kishanganj, for alleged incorrect GST reimbursements under the Bihar Industrial Promotion Policy. The company has provided ₹6.66 Crore as an exceptional item in its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, to cover potential liabilities. Regaal Resources is currently examining the notice and intends to pursue appropriate legal steps, including filing replies and appeals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:06:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6580757d40c7818aef69_1770743457346.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NephroPlus Q3 PAT Surges 71% Driven by International Growth and Margin Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/NephroPlus-Q3-PAT-Surges-71percent-Driven-by-International-Growth-and-Margin-Expansion/698b6531757d40c7818aede1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/NephroPlus-Q3-PAT-Surges-71percent-Driven-by-International-Growth-and-Margin-Expansion/698b6531757d40c7818aede1</guid><description>NephroPlus posted stellar Q3 FY26 results, with PAT surging 71.3% YoY to ₹34.4 crore on 31.7% revenue growth to ₹259.7 crore. Margin expansion and a strong shift to international markets, now 41.1% of revenue, fueled profit growth. Annualized ROCE improved to 24.7%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:04:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b6531757d40c7818aede0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's $22.7T Net Zero Goal: Massive Funding Gap &amp; Sectoral Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-227T-Net-Zero-Goal-Massive-Funding-Gap-and-Sectoral-Hurdles/698b650f757d40c7818aed0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-227T-Net-Zero-Goal-Massive-Funding-Gap-and-Sectoral-Hurdles/698b650f757d40c7818aed0b</guid><description>India's premier think tank, NITI Aayog, has unveiled a comprehensive roadmap for achieving Net Zero emissions by 2070, envisioning a $22.7 trillion investment requirement. While the plan details sectoral strategies for clean energy transition, it highlights substantial financing gaps and formidable implementation hurdles, particularly in securing critical mineral supply chains and decarbonizing industrial heavyweights. The ambitious pathway necessitates significant external capital and coordinated policy execution to overcome these complex challenges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:04:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b650f757d40c7818aed0a_1770743526528.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CNH India Targets $500M Exports via US Trade Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CNH-India-Targets-500M-Exports-via-US-Trade-Deal/698b6425757d40c7818abe89</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CNH-India-Targets-500M-Exports-via-US-Trade-Deal/698b6425757d40c7818abe89</guid><description>CNH India is restarting significant tractor and component exports to the United States, projecting a three-year target of $500 million, a substantial increase from its 2025 figures. This resumption follows a temporary halt due to U.S. tariffs but is now facilitated by a new India-U.S. trade agreement that reduces duties. Concurrently, the company plans to import higher-horsepower tractors from the U.S. into India, capitalizing on trade pacts to enhance its domestic offerings and expand its global manufacturing role.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:00:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6425757d40c7818abe88_1770743035516.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC's Omnichannel Gambit: Kiranas Meet Q-Commerce for FMCG Edge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITCs-Omnichannel-Gambit-Kiranas-Meet-Q-Commerce-for-FMCG-Edge/698b63a5757d40c7818abca7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITCs-Omnichannel-Gambit-Kiranas-Meet-Q-Commerce-for-FMCG-Edge/698b63a5757d40c7818abca7</guid><description>ITC's executive B. Sumant outlines a strategy leveraging quick commerce for enhanced product availability and faster consumer trial, while reinforcing the enduring relevance of kirana stores. This omnichannel approach aims to capitalize on India's FMCG demand recovery and premiumization trend, driven by government stimulus and digital adoption. The company is enhancing its deep distribution network through digital enablement and tailored assortments, positioning for growth across diverse product categories. This balanced strategy seeks to mitigate risks inherent in a rapidly digitizing retail environment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:58:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b63a5757d40c7818abca6_1770742791921.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India FTAs Unlocked: Dixon Eyes Global Reach Amidst Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-FTAs-Unlocked-Dixon-Eyes-Global-Reach-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/698b6281757d40c78189b4c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-FTAs-Unlocked-Dixon-Eyes-Global-Reach-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/698b6281757d40c78189b4c9</guid><description>India's recent Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) signal a paradigm shift, unlocking global market potential for electronics manufacturers like Dixon Technologies. While this presents a significant growth opportunity, Dixon faces the formidable challenge of overcoming established international competition and addressing internal gaps in talent, technology, and product standards. The company is diversifying into new verticals, including automotive electronics and component manufacturing, to leverage these trade dynamics, even as its core mobile segment navigates recent sales headwinds. Analyst sentiment remains cautiously optimistic, with price targets suggesting potential upside, but the path to capitalizing on global trade is underscored by the need for substantial operational evolution and strategic execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:53:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6281757d40c78189b4c8_1770742780045.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's EV Ambition: Navigating Growth, Affordability, and Global Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-EV-Ambition-Navigating-Growth-Affordability-and-Global-Competition/698b6266757d40c78189b347</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-EV-Ambition-Navigating-Growth-Affordability-and-Global-Competition/698b6266757d40c78189b347</guid><description>India is aggressively pursuing global leadership in electric vehicles (EVs) with ambitious net-zero targets by 2070 and substantial market growth, evidenced by a 60% CAGR in FY25 and nearly two million registrations. Government initiatives like Production Linked Incentive schemes and the PM E-DRIVE program are bolstering domestic manufacturing and charging infrastructure. However, the sector faces challenges including lower-than-global-average EV penetration, an underdeveloped charging network, and dependence on imported components. India is also emerging as a disruptor in the affordable EV segment, with ultra-low-cost models challenging established premium EV markets, though domestic players like Tata Motors and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra grapple with valuation metrics and competitive pressures from both local and international manufacturers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:52:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b6266757d40c78189b346_1770743064830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coca-Cola Bets Big on India Amid Headwinds: Digital Push Meets Price Sensitivity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Coca-Cola-Bets-Big-on-India-Amid-Headwinds-Digital-Push-Meets-Price-Sensitivity/698b623c757d40c78189b244</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Coca-Cola-Bets-Big-on-India-Amid-Headwinds-Digital-Push-Meets-Price-Sensitivity/698b623c757d40c78189b244</guid><description>Coca-Cola views India as a "market of the future," pledging unprecedented investments with bottling partners to drive volume growth. Despite a challenging 2025 marked by macroeconomic issues, tax dynamics, and weather impacts, the company anticipates recovery in 2026, bolstered by significant digital initiatives like the Coke Buddy platform. However, this optimistic outlook confronts a 6% unit case volume decline in the recent quarter, increasing competitive pressures from PepsiCo, and questions about consumer price sensitivity, even as analysts maintain a 'Buy' consensus.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:52:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b623c757d40c78189b243_1770743201296.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>