<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:34:20 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver EXPLODE: Record Rally in 2025! Will the Golden Streak Continue in 2026 Amidst Wild Swings?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-EXPLODE-Record-Rally-in-2025-Will-the-Golden-Streak-Continue-in-2026-Amidst-Wild-Swings/6955182f4342f77179ee860d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-EXPLODE-Record-Rally-in-2025-Will-the-Golden-Streak-Continue-in-2026-Amidst-Wild-Swings/6955182f4342f77179ee860d</guid><description>Gold and silver achieved their best returns in decades in 2025, with gold up nearly 65% globally and 76.7% in rupees, while silver surged almost 150% internationally and 170% in India. Recent sharp volatility and profit-booking suggest overbought conditions and near-term pullback risks. However, experts believe macro factors could support continued rallies in 2026, advising investors to buy on dips.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Anand Mahindra's Bold Vision: AI to Make Blue Collar Jobs 'Gold Collar'!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Anand-Mahindras-Bold-Vision-AI-to-Make-Blue-Collar-Jobs-Gold-Collar/6955181b4342f77179ee85ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Anand-Mahindras-Bold-Vision-AI-to-Make-Blue-Collar-Jobs-Gold-Collar/6955181b4342f77179ee85ba</guid><description>Mahindra Group Chairperson Anand Mahindra's New Year message highlights a year of market leadership and redefines expectations. He foresees Artificial Intelligence transforming blue-collar jobs into 'gold collar' opportunities by enhancing practical skills. Mahindra also emphasizes India's potential for a 'brain gain' and the vital role of institutions like Mahindra University in nurturing future global innovators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Redington Faces ₹148 Crore GST Demand: Company Assures No Material Impact Amidst Strong Q2 Performance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Redington-Faces-148-Crore-GST-Demand-Company-Assures-No-Material-Impact-Amidst-Strong-Q2-Performance/695517034342f77179ee81e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Redington-Faces-148-Crore-GST-Demand-Company-Assures-No-Material-Impact-Amidst-Strong-Q2-Performance/695517034342f77179ee81e6</guid><description>Redington Limited has disclosed receiving a Goods and Services Tax (GST) assessment order totaling ₹148.33 crore, including interest and penalties, from CGST Gurugram. The demand arises from the disallowance of input tax credit claimed for financial years 2018-19, 2019-20, and 2021-22, under Section 74 of the GST Act. The technology solutions provider stated that this order will not materially impact its financials or operations, based on its assessment and legal advice. This news comes shortly after Redington reported a robust 32% year-on-year growth in net profit to ₹388 crore for the quarter ended September 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:01:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695517034342f77179ee81e5_1767184404692.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LIC Faces ₹57 Crore GST Demand! Insurer to Fight Orders in Court</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Faces-57-Crore-GST-Demand-Insurer-to-Fight-Orders-in-Court/695516b74342f77179ee8055</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Faces-57-Crore-GST-Demand-Insurer-to-Fight-Orders-in-Court/695516b74342f77179ee8055</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has received Goods and Services Tax (GST) demand orders totaling approximately ₹57.52 crore across Telangana, Maharashtra, and Delhi for the financial year 2021-22. The company plans to file appeals against these demands, citing short payment of tax and wrongly claimed input tax credit, but assures no material impact on its operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:01:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695516b74342f77179ee8054_1767184240947.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Sugar Output Surges 23.43% in Early Season: Maharashtra Leads the Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Sugar-Output-Surges-2343percent-in-Early-Season-Maharashtra-Leads-the-Boom/695516a04342f77179ee7fdc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Sugar-Output-Surges-2343percent-in-Early-Season-Maharashtra-Leads-the-Boom/695516a04342f77179ee7fdc</guid><description>India's sugar production has surged by 23.43% to 11.83 million tonnes during the first three months (October-December) of the 2025-26 season. This significant increase is largely driven by a sharp rise in output from Maharashtra, the country's second-largest sugar-producing state, according to the National Federation of Cooperative Sugar Factories Ltd (NFCSF).</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:01:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695516a04342f77179ee7fdb_1767184226680.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Powerhouse: ₹35,657 Cr Invested, ₹2,321 Cr Incentives Paid Under PLI Scheme - EV Revolution Ignites!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Powerhouse-35657-Cr-Invested-2321-Cr-Incentives-Paid-Under-PLI-Scheme-EV-Revolution-Ignites/695515314342f77179ee79bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Powerhouse-35657-Cr-Invested-2321-Cr-Incentives-Paid-Under-PLI-Scheme-EV-Revolution-Ignites/695515314342f77179ee79bf</guid><description>India's Production Linked Incentive (PLI) Auto scheme has successfully boosted advanced automotive technology (AAT) manufacturing, attracting ₹35,657 crore in investments and disbursing ₹2,321.94 crore in incentives as of December 31, 2025. Major players like Tata Motors, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, and Ola Electric have benefited, with incentives supporting over 1.3 million electric vehicles across various categories, reinforcing the 'Atmanirbhar Bharat' vision.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:01:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695515314342f77179ee79be_1767184068951.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Report Stuns: India Stocks Lag Global Peers in 2025 After Peak Performance! DIIs Become Market Saviors?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Report-Stuns-India-Stocks-Lag-Global-Peers-in-2025-After-Peak-Performance-DIIs-Become-Market-Saviors/695515da4342f77179ee7cce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Report-Stuns-India-Stocks-Lag-Global-Peers-in-2025-After-Peak-Performance-DIIs-Become-Market-Saviors/695515da4342f77179ee7cce</guid><description>A Reserve Bank of India report reveals Indian equities underperformed emerging and advanced economies in 2025, reversing a five-year outperformance trend. Despite this, domestic institutional investors (DIIs) cushioned market volatility, surpassing foreign investor ownership and inflows. Market volatility remained notably low compared to global benchmarks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:58:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695515da4342f77179ee7ccd_1767184059202.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Warns: AI Stock Frenzy Risks Asian Markets! Is a US Crash Coming?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Warns-AI-Stock-Frenzy-Risks-Asian-Markets-Is-a-US-Crash-Coming/695515164342f77179ee7959</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Warns-AI-Stock-Frenzy-Risks-Asian-Markets-Is-a-US-Crash-Coming/695515164342f77179ee7959</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Financial Stability Report highlights a significant risk: Asian equity markets are being artificially inflated by a small number of AI-linked technology stocks. This narrow concentration mirrors trends in the US, where just a few tech giants are responsible for the majority of market gains. The RBI warns that a major correction in US equities could trigger global spillovers, impacting markets across Asia and potentially leading to widespread financial instability. High capital requirements for AI investments are also increasing debt financing in the tech sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:58:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695515164342f77179ee7958_1767184176178.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Insurers Slash Government Bonds, Pouring Billions into Stocks: What it Means for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Insurers-Slash-Government-Bonds-Pouring-Billions-into-Stocks-What-it-Means-for-Your-Investments/695514794342f77179ee76fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Insurers-Slash-Government-Bonds-Pouring-Billions-into-Stocks-What-it-Means-for-Your-Investments/695514794342f77179ee76fc</guid><description>India's insurance companies are significantly reducing their holdings in government securities, with the share of Central and State government bonds falling to 59.7% from 61.7% year-on-year. This shift, detailed in the Reserve Bank of India's Financial Stability Report, sees insurers increasing their exposure to equities and mutual funds to ₹16.6 lakh crore from ₹14.3 lakh crore. Corporate bond investments also rose to 15.6% of portfolios. This strategic rebalancing signals a move towards potentially higher-yielding assets amidst increasing government borrowings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:58:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695514794342f77179ee76fb_1767184213069.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Car Price Shock Incoming: Major Automakers Set to Hike Prices in January Amidst Rising Costs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Car-Price-Shock-Incoming-Major-Automakers-Set-to-Hike-Prices-in-January-Amidst-Rising-Costs/695513444342f77179ee729f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Car-Price-Shock-Incoming-Major-Automakers-Set-to-Hike-Prices-in-January-Amidst-Rising-Costs/695513444342f77179ee729f</guid><description>Several leading car manufacturers, including Tata Motors, Hyundai, Honda, and luxury brands like Mercedes-Benz and BMW, are planning significant price increases effective January 2026. These hikes, ranging up to 3%, are driven by escalating input costs for raw materials and the continued depreciation of the Indian rupee against global currencies. This move comes as automakers aim to partially offset the demand boost from September's GST reduction, making new car purchases costlier for consumers in the new year.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:57:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695513444342f77179ee729e_1767183518669.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FMCG Secret: 2026 Outlook Reveals Massive Volume Surge Ahead! Are You Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-FMCG-Secret-2026-Outlook-Reveals-Massive-Volume-Surge-Ahead-Are-You-Ready/695513a44342f77179ee73eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-FMCG-Secret-2026-Outlook-Reveals-Massive-Volume-Surge-Ahead-Are-You-Ready/695513a44342f77179ee73eb</guid><description>India's FMCG companies anticipate volume-led growth in 2026, driven by stable commodity prices, lower inflation, and GST adjustments. Easing consumer sentiment, particularly in rural markets, is boosting demand. Despite challenges like a weakening rupee posing margin risks, new leadership and a focus on innovation are expected to fuel a promising year for the sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:57:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695513a44342f77179ee73ea_1767183744381.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Sector SHATTERS Records! Car &amp; Bike Sales Hit Unprecedented Highs – What It Means for Your Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Sector-SHATTERS-Records-Car-and-Bike-Sales-Hit-Unprecedented-Highs-What-It-Means-for-Your-Investments/6955130e4342f77179ee71e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Sector-SHATTERS-Records-Car-and-Bike-Sales-Hit-Unprecedented-Highs-What-It-Means-for-Your-Investments/6955130e4342f77179ee71e4</guid><description>Indian automakers are set for a record year as two-wheeler sales surpass 20 million and passenger vehicle sales exceed 4.3 million for the first time. This surge, boosted by recent GST cuts that lowered prices, reflects strong demand across segments, particularly for entry-level vehicles. The auto sector's Nifty Auto index significantly outperformed the Nifty 50. Companies like Mahindra and Mahindra have climbed to second place in passenger vehicles, while TVS Motor leads in EV two-wheeler sales. Analysts anticipate reduced discounts ahead as companies focus on margins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:57:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955130e4342f77179ee71e3_1767183808674.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Must-Know: Jan 1 Deadline For Mandatory Star Ratings On Your Appliances!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Must-Know-Jan-1-Deadline-For-Mandatory-Star-Ratings-On-Your-Appliances/6955121c4342f77179ee6f64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Must-Know-Jan-1-Deadline-For-Mandatory-Star-Ratings-On-Your-Appliances/6955121c4342f77179ee6f64</guid><description>The Indian government has made energy efficiency star-labelling mandatory for popular appliances like refrigerators, televisions, and LPG gas stoves starting January 1. This new regulation, issued by the Bureau of Energy Efficiency, also covers cooling towers, chillers, deep freezers, distribution transformers, and grid-connected solar inverters. Previously voluntary for some items, this move aims to promote energy conservation and informed consumer choices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:53:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955121c4342f77179ee6f63_1767182959362.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 10,000 Crore Pharma Bonanza: Ozempic Patent Expiry Set to Reshape India's Weight-Loss Market!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Rs-10000-Crore-Pharma-Bonanza-Ozempic-Patent-Expiry-Set-to-Reshape-Indias-Weight-Loss-Market/695510f94342f77179ee6c04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Rs-10000-Crore-Pharma-Bonanza-Ozempic-Patent-Expiry-Set-to-Reshape-Indias-Weight-Loss-Market/695510f94342f77179ee6c04</guid><description>India's pharmaceutical market is poised for a major shift as the patent for Semaglutide (Ozempic) expires in March 2026. This is expected to halve the cost of leading weight-loss drugs, potentially bringing them down from ₹8,000-₹10,000 per month to ₹4,000-₹6,000. Elara Securities projects a ₹10,000 crore opportunity, with Sun Pharma, Lupin, Torrent Pharma, and Intas Pharmaceuticals emerging as key players set to capitalize on increased volume demand.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:52:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695510f94342f77179ee6c03_1767182800109.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bill Ackman's Shocking 2026 Stock Pick: Could These 'Zombie' Giants Make You Rich?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bill-Ackmans-Shocking-2026-Stock-Pick-Could-These-Zombie-Giants-Make-You-Rich/695512204342f77179ee6fc5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bill-Ackmans-Shocking-2026-Stock-Pick-Could-These-Zombie-Giants-Make-You-Rich/695512204342f77179ee6fc5</guid><description>Billionaire investor Bill Ackman is publicly recommending Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac for 2026, calling them a "$10 billion lottery ticket". Despite being under government conservatorship since 2008, Ackman believes these undervalued mortgage giants, which back 70% of US home loans, are poised for a major revaluation, potentially through a relisting on the NYSE. He sees significant upside, with shares trading at low multiples of earnings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:52:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695512204342f77179ee6fc4_1767183318093.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cabinet Approves Massive ₹19,142 Crore Maharashtra Expressway Project: What It Means For You!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cabinet-Approves-Massive-19142-Crore-Maharashtra-Expressway-Project-What-It-Means-For-You/695510c14342f77179ee6b52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cabinet-Approves-Massive-19142-Crore-Maharashtra-Expressway-Project-What-It-Means-For-You/695510c14342f77179ee6b52</guid><description>The Union Cabinet has greenlit a new 374 km, six-lane greenfield expressway connecting Nashik, Solapur, and Akkalkot in Maharashtra. Approved under the BOT (Toll) model, the ₹19,142 crore project aims to drastically cut travel time by 17 hours between Nashik and Akkalkot, boost logistics, create millions of jobs, and enhance connectivity as part of the PM Gati Shakti plan.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:52:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695510c14342f77179ee6b51_1767182742424.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fino Bank's Bold Leap: From Payments to Universal Banking by 2035? RBI Nod Sparks Lending Dreams!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Banks-Bold-Leap-From-Payments-to-Universal-Banking-by-2035-RBI-Nod-Sparks-Lending-Dreams/69550f574342f77179ee66f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Banks-Bold-Leap-From-Payments-to-Universal-Banking-by-2035-RBI-Nod-Sparks-Lending-Dreams/69550f574342f77179ee66f7</guid><description>Fino Payments Bank has received in-principle approval from the Reserve Bank of India to transition into a Small Finance Bank, marking a significant step towards offering lending services. With a strong base of over 20 lakh merchants and 1.6 crore customers, the bank plans substantial technology investments and a hub-and-spoke branch model. Fino Bank aims for a universal bank license by around 2035, building on its merchant-first, tech-led strategy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:46:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69550f574342f77179ee66f6_1767182481843.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Skyrockets 164% in 2025! Gold, Stocks &amp; Crypto Recap: Who Won Your Portfolio?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Silver-Skyrockets-164percent-in-2025-Gold-Stocks-and-Crypto-Recap-Who-Won-Your-Portfolio/69550e6a4342f77179ee644f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Silver-Skyrockets-164percent-in-2025-Gold-Stocks-and-Crypto-Recap-Who-Won-Your-Portfolio/69550e6a4342f77179ee644f</guid><description>In 2025, silver was the top performer with a massive 164% surge, doubling investor money, followed by gold with 65% gains. Technology-heavy NASDAQ achieved 21% returns, outperforming Indian indices Nifty 50 (9.7%) and Sensex (8.3%). Bitcoin saw a decline, and fixed deposits offered modest gains. Precious metals and select equities emerged as key wealth creators for the year, highlighting the importance of diversified portfolios.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:31:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69550e6a4342f77179ee644e_1767182113490.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2025 'Hidden Bear Market' Over? Expert Predicts HUGE Stock Market Comeback in 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2025-Hidden-Bear-Market-Over-Expert-Predicts-HUGE-Stock-Market-Comeback-in-2026/69550e184342f77179ee6356</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2025-Hidden-Bear-Market-Over-Expert-Predicts-HUGE-Stock-Market-Comeback-in-2026/69550e184342f77179ee6356</guid><description>Dipan Mehta of Elixir Equities anticipates a brighter 2026 for the Indian stock market after a challenging 2025, which he terms a 'disguised bear market.' Despite Nifty's gains, over 70% of stocks declined. He sees selective opportunities emerging in autos, software services, pharma, and export-oriented sectors, advising cautious optimism and emphasizing stock selection over index chasing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:31:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69550e184342f77179ee6355_1767181948920.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Small Caps AREN'T Coming Back! Devina Mehra's Shocking 2026 Strategy: Clean Your Portfolio &amp; Buy THESE Sectors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Small-Caps-ARENT-Coming-Back-Devina-Mehras-Shocking-2026-Strategy-Clean-Your-Portfolio-and-Buy-THESE-Sectors/69550d6a4342f77179ee60f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Small-Caps-ARENT-Coming-Back-Devina-Mehras-Shocking-2026-Strategy-Clean-Your-Portfolio-and-Buy-THESE-Sectors/69550d6a4342f77179ee60f1</guid><description>Devina Mehra, founder of First Global, warns investors against FOMO and a guaranteed small-cap comeback. She advises staying invested but rigorously cleaning portfolios of underperforming assets. Mehra favors autos, pharma, FMCG, and cautious banking exposure, seeing IT as a potential turnaround. Gold should remain a minor allocation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:31:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69550d6a4342f77179ee60f0_1767181756762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Group's Bold Vision: N Chandrasekaran Unveils Masterplan for Record Success Driven by AI &amp; Manufacturing Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Groups-Bold-Vision-N-Chandrasekaran-Unveils-Masterplan-for-Record-Success-Driven-by-AI-and-Manufacturing-Boom/69550d754342f77179ee614e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Groups-Bold-Vision-N-Chandrasekaran-Unveils-Masterplan-for-Record-Success-Driven-by-AI-and-Manufacturing-Boom/69550d754342f77179ee614e</guid><description>Tata Group Chairman N Chandrasekaran is setting ambitious goals for the conglomerate, targeting its 'most successful years' by focusing on advanced manufacturing, artificial intelligence, and sustainability. He highlighted significant investments in new factories, including semiconductor and gigafactories, AI-first operations, and a 1 GW AI data center. Key subsidiaries like Tata Motors, Tata Steel, Trent, and Indian Hotels have achieved major milestones. Chandrasekaran emphasizes disciplined execution, teamwork, and bold risks to navigate global uncertainty and drive future growth towards 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:30:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69550d754342f77179ee614d_1767182308131.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Why Rs 1 Crore Salary Isn't Enough for a Rs 5 Crore Gurgaon Home: Expert Reveals Shocking Truth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Why-Rs-1-Crore-Salary-Isnt-Enough-for-a-Rs-5-Crore-Gurgaon-Home-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-Truth/69550d074342f77179ee5fbe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Why-Rs-1-Crore-Salary-Isnt-Enough-for-a-Rs-5-Crore-Gurgaon-Home-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-Truth/69550d074342f77179ee5fbe</guid><description>Even earning ₹1.2 crore annually, many Indian professionals struggle to afford luxury homes in cities like Gurgaon. Investment adviser Abhishek Kumar explains this isn't poor financial planning but a systemic issue. Factors include high taxes reducing net income to ₹70 lakh, soaring property prices where basic flats cost ₹5 crore, and competition from established wealth. Job uncertainty adds to the pressure, highlighting a growing gap between incomes and asset values.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:28:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69550d074342f77179ee5fbd_1767181759581.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto Shock: XRP &amp; Solana's Wild 2025 Ride Was TWICE Bitcoin's Volatility! 🎢</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Crypto-Shock-XRP-and-Solanas-Wild-2025-Ride-Was-TWICE-Bitcoins-Volatility/69550c4e4342f77179ee5d8a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Crypto-Shock-XRP-and-Solanas-Wild-2025-Ride-Was-TWICE-Bitcoins-Volatility/69550c4e4342f77179ee5d8a</guid><description>In 2025, XRP and Solana experienced significantly higher price swings than Bitcoin, showing crypto market immaturity. Solana's realized volatility hit 87% and XRP's 80%, dwarfing Bitcoin's 43%. Despite billions flowing into XRP and SOL ETFs, this 'bumpy' ride suggests a need for deeper liquidity to stabilize these altcoins and match Bitcoin's calmer trading, even as structural progress abounds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:28:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69550c4e4342f77179ee5d89_1767181592383.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BREAKING: Year-End Rally Ignites Indian Markets! Sensex Surges 546 Points, Nifty Soars Above 26,100 - What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/BREAKING-Year-End-Rally-Ignites-Indian-Markets-Sensex-Surges-546-Points-Nifty-Soars-Above-26100-Whats-Next/69550c004342f77179ee5c43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/BREAKING-Year-End-Rally-Ignites-Indian-Markets-Sensex-Surges-546-Points-Nifty-Soars-Above-26100-Whats-Next/69550c004342f77179ee5c43</guid><description>Indian equity markets closed 2025 with a strong rally, as the Sensex jumped 546 points to 85,220 and the Nifty climbed 190 points to surpass 26,100. The broad-based surge was led by metals, PSU banks, and oil &amp; gas sectors, despite a lag in IT and telecom. Both benchmarks ended 2025 with a 10% gain. Experts suggest a positive but cautious outlook, favoring banking, auto, and metal stocks for the upcoming trading sessions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:27:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69550c004342f77179ee5c42_1767181776546.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Flags Global Storms for India's Economy, But Forecasts Surprising Growth Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Flags-Global-Storms-for-Indias-Economy-But-Forecasts-Surprising-Growth-Surge/69550c2f4342f77179ee5cf7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Flags-Global-Storms-for-Indias-Economy-But-Forecasts-Surprising-Growth-Surge/69550c2f4342f77179ee5cf7</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Financial Stability Report warns that global market volatility and geopolitical tensions pose near-term risks to India's economy. These external uncertainties could impact the rupee, trade, corporate earnings, and foreign investment. However, the report also highlights resilient domestic demand and has revised India's GDP growth forecast for 2025-26 upwards to 7.3 percent, signaling a positive underlying economic outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:27:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69550c2f4342f77179ee5cf6_1767181968489.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Railway Sleeper Maker Vishal Nirmiti Files for IPO: Huge Funding Plans Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Railway-Sleeper-Maker-Vishal-Nirmiti-Files-for-IPO-Huge-Funding-Plans-Revealed/69550b564342f77179ee5a74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Railway-Sleeper-Maker-Vishal-Nirmiti-Files-for-IPO-Huge-Funding-Plans-Revealed/69550b564342f77179ee5a74</guid><description>Pune-based Vishal Nirmiti, a manufacturer of pre-stressed concrete sleepers for railways, has filed draft papers with SEBI for an Initial Public Offering (IPO). The company aims to raise ₹125 crore through a fresh issuance of shares, alongside an offer-for-sale of 15 lakh shares by promoter Vaman Prestressing Company. Funds will be used for working capital and loan repayment, with remaining for general corporate purposes. The company reported significant profit and revenue growth for the fiscal year ending March 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:27:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69550b564342f77179ee5a73_1767181378370.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Deficit Skyrockets: Government Spends Big on Infrastructure, Tax Inflows Lag!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Deficit-Skyrockets-Government-Spends-Big-on-Infrastructure-Tax-Inflows-Lag/69550b454342f77179ee5a26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Deficit-Skyrockets-Government-Spends-Big-on-Infrastructure-Tax-Inflows-Lag/69550b454342f77179ee5a26</guid><description>India's fiscal deficit reached 62.3% of its annual target by November FY26, a significant jump from 52.5% last year. This widening gap is driven by robust capital expenditure driving infrastructure growth, which has pushed industrial output to a 25-month high. However, net tax revenue collection is slower than anticipated, only reaching 49.1% of Budget Estimates. Non-tax revenue, boosted by dividends, performed strongly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:27:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69550b454342f77179ee5a25_1767181340281.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Denies Govt Dues Relief, Shares Plunge Amid Confusion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Denies-Govt-Dues-Relief-Shares-Plunge-Amid-Confusion/695509af4342f77179ee5675</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Denies-Govt-Dues-Relief-Shares-Plunge-Amid-Confusion/695509af4342f77179ee5675</guid><description>Vodafone Idea has clarified that it has not yet received any official communication from the government regarding the reported approval of a five-year moratorium on its Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) dues amounting to ₹87,695 crore. This clarification led to a sharp decline in the company's shares, which fell significantly during trading hours.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:24:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695509af4342f77179ee5674_1767180793857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Prices Slide: Geopolitical Fears Ease, Investors Turn Cautious - What It Means for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Slide-Geopolitical-Fears-Ease-Investors-Turn-Cautious-What-It-Means-for-Your-Investments/695507c84342f77179ee5219</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Slide-Geopolitical-Fears-Ease-Investors-Turn-Cautious-What-It-Means-for-Your-Investments/695507c84342f77179ee5219</guid><description>Gold prices saw a slight decline on Wednesday, with MCX gold futures dropping by Rs 1,140 after recent volatility. This follows a rally driven by geopolitical tensions. COMEX gold futures also traded marginally lower. Market sentiment remains cautious as investors monitor global developments, including peace talks, strikes, and naval drills, which had previously spurred safe-haven demand for gold and silver.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:16:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695507c84342f77179ee5218_1767180556105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2025 Workplace Revolution: New Rules Unveiled That Will Change YOUR Job Forever!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-Workplace-Revolution-New-Rules-Unveiled-That-Will-Change-YOUR-Job-Forever/695503ef4342f77179ee4a9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-Workplace-Revolution-New-Rules-Unveiled-That-Will-Change-YOUR-Job-Forever/695503ef4342f77179ee4a9c</guid><description>India ushered in significant workplace reforms in 2025 with the push to implement four new Labour Codes. These changes modernize hiring, wages, working hours, and industrial relations, aiming to simplify compliance. A major highlight is the legal recognition and expanded social security for gig and platform workers. Companies face evolving HR policies, balancing greater flexibility with stringent compliance, marking a pivotal transition year for the Indian workforce.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:58:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695503ef4342f77179ee4a9b_1767179328000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fashion Forward: Chique's ₹100 Crore Leap &amp; India's Digital Surge in 2025!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Fashion-Forward-Chiques-100-Crore-Leap-and-Indias-Digital-Surge-in-2025/695504814342f77179ee4bbf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Fashion-Forward-Chiques-100-Crore-Leap-and-Indias-Digital-Surge-in-2025/695504814342f77179ee4bbf</guid><description>In 2025, Indo-western brand Chique achieved ₹100 crore in annual recurring revenue by strengthening its digital strategy, operations, and brand visibility through collaborations with actor Malaika Arora and influencers. Meanwhile, IndiaMART reported increased digital adoption among MSMEs, with a growing demand for sustainable and health-focused products, signaling a pivotal year for B2B e-commerce.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:58:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695504814342f77179ee4bbe_1767179529593.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Richest Add Record $2.2 Trillion In 2025 As Markets Soar!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Richest-Add-Record-22-Trillion-In-2025-As-Markets-Soar/6954ffe74342f77179ee417d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Richest-Add-Record-22-Trillion-In-2025-As-Markets-Soar/6954ffe74342f77179ee417d</guid><description>The world's 500 wealthiest individuals saw their collective fortunes surge by a record $2.2 trillion in 2025, reaching a total of $11.9 trillion. This unprecedented growth was driven by booming global markets in equities, cryptocurrencies, and precious metals, amplified by artificial intelligence euphoria and Donald Trump's election victory. Oracle Chairman Larry Ellison notably overtook Elon Musk as the world's richest man for a period.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:41:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954ffe74342f77179ee417c_1767178400192.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Banks in Tight Spot: Credit Surges, Deposit Growth Stalls – What This Means for Your Money!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Banks-in-Tight-Spot-Credit-Surges-Deposit-Growth-Stalls-What-This-Means-for-Your-Money/6955001a4342f77179ee4208</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Banks-in-Tight-Spot-Credit-Surges-Deposit-Growth-Stalls-What-This-Means-for-Your-Money/6955001a4342f77179ee4208</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India data shows Indian bank credit grew by nearly 12% year-on-year by December 15, while deposit growth slowed to 9.35%. This widening gap highlights ongoing liquidity tightness in the banking system. Banks face challenges balancing deposit mobilization to fund credit expansion with pressure to lower deposit rates to protect profit margins, potentially pushing savers towards equity markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:28:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955001a4342f77179ee4207_1767178328131.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSE Stocks Dive Up to 29% in 2025: Experts Bullish on 2 Turnaround Stars for 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PSE-Stocks-Dive-Up-to-29percent-in-2025-Experts-Bullish-on-2-Turnaround-Stars-for-2026/6954fe0e4342f77179ee3b15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PSE-Stocks-Dive-Up-to-29percent-in-2025-Experts-Bullish-on-2-Turnaround-Stars-for-2026/6954fe0e4342f77179ee3b15</guid><description>While many public sector enterprise (PSE) stocks saw significant dips up to 29% in 2025, with RECL and Power Finance Corporation (PFC) leading the decline, market experts are now turning bullish on these two stocks for 2026. Analysts at HDFC Securities and Ventura Securities cite attractive current valuations and healthy dividend yields as key reasons to buy these stocks on dips, expecting a potential 15-20% upside.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:28:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954fe0e4342f77179ee3b14_1767177902719.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VIP Industries Promoters Prepare Major Stake Sale: Is This the Final Act?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VIP-Industries-Promoters-Prepare-Major-Stake-Sale-Is-This-the-Final-Act/6954fe284342f77179ee3b6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VIP-Industries-Promoters-Prepare-Major-Stake-Sale-Is-This-the-Final-Act/6954fe284342f77179ee3b6a</guid><description>VIP Industries promoters are reportedly planning to sell an additional 4% stake in the company via a block deal, marking the final phase of their divestment. Bankers have initiated the book-building process for this transaction, which is expected to conclude soon. Following this sale, promoters are anticipated to hold approximately 16% of the company's shares. This move follows an earlier stake transfer of 26% to Multiples PE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:27:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954fe284342f77179ee3b69_1767177921162.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Health Claims Skyrocket 11% to Rs 94,248 Crore in FY25! Are Insurers Ready for the Payout Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Health-Claims-Skyrocket-11percent-to-Rs-94248-Crore-in-FY25-Are-Insurers-Ready-for-the-Payout-Surge/6954fc104342f77179ee3694</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Health-Claims-Skyrocket-11percent-to-Rs-94248-Crore-in-FY25-Are-Insurers-Ready-for-the-Payout-Surge/6954fc104342f77179ee3694</guid><description>India's health insurance sector saw claim payouts jump 11% year-on-year to Rs 94,248 crore in FY25, covering 3.26 crore claims. Cashless settlements dominated, accounting for 66% of the total claim value, reflecting growing consumer preference for hassle-free processing. Group policies remained the largest contributors to premiums collected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:23:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954fc104342f77179ee3693_1767177335632.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EV Subsidy SHOCKER: Electric Three-Wheelers Lose Govt Support! What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/EV-Subsidy-SHOCKER-Electric-Three-Wheelers-Lose-Govt-Support-Whats-Next/6954fb864342f77179ee3546</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/EV-Subsidy-SHOCKER-Electric-Three-Wheelers-Lose-Govt-Support-Whats-Next/6954fb864342f77179ee3546</guid><description>The Indian government has ended subsidies for electric three-wheelers under the PM e-Drive scheme, achieving its target adoption rate of 32%. Support will continue for electric two-wheelers, where adoption is significantly lower at around 7.5%. The Centre is shifting focus to state governments to drive future EV adoption, especially in segments lagging behind, while the auto industry highlights the need for faster charging infrastructure development.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:22:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954fb864342f77179ee3545_1767177200205.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vande Bharat Sleeper Trial SUCCESS! 180 KMPH Shatters Speed Records in Final High-Speed Test! India's Rail Tech Leaps Forward!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vande-Bharat-Sleeper-Trial-SUCCESS-180-KMPH-Shatters-Speed-Records-in-Final-High-Speed-Test-Indias-Rail-Tech-Leaps-Forward/6954fb224342f77179ee339b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vande-Bharat-Sleeper-Trial-SUCCESS-180-KMPH-Shatters-Speed-Records-in-Final-High-Speed-Test-Indias-Rail-Tech-Leaps-Forward/6954fb224342f77179ee339b</guid><description>Indian Railways has successfully completed the final high-speed trial of its indigenously designed Vande Bharat sleeper train, achieving a maximum speed of 180 kmph. Conducted on the Kota-Nagda section under the Commissioner of Railway Safety's supervision, the trial proved the train's technological capabilities and ride stability. This milestone signifies a major achievement in self-reliant rail manufacturing and paves the way for its upcoming launch, bringing world-class travel experiences to long-distance passengers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:21:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954fb224342f77179ee339a_1767177108656.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks Soar! Top 3 Reasons Behind Today's Massive Market Rally Revealed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Stocks-Soar-Top-3-Reasons-Behind-Todays-Massive-Market-Rally-Revealed/6954fae44342f77179ee32e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Stocks-Soar-Top-3-Reasons-Behind-Todays-Massive-Market-Rally-Revealed/6954fae44342f77179ee32e8</guid><description>India's stock market, including Nifty and Sensex, surged on the last day of 2025, driven by a government safeguard duty on steel imports boosting domestic producers, optimism over upcoming Q3 corporate earnings, and expectations of robust December auto sales. Reliance Industries led gains, while IT stocks lagged slightly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:18:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954fae44342f77179ee32e7_1767177158331.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Government Throws Lifeline: Vodafone Idea's Massive Rs 87,695 Crore Dues Frozen in Major Relief Package!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Government-Throws-Lifeline-Vodafone-Ideas-Massive-Rs-87695-Crore-Dues-Frozen-in-Major-Relief-Package/6954f7874342f77179ee2a0d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Government-Throws-Lifeline-Vodafone-Ideas-Massive-Rs-87695-Crore-Dues-Frozen-in-Major-Relief-Package/6954f7874342f77179ee2a0d</guid><description>The Union Cabinet has approved a significant relief package for Vodafone Idea, freezing its Rs 87,695 crore Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) dues. Repayment has been deferred from fiscal year 2032 to 2041. The Department of Telecommunications will reassess final liabilities, aiming to safeguard government interests, maintain telecom sector competition, and protect the interests of its 20 crore subscribers. Dues for FY18-19 remain unchanged and payable between FY26-FY31.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:56:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954f7874342f77179ee2a0c_1767176190180.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>