<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:44:38 +0000</pubDate><item><title>HUL's India Pivot: Premium Push Meets Growth Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HULs-India-Pivot-Premium-Push-Meets-Growth-Headwinds/6997b4ad057e346edab37df7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HULs-India-Pivot-Premium-Push-Meets-Growth-Headwinds/6997b4ad057e346edab37df7</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever (HUL) is reorienting its strategy to elevate the US and India's combined revenue contribution to 45%, from the current 33%. This involves a strong emphasis on premiumizing its Indian portfolio to 50% of offerings and expanding digital commerce. The company has also signaled intent for strategic acquisitions in India and is under new leadership with Priya Nair at the helm. However, despite these initiatives, analysts highlight concerns over decelerating earnings growth and increasing market competition, leading to target price revisions and a cautious outlook for the consumer giant.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:11:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997b4ad057e346edab37df6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Atul Auto's EV Pivot: Rural Bet Faces Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Atul-Autos-EV-Pivot-Rural-Bet-Faces-Fierce-Competition/6997b3c1057e346edab37cfb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Atul-Autos-EV-Pivot-Rural-Bet-Faces-Fierce-Competition/6997b3c1057e346edab37cfb</guid><description>Atul Auto has merged its electric vehicle (EV) business into the parent company, aiming for sales synergy and balance sheet clarity. While investor Vijay Kedia's long-term conviction highlights the company's rural focus and engineering heritage, the transition is set against a backdrop of escalating competition from Bajaj Auto and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, and significant volatility in battery material costs. The company's target of 30% volume growth for FY27 will test its ability to navigate these demanding market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:07:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997b3c1057e346edab37cfa_1771549868184.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Trio: Divergent Paths in a Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Trio-Divergent-Paths-in-a-Boom/6997b3c0057e346edab37ce4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Trio-Divergent-Paths-in-a-Boom/6997b3c0057e346edab37ce4</guid><description>As India champions its sovereign AI ecosystem with a ₹10,300 crore mission, three companies—Netweb Technologies, Aurionpro Solutions, and E2E Networks—are carving distinct niches. Netweb drives AI hardware innovation, Aurionpro redefines enterprise software, and E2E Networks builds critical cloud infrastructure. Their vastly different financial metrics and strategic plays reveal a spectrum of opportunities and risks in India's AI gold rush.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:07:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997b3c0057e346edab37ce3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Electronics Boom: Profitability Under Pressure?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Electronics-Boom-Profitability-Under-Pressure/6997b3bc057e346edab37ccd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Electronics-Boom-Profitability-Under-Pressure/6997b3bc057e346edab37ccd</guid><description>India's electronics manufacturing sector is experiencing robust growth, fueled by Production Linked Incentive (PLI) schemes and global supply chain realignments. Companies like Dixon Technologies, Syrma SGS, Kaynes Technology, and Netweb Technologies are rapidly expanding production and investing heavily in new capacities. However, this expansion comes with significant risks. Persistent margin pressures, escalating input costs, and increasingly demanding valuations suggest that the sector's rapid growth may not translate directly into sustainable profitability, posing a critical challenge for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:07:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997b3bc057e346edab37ccc_1771549883134.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Accenture Bets AI on Growth, Redefining Markets for SMEs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Accenture-Bets-AI-on-Growth-Redefining-Markets-for-SMEs/6997b258057e346edab37bc6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Accenture-Bets-AI-on-Growth-Redefining-Markets-for-SMEs/6997b258057e346edab37bc6</guid><description>Accenture's strategic pivot emphasizes AI's role in driving enterprise growth, not just efficiency. CEO Julie Sweet highlighted Large Language Models (LLMs) as new marketplaces enabling Small and Medium-sized Enterprises (SMEs) global access. The company faces significant adoption hurdles and evolving market dynamics within the IT services sector, with analysts offering a mixed but generally positive outlook on its AI-centric transformation. Accenture's fiscal year 2025 performance showed strong revenue growth driven by substantial AI investments, though market sentiment has seen recent volatility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:01:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997b258057e346edab37bc5_1771549392969.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Stocks Dip as Financial Fears, Geopolitics Spark Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/US-Stocks-Dip-as-Financial-Fears-Geopolitics-Spark-Caution/6997b077057e346edab37abe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/US-Stocks-Dip-as-Financial-Fears-Geopolitics-Spark-Caution/6997b077057e346edab37abe</guid><description>US equities declined on Thursday, pushing the S&amp;P 500 near flat year-to-date. Financials led losses after Blue Owl Capital tightened liquidity, fueling private credit jitters. Tech stocks remained under pressure from AI disruption fears, while geopolitical tensions and a cautious retail outlook from Walmart added to investor unease. This market pullback confirms a shift in leadership, as investors recalibrate portfolios amid rising systemic risks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997b077057e346edab37abd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Ethics Mandate: Indian Banks Face Sales Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Ethics-Mandate-Indian-Banks-Face-Sales-Overhaul/6997ae1c057e346edab379b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Ethics-Mandate-Indian-Banks-Face-Sales-Overhaul/6997ae1c057e346edab379b9</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is elevating banking ethics from a 'soft theme' to a core operational imperative, introducing stringent draft guidelines on product advertising and sales. This regulatory shift compels financial institutions to embed transparency and 'inward honesty' across all functions, from frontline staff interactions to digital lending processes. The move targets historical mis-selling issues and aggressive sales tactics, signaling increased compliance burdens and a potential recalibration of revenue models heavily reliant on product commissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:43:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997ae1c057e346edab379b8_1771548328798.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Reboots AI Race: Local Intel Trumps Global Scale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Reboots-AI-Race-Local-Intel-Trumps-Global-Scale/6997adad057e346edab37912</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Reboots-AI-Race-Local-Intel-Trumps-Global-Scale/6997adad057e346edab37912</guid><description>India's AI sector is undergoing a strategic transformation, moving beyond sheer parameter counts to prioritize deep linguistic and cultural relevance. Companies like Sarvam AI and BharatGen are launching sophisticated models tailored for India's diverse populace, aiming for a "sovereign AI" capability. This approach, bolstered by government initiatives like the IndiaAI Mission and significant funding, positions India to lead not just in AI development, but in creating AI that truly understands and serves its unique 1.4 billion population, potentially offering a competitive edge over globally focused giants.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:41:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997adad057e346edab37911.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Qualcomm Taps India for Global Auto Modules: Resilience Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Taps-India-for-Global-Auto-Modules-Resilience-Play/6997ad2c057e346edab378b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Taps-India-for-Global-Auto-Modules-Resilience-Play/6997ad2c057e346edab378b9</guid><description>Qualcomm is expanding its manufacturing footprint in India by partnering to produce and source automotive modules, aiming to bolster global supply chain resilience and leverage the nation's R&amp;D capabilities. This strategic move diversifies production away from traditional East Asian hubs, aligning with India's growing semiconductor ecosystem and government incentives. While the company faces headwinds from memory chip shortages impacting its core smartphone business, the India initiative signals a long-term commitment to growth in automotive and AI sectors. Qualcomm's valuation, with a P/E ratio of approximately 29x, positions it favorably against semiconductor industry averages, though execution risks and competitive pressures remain key considerations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:39:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997ad2c057e346edab378b8_1771548144468.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys Chief: Use Cases, Not Tech Race, Key for India's AI Lead</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Chief-Use-Cases-Not-Tech-Race-Key-for-Indias-AI-Lead/6997a81b057e346edab3773f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Chief-Use-Cases-Not-Tech-Race-Key-for-Indias-AI-Lead/6997a81b057e346edab3773f</guid><description>Infosys Chairman Nandan Nilekani has cautioned that uncontrolled AI proliferation could alienate white-collar workers, potentially triggering an "AI train wreck." He advocates for India to seize leadership in developing beneficial AI use cases, emphasizing responsible diffusion and societal integration over a purely technological race. This strategic pivot is critical for the Indian IT sector amidst intensifying AI disruption and macroeconomic headwinds impacting valuations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:17:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997a81b057e346edab3773e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>