<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:38:20 +0000</pubDate><item><title>P&amp;G Health Revenue Surges 20.7%, But Profit Drops 14.6% On Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/PandG-Health-Revenue-Surges-207percent-But-Profit-Drops-146percent-On-Costs/6985b42ae769d12df1d604cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/PandG-Health-Revenue-Surges-207percent-But-Profit-Drops-146percent-On-Costs/6985b42ae769d12df1d604cd</guid><description>Procter &amp; Gamble Health reported a robust 20.7% YoY revenue growth in Q3 FY26, reaching ₹37,386 lakhs. However, net profit saw a significant 14.6% YoY decline to ₹7,759 lakhs, primarily driven by a 40.3% surge in operating expenses that compressed margins. Despite the quarterly profit dip, the company declared a substantial interim dividend of ₹160 per share, including a special ₹50 payout.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ITC Stock Jumps Amid Results, But Tax Hikes Loom Large</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-Jumps-Amid-Results-But-Tax-Hikes-Loom-Large/6985b3d0e769d12df1d6032c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-Jumps-Amid-Results-But-Tax-Hikes-Loom-Large/6985b3d0e769d12df1d6032c</guid><description>ITC shares climbed Friday following a 7.1% revenue increase in Q3 FY26, fueled by FMCG-Others and Cigarettes segments. The company recommended a ₹6.50 dividend. However, this positive momentum faces significant headwinds from imminent excise duty and GST hikes on tobacco products, effective February 1, 2026. These tax changes are expected to increase the overall tax incidence on cigarettes to 40-50%, potentially driving price hikes, impacting volumes, and encouraging illicit trade. While ITC's diversification efforts provide some buffer, the core cigarette business faces considerable regulatory pressure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>P&amp;G Health Revenue Surges 20.7%, But Q3 Profit Dives 14.6% On Soaring Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/PandG-Health-Revenue-Surges-207percent-But-Q3-Profit-Dives-146percent-On-Soaring-Costs/6985b3b5e769d12df1d6025a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/PandG-Health-Revenue-Surges-207percent-But-Q3-Profit-Dives-146percent-On-Soaring-Costs/6985b3b5e769d12df1d6025a</guid><description>Procter &amp; Gamble Health Limited posted a 20.7% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹37,386 lakhs in Q3 FY26. However, profitability came under pressure as total expenses surged 40.3%, driven by higher material, employee, and other costs. Consequently, net profit declined 14.6% YoY to ₹7,759 lakhs, with EPS falling from ₹54.76 to ₹46.74. For the nine months, revenue grew 14.4% and net profit rose 22.3%, aided by the absence of an exceptional item. The board declared an interim dividend of ₹160 per share.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Equips REITs With Bank Loans: Asset Monetization</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Equips-REITs-With-Bank-Loans-Asset-Monetization/6985b34fe769d12df1d600b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Equips-REITs-With-Bank-Loans-Asset-Monetization/6985b34fe769d12df1d600b7</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has enabled direct bank lending to Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs) at the trust level, aligning them with Infrastructure Investment Trusts (InvITs). This policy shift, announced by Governor Sanjay Malhotra, aims to unlock significant value from underutilized government assets by providing a more accessible financing channel. The move is expected to redefine real estate finance, potentially lowering borrowing costs for REITs and spurring increased investment across commercial properties, rental housing, and other real estate assets, thereby accelerating development and economic activity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HeidelbergCement India Surges Profit 200%, Becomes Debt-Free</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HeidelbergCement-India-Surges-Profit-200percent-Becomes-Debt-Free/6985b33ae769d12df1d5fff5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HeidelbergCement-India-Surges-Profit-200percent-Becomes-Debt-Free/6985b33ae769d12df1d5fff5</guid><description>HeidelbergCement India reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 200.6% YoY to ₹156 million. Revenue grew 5.8% to ₹5,741.7 million, driven by 7.4% volume growth. EBITDA surged 59.1% to ₹529 million, expanding margins by 309 bps. Notably, the company achieved debt-free status, repaying its final loan tranche and maintaining a healthy cash balance of ₹4,032 million. An exceptional item of ₹45.6 million was recognized for new Labour Codes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gateway Distriparks Posts Mixed Q3: Standalone Profit Surges, Consolidated PAT Plunges 85%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Gateway-Distriparks-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Standalone-Profit-Surges-Consolidated-PAT-Plunges-85percent/6985b302e769d12df1d5feb7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Gateway-Distriparks-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Standalone-Profit-Surges-Consolidated-PAT-Plunges-85percent/6985b302e769d12df1d5feb7</guid><description>Gateway Distriparks reported a robust 25.26% YoY jump in standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹7,116.63 lakhs. However, consolidated PAT saw a sharp 85.26% decline to ₹6,716.59 lakhs, largely due to a significant exceptional gain in the prior year from Snowman Logistics valuation. The company achieved a net debt-free status and declared dividends but faces substantial legal and tax disputes, casting a shadow over its outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI's ₹25,000 fraud cover boosts digital payment trust</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-25000-fraud-cover-boosts-digital-payment-trust/6985b2e5e769d12df1d5fd35</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-25000-fraud-cover-boosts-digital-payment-trust/6985b2e5e769d12df1d5fd35</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has unveiled a consumer protection framework, promising compensation up to ₹25,000 for small-value digital fraud losses. This initiative, which shares liability between customers, banks, and the central bank, aims to bolster confidence in India's digital payment ecosystem. The RBI will also release draft guidelines on mis-selling, loan recovery, and unauthorized transaction liability, alongside a discussion paper on enhancing digital payment security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicswallah Slumps Despite Earnings Beat: Valuation Woes Dominate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Physicswallah-Slumps-Despite-Earnings-Beat-Valuation-Woes-Dominate/6985b2cae769d12df1d5fcc4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Physicswallah-Slumps-Despite-Earnings-Beat-Valuation-Woes-Dominate/6985b2cae769d12df1d5fcc4</guid><description>Physicswallah's stock tumbled following its fiscal third-quarter earnings report for the period ending December 2025. Despite a 33% year-over-year rise in net profit to ₹102.3 crore and a 34% revenue increase to ₹1,082.4 crore, investor sentiment soured. The sell-off drove shares to an intraday low of ₹116.61 on the NSE, marking a significant deviation from its listing day high and signaling market dissatisfaction with its current valuation trajectory amid a challenging edtech environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Clarifies US Treasury Holdings Amidst Reserve Diversification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Clarifies-US-Treasury-Holdings-Amidst-Reserve-Diversification/6985b28ce769d12df1d5fb5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Clarifies-US-Treasury-Holdings-Amidst-Reserve-Diversification/6985b28ce769d12df1d5fb5b</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) clarified it is not selling its US Treasury holdings, emphasizing active management of forex reserves. Holdings have declined to a five-year low, with diversification into gold and other assets, while reserves hit a record $723.8 billion. The RBI has intervened to support the rupee, which has seen recent depreciation. A new US-India trade deal has bolstered sentiment, reducing tariffs to 18% and positively impacting the currency.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BEML Losses Mount as Expenses Surge Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BEML-Losses-Mount-as-Expenses-Surge-Despite-Revenue-Growth/6985b275e769d12df1d5fa79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BEML-Losses-Mount-as-Expenses-Surge-Despite-Revenue-Growth/6985b275e769d12df1d5fa79</guid><description>BEML Ltd. reported a net loss of ₹22.4 crore for the December quarter, a sharp reversal from last year's profit, as operating profit was decimated by a 94% decline to ₹4 crore. Despite a 23.7% revenue increase to ₹1,083 crore, 'other' expenses, materials, and employee costs surged, eroding margins to a mere 0.3%. The stock plunged 8% to ₹1,607.4, extending its 12-month negative returns and signaling investor concerns over cost management.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Branch Rule Easing Lifts Gold Lenders</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Branch-Rule-Easing-Lifts-Gold-Lenders/6985b24be769d12df1d5f974</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Branch-Rule-Easing-Lifts-Gold-Lenders/6985b24be769d12df1d5f974</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's proposal to remove prior branch approval for large gold Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs) with over 1,000 branches is expected to streamline operations and boost investor sentiment. Companies like Muthoot Finance, Manappuram Finance, and IIFL Finance, already possessing extensive branch networks, are poised to benefit from this procedural relief. The RBI cited the established prudential framework as justification, with draft instructions to be issued for public comment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HeidelbergCement India Soars 200% Profit, Achieves Debt-Free Status</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HeidelbergCement-India-Soars-200percent-Profit-Achieves-Debt-Free-Status/6985b1d2e769d12df1d5f815</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HeidelbergCement-India-Soars-200percent-Profit-Achieves-Debt-Free-Status/6985b1d2e769d12df1d5f815</guid><description>HeidelbergCement India reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with Net Profit soaring 200.6% year-on-year to ₹156 million. Driven by a 7.4% rise in sales volumes and improved EBITDA margins (9.2% vs 6.1%), the company also achieved a significant milestone by becoming debt-free after repaying its final loan tranche. Revenue grew 5.8% to ₹5,742 million, with EBITDA up 59.1% YoY. For the nine months, PAT rose 57.7% to ₹888 million.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>P&amp;G Health Q3 Profit Falls 15% Despite 21% Revenue Jump; ₹160 Dividend Declared</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PandG-Health-Q3-Profit-Falls-15percent-Despite-21percent-Revenue-Jump-160-Dividend-Declared/6985b19de769d12df1d5f682</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PandG-Health-Q3-Profit-Falls-15percent-Despite-21percent-Revenue-Jump-160-Dividend-Declared/6985b19de769d12df1d5f682</guid><description>Procter &amp; Gamble Health Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue climbing 20.7% YoY to ₹373.86 Cr. However, net profit declined 14.6% YoY to ₹77.59 Cr, with EPS falling to ₹46.74. For the nine months ended Dec 31, 2025, revenue grew 14.4% to ₹1037.52 Cr, and net profit surged 22.3% to ₹232.31 Cr, aided by a prior year's exceptional charge. The board declared an interim dividend of ₹160 per share, including a special ₹50 payout.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dormant Firm's Stock Soars 1900% as New Promoters Launch ₹10 Open Offer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dormant-Firms-Stock-Soars-1900percent-as-New-Promoters-Launch-10-Open-Offer/6985b185e769d12df1d5f5cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dormant-Firms-Stock-Soars-1900percent-as-New-Promoters-Launch-10-Open-Offer/6985b185e769d12df1d5f5cc</guid><description>Navigant Corporate Advisors has filed a Letter of Offer for Western Ministil Limited's open offer, orchestrated by Mr. Kalpesh Naginbhai Patel and Mrs. Vandana Patel. The acquirers propose to buy up to 26% (33.80 lakh shares) at ₹10 per share, a stark contrast to the stock's current ₹0.50 market price. This mandatory offer follows a preferential allotment and signifies a change of control, with the acquirers aiming to revive the dormant, loss-making entity. The offer period runs from Feb 18 to Mar 05, 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Star Cement Declares 100% Dividend, Reclassifies Promoters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Star-Cement-Declares-100percent-Dividend-Reclassifies-Promoters/6985b15fe769d12df1d5f4b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Star-Cement-Declares-100percent-Dividend-Reclassifies-Promoters/6985b15fe769d12df1d5f4b5</guid><description>Star Cement Limited's board approved un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company declared a 100% interim dividend (Re. 1 per share) and will re-classify 29 members of the Chamaria Group from promoter to public category, subject to exchange approval. An exceptional item of ₹5.52 crore was recognized due to changes in labor regulations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:16:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985b15fe769d12df1d5f4b4_1770370655576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus' SCD Drug Gets USFDA Orphan Status Amidst Stock Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-SCD-Drug-Gets-USFDA-Orphan-Status-Amidst-Stock-Dip/6985b052e769d12df1d5f204</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-SCD-Drug-Gets-USFDA-Orphan-Status-Amidst-Stock-Dip/6985b052e769d12df1d5f204</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences has secured Orphan Drug Designation from the USFDA for Desidustat, an oral medication targeting sickle cell disease (SCD). This regulatory milestone unlocks significant incentives, including potential seven-year market exclusivity and tax credits, to address a critical unmet medical need. However, despite the positive designation, Zydus shares declined, indicating a cautious investor outlook amidst a competitive therapeutic landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:11:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985b052e769d12df1d5f203_1770370542341.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>M&amp;M's Rs 15K Cr Plant: Stock's Quiet Response Puzzles Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandMs-Rs-15K-Cr-Plant-Stocks-Quiet-Response-Puzzles-Investors/6985b02be769d12df1d5f11f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandMs-Rs-15K-Cr-Plant-Stocks-Quiet-Response-Puzzles-Investors/6985b02be769d12df1d5f11f</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra announced a ₹15,000 crore, decade-long investment for its largest integrated auto and tractor facility in Nagpur, Maharashtra, targeting 2028 production. This expansive project includes 1,500 acres for manufacturing and a 150-acre supplier park, aiming for 5 lakh vehicles and 1 lakh tractors annually across ICE and EV platforms. Despite bolstering future capacity, the stock's flat performance suggests investor focus on the long gestation period and capital outlay's immediate financial impact in a competitive market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985b02be769d12df1d5f11e_1770370411372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BLS International Surges on Strong Q3 Consolidated Growth, Declares 200% Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BLS-International-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Consolidated-Growth-Declares-200percent-Dividend/6985b008e769d12df1d5f00f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BLS-International-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Consolidated-Growth-Declares-200percent-Dividend/6985b008e769d12df1d5f00f</guid><description>BLS International Services Limited reported a robust third quarter for FY26, with consolidated revenue soaring 43.6% year-on-year to ₹736.46 Cr. Net profit attributable to owners grew 33.1% YoY to ₹170.22 Cr. The company also declared a first interim dividend of 200% (₹2 per share). However, standalone net profit saw a 4.6% decline YoY to ₹25.29 Cr, attributed to tax adjustments. The board also noted an emphasis of matter regarding a subsidiary's going concern status.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:10:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985b008e769d12df1d5f00e_1770370238350.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titan Completes Damas Acquisition, Eyes GCC Jewellery Market Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Completes-Damas-Acquisition-Eyes-GCC-Jewellery-Market-Dominance/6985afabe769d12df1d5ee58</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Completes-Damas-Acquisition-Eyes-GCC-Jewellery-Market-Dominance/6985afabe769d12df1d5ee58</guid><description>Titan Company Limited has successfully completed the acquisition of a 67% stake in Damas Jewellery, a prominent business operating across GCC countries. The transaction was facilitated through its UAE-based subsidiary, Titan Holdings International FZCO, with Signature Jewellery Holding Ltd. now serving as the holding company. This strategic move partners Titan with MC International Limited, a subsidiary of Qatar-based Mannai Corporation QPSC, which retains a 33% stake, bolstering Titan's presence in the lucrative Middle Eastern jewellery market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:08:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985afabe769d12df1d5ee57_1770370109822.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-EU FTA: Export Gains vs. CBAM Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Export-Gains-vs-CBAM-Challenges/6985af7ce769d12df1d5ed86</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Export-Gains-vs-CBAM-Challenges/6985af7ce769d12df1d5ed86</guid><description>India finalized a Free Trade Agreement with the EU in January 2026, establishing an export-first manufacturing strategy. The pact eliminates tariffs on over 90% of goods, granting India 97% preferential access to EU markets by value. Key sectors like automotive components, chemicals, pharmaceuticals, and textiles are positioned for significant export growth, correcting historical disadvantages. However, steel exports confront challenges from the EU's Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism, highlighting the need for strategic navigation beyond tariff reductions as bilateral trade aims to scale beyond $137 billion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:08:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985af7ce769d12df1d5ed85_1770370041240.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TPI India Revenue Surges 71% YoY, But Auditor Flags 'Eroded Net Worth'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TPI-India-Revenue-Surges-71percent-YoY-But-Auditor-Flags-Eroded-Net-Worth/6985af04e769d12df1d5eba4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TPI-India-Revenue-Surges-71percent-YoY-But-Auditor-Flags-Eroded-Net-Worth/6985af04e769d12df1d5eba4</guid><description>TPI India Limited reported a strong 71.16% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹892.60 Lakhs in Q3 FY26. However, this positive top-line performance is overshadowed by a critical statement from auditors, Jain Jagawat Kamdar &amp; Co., indicating that the company's net worth has been 'completely eroded.' This raises significant concerns about the company's ability to continue as a going concern, despite the auditors finding no material misstatements in the reviewed financial statements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:06:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985af04e769d12df1d5eba3_1770369870235.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Magadh Sugar Q3 Soars, But 9-Month Profit Plunges on Labour Code Impact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Magadh-Sugar-Q3-Soars-But-9-Month-Profit-Plunges-on-Labour-Code-Impact/6985ae96e769d12df1d5e9e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Magadh-Sugar-Q3-Soars-But-9-Month-Profit-Plunges-on-Labour-Code-Impact/6985ae96e769d12df1d5e9e7</guid><description>Magadh Sugar &amp; Energy posted a strong third quarter for FY26, with revenue up 4.43% YoY to ₹29,641.99 lakh and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 18.61% YoY to ₹2,508.55 lakh. However, its nine-month performance saw a 1.37% revenue dip and a significant 60.59% PAT decline to ₹1,495.60 lakh. This slump was primarily due to an exceptional item of ₹156.35 lakh related to new government Labour Codes, which the company is monitoring.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:04:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985ae96e769d12df1d5e9e6_1770369666112.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCX Margin Hikes Amplify Precious Metal Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Margin-Hikes-Amplify-Precious-Metal-Plunge/6985ad9fe769d12df1d5e770</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Margin-Hikes-Amplify-Precious-Metal-Plunge/6985ad9fe769d12df1d5e770</guid><description>Precious metals on India's Multi Commodity Exchange (MCX) suffered steep losses Friday, marking a second consecutive session of declines. This sharp fall was driven by a potent combination of weak global sentiment, a stronger U.S. dollar, and, critically, a series of aggressive margin hikes by the MCX. These exchange-driven credit tightening measures amplified selling pressure, forcing leveraged traders to liquidate positions and exacerbating the price drop for both gold and silver futures. Market participants are navigating heightened volatility as external economic headwinds converge with internal exchange risk management actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TPI India Slumps: Net Worth Eroded Amidst Widening Quarterly Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TPI-India-Slumps-Net-Worth-Eroded-Amidst-Widening-Quarterly-Losses/6985ac30e769d12df1d5e491</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TPI-India-Slumps-Net-Worth-Eroded-Amidst-Widening-Quarterly-Losses/6985ac30e769d12df1d5e491</guid><description>TPI India Limited posted a net loss of ₹1462.20 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, a YoY deterioration, despite a 9.05% revenue increase. The company's net worth has been completely eroded, a critical concern highlighted by auditors. For the nine months, revenue rose 9.33% but swung to a net loss of ₹1.09 Lakhs from a profit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:54:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985ac30e769d12df1d5e490_1770369478379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paisalo Digital's PAT Growth Slows, 9M EPS Flat Despite Revenue Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digitals-PAT-Growth-Slows-9M-EPS-Flat-Despite-Revenue-Rise/6985abdde769d12df1d5e2e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digitals-PAT-Growth-Slows-9M-EPS-Flat-Despite-Revenue-Rise/6985abdde769d12df1d5e2e2</guid><description>Paisalo Digital reported its Q3 FY26 results, with revenue from operations climbing 11.14% year-on-year to ₹23,987.47 Lakhs. While Profit Before Tax (PBT) surged 17.07%, Profit After Tax (PAT) saw a more modest 7.43% increase. For the nine-month period, revenue grew 3.30%, but PAT remained nearly flat, resulting in an unchanged basic EPS of ₹1.70. The company also raised ₹75 Crores via NCDs and CPs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:52:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985abdde769d12df1d5e2e1_1770369317645.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sapphire Foods posts net loss, margins squeezed despite revenue growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sapphire-Foods-posts-net-loss-margins-squeezed-despite-revenue-growth/6985abcbe769d12df1d5e215</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sapphire-Foods-posts-net-loss-margins-squeezed-despite-revenue-growth/6985abcbe769d12df1d5e215</guid><description>Sapphire Foods India Limited reported a challenging third quarter for FY26, posting a net loss of ₹ 48.08 Mn against a profit last year, despite a 7% YoY revenue growth to ₹ 8,112 Mn. Consolidated EBITDA declined 3% YoY, with margins contracting by 170 bps. While KFC India showed robust growth and margin improvement, Pizza Hut India faced an 11% revenue decline and negative EBITDA margins. Exceptional items also impacted profitability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:52:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985abcbe769d12df1d5e214_1770369149368.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TACL Bags ₹1,000 Cr Orders, Eyes Export and EV Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TACL-Bags-1000-Cr-Orders-Eyes-Export-and-EV-Growth/6985abb8e769d12df1d5e152</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TACL-Bags-1000-Cr-Orders-Eyes-Export-and-EV-Growth/6985abb8e769d12df1d5e152</guid><description>Talbros Automotive Components (TACL) has secured over ₹1,000 crore in multi-year orders, slated for execution from FY27 to FY31. A significant ₹700 crore stems from export markets, including a ₹500 crore forging order from a new European supplier. The company is also allocating ₹100 crore to electric vehicle (EV) components for luxury manufacturers via its JV. These wins enhance revenue visibility and bolster TACL's competitive standing in global automotive supply chains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:52:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985abb8e769d12df1d5e151_1770369035324.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India: Listed Firms' Tax Dominance Widens Amid Capital Moat</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Listed-Firms-Tax-Dominance-Widens-Amid-Capital-Moat/6985ab61e769d12df1d5dfaf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Listed-Firms-Tax-Dominance-Widens-Amid-Capital-Moat/6985ab61e769d12df1d5dfaf</guid><description>Listed Indian companies now contribute a larger share to corporate tax revenues than their unlisted counterparts, a trend amplified by superior access to capital. This divergence, exacerbated by the pandemic, allows listed entities to invest more in technology and operational efficiency, building a significant competitive moat and driving higher tax contributions. Unlisted firms face challenges like limited liquidity and valuation complexities, widening the gap.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:50:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985ab61e769d12df1d5dfae_1770368883852.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kakatiya Cement Posts Sharp Revenue Fall, Deepening Net Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kakatiya-Cement-Posts-Sharp-Revenue-Fall-Deepening-Net-Losses/6985ab48e769d12df1d5def3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kakatiya-Cement-Posts-Sharp-Revenue-Fall-Deepening-Net-Losses/6985ab48e769d12df1d5def3</guid><description>Kakatiya Cement Sugar &amp; Industries Limited reported dismal Q3 FY26 results, with revenue from operations plunging 48.5% sequentially to ₹1,306.98 lakhs and down 24.5% year-on-year. The company posted a net loss of ₹491.20 lakhs, worsening from the previous quarter. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, net losses widened significantly to ₹1,962.14 lakhs. Earnings per share also declined sharply.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:50:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985ab48e769d12df1d5def2_1770368746660.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Greaves Cotton Earnings Beat: Margin Gains Eyed, Valuation Questions Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Greaves-Cotton-Earnings-Beat-Margin-Gains-Eyed-Valuation-Questions-Linger/6985aaf3e769d12df1d5dd87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Greaves-Cotton-Earnings-Beat-Margin-Gains-Eyed-Valuation-Questions-Linger/6985aaf3e769d12df1d5dd87</guid><description>Greaves Cotton reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with net profit climbing 22.6% to ₹25.5 crore on a 16.6% revenue increase to ₹875.5 crore. A substantial 56.3% surge in EBITDA to ₹61.8 crore underpinned a significant margin expansion to 7%, up from 5.3% year-on-year. This operational efficiency drove a modest 1.64% stock gain post-announcement. While positive, the market is assessing the sustainability of these gains against persistent concerns regarding profitability metrics and valuation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:48:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985aaf3e769d12df1d5dd86_1770368569343.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Secures Orphan Drug Status for Sickle Cell Therapy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Secures-Orphan-Drug-Status-for-Sickle-Cell-Therapy/6985aacde769d12df1d5dc9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Secures-Orphan-Drug-Status-for-Sickle-Cell-Therapy/6985aacde769d12df1d5dc9e</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences announced receiving Orphan Drug Designation (ODD) from the USFDA for Desidustat, targeting sickle cell disease (SCD). This designation offers significant incentives including a potential seven-year marketing exclusivity, crucial for a rare disease therapy. The news emerges as Zydus explores acquiring Ardelyx and follows a year of stock decline. Desidustat's Phase II study is complete, adding to Zydus's strategic pivot towards niche therapeutic areas.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:48:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985aacde769d12df1d5dc9d_1770368588110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sapphire Foods Posts Loss Amid Devyani International Merger Talks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sapphire-Foods-Posts-Loss-Amid-Devyani-International-Merger-Talks/6985aa78e769d12df1d5db27</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sapphire-Foods-Posts-Loss-Amid-Devyani-International-Merger-Talks/6985aa78e769d12df1d5db27</guid><description>Sapphire Foods India reported a consolidated net loss of ₹48.08 crore for Q3 FY26, a sharp turnaround from a profit of ₹127.32 crore in the prior year, despite a 7.56% revenue increase to ₹8,138.29 crore. The nine-month loss widened to ₹193.33 crore. Amidst this performance, the Board approved a significant merger with Devyani International Limited, proposing a share swap ratio of 177 Devyani shares for every 100 Sapphire Foods shares.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:46:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985aa78e769d12df1d5db26_1770368358133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Opens Bank Loans to REITs, Reshaping Real Estate Finance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBI-Opens-Bank-Loans-to-REITs-Reshaping-Real-Estate-Finance/6985aa51e769d12df1d5da3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBI-Opens-Bank-Loans-to-REITs-Reshaping-Real-Estate-Finance/6985aa51e769d12df1d5da3e</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has authorized direct bank lending to Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs), a move poised to significantly lower funding costs and enhance balance sheet flexibility for these entities. This regulatory shift aims to redirect bank exposure from development risks towards stabilized, income-generating properties, marking a structural easing in real estate finance. While enhancing liquidity and confidence, the policy encourages a more robust capital allocation towards mature assets within India's burgeoning REIT market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:46:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985aa51e769d12df1d5da3d_1770368216096.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ACME Solar Secures Key FDRE Project, Eyes Dispatchable Power Edge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ACME-Solar-Secures-Key-FDRE-Project-Eyes-Dispatchable-Power-Edge/6985a9dce769d12df1d5d8ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ACME-Solar-Secures-Key-FDRE-Project-Eyes-Dispatchable-Power-Edge/6985a9dce769d12df1d5d8ac</guid><description>ACME Solar Holdings has secured a significant 301 MW/1,204 MWh Firm and Dispatchable Renewable Energy (FDRE) project from SECI via an e-reverse auction. This win reinforces the company's strategy in the critical FDRE segment, which integrates advanced storage for reliable, non-solar hour power delivery. The project expansion brings ACME Solar's total contracted capacity to 8,071 MW, underscoring its diversified approach to renewable energy development.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:44:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985a9dce769d12df1d5d8ab_1770368171807.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alembic Pharma Bags USFDA Approval for Parkinson's Drug</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alembic-Pharma-Bags-USFDA-Approval-for-Parkinsons-Drug/6985a961e769d12df1d5d719</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alembic-Pharma-Bags-USFDA-Approval-for-Parkinsons-Drug/6985a961e769d12df1d5d719</guid><description>Alembic Pharmaceuticals has received USFDA approval for its generic Carbidopa, Levodopa, and Entacapone tablets, targeting Parkinson's disease treatment. This approval, covering multiple dosage strengths equivalent to Orion Corporation's Stalevo, aims to expand Alembic's U.S. market presence within the growing generic CNS drug sector. The move comes amid recent analyst downgrades and existing margin pressures for the company, highlighting the competitive challenges in the pharmaceutical generics space.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:42:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985a961e769d12df1d5d718_1770368014797.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Mandates Consumer Protection in Digital Finance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Mandates-Consumer-Protection-in-Digital-Finance/6985a91be769d12df1d5d567</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Mandates-Consumer-Protection-in-Digital-Finance/6985a91be769d12df1d5d567</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is implementing significant consumer protection measures for digital transactions, proposing compensation of up to Rs 25,000 for small-value fraud losses. These initiatives, announced during the recent monetary policy review, also include a review of the 2017 customer liability framework for unauthorized electronic banking transactions and a discussion paper on enhanced payment safety. These measures aim to bolster consumer confidence amid rising digital fraud cases, which saw 13,516 incidents involving Rs 520 crore in FY25.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:40:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985a91be769d12df1d5d566_1770367858133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Tightens Grip: New Rules Target Mis-selling, Recovery Tactics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Tightens-Grip-New-Rules-Target-Mis-selling-Recovery-Tactics/6985a8fee769d12df1d5d48b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Tightens-Grip-New-Rules-Target-Mis-selling-Recovery-Tactics/6985a8fee769d12df1d5d48b</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is set to issue comprehensive draft guidelines aimed at curbing the mis-selling of financial products and standardizing loan recovery practices. Governor Sanjay Malhotra highlighted the necessity of ensuring third-party products are suitable for customer needs. Concurrently, a compensation framework for small-value digital frauds, capped at ₹25,000, is being introduced. These measures signal a significant regulatory push towards enhanced borrower protection and greater market accountability across the financial sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:40:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985a8fee769d12df1d5d48a_1770367703282.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Tightens Loan Recovery Rules, Offers Rs 25,000 Fraud Cover</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Tightens-Loan-Recovery-Rules-Offers-Rs-25000-Fraud-Cover/6985a8eae769d12df1d5d3d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Tightens-Loan-Recovery-Rules-Offers-Rs-25000-Fraud-Cover/6985a8eae769d12df1d5d3d3</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is set to enforce stricter rules for loan recovery agents to curb harassment and ensure fair borrower treatment. New draft guidelines will also address mis-selling and offer up to Rs 25,000 compensation for losses from unauthorized electronic banking transactions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:40:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985a8eae769d12df1d5d3d2_1770367539047.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Siemens India PAT Dips 26% Despite Revenue Growth; LVM Sale Approved</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Siemens-India-PAT-Dips-26percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth-LVM-Sale-Approved/6985a894e769d12df1d5d264</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Siemens-India-PAT-Dips-26percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth-LVM-Sale-Approved/6985a894e769d12df1d5d264</guid><description>Siemens Limited reported a 14.0% year-on-year increase in consolidated revenue from continuing operations to INR 3,831 crore for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) from continuing operations declined 26.0% YoY to INR 269 crore. This drop was attributed to forex losses, commodity gains impact, and a one-time exceptional cost of INR 74 crore related to new Labour Codes. The company's order backlog grew 7% YoY to INR 43,004 crore, and management remains optimistic about India's economic growth. Key strategic moves include the approval for the sale of its Low Voltage Motors (LVM) business and the indefinite deferral of a metro car assembly setup capex.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985a894e769d12df1d5d263_1770367384079.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Diverges: Tobacco Stocks Rally, IT Sags on Mixed Signals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Diverges-Tobacco-Stocks-Rally-IT-Sags-on-Mixed-Signals/6985a872e769d12df1d5d15b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Diverges-Tobacco-Stocks-Rally-IT-Sags-on-Mixed-Signals/6985a872e769d12df1d5d15b</guid><description>Indian equity markets navigated a cautious trading session Thursday, marked by significant sectoral divergence. Tobacco stocks recovered sharply, seemingly recalibrating expectations following parliamentary approval of excise duty adjustments. Conversely, the technology sector extended its decline, with major IT players and mid-cap firms facing renewed selling pressure. Individual companies reported varied earnings outcomes: Kaynes Technology missed street expectations despite growth, while Hitachi Energy, Nykaa, and Indian Oil Corporation posted strong performances. Investor sentiment appears highly selective, prioritizing resilient earnings and sector-specific demand drivers over broader market uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:38:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985a872e769d12df1d5d15a_1770367263960.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>