<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 21:20:18 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Indian TV Sector Faces Seismic Shift: Adaptation or Obsolescence?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indian-TV-Sector-Faces-Seismic-Shift-Adaptation-or-Obsolescence/69921f182e6a0b8ae17c5fd3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indian-TV-Sector-Faces-Seismic-Shift-Adaptation-or-Obsolescence/69921f182e6a0b8ae17c5fd3</guid><description>India's television broadcasting and distribution sector is undergoing a pronounced structural slowdown in FY26. Declining linear TV viewership and a rapid migration to digital platforms are pressuring both advertising and subscription revenues. BARC data shows a dip in overall linear TV audience reach, accelerating the shift towards free and ad-supported digital services. Media agencies predict a significant shrinkage in television's share of the advertising pie by 2027. Key players like Zee Entertainment are already reporting profit declines, underscoring the urgency for strategic recalibration amidst evolving consumer habits and competitive pressures.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 19:31:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69921f182e6a0b8ae17c5fd2_1771184083695.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Rail Tech Dominance: Policy Fuels Local Manufacturing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/India-Eyes-Rail-Tech-Dominance-Policy-Fuels-Local-Manufacturing/69921f132e6a0b8ae17c5fbc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/India-Eyes-Rail-Tech-Dominance-Policy-Fuels-Local-Manufacturing/69921f132e6a0b8ae17c5fbc</guid><description>India's forthcoming railway technology policy targets robust local manufacturing, aiming to curb substantial import bills and foster indigenous innovation for next-generation rail systems. Supported by record capital expenditure, the initiative seeks to transform India into a global hub for rail technology, mirroring past "Make in India" objectives while navigating existing sector challenges and competitive global dynamics.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 19:31:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69921f132e6a0b8ae17c5fbb_1771184063569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Pak Match Fuels Ad Rate Surge, Boosts Economy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Sports/India-Pak-Match-Fuels-Ad-Rate-Surge-Boosts-Economy/69921f0f2e6a0b8ae17c5fa4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Sports/India-Pak-Match-Fuels-Ad-Rate-Surge-Boosts-Economy/69921f0f2e6a0b8ae17c5fa4</guid><description>The high-stakes India-Pakistan T20 World Cup fixture has triggered an economic surge, most notably inflating advertising rates to record highs. Ten-second TV ad slots commanded ₹30-40 lakh, reflecting an intense demand for limited inventory following the last-minute confirmation of the match. Food delivery platforms and hospitality services also experienced significant order and footfall increases, capitalizing on event-driven consumer engagement.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 19:31:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69921f0f2e6a0b8ae17c5fa3_1771184089851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lavasa Takeover: Welspun Wins Creditor Vote Amid Valor's Legal Challenge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Lavasa-Takeover-Welspun-Wins-Creditor-Vote-Amid-Valors-Legal-Challenge/69921f0a2e6a0b8ae17c5f8c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Lavasa-Takeover-Welspun-Wins-Creditor-Vote-Amid-Valors-Legal-Challenge/69921f0a2e6a0b8ae17c5f8c</guid><description>Creditors have backed the Welspun-Ashdan consortium to acquire the debt-laden Lavasa Corp project with 92.21% of votes. However, rival bidder Valor Estate, which submitted a higher Net Present Value offer, is contesting the outcome. Valor alleges procedural unfairness after the Welspun-Ashdan consortium was permitted to modify its payment plan post-deadline, a move that has led to Valor's own legal challenge at the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT). This protracted resolution process highlights the complexities of distressed asset management in India's infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 19:31:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69921f0a2e6a0b8ae17c5f8b_1771184035700.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RERA Oversight Tightens Amidst State vs. Centre Clash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RERA-Oversight-Tightens-Amidst-State-vs-Centre-Clash/69921ef92e6a0b8ae17c5f55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RERA-Oversight-Tightens-Amidst-State-vs-Centre-Clash/69921ef92e6a0b8ae17c5f55</guid><description>Housing Minister Manohar Lal Khattar is proposing central government vetting of state-level Real Estate (Regulation and Development) Act (RERA) bye-laws, responding to Supreme Court concerns about inconsistent implementation and builder-friendly outcomes. This move signals an attempt to reconcile central policy objectives with state autonomy, a persistent friction point. Concurrently, the ministry is exploring unconventional funding models for affordable housing and stalled pre-RERA projects, underscoring ongoing structural financing gaps within the real estate sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 19:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69921ef92e6a0b8ae17c5f54_1771184023103.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Retail: Inventory Gluts Eat Profits Despite Sales Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Retail-Inventory-Gluts-Eat-Profits-Despite-Sales-Growth/69921ef72e6a0b8ae17c5f3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Retail-Inventory-Gluts-Eat-Profits-Despite-Sales-Growth/69921ef72e6a0b8ae17c5f3e</guid><description>A significant portion of India's organized retail outlets operate at a loss, with 28% to 40% struggling even amidst reported sales growth. Vector Consulting Group's survey indicates this is primarily due to shelves crowded with stagnant stock, as retailers introduce new items without clearing old ones. This inventory overload shrinks the profitable selling window, forcing companies like Shoppers Stop to consider store closures and aggressive capital reallocation. The core challenge lies in translating sales and profit per square foot data into decisive inventory management actions, a gap that hinders overall sector profitability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 19:31:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69921ef72e6a0b8ae17c5f3d_1771184015111.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FMCG Firms Pivot to Value Packs Amid Rural Demand Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Firms-Pivot-to-Value-Packs-Amid-Rural-Demand-Surge/69921e852e6a0b8ae17c5e83</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Firms-Pivot-to-Value-Packs-Amid-Rural-Demand-Surge/69921e852e6a0b8ae17c5e83</guid><description>Consumer goods giants are strategically re-emphasizing entry-level products and smaller pack sizes, a marked departure from recent premiumization efforts. This pivot, observed since December, is fueled by nascent demand recovery in rural markets and among lower-income demographics, further supported by the September 2025 GST rate reductions. Companies like Emami, LG Electronics India, Varun Beverages, Dabur, Hindustan Unilever, and Colgate-Palmolive are launching new value-focused offerings and smaller SKUs to capture volume growth. Executives anticipate improved sales volumes across both rural and urban segments in the coming quarters, signaling a potential turnaround after a prolonged slowdown.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 19:29:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69921e852e6a0b8ae17c5e82_1771183959404.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Restores DLGs, Unlocking NBFC Lending Capacity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Restores-DLGs-Unlocking-NBFC-Lending-Capacity/69921e802e6a0b8ae17c5e69</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Restores-DLGs-Unlocking-NBFC-Lending-Capacity/69921e802e6a0b8ae17c5e69</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has reinstated Default Loss Guarantees (DLGs) for non-bank lenders, effectively reversing restrictive May 2025 rules. This move significantly reduces provisioning burdens for NBFCs partnering with fintech firms, thereby improving profitability and freeing up capital for fresh lending. It is anticipated to invigorate digital loan origination and expand access to under-penetrated retail customer segments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 19:29:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69921e802e6a0b8ae17c5e68_1771183924460.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ixigo Buys Spanish Train OTA to Enter Europe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ixigo-Buys-Spanish-Train-OTA-to-Enter-Europe/69920f0e2e6a0b8ae17c5238</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ixigo-Buys-Spanish-Train-OTA-to-Enter-Europe/69920f0e2e6a0b8ae17c5238</guid><description>Travel tech firm ixigo is set to acquire a 60% stake in Spain's second-largest train Online Travel Agency, Trenes, for €11.70 million (approx. INR 126 crore). This strategic move aims to expand ixigo's market reach into Europe, leveraging its AI capabilities in a mature rail ecosystem, while India remains its core focus. Trenes is a profitable, debt-free business, and the acquisition is funded by a recent preferential issue from Prosus.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 18:23:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69920f0e2e6a0b8ae17c5237_1771179897318.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ace Software Buys UK Energy Tech Firms in Major Diversification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ace-Software-Buys-UK-Energy-Tech-Firms-in-Major-Diversification/699209672e6a0b8ae17c50fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ace-Software-Buys-UK-Energy-Tech-Firms-in-Major-Diversification/699209672e6a0b8ae17c50fe</guid><description>Ace Software Exports Limited has signed a term sheet to invest up to GBP 5 million in UK energy technology firms MyUtilityGenius and MyUtilityGenius Commercial. This strategic move diversifies the company's portfolio into a regulated, technology-led services sector, focusing on data-centric platforms in developed markets. The deal, involving cash and share swap, will give Ace Software a 40% stake and control, potentially making them subsidiaries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:59:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699209672e6a0b8ae17c50fd_1771178452933.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apollo Finvest Bets Big on Direct Lending with 'Apollo Cash' Launch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Apollo-Finvest-Bets-Big-on-Direct-Lending-with-Apollo-Cash-Launch/699208b22e6a0b8ae17c507f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Apollo-Finvest-Bets-Big-on-Direct-Lending-with-Apollo-Cash-Launch/699208b22e6a0b8ae17c507f</guid><description>Apollo Finvest (India) Limited is strategically shifting gears by launching 'Apollo Cash', a new direct lending arm. This move aims to boost its Assets Under Management (AUM) by directly engaging customers, leveraging its fintech experience. The company plans significant investment in technology and talent, targeting higher double-digit Return on Equity (ROE) and a debt-to-equity ratio of around 3X to fuel expansion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:56:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699208b22e6a0b8ae17c507e_1771178303799.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pilots CBDC for Food Subsidies: A New Fiscal Control Lever</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Pilots-CBDC-for-Food-Subsidies-A-New-Fiscal-Control-Lever/699200fc2e6a0b8ae17c4ea9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Pilots-CBDC-for-Food-Subsidies-A-New-Fiscal-Control-Lever/699200fc2e6a0b8ae17c4ea9</guid><description>India has initiated a significant pilot program leveraging Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) for its Public Distribution System (PDS) in Gujarat. This digital food currency, e-Rupee (e₹), aims to credit programmable digital coupons directly to beneficiaries, redeemable exclusively for foodgrains. The initiative promises enhanced transparency, traceability, and real-time transaction monitoring, addressing long-standing issues in subsidy delivery. Beyond operational efficiencies, it represents a strategic pivot towards tighter fiscal management and a digitized welfare architecture.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:23:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699200fc2e6a0b8ae17c4ea8_1771176330534.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rural Budget: VB-G RAM G Dominates, MGNREGA Cuts Deep</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Rural-Budget-VB-G-RAM-G-Dominates-MGNREGA-Cuts-Deep/6991fd052e6a0b8ae17c4d00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Rural-Budget-VB-G-RAM-G-Dominates-MGNREGA-Cuts-Deep/6991fd052e6a0b8ae17c4d00</guid><description>The Union Budget for FY 2026-27 marks a significant restructuring of rural development spending. The new VB-G RAM G scheme has secured a dominant 40% share (Rs 95,692 crore), eclipsing the Mahatma Gandhi National Rural Employment Guarantee Act (MGNREGA), which faces a drastic 66% funding cut to Rs 30,000 crore. This reallocation, analyzed by PRS Legislative Research, also boosts allocations for rural housing (PMAY-G) and rural roads (PMGSY). Crucially, VB-G RAM G introduces a 60:40 Centre-State funding model, shifting fiscal burden compared to MGNREGA's predominantly central funding, potentially increasing state expenditure on rural programs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:06:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991fd052e6a0b8ae17c4cff_1771175302540.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Wave Hits Wealth Management; India Regulators Tighten Grip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Wave-Hits-Wealth-Management-India-Regulators-Tighten-Grip/6991fa012e6a0b8ae17c4b57</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Wave-Hits-Wealth-Management-India-Regulators-Tighten-Grip/6991fa012e6a0b8ae17c4b57</guid><description>The AI revolution is expanding its reach beyond India's IT sector, now posing a direct threat to the operational models and fee structures of wealth management firms. Concurrently, the Association of Portfolio Managers in India (APMI) has intensified compliance requirements, mandating rigorous verification of fund inflows and outflows to combat fraud. In a parallel development, GIFT City's IFSCA is streamlining operations through a unified registration system, signaling a strategic effort to bolster its position as an international financial hub by reducing regulatory friction.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:53:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991fa012e6a0b8ae17c4b56_1771174563746.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MFs Pile into Private Banks: Valuations, PSB Competition Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MFs-Pile-into-Private-Banks-Valuations-PSB-Competition-Loom/6991f9f72e6a0b8ae17c4b40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MFs-Pile-into-Private-Banks-Valuations-PSB-Competition-Loom/6991f9f72e6a0b8ae17c4b40</guid><description>In January, mutual funds significantly increased their exposure to leading private sector banks, deploying approximately ₹15,400 crore into HDFC Bank and ICICI Bank, and another ₹3,000 crore into Kotak Mahindra Bank. This concentrated buying, representing 45% of total MF equity purchases that month, signals a strategic pivot driven by perceived attractive valuations after a period of underperformance against public sector banks. However, this influx occurs as PSBs demonstrate robust advance growth and competitive deposit-gathering, while valuations for some private banks are nearing or entering 'expensive' territory, raising questions about sustainability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:53:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991f9f72e6a0b8ae17c4b3f_1771174600832.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auto Ancillaries Surge on Exports, Masking Global Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Ancillaries-Surge-on-Exports-Masking-Global-Risks/6991f9f62e6a0b8ae17c4b29</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Ancillaries-Surge-on-Exports-Masking-Global-Risks/6991f9f62e6a0b8ae17c4b29</guid><description>Auto ancillary stocks are outperforming due to strong Q3 results, favorable trade pacts with the EU, UK, and US, and global supply chain diversification. Bharat Forge and Sona BLW lead recent gains. However, significant exposure to European markets and evolving global competition pose considerable risks to sustained growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991f9f62e6a0b8ae17c4b28_1771174553867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Radhagobind Commercial in Insolvency Sees Profits Fall Sharply Year-on-Year</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Radhagobind-Commercial-in-Insolvency-Sees-Profits-Fall-Sharply-Year-on-Year/6991f8112e6a0b8ae17c4a5e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Radhagobind-Commercial-in-Insolvency-Sees-Profits-Fall-Sharply-Year-on-Year/6991f8112e6a0b8ae17c4a5e</guid><description>Radhagobind Commercial Limited, formerly Tejmangal Commercial Company Limited, has reported its unaudited quarterly results for December 31, 2025, while operating under an Insolvency Resolution Professional (IRP). The company posted a year-on-year revenue decline of 2.76% and a significant 47.24% drop in profit after tax. This contrasts sharply with some peers who reported growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:45:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991f8112e6a0b8ae17c4a5d_1771174518625.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises Unit Takes Full Control of Stelltek JV</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-Unit-Takes-Full-Control-of-Stelltek-JV/6991f3602e6a0b8ae17c48e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-Unit-Takes-Full-Control-of-Stelltek-JV/6991f3602e6a0b8ae17c48e0</guid><description>Amber Enterprises India Limited, through its material subsidiary IL JIN Electronics India Private Limited, has taken full control of Stelltek Technologies Private Limited. Stelltek, previously a joint venture, now becomes a subsidiary, enhancing governance and strategic alignment. Stelltek was incorporated in December 2023 and has reported zero turnover, indicating its early stage. This move is part of Amber's strategy to consolidate its electronics manufacturing operations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:25:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991f3602e6a0b8ae17c48df_1771172849767.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dynacons Systems Q3 Profit Soars 27%, Debt Drops Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Dynacons-Systems-Q3-Profit-Soars-27percent-Debt-Drops-Sharply/6991f35e2e6a0b8ae17c48ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Dynacons-Systems-Q3-Profit-Soars-27percent-Debt-Drops-Sharply/6991f35e2e6a0b8ae17c48ca</guid><description>Dynacons Systems &amp; Solutions Limited reported strong Q3 FY26 results, with net profit jumping 27.3% year-on-year to ₹23 crore. The company also saw significant improvement in EBITDA, which rose 49.2% to ₹41 crore, with EBITDA margins expanding to 11.9%. This robust performance was driven by increased wallet share, new client acquisitions in BFSI and PSU sectors, and an enhanced focus on higher-margin solutions like AI-ready infrastructure. The company also continued its deleveraging efforts, reducing net debt to ₹14 crore, and reported a healthy order book of over ₹2,300 crore.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:25:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991f35e2e6a0b8ae17c48c9_1771172865539.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Embassy Developments Posts Loss Despite Record Sales; Eyes Mumbai Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-Developments-Posts-Loss-Despite-Record-Sales-Eyes-Mumbai-Market/6991f08f2e6a0b8ae17c47cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-Developments-Posts-Loss-Despite-Record-Sales-Eyes-Mumbai-Market/6991f08f2e6a0b8ae17c47cc</guid><description>Embassy Developments Limited (EDL) reported a robust Q3 FY'26 with pre-sales surging 240% QoQ to ₹1,392 Cr. However, the company posted an EBITDA loss of ₹107 Cr for the nine months due to costs from legacy Indiabulls projects. Management forecasts PAT to remain negative for 6-8 quarters, while cash flows are expected to be profitable. EDL is strategically entering the Mumbai market with projects worth over ₹12,000 Cr GDV and aims to reduce its debt cost from 14% to 10%.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:13:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991f08f2e6a0b8ae17c47cb_1771172095671.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economic Shift: New Hubs Challenge Metro Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Shift-New-Hubs-Challenge-Metro-Dominance/6991efb32e6a0b8ae17c4733</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Shift-New-Hubs-Challenge-Metro-Dominance/6991efb32e6a0b8ae17c4733</guid><description>India's economic expansion is decisively decentralizing, with emerging districts in northern and eastern states rapidly gaining prominence according to Dun &amp; Bradstreet's City Vitality Index. While established metros retain top rankings, this shift signals a fundamental rebalancing, driven by infrastructure improvements and government initiatives. Tier-2 and Tier-3 cities now offer significant cost advantages and attract new investment, challenging the long-held dominance of legacy economic centers and presenting a new frontier for growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:09:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991efb32e6a0b8ae17c4732_1771171907678.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Domestic Investors Shield Indian Markets Amidst Equity Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Domestic-Investors-Shield-Indian-Markets-Amidst-Equity-Volatility/6991ea812e6a0b8ae17c45d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Domestic-Investors-Shield-Indian-Markets-Amidst-Equity-Volatility/6991ea812e6a0b8ae17c45d7</guid><description>Despite equity market turbulence and significant foreign investor selling in January 2026, India's mutual fund industry experienced robust growth. Over 5 million new folios were added, pushing the total to 266.3 million. This surge was propelled by sustained Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) contributions and a record inflow into Gold and Silver Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs), signaling domestic investors' increasing confidence and diversification strategies amid global uncertainties. The total industry Assets Under Management (AUM) crossed ₹81 lakh crore.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:47:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991ea812e6a0b8ae17c45d6_1771170663940.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Altman Signals India's AI Leap Amid Global Tech Influx</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Altman-Signals-Indias-AI-Leap-Amid-Global-Tech-Influx/6991e4e52e6a0b8ae17c4478</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Altman-Signals-Indias-AI-Leap-Amid-Global-Tech-Influx/6991e4e52e6a0b8ae17c4478</guid><description>OpenAI CEO Sam Altman identifies India as a burgeoning "full-stack AI leader," citing its talent, strategy, and 100 million weekly AI users. His endorsement, coinciding with major AI executives converging in India, underscores the nation's growing strategic importance. While optimistic, challenges remain regarding infrastructure, talent, and monetization, as global AI giants vie for market share and influence in this critical emerging economy.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:23:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991e4e52e6a0b8ae17c4477_1771169126308.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Tea Woes: Cost Squeeze Fuels Sector Bifurcation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indian-Tea-Woes-Cost-Squeeze-Fuels-Sector-Bifurcation/6991df362e6a0b8ae17c42fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indian-Tea-Woes-Cost-Squeeze-Fuels-Sector-Bifurcation/6991df362e6a0b8ae17c42fa</guid><description>India's tea sector is under mounting financial pressure as escalating wages, input costs, and labor shortages force estates to sell below cost. Climate variability further erodes yields and quality. While calls for policy reform and support intensify, the industry faces a bifurcated future, with high-quality specialty teas showing resilience against the commoditized segment's struggles.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:59:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991df362e6a0b8ae17c42f9_1771167684224.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mold-Tek Packaging Eyes ₹1000 Cr Revenue; Pharma &amp; Food Drive Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mold-Tek-Packaging-Eyes-1000-Cr-Revenue-Pharma-and-Food-Drive-Growth/6991debf2e6a0b8ae17c42aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mold-Tek-Packaging-Eyes-1000-Cr-Revenue-Pharma-and-Food-Drive-Growth/6991debf2e6a0b8ae17c42aa</guid><description>Mold-Tek Packaging reported a strong Q3 FY26 with sales volumes up 6% and EBITDA growing 14% year-on-year. For the nine months, sales rose 12% and EBITDA jumped 20%. The company is strategically expanding into the Pharma and Food &amp; FMCG segments, targeting over ₹1,000 Crores in revenue by FY27 with improved EBITDA margins. Despite a dip in lubricant volumes, operational efficiencies and new partnerships are key growth drivers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:57:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991debf2e6a0b8ae17c42a9_1771167563645.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Co-op Banks Balk at RBI License: Autonomy Fears Trump Bank Status</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Co-op-Banks-Balk-at-RBI-License-Autonomy-Fears-Trump-Bank-Status/6991dc8e878851adec4d71c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Co-op-Banks-Balk-at-RBI-License-Autonomy-Fears-Trump-Bank-Status/6991dc8e878851adec4d71c4</guid><description>Large urban co-operative credit societies are poised to decline Reserve Bank of India (RBI) licenses for conversion into urban co-operative banks. Societies fear the stringent, dual regulatory oversight from the RBI, in addition to existing state registrars, will impose prohibitive costs and operational complexities. This reluctance stems from a desire to preserve their distinct community-centric governance and localized trust, which they believe would be compromised under formal banking regulations. Recent RBI reforms aimed at strengthening co-operative banks might not be enough to offset these deep-seated concerns about losing operational autonomy.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:47:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991dc8e878851adec4d71c3_1771166954417.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bain Capital Navigates RBI Hurdles for Manappuram Finance Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bain-Capital-Navigates-RBI-Hurdles-for-Manappuram-Finance-Stake/6991dbf6878851adec4d7134</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bain-Capital-Navigates-RBI-Hurdles-for-Manappuram-Finance-Stake/6991dbf6878851adec4d7134</guid><description>Bain Capital's significant investment in Manappuram Finance is proceeding under a conditional approval from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI). The approval mandates Bain to divest its majority stake in Tyger Capital, another NBFC it controls, to comply with regulations against controlling multiple entities in the same financial category. This strategic move signals Bain's focus on Manappuram's strong market position in gold loans and its potential for growth, despite the cost of regulatory compliance and divestment. Analysts see Manappuram as a more attractive proposition compared to Tyger, reflecting a calculated trade-off for capital infusion and market access in India's expanding NBFC sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:45:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991dbf6878851adec4d7133_1771166867740.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CarTrade Tech Leaps Ahead with AI, Posts Record Revenue and Strong Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CarTrade-Tech-Leaps-Ahead-with-AI-Posts-Record-Revenue-and-Strong-Margins/6991db77878851adec4d70c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CarTrade-Tech-Leaps-Ahead-with-AI-Posts-Record-Revenue-and-Strong-Margins/6991db77878851adec4d70c7</guid><description>CarTrade Tech is making a big stride with its new Multi-Agent AI Ecosystem, aimed at revolutionizing customer experience and boosting profits on platforms like CarWale and BikeWale. This follows a stellar Q3 FY26 where the company hit record revenue of ₹228 crore and achieved an impressive 37% EBITDA margin, a significant jump from single digits historically. The AI initiative will deploy specialized agents across its brands to manage transactions, connect buyers and sellers, and simplify vehicle discovery and purchasing, promising to boost transaction speed and customer satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:43:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991db77878851adec4d70c6_1771166723510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BEL Seals French Defence JV for HAMMER Missile Kits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/BEL-Seals-French-Defence-JV-for-HAMMER-Missile-Kits/6991d99d878851adec4d7007</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/BEL-Seals-French-Defence-JV-for-HAMMER-Missile-Kits/6991d99d878851adec4d7007</guid><description>Bharat Electronics Limited (BEL) has received board approval to sign a Joint Venture Agreement (JVA) with France's Safran Electronics and Defence (SED). The JV will establish a 'Center of Excellence' for the manufacturing, supply, maintenance, and repair of Guidance Kits for the HAMMER Weapon System, primarily for the Indian Air Force and Navy. This move is a significant step in India's defence indigenization efforts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:35:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991d99d878851adec4d7006_1771166218551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IPO Surge: 6 Companies Debut Amidst Muted Grey Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Surge-6-Companies-Debut-Amidst-Muted-Grey-Market/6991d70b878851adec4d6f34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Surge-6-Companies-Debut-Amidst-Muted-Grey-Market/6991d70b878851adec4d6f34</guid><description>The Indian primary market is poised for an active week starting February 16, featuring three IPO openings and three new listings, including Gaudium IVF, Fractal Industries, Yashhtej Industries, Marushika Technology, Fractal Analytics, and Aye Finance. Despite a robust pipeline, key mainboard debutants Fractal Analytics and Aye Finance are seeing no premium in the grey market, indicating investor caution amidst AI disruption fears and geopolitical tensions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:24:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991d70b878851adec4d6f33_1771165583101.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Health Push: Scaling Challenges Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Health-Push-Scaling-Challenges-Emerge/6991d583878851adec4d6dd7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Health-Push-Scaling-Challenges-Emerge/6991d583878851adec4d6dd7</guid><description>India is aggressively digitizing rural healthcare with AI, backed by significant government investment and initiatives like Ayushman Bharat. While AI-driven diagnostics and telemedicine are expanding access, the sector's true potential hinges on overcoming challenges in scalability, digital literacy, and fostering deeper private sector involvement to ensure equitable and sustainable healthcare outcomes for its vast rural population.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:17:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991d583878851adec4d6dd6_1771165197859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Record Power Growth: Grid Stability Faces Test Amidst Green Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Record-Power-Growth-Grid-Stability-Faces-Test-Amidst-Green-Surge/6991d566878851adec4d6d9f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Record-Power-Growth-Grid-Stability-Faces-Test-Amidst-Green-Surge/6991d566878851adec4d6d9f</guid><description>India has set an unprecedented record by adding over 52 GW of power generation capacity in the first ten months of FY26, pushing its non-fossil fuel share past 50% ahead of schedule. While this surge, primarily driven by renewables like solar and wind, signifies a monumental stride in its energy transition, it simultaneously magnifies existing vulnerabilities in grid stability and necessitates substantial investment in storage and infrastructure upgrades to manage intermittency and ensure reliable power delivery. The rapid expansion, though record-breaking, highlights an ongoing tension between capacity targets and the practicalities of grid management, demanding a critical reassessment of integration strategies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:17:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991d566878851adec4d6d9e_1771165221627.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Oil Pivot: Strategic Realignment or Costly Gamble?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Oil-Pivot-Strategic-Realignment-or-Costly-Gamble/6991d554878851adec4d6d61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Oil-Pivot-Strategic-Realignment-or-Costly-Gamble/6991d554878851adec4d6d61</guid><description>India's directive to shift from Russian crude oil imports to US and Venezuelan sources signals a strategic geopolitical pivot but introduces considerable economic friction. Moody's Analytics highlights that this transition will inevitably drive up domestic energy prices and strain India's fiscal balance due to extensive fuel subsidies. Refineries face higher processing costs adapting to different crude grades, while the lack of detailed trade agreement terms introduces uncertainty. The move reflects a broader effort to diversify energy sources, though immediate full replacement of Russian supplies is deemed infeasible in the near term.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:16:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6991d554878851adec4d6d60.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Revenue Surges 30%, Settles US Patent Case</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Zydus-Lifesciences-Revenue-Surges-30percent-Settles-US-Patent-Case/6991cfc3878851adec4d6bed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Zydus-Lifesciences-Revenue-Surges-30percent-Settles-US-Patent-Case/6991cfc3878851adec4d6bed</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences posted a strong Q3 FY26, with revenue jumping 30% year-on-year to ₹68.6 billion and EBITDA up 31%. This growth was fueled by significant contributions from recent acquisitions like Amplitude Surgical and Comfort Click, alongside robust performance in its US, India, and international markets. The company also announced a $120 million settlement in its US patent litigation concerning generic Mirabegron, securing continued market access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:53:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991cfc3878851adec4d6bec_1771163723235.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Bets on Proprietary AI World Models</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Mahindra-Bets-on-Proprietary-AI-World-Models/6991c6a40caf1c998745df98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Mahindra-Bets-on-Proprietary-AI-World-Models/6991c6a40caf1c998745df98</guid><description>Tech Mahindra is investing in proprietary AI "world models" designed for complex, contextual simulations in sectors like telecom and healthcare. This initiative anticipates future client demand for highly tailored AI, differentiating the company in the evolving agentic AI landscape. This strategic R&amp;D aims to secure a competitive edge amid industry-wide challenges, including talent deficits and the broader Indian IT sector's navigation of macroeconomic pressures and policy recommendations for AI sovereignty.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:14:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991c6a40caf1c998745df97_1771161390248.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Signature Global Expands with ₹12,500 Cr Projects Amidst Sales Target Revision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-Expands-with-12500-Cr-Projects-Amidst-Sales-Target-Revision/6991c0fb0caf1c998745de1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-Expands-with-12500-Cr-Projects-Amidst-Sales-Target-Revision/6991c0fb0caf1c998745de1e</guid><description>Signature Global is set to launch a branded luxury housing project in Gurugram with an estimated ₹5,000 crore revenue potential and a significant mixed-use commercial development through a ₹7,500 crore joint venture with RMZ Group. This aggressive expansion comes as the company revises its fiscal year sales booking target downwards to ₹10,300 crore, citing a softening housing demand in Gurugram. Construction activities have accelerated, anticipating increased revenue recognition in the current quarter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:50:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991c0fb0caf1c998745de1d_1771159964184.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Embassy REIT's Expansion: Growth Hype Meets Valuation Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-REITs-Expansion-Growth-Hype-Meets-Valuation-Headwinds/6991bfd10caf1c998745dd67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-REITs-Expansion-Growth-Hype-Meets-Valuation-Headwinds/6991bfd10caf1c998745dd67</guid><description>Embassy Office Parks REIT is leveraging a booming Indian office market, characterized by rising rents and tight vacancies, to fund a substantial 7.6 million sq ft expansion pipeline. The REIT reported a 17% YoY revenue increase to ₹1,193 crore and 19% NOI growth to ₹985 crore. However, questions linger regarding its premium valuation, lower occupancy compared to retail peers, and the performance of specific assets, even as analyst sentiment remains cautiously optimistic.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:45:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991bfd10caf1c998745dd66_1771159642196.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-UK Trade Pact Ratification Awaits Parliament; Tariff Cuts Spark Sector Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-UK-Trade-Pact-Ratification-Awaits-Parliament-Tariff-Cuts-Spark-Sector-Debate/6991bb570caf1c998745dbe9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-UK-Trade-Pact-Ratification-Awaits-Parliament-Tariff-Cuts-Spark-Sector-Debate/6991bb570caf1c998745dbe9</guid><description>The India-UK Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement (CETA), signed in July 2025, is targeting an April 2026 rollout, contingent on UK parliamentary ratification. This pact aims to boost bilateral trade beyond the current estimated $56 billion by 2030, offering Indian exporters 99% duty-free access to the UK while phasing down tariffs on key British goods like Scotch whisky and automobiles. A parallel Double Contributions Convention is also set for implementation. Debates in the UK's House of Commons and House of Lords are underway, representing the critical next phase. Chris Bryant, Minister of State, described the agreement as a "momentous achievement."</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:25:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991bb570caf1c998745dbe8_1771158469809.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manappuram Finance: RBI Nod Comes With Regulatory Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-RBI-Nod-Comes-With-Regulatory-Scrutiny/6991bb280caf1c998745dbd2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-RBI-Nod-Comes-With-Regulatory-Scrutiny/6991bb280caf1c998745dbd2</guid><description>Manappuram Finance shares are under observation following the Reserve Bank of India's conditional approval for Bain Capital affiliates to acquire up to 41.66% stake. This marks the transition to a joint promoter structure, with significant regulatory conditions requiring ongoing compliance and strategic planning. Despite the milestone, the stock saw a slight dip, reflecting investor caution regarding the intricate oversight and future operational adjustments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:25:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991bb280caf1c998745dbd1_1771158476851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Centum Electronics Exits Loss-Making Units, Bets Big on India's Defence &amp; Space Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Centum-Electronics-Exits-Loss-Making-Units-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Defence-and-Space-Boom/6991b3260caf1c998745da3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Centum-Electronics-Exits-Loss-Making-Units-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Defence-and-Space-Boom/6991b3260caf1c998745da3d</guid><description>Centum Electronics Limited is undergoing a significant strategic overhaul, exiting its loss-making operations in Canada and initiating restructuring for its French subsidiaries. This move, which includes recognizing substantial impairment charges, aims to sharpen the company's focus on the booming high-reliability Electronics System Design and Manufacturing (ESDM) sector in India, particularly in defence, space, and aerospace. The company expects these actions to strengthen its financial foundation and drive value-accretive growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:51:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991b3260caf1c998745da3c_1771161835526.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>