<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:21:12 +0000</pubDate><item><title>2026 Auto Wars: Maruti, Tata, Kia Gear Up for Electrifying SUV Offensive!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/2026-Auto-Wars-Maruti-Tata-Kia-Gear-Up-for-Electrifying-SUV-Offensive/69578d4e4342f77179fb1dc2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/2026-Auto-Wars-Maruti-Tata-Kia-Gear-Up-for-Electrifying-SUV-Offensive/69578d4e4342f77179fb1dc2</guid><description>Indian automakers Maruti Suzuki, Tata Motors, Kia, Renault, and Mahindra are set to flood the market with new Electric Vehicles (EVs) and Internal Combustion Engine (ICE) SUVs in early 2026. Key launches include Maruti's e-Vitara EV, Tata's Sierra EV, and updated SUV models from Kia, Hyundai, Renault, and Mahindra, intensifying competition and focusing on advanced features and extended range.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:09:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69578d4e4342f77179fb1dc1_1767345651437.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Gold Rush: Record Prices Expected to Soar in 2026 – What Investors MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Gold-Rush-Record-Prices-Expected-to-Soar-in-2026-What-Investors-MUST-Know/69578d4a4342f77179fb1d8a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Gold-Rush-Record-Prices-Expected-to-Soar-in-2026-What-Investors-MUST-Know/69578d4a4342f77179fb1d8a</guid><description>Gold prices are projected to hit record highs in 2025 and maintain strength through 2026, according to World Gold Council's Sachin Jain. Global factors like interest rates and geopolitical tensions, combined with India's robust domestic demand, are driving gold's appeal as a safe-haven and inflation hedge. Indian investors show strong interest in gold ETFs, bars, and coins for diversification and wealth preservation, while adapting jewellery consumption to lighter designs and using old pieces for loans. Despite high prices, outright selling of gold is not intensifying, indicating strategic consumer behavior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:08:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69578d4a4342f77179fb1d89_1767345657373.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Prices Soar! See Today's Rates in Delhi, Mumbai, Chennai &amp; Your City – Safe Haven Demand Surges on Rate Cut Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Soar-See-Todays-Rates-in-Delhi-Mumbai-Chennai-and-Your-City-Safe-Haven-Demand-Surges-on-Rate-Cut-Hopes/69578bd34342f77179fb16b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Soar-See-Todays-Rates-in-Delhi-Mumbai-Chennai-and-Your-City-Safe-Haven-Demand-Surges-on-Rate-Cut-Hopes/69578bd34342f77179fb16b2</guid><description>Gold and silver futures surged to start the year, driven by expectations of lower US interest rates and a move towards safe-haven assets. On MCX, gold futures for February delivery rose ₹948 to ₹1,36,752 per 10 grams, while March silver futures jumped ₹7,107 to ₹2,42,980 per kg. Global markets on Comex also saw significant gains. City-wise rates reveal variations, with Chennai commanding higher prices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:02:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69578bd34342f77179fb16b1_1767345204654.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Silver Export Ban Sparks $84 Rally! Is This the Hunt Brothers Moment Revisited?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Chinas-Silver-Export-Ban-Sparks-84-Rally-Is-This-the-Hunt-Brothers-Moment-Revisited/695789274342f77179fb0bdb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Chinas-Silver-Export-Ban-Sparks-84-Rally-Is-This-the-Hunt-Brothers-Moment-Revisited/695789274342f77179fb0bdb</guid><description>China is implementing a new 2-year special government license for silver exports starting January 1, 2026, replacing the previous quota system. This move has caused significant market volatility, pushing spot silver to an all-time high of $84 before cooling off due to margin hikes. The restrictions aim to secure domestic supply for industrial demand, impacting 7-10% of global silver supply and tightening an already deficit market. Analysts suggest cautious dip buying for long-term investors (3-5 years).</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:46:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695789274342f77179fb0bda_1767344824335.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BYD Set to Dethrone Tesla! India Sees Premium EV SUV Price Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/BYD-Set-to-Dethrone-Tesla-India-Sees-Premium-EV-SUV-Price-Hike/695788484342f77179fb0713</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/BYD-Set-to-Dethrone-Tesla-India-Sees-Premium-EV-SUV-Price-Hike/695788484342f77179fb0713</guid><description>China's BYD is on track to become the world's largest electric vehicle seller, surpassing Tesla, after reporting a nearly 28% rise in battery-powered car sales to over 2.25 million last year. In India, BYD has announced a ₹50,000 price increase for the premium variant of its SUV, SEALION 7, effective January 1, 2026, citing evolving cost dynamics. The premium variant will now cost ₹49.4 lakh, while the performance variant remains unchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:45:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695788484342f77179fb0712_1767344358279.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Wellness Charts New Growth Path: Dominating Sugar-Free &amp; Protein Markets Amidst Health Shift!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zydus-Wellness-Charts-New-Growth-Path-Dominating-Sugar-Free-and-Protein-Markets-Amidst-Health-Shift/695788254342f77179fb0668</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zydus-Wellness-Charts-New-Growth-Path-Dominating-Sugar-Free-and-Protein-Markets-Amidst-Health-Shift/695788254342f77179fb0668</guid><description>Zydus Wellness is strategically expanding into the booming sugar-free and protein segments, driven by a significant shift in consumer health habits. CEO Tarun Arora highlighted the company's dominant 96% share in the sugar substitutes market and its ambitious plans for protein-based products, including new formats and acquisitions. Innovation across its key brands like Glucon-D, Complan, and Max Protein is central to this growth strategy, aiming to meet evolving daily nutrition needs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:45:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695788254342f77179fb0667_1767344324121.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rental Income Myth Busted: Is Your Second Home Actually Costing You More in India?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Rental-Income-Myth-Busted-Is-Your-Second-Home-Actually-Costing-You-More-in-India/695787bc4342f77179fb044e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Rental-Income-Myth-Busted-Is-Your-Second-Home-Actually-Costing-You-More-in-India/695787bc4342f77179fb044e</guid><description>Investing in a second home for rental income in India often looks appealing but proves costly. Gross rental yields are typically 2-3%, but expenses like maintenance, taxes, and loan costs can slash net returns below 2%. Vacancy periods and uncertain capital appreciation further diminish profitability, making it a business with hidden risks rather than steady income.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:40:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695787bc4342f77179fb044d_1767344362125.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GST CUT SHOCKER: India's Cheapest Cars &amp; Bikes Stage Massive Comeback! Sales Surge 55% - Is This The New Market Trend?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/GST-CUT-SHOCKER-Indias-Cheapest-Cars-and-Bikes-Stage-Massive-Comeback-Sales-Surge-55percent-Is-This-The-New-Market-Trend/695786bc4342f77179faff46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/GST-CUT-SHOCKER-Indias-Cheapest-Cars-and-Bikes-Stage-Massive-Comeback-Sales-Surge-55percent-Is-This-The-New-Market-Trend/695786bc4342f77179faff46</guid><description>A significant Goods and Services Tax (GST) reduction from 28% to 18% has dramatically revived India's entry-level car and two-wheeler markets. Sales of Maruti Suzuki's Alto K10 and S-Presso, and Hero MotoCorp's HF Deluxe and Splendor bikes, surged by 55% in November-December, reversing months of decline. This rebound challenges the notion that tax cuts exclusively drive premiumisation, highlighting persistent demand for affordable vehicles.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:40:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695786bc4342f77179faff45_1767344046794.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GST Tax Trap: Billions in Cess Credit Blocked! Businesses Fight for Their Money Back!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/GST-Tax-Trap-Billions-in-Cess-Credit-Blocked-Businesses-Fight-for-Their-Money-Back/695787764342f77179fb02b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/GST-Tax-Trap-Billions-in-Cess-Credit-Blocked-Businesses-Fight-for-Their-Money-Back/695787764342f77179fb02b6</guid><description>Indian businesses are facing a major challenge with accumulated Goods and Services Tax (GST) Compensation Cess credits that are now blocked following the discontinuation of the levy on most goods from September 22, 2025. Notification No. 2/2025 has rendered the cess 'NIL', preventing its utilization against other GST liabilities. This article explores potential avenues for refunds or cross-utilization of this unutilized credit, with industry groups actively seeking resolution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:39:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695787764342f77179fb02b5_1767344156880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Govt Launched Probe Into Shree Cement! Key Information Sought - What Investors Need to Know Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Govt-Launched-Probe-Into-Shree-Cement-Key-Information-Sought-What-Investors-Need-to-Know-Now/695787164342f77179fb00a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Govt-Launched-Probe-Into-Shree-Cement-Key-Information-Sought-What-Investors-Need-to-Know-Now/695787164342f77179fb00a6</guid><description>The Ministry of Corporate Affairs (MCA) has ordered an investigation into Shree Cement Limited under the Companies Act, 2013. The company confirmed receiving communication from the Regional Director's office in Ahmedabad, initiating the probe under Section 210(1)(c). Shree Cement stated that the MCA is seeking information as part of the process, with no allegations of violations mentioned at this stage. The company assured that this development will not impact its financial position or business operations, and it will provide the requested information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:37:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695787164342f77179fb00a5_1767343993364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zappfresh's Bold Move: Acquiring Ready-To-Cook Giant to Conquer New Markets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zappfreshs-Bold-Move-Acquiring-Ready-To-Cook-Giant-to-Conquer-New-Markets/6957845c4342f77179faf4c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zappfreshs-Bold-Move-Acquiring-Ready-To-Cook-Giant-to-Conquer-New-Markets/6957845c4342f77179faf4c7</guid><description>Zappfresh, a Delhi NCR-based meat delivery startup, is set to acquire a 51% majority stake in Avyom Foodtech Private Limited for INR 7.5 Cr. This strategic move aims to expand Zappfresh's business into the ready-to-eat and ready-to-cook food segments and tap into overseas export markets. The acquisition, expected to finalize within 3-9 months, also involves Avyom Foodtech acquiring Ambrozia Frozen Foods' business, including land and a processing facility, enhancing Zappfresh's capabilities and market reach.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:32:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957845c4342f77179faf4c6_1767343289650.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Sales Surge 14% in December! Key Growth Drivers Revealed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Sales-Surge-14percent-in-December-Key-Growth-Drivers-Revealed/695783af4342f77179faf1eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Sales-Surge-14percent-in-December-Key-Growth-Drivers-Revealed/695783af4342f77179faf1eb</guid><description>Bajaj Auto Ltd. reported a significant 14% year-over-year increase in total sales for December, reaching 3,69,809 units compared to 3,23,125 units in the prior year. Domestic sales saw a 4% rise, with two-wheeler sales growing by 3%. The company's export performance was particularly strong, showing a 24% jump in two-wheeler exports and a remarkable 32% increase in commercial vehicle exports. Overall commercial vehicle sales climbed 17%, indicating robust demand across segments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:29:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695783af4342f77179faf1ea_1767343093977.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC Stock Plummets 10% After Massive Tax Shock: Is It Time to Buy?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-Plummets-10percent-After-Massive-Tax-Shock-Is-It-Time-to-Buy/695782c04342f77179faedfa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-Plummets-10percent-After-Massive-Tax-Shock-Is-It-Time-to-Buy/695782c04342f77179faedfa</guid><description>India's government has announced a sharp increase in excise duty and GST for tobacco products, raising the GST rate on tobacco to 40% from February 1, 2026. This unexpected tax overhaul caused ITC's stock to fall 10% and Godfrey Phillips' stock by over 17%. While near-term volume and margins may be impacted, analysts suggest ITC's diversification and strong market position make it a long-term value play. The current stock price, trading below its 10-year average P/E, presents a potential accumulation opportunity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:22:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695782c04342f77179faedf9_1767343010731.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Touch Rockets to Record High: Bonus Share &amp; Stock Split Plans Ignite Investor Frenzy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silver-Touch-Rockets-to-Record-High-Bonus-Share-and-Stock-Split-Plans-Ignite-Investor-Frenzy/695782074342f77179faea90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silver-Touch-Rockets-to-Record-High-Bonus-Share-and-Stock-Split-Plans-Ignite-Investor-Frenzy/695782074342f77179faea90</guid><description>Silver Touch Technologies stock surged to a new high, gaining 77% in 17 days. The company announced a board meeting on January 16, 2026, to consider bonus share issuance and a stock split, aiming to boost liquidity and affordability. Recent wins, including a deal with the Indian Navy, and strong Q2 financial growth underpin the rally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:13:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695782074342f77179faea8f_1767342659320.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Capital Goods Sector Poised for 10% Revenue Surge in Q3; Consumer Durables to Jump 22%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Capital-Goods-Sector-Poised-for-10percent-Revenue-Surge-in-Q3-Consumer-Durables-to-Jump-22percent/695781984342f77179fae889</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Capital-Goods-Sector-Poised-for-10percent-Revenue-Surge-in-Q3-Consumer-Durables-to-Jump-22percent/695781984342f77179fae889</guid><description>Elara Capital forecasts a robust 10% year-on-year revenue growth for India's capital goods sector in Q3FY26, driven by strong industrial demand and execution. The consumer electricals and durables segment is expected to see an even more significant 22% rise. While many companies like KEI Industries and Kaynes Technology show strong individual growth prospects, challenges exist for others like Voltas. Order inflows experienced a year-on-year decline, impacting some firms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:13:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695781984342f77179fae888_1767342659022.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cement Prices Poised for Major Comeback: Brokerage Names Top Stock for April 2026 Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Prices-Poised-for-Major-Comeback-Brokerage-Names-Top-Stock-for-April-2026-Surge/6957818a4342f77179fae800</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Prices-Poised-for-Major-Comeback-Brokerage-Names-Top-Stock-for-April-2026-Surge/6957818a4342f77179fae800</guid><description>JM Financial forecasts a recovery in Indian cement prices from April 2026, following a marginal dip in December 2025. Despite rising input costs, industry demand saw low double-digit growth year-on-year. UltraTech Cement is highlighted as the top pick with a 'Buy' rating and a target price of ₹14,250.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:13:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957818a4342f77179fae7ff_1767342577411.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>4 Stocks Set for Major Moves Next Week: Bonus, Split &amp; Buyback Action Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/4-Stocks-Set-for-Major-Moves-Next-Week-Bonus-Split-and-Buyback-Action-Ahead/695781154342f77179fae60b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/4-Stocks-Set-for-Major-Moves-Next-Week-Bonus-Split-and-Buyback-Action-Ahead/695781154342f77179fae60b</guid><description>Next week, four stocks – Orient Technologies, Fairchem Organics, A-1 Limited, and Antariksh Industries – will trade ex-date for significant corporate actions. Orient Technologies and Antariksh Industries will go ex-bonus for a 1:10 ratio, A-1 Limited for a 1:10 equity share split, and Fairchem Organics for a share buyback up to ₹34 crore. Investors must hold shares before these ex-dates to be eligible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:13:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695781154342f77179fae60a_1767342425097.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Hits New Low: Will RBI's Defense Hold Against Surging Dollar Demand?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Hits-New-Low-Will-RBIs-Defense-Hold-Against-Surging-Dollar-Demand/6957809e4342f77179fae2c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Hits-New-Low-Will-RBIs-Defense-Hold-Against-Surging-Dollar-Demand/6957809e4342f77179fae2c3</guid><description>The Indian rupee touched an intraday low of 90.12 against the US dollar on Friday, January 2, 2026. This decline occurred despite early gains and interventions by the Reserve Bank of India, which has been defending the 90 level. Persistent demand for dollars, exacerbated by thin market liquidity and foreign investors selling Indian equities, continues to pressure the rupee. Analysts are questioning the sustainability of the RBI's defense against strong underlying dollar demand.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:12:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957809e4342f77179fae2c2_1767342310125.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bank Nifty Shatters Records: Is This Just the Beginning of a Massive Rally? 🚀</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-Nifty-Shatters-Records-Is-This-Just-the-Beginning-of-a-Massive-Rally/69577fb04342f77179fade88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-Nifty-Shatters-Records-Is-This-Just-the-Beginning-of-a-Massive-Rally/69577fb04342f77179fade88</guid><description>Bank Nifty surged to an all-time high of 60,152.35, marking a 0.73% increase driven by robust Q3 business updates. Both Nifty PSU Bank and Private Bank indices also hit fresh record highs. Yes Bank led the gains, surging over 3%, with 13 out of 14 Bank Nifty constituents trading in positive territory, signaling strong investor confidence in the banking sector's recovery and improved asset quality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:08:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69577fb04342f77179fade87_1767342100178.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Newsletter Boom! Substack, Beehiiv Skyrocket as Creators and Brands Flock to Direct Audience Platforms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Newsletter-Boom-Substack-Beehiiv-Skyrocket-as-Creators-and-Brands-Flock-to-Direct-Audience-Platforms/69577f184342f77179fadb90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Newsletter-Boom-Substack-Beehiiv-Skyrocket-as-Creators-and-Brands-Flock-to-Direct-Audience-Platforms/69577f184342f77179fadb90</guid><description>The newsletter business is experiencing a major surge, with platforms like Substack and Beehiiv becoming hubs for creators and brands. Celebrities, investors, and media outlets are launching direct-to-consumer newsletters, reporting significant subscriber growth and healthy revenue streams. Substack, valued at $1.1 billion, and Beehiiv, valued at $225 million, have both secured substantial funding as they adapt to demand for personalized content and direct audience engagement, offering alternatives to traditional media distribution channels.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:07:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69577f184342f77179fadb8f_1767341927891.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stock Market 2026: End of the Party? Expert Forecasts Gloomy Outlook After Record Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Stock-Market-2026-End-of-the-Party-Expert-Forecasts-Gloomy-Outlook-After-Record-Gains/69577f344342f77179fadc30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Stock-Market-2026-End-of-the-Party-Expert-Forecasts-Gloomy-Outlook-After-Record-Gains/69577f344342f77179fadc30</guid><description>After a strong 16% gain in 2025 fueled by AI and policy, the U.S. stock market faces a challenging 2026. Experts predict significantly lower returns, possibly flat or negative, due to midterm election cycles, potential inflation from stronger growth, and complexities in the AI trade. Investors should prepare for a less celebratory year compared to recent successes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:07:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69577f344342f77179fadc2f_1767341996593.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axis Securities Top Picks: 15 Stocks for 2026 with Up to 54% Rocket Ride!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Axis-Securities-Top-Picks-15-Stocks-for-2026-with-Up-to-54percent-Rocket-Ride/69577eb74342f77179fad98a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Axis-Securities-Top-Picks-15-Stocks-for-2026-with-Up-to-54percent-Rocket-Ride/69577eb74342f77179fad98a</guid><description>Axis Securities has unveiled its top 15 stock picks for January 2026, forecasting a strong earnings revival after a challenging 2025. These selections across various sectors offer potential upsides up to 54%, guiding investors toward significant growth opportunities over the next 12 months.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:02:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69577eb74342f77179fad989_1767341815036.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Auto Stars Shine! TVS, Eicher Hit Record Highs; Ola Electric's Big Comeback Stuns Market!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Auto-Stars-Shine-TVS-Eicher-Hit-Record-Highs-Ola-Electrics-Big-Comeback-Stuns-Market/69577dff4342f77179fad593</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Auto-Stars-Shine-TVS-Eicher-Hit-Record-Highs-Ola-Electrics-Big-Comeback-Stuns-Market/69577dff4342f77179fad593</guid><description>TVS Motor Company and Eicher Motors surged to new 52-week highs following robust Q3 FY2025-26 sales reports. TVS Motor achieved its highest-ever quarterly sales at 15.44 Lakh units, driven by significant growth in two-wheeler, three-wheeler, and international segments. Eicher Motors' Royal Enfield brand posted strong monthly sales, marking a 30% year-on-year increase. Meanwhile, Ola Electric Mobility saw a significant jump of 9% after reclaiming market share to 9.3% in December, boosted by its Hyperservice program and new scooter deliveries. Conversely, Bajaj Auto reported a modest 3% domestic sales growth, with overall sales up 14%, but saw a year-on-year decline in year-to-date figures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:01:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69577dff4342f77179fad592_1767341750564.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCX Shares 'Crash' 80% After Split: The Truth Revealed! Is Your Investment Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Shares-Crash-80percent-After-Split-The-Truth-Revealed-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/69577e364342f77179fad6c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Shares-Crash-80percent-After-Split-The-Truth-Revealed-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/69577e364342f77179fad6c1</guid><description>Multi Commodity Exchange of India (MCX) shares appeared to crash by over 80% today due to a 1:5 stock split. This technical adjustment makes shares more affordable and boosts liquidity, leaving investor wealth unaffected. On an adjusted basis, MCX shares are up, hitting a 52-week high. SEBI also plans reforms to boost commodity market participation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:01:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69577e364342f77179fad6c0_1767341799701.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's First Online-Only Housing Project Sells Out 1,419 Homes in Mumbai Breakthrough!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-First-Online-Only-Housing-Project-Sells-Out-1419-Homes-in-Mumbai-Breakthrough/69577d2e4342f77179fad1d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-First-Online-Only-Housing-Project-Sells-Out-1419-Homes-in-Mumbai-Breakthrough/69577d2e4342f77179fad1d3</guid><description>House of Abhinandan Lodha (HoABL) has successfully allotted 1,419 homes in its Naigaon, Mumbai project using India's first large-scale, fully online-only housing model. The innovative digital process, which skipped site visits and sales teams, saw 80% of buyers adhere to the payment schedule, marking a significant milestone for affordable housing. The project, a joint venture with Mittal Builders, aims to set new standards in transparency and technology adoption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:01:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69577d2e4342f77179fad1d2_1767341432486.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Surge: Sensex &amp; Nifty Hit New Highs, Bank Nifty Crosses 60,000!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Surge-Sensex-and-Nifty-Hit-New-Highs-Bank-Nifty-Crosses-60000/69577ce24342f77179fad06e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Surge-Sensex-and-Nifty-Hit-New-Highs-Bank-Nifty-Crosses-60000/69577ce24342f77179fad06e</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks, Sensex and Nifty, extended their gains past midday on Friday, driven by sectoral rotation. The BSE Sensex climbed 492.13 points to ₹85,680.73 and the NSE Nifty advanced 161.05 points to 26,307.60. The banking sector showed strong momentum, with Bank Nifty breaching the 60,000 mark. Market breadth was positive, and mid and smallcap indices also participated in the rally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:00:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69577ce24342f77179fad06d_1767341713169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Group's Massive ₹1,000 Crore Bond Launch Next Week – What Investors NEED to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Adani-Groups-Massive-1000-Crore-Bond-Launch-Next-Week-What-Investors-NEED-to-Know/69577d3e4342f77179fad226</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Adani-Groups-Massive-1000-Crore-Bond-Launch-Next-Week-What-Investors-NEED-to-Know/69577d3e4342f77179fad226</guid><description>Adani Enterprises, the flagship company of Adani Group, is set to launch a public bond issue next week to raise ₹1,000 crore, with an option to raise an additional ₹500 crore. The bonds will have maturities of two, three, and five years, offering annual coupon rates ranging from 8.60% to 8.90%. The issue, rated AA- by CARE Ratings and ICRA, opens on January 6 and closes on January 19, with 35% allocated for retail investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:00:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69577d3e4342f77179fad225_1767341560633.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Insolation Energy Skyrockets: 9-Month Sales Smash Entire Previous Year's Record! Investors Cheer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Insolation-Energy-Skyrockets-9-Month-Sales-Smash-Entire-Previous-Years-Record-Investors-Cheer/69577b524342f77179fac7da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Insolation-Energy-Skyrockets-9-Month-Sales-Smash-Entire-Previous-Years-Record-Investors-Cheer/69577b524342f77179fac7da</guid><description>Insolation Energy Ltd. shares surged over 5% after its provisional sales for the nine months ending December 31, 2025, surpassed the entire previous financial year's total. The company also achieved its highest-ever monthly sales in December 2025, valued at ₹354.59 crore. This strong performance is attributed to strategic execution and favorable market conditions, boosting investor confidence despite a significant 12-month decline in the stock. The company recently secured substantial purchase orders for solar PV modules and a turnkey project.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:38:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69577b524342f77179fac7d9_1767341094297.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sambhv Steel Tubes Surges 7% on Record Sales Volume! Is This a New Bull Run?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sambhv-Steel-Tubes-Surges-7percent-on-Record-Sales-Volume-Is-This-a-New-Bull-Run/69577b044342f77179fac66a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sambhv-Steel-Tubes-Surges-7percent-on-Record-Sales-Volume-Is-This-a-New-Bull-Run/69577b044342f77179fac66a</guid><description>Sambhv Steel Tubes reported its highest-ever sales volume for value-added products in Q3 FY26, a significant jump of 64% year-on-year to 90,612 tonnes. Total sales volume also saw a robust increase of 34% to 97,472 tonnes compared to Q3 FY25. This strong performance, particularly in the Stainless Steel segment, drove investor interest, pushing the company's shares up by approximately 7% during intra-day trading. The company is a key manufacturer of ERW steel pipes and structural tubes in India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:38:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69577b044342f77179fac669_1767341590935.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Movers! Top Stocks Soar and Plunge on Jan 2, 2026 - See Who Made the Biggest Gains &amp; Biggest Losses!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Movers-Top-Stocks-Soar-and-Plunge-on-Jan-2-2026-See-Who-Made-the-Biggest-Gains-and-Biggest-Losses/6957789b4342f77179fabcea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Movers-Top-Stocks-Soar-and-Plunge-on-Jan-2-2026-See-Who-Made-the-Biggest-Gains-and-Biggest-Losses/6957789b4342f77179fabcea</guid><description>On January 2, 2026, Indian stock markets saw significant movement. Coal India Ltd and NTPC Ltd led the gains, while ITC Ltd and Nestle India Ltd were among the top losers. The broader market indices, including Sensex, Nifty 50, and Nifty Bank, traded higher, indicating a positive overall session despite sector-specific declines. Investors tracked these price movements and volume changes closely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:38:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957789b4342f77179fabce9_1767340252793.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Stock Skyrockets! Foreign Buyers Flood Auctions, Sending Shares to 52-Week High!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Stock-Skyrockets-Foreign-Buyers-Flood-Auctions-Sending-Shares-to-52-Week-High/695777fc4342f77179fab9a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Stock-Skyrockets-Foreign-Buyers-Flood-Auctions-Sending-Shares-to-52-Week-High/695777fc4342f77179fab9a7</guid><description>Coal India shares surged 5% to a 52-week high after the company began allowing coal consumers from Bangladesh, Bhutan, and Nepal to directly participate in its Single Window Mode Agnostic e-auctions. Previously, foreign buyers could only access Indian coal through domestic traders. This move aims to expand market reach while ensuring domestic requirements are met.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:37:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695777fc4342f77179fab9a6_1767340112842.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BHEL Scores Big Win: Telangana Tax Dept Drops Massive ₹183 Crore GST Demand!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BHEL-Scores-Big-Win-Telangana-Tax-Dept-Drops-Massive-183-Crore-GST-Demand/695777b04342f77179fab85f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BHEL-Scores-Big-Win-Telangana-Tax-Dept-Drops-Massive-183-Crore-GST-Demand/695777b04342f77179fab85f</guid><description>State-owned engineering firm Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited (BHEL) received substantial tax relief as the Telangana Commercial Tax Department has dropped a Goods and Services Tax (GST) demand of ₹183.77 crore, along with interest and penalty, for the financial year 2021-22. The company received the adjudication order on January 2, 2026, which ruled in its favour concerning export services. A residual dispute of ₹1.43 crore remains, against which BHEL plans to appeal, expecting no significant financial impact.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:37:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695777b04342f77179fab85e_1767340031720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Real Estate Sees MASSIVE Capital Inflow: Billions Return as Land &amp; Data Centers Lead the Charge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Real-Estate-Sees-MASSIVE-Capital-Inflow-Billions-Return-as-Land-and-Data-Centers-Lead-the-Charge/695777a54342f77179fab822</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Real-Estate-Sees-MASSIVE-Capital-Inflow-Billions-Return-as-Land-and-Data-Centers-Lead-the-Charge/695777a54342f77179fab822</guid><description>Private equity investments in Indian real estate hit $6.7 billion in 2025, returning to pre-pandemic levels. Land parcels and data centers were key attractors, accounting for a significant portion of inflows. The office segment also drew substantial capital, supported by stable leasing. This resurgence reflects improved market transparency and asset performance, with expectations for continued steady investment in 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:33:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695777a54342f77179fab821_1767340183082.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 42,000 Cr Boost! India Approves Mega Electronics Manufacturing Projects, Huge Job Creation Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rs-42000-Cr-Boost-India-Approves-Mega-Electronics-Manufacturing-Projects-Huge-Job-Creation-Ahead/695777c04342f77179fab8ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rs-42000-Cr-Boost-India-Approves-Mega-Electronics-Manufacturing-Projects-Huge-Job-Creation-Ahead/695777c04342f77179fab8ce</guid><description>India's Ministry of Electronics and IT has approved 22 new proposals worth ₹41,863 crore under the Electronics Components Manufacturing Scheme (ECMS). These projects are expected to generate ₹2,58,152 crore in production and create over 33,791 direct jobs. Key companies like Dixon, Samsung Display Noida, Foxconn, and Hindalco Industries are among the beneficiaries. The approvals aim to bolster domestic supply chains and reduce import dependence.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:33:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695777c04342f77179fab8cd_1767340129531.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sector Funds Skyrocket: 26% Gains Beckon, But Are You Ready for the Wild Ride?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Sector-Funds-Skyrocket-26percent-Gains-Beckon-But-Are-You-Ready-for-the-Wild-Ride/695776c64342f77179fab465</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Sector-Funds-Skyrocket-26percent-Gains-Beckon-But-Are-You-Ready-for-the-Wild-Ride/695776c64342f77179fab465</guid><description>In 2025, sectoral and thematic funds delivered exceptional returns, with Nifty PSU Bank, Metal, and Auto indices surging by approximately 26%, 24%, and 20% respectively, driven by favorable macroeconomics, demand recovery, and commodity price surges. However, experts warn of significant volatility due to concentrated exposure, recommending these funds only as satellite allocations within a diversified portfolio. Timing remains critical, and new investors are advised to stick to diversified equity funds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:32:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695776c64342f77179fab464_1767339788534.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Resumes Russian Oil Imports: Is India Defying US Scrutiny for Cheaper Fuel?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Reliance-Resumes-Russian-Oil-Imports-Is-India-Defying-US-Scrutiny-for-Cheaper-Fuel/695776714342f77179fab280</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Reliance-Resumes-Russian-Oil-Imports-Is-India-Defying-US-Scrutiny-for-Cheaper-Fuel/695776714342f77179fab280</guid><description>Reliance Industries Ltd. has resumed modest purchases of Russian crude oil, with three tankers carrying nearly 2.2 million barrels heading to its Jamnagar refinery for domestic fuel processing. This move follows a temporary pause due to increased US scrutiny but signals India's continued reliance on discounted Russian energy, despite geopolitical tensions and previous US criticism.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:29:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695776714342f77179fab27f_1767339699941.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Farmers SHOCKED: India's New Tobacco Tax Could Fuel Smuggling and Slash Income!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Farmers-SHOCKED-Indias-New-Tobacco-Tax-Could-Fuel-Smuggling-and-Slash-Income/695776ac4342f77179fab3ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Farmers-SHOCKED-Indias-New-Tobacco-Tax-Could-Fuel-Smuggling-and-Slash-Income/695776ac4342f77179fab3ba</guid><description>The Federation of All India Farmer Associations (FAIFA) warns that the recent excise duty hike on tobacco products will harm farmers' incomes and boost illegal trade. The increase, effective February 1, contradicts government assurances and could reduce demand for domestically grown tobacco, potentially leading to a crop surplus. FAIFA highlights a significant tax disparity between cigarette tobacco and beedis, urging the government to reconsider the duties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:29:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695776ac4342f77179fab3b9_1767339757661.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GST 2.0 Success: Auto &amp; FMCG Sectors Surge With Record Sales – What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/GST-20-Success-Auto-and-FMCG-Sectors-Surge-With-Record-Sales-Whats-Next/695775064342f77179faa985</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/GST-20-Success-Auto-and-FMCG-Sectors-Surge-With-Record-Sales-Whats-Next/695775064342f77179faa985</guid><description>Three months after GST 2.0, Indian automobile and FMCG companies are witnessing a rebound. Pent-up demand has surfaced, and companies expect stronger sales and volume growth in coming months as GST rate cut benefits are fully passed on. Key players like Tata Motors, Parle Products, and Nestle India report positive impacts and anticipate further growth driven by consumer demand and government infrastructure initiatives.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:25:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695775064342f77179faa984_1767339368950.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fintech Knight FinTech Secures $23.6 Million to Revolutionize Banking Infrastructure!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fintech-Knight-FinTech-Secures-236-Million-to-Revolutionize-Banking-Infrastructure/695775ca4342f77179faaeaa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fintech-Knight-FinTech-Secures-236-Million-to-Revolutionize-Banking-Infrastructure/695775ca4342f77179faaeaa</guid><description>Knight FinTech, an AI-based banking and lending infrastructure provider, has successfully raised $23.6 million (around INR 196 crore) in a Series A funding round led by Accel. The capital infusion, which the startup claims was at a 'soon-icorn' valuation, will fuel AI-first innovation in risk intelligence, automated credit underwriting, and data analytics. The funds will also support international expansion into the Middle East and Asia-Pacific. Knight FinTech serves over 85 financial institutions, having enabled over $7 billion in cumulative disbursements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:24:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695775ca4342f77179faaea9_1767339549736.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Agri-Tech Star Arya.ag Bags $81 Million! How They Stay Profitable While Global Crops Tumble?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Agri-Tech-Star-Aryaag-Bags-81-Million-How-They-Stay-Profitable-While-Global-Crops-Tumble/695773ee4342f77179faa15b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Agri-Tech-Star-Aryaag-Bags-81-Million-How-They-Stay-Profitable-While-Global-Crops-Tumble/695773ee4342f77179faa15b</guid><description>Indian agritech firm Arya.ag, offering farm-adjacent storage and lending, has secured $81 million in a Series D funding round led by GEF Capital Partners. The company remains profitable despite falling global commodity prices by avoiding direct commodity bets and using a model that absorbs price shocks. Arya.ag aggregates $3 billion in grain annually, facilitates $1.5 billion in loans with a bad loan rate below 0.5%, and plans to use the capital for technology scaling, aiming for an IPO within 18-20 months.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:19:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695773ee4342f77179faa15a_1767339099696.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>