<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:34 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India States' Deficit Jumps: Central Loans Mask Revenue Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-States-Deficit-Jumps-Central-Loans-Mask-Revenue-Strain/699eee8a04a25a58c854730e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-States-Deficit-Jumps-Central-Loans-Mask-Revenue-Strain/699eee8a04a25a58c854730e</guid><description>India's states are facing renewed fiscal pressure as their aggregate fiscal deficit climbed to 3.3% of GSDP in FY25, breaching the 3% mark for the first time in three years. This widening gap is significantly fueled by increased borrowing under the Centre's special assistance program for capital expenditure, masking underlying revenue strains from reduced GST compensation cess and lower central grants. While aggregate debt has moderated from pandemic peaks, it remains substantially above recommended levels, and a rising revenue deficit, coupled with increasing social sector spending, poses long-term fiscal challenges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KSB Limited Recommends ₹4.40 Final Dividend for FY25</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSB-Limited-Recommends-440-Final-Dividend-for-FY25/699eecf304a25a58c8547001</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSB-Limited-Recommends-440-Final-Dividend-for-FY25/699eecf304a25a58c8547001</guid><description>KSB Limited's board has proposed a final dividend of ₹4.40 per equity share for FY25, amounting to 220% of its face value. This recommendation is subject to shareholder approval at the upcoming Annual General Meeting (AGM) on May 20, 2026. The record date for determining eligible shareholders is set for May 8, 2026, marking a regular return of value to its investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Adobe at AI Crossroads: Valuation Squeeze Amidst Subscription Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Adobe-at-AI-Crossroads-Valuation-Squeeze-Amidst-Subscription-Strength/699eecf004a25a58c8546feb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Adobe-at-AI-Crossroads-Valuation-Squeeze-Amidst-Subscription-Strength/699eecf004a25a58c8546feb</guid><description>Adobe's long-standing dominance in creative software, built on a successful subscription model, is now being tested by the rapid advancement of generative AI. Despite robust revenue growth and a near-monopoly in professional creative tools, the company's stock is trading near multi-year lows, reflecting investor concerns about escalating competition from AI-native rivals and potential legal challenges related to AI training data. Analysts are split, with a 'Hold' consensus emerging as the market reassesses Adobe's ability to monetize its AI strategy effectively.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank: Governance Crisis Looms After ₹590 Cr Fraud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Governance-Crisis-Looms-After-590-Cr-Fraud/699eec0604a25a58c8546e0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Governance-Crisis-Looms-After-590-Cr-Fraud/699eec0604a25a58c8546e0a</guid><description>IDFC First Bank is grappling with the fallout from a ₹590 crore fraud, allegedly orchestrated by former employees and external parties. Four individuals have been arrested, including two ex-bankers and the owners of Swastik Desh Project, identified as the fund recipient. While the bank has repaid ₹583 crore to the Haryana government, the incident has triggered a significant market sell-off, erasing over ₹14,000 crore in market capitalization. Analysts highlight governance concerns and potential hits to profitability, even as the bank's fundamental performance remains robust. The situation demands a deep dive into internal controls and risk management protocols, potentially impacting future investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Green Energy Incorporates UAE Subsidiary for Renewable Power Generation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Adani-Green-Energy-Incorporates-UAE-Subsidiary-for-Renewable-Power-Generation/699eec0404a25a58c8546df3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Adani-Green-Energy-Incorporates-UAE-Subsidiary-for-Renewable-Power-Generation/699eec0404a25a58c8546df3</guid><description>Adani Green Energy Limited has incorporated a new wholly-owned subsidiary, Adani Renewable Energy Middle East Ltd (AREMEL), in the United Arab Emirates. The new entity will focus on generating power from renewable energy sources, marking AGEL's strategic expansion into the Middle East market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Orient Technologies Q3 Loss ₹15 Cr; New Govt Contract Adds ₹60 Cr Annual Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Orient-Technologies-Q3-Loss-15-Cr-New-Govt-Contract-Adds-60-Cr-Annual-Revenue/699eebff04a25a58c8546ddd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Orient-Technologies-Q3-Loss-15-Cr-New-Govt-Contract-Adds-60-Cr-Annual-Revenue/699eebff04a25a58c8546ddd</guid><description>Orient Technologies reported a net loss of Rs. 14.96 crore in Q3 FY26, impacted by global semiconductor shortages, supply chain disruptions, and the loss of a major telecom client. Despite the setback, the company secured a Rs. 60 crore annual managed services contract from Digital India Corporation and recorded 18.10% revenue growth for the first nine months of FY26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Signals Rate Stability Amid Inflation Concerns, Growth Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Signals-Rate-Stability-Amid-Inflation-Concerns-Growth-Focus/699eea2704a25a58c8546bc6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Signals-Rate-Stability-Amid-Inflation-Concerns-Growth-Focus/699eea2704a25a58c8546bc6</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee member, Saugata Bhattacharya, stated that benchmark interest rate hikes are 'negligible,' even with rising geopolitical inflation pressures. The central bank's policy of keeping the repo rate at 5.25% underscores a commitment to supporting economic growth, driven by strong domestic consumption and credit expansion. While inflation forecasts show a slight uptick towards 4% in H1 FY27 due to base effects and commodity prices, underlying inflation is seen as benign. Robust credit growth to corporates, mid-corporates, MSMEs, and NBFCs, alongside improving capacity utilization, supports this optimistic economic outlook. India's diversified export strategy also bolsters resilience against global trade uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:25:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eea2704a25a58c8546bc5_1772022586110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KSB Ltd Q3 FY26 Profit Rises 10.8%; Revenue Climbs 8.7% Amidst Labour Code Impact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSB-Ltd-Q3-FY26-Profit-Rises-108percent-Revenue-Climbs-87percent-Amidst-Labour-Code-Impact/699ee93104a25a58c85469ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSB-Ltd-Q3-FY26-Profit-Rises-108percent-Revenue-Climbs-87percent-Amidst-Labour-Code-Impact/699ee93104a25a58c85469ea</guid><description>KSB Limited reported a 10.81% year-on-year increase in consolidated quarterly profit for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹81 crore, on an 8.66% rise in revenue to ₹800.40 crore. The company also posted a full-year profit growth of 9.29%. However, a one-time charge of ₹25.50 crore for new labour codes impacted earnings, a factor investors will monitor.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kesoram Industries Open Offer: ₹2,378 Cr at ₹25/share Launched</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kesoram-Industries-Open-Offer-2378-Cr-at-25share-Launched/699ee8d404a25a58c85468b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kesoram-Industries-Open-Offer-2378-Cr-at-25share-Launched/699ee8d404a25a58c85468b2</guid><description>Kesoram Industries announced an open offer to acquire up to 95.54 crore shares at ₹25.00 each, valuing the total offer at ₹2,378.65 crore. The offer, which opened on February 25, 2026, provides a significant exit opportunity for public shareholders. This move follows Frontier Warehousing Limited's acquisition of a substantial promoter stake, signaling a change in the company's ownership structure. Kesoram Industries has historically been involved in cement, tire, and rayon businesses, with its cement division recently demerged into UltraTech Cement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Arbitration Law Gap Fuels Systemic Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Arbitration-Law-Gap-Fuels-Systemic-Risk/699ee8bb04a25a58c854687d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Arbitration-Law-Gap-Fuels-Systemic-Risk/699ee8bb04a25a58c854687d</guid><description>The Madras High Court has criticized the Central government for failing to notify key provisions of the 2019 Arbitration and Conciliation (Amendment) Act. This oversight has created a significant legislative vacuum, impeding the formal designation of arbitral institutions and forcing courts into a 'balancing act.' The absence of clear guidelines raises concerns about the integrity of arbitral awards and potentially allows financial entities to exploit ambiguities, impacting the efficiency of dispute resolution within the sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cipla Yurpeak Dominates Tier-2/3, But Faces Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Cipla-Yurpeak-Dominates-Tier-23-But-Faces-Headwinds/699ee86b04a25a58c85467a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Cipla-Yurpeak-Dominates-Tier-23-But-Faces-Headwinds/699ee86b04a25a58c85467a2</guid><description>Cipla's tirzepatide brand Yurpeak recorded robust ₹18.8 crore in January 2026 sales, exceeding expectations via aggressive tier-2/3 city penetration, a strategy contrasting with Eli Lilly's Mounjaro. While this expands access in India's growing chronic disease market, Cipla faces mixed analyst sentiment, mounting competitive pressures from semaglutide generics, and scrutiny over past regulatory issues. The company aims to leverage this momentum to deepen its focus on chronic and obesity care segments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank: Fraud Exposes Control Gaps Amid Premium Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Exposes-Control-Gaps-Amid-Premium-Valuation/699ee86804a25a58c854678b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Exposes-Control-Gaps-Amid-Premium-Valuation/699ee86804a25a58c854678b</guid><description>IDFC First Bank reported a ₹590 crore fraud at its Chandigarh branch, leading to a significant stock decline. While the bank repaid the affected Haryana government departments ₹583 crore and maintains strong capital buffers, the incident exposes critical internal control failures. The fraud's scale, exceeding quarterly profit, prompts scrutiny of operational risk management, especially given IDFC First Bank's premium valuation compared to sector peers. Investor confidence and the bank's ability to attract large deposits face ongoing challenges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tax Authorities Tighten Grip: 200% Penalty for 'Misreporting'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Tax-Authorities-Tighten-Grip-200percent-Penalty-for-Misreporting/699ee78d04a25a58c8546639</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Tax-Authorities-Tighten-Grip-200percent-Penalty-for-Misreporting/699ee78d04a25a58c8546639</guid><description>A recent ruling by the Income Tax Appellate Tribunal (ITAT) Pune has reinforced the severe consequences of income misreporting, upholding a 200% penalty on a salaried individual for claiming Rs 10.65 lakh in unsubstantiated deductions. The decision underscores that paying the tax demand post-detection is insufficient to escape penalties when deliberate misrepresentation is established, reflecting a broader trend of intensified tax enforcement driven by advanced data analytics.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Scoda Tubes Expands Welded Pipes Capacity by 8,000 MTPA with ₹400M Investment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Scoda-Tubes-Expands-Welded-Pipes-Capacity-by-8000-MTPA-with-400M-Investment/699ee68104a25a58c85464ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Scoda-Tubes-Expands-Welded-Pipes-Capacity-by-8000-MTPA-with-400M-Investment/699ee68104a25a58c85464ae</guid><description>Scoda Tubes Limited is set to significantly boost its manufacturing capabilities with a proposed expansion of 8,000 MTPA for its Welded Tubes &amp; Pipes segment. The company plans to invest ₹400 million in this project at its Mehsana, Gujarat facility, targeting completion by the end of Q3 FY2026-27. This strategic move aims to strengthen its product offerings and market position by better addressing customer demand.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Price Surges Past $5,200 as Banks Raise 2026 Forecasts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Price-Surges-Past-5200-as-Banks-Raise-2026-Forecasts/699ee34904a25a58c854614e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Price-Surges-Past-5200-as-Banks-Raise-2026-Forecasts/699ee34904a25a58c854614e</guid><description>JPMorgan and Macquarie have substantially boosted their gold price projections for 2026, now eyeing $4,500 per ounce and higher long-term, driven by aggressive central bank accumulation and a structural shift away from dollar dominance. This bullish sentiment is supported by recent strong performance in spot gold, which has surged approximately 20% year-to-date. These revisions reflect a broader market trend anticipating sustained demand due to evolving global financial dynamics and geopolitical uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Suryoday SFB Plans ₹1,000 Cr Raise Amid NPA Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Suryoday-SFB-Plans-1000-Cr-Raise-Amid-NPA-Rise/699ee23b04a25a58c8545f43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Suryoday-SFB-Plans-1000-Cr-Raise-Amid-NPA-Rise/699ee23b04a25a58c8545f43</guid><description>Suryoday Small Finance Bank is proposing a significant ₹1,000 crore capital raise through shareholder approval, positioning it for future growth. The bank reported a 9.6% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹36.5 crore in Q3 FY26, with Net Interest Income up 3.2%. However, asset quality showed deterioration, with gross NPAs rising to 4.35% sequentially. Despite this, the bank maintains strong capitalization, with its CRAR at 21.9% as of December 31, 2025, well above regulatory minimums.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:51:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ee23b04a25a58c8545f42_1772020971082.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shaily Engineering Plastics Secures ₹423 Cr Order, Eyes Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shaily-Engineering-Plastics-Secures-423-Cr-Order-Eyes-Global-Expansion/699ee23604a25a58c8545f23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shaily-Engineering-Plastics-Secures-423-Cr-Order-Eyes-Global-Expansion/699ee23604a25a58c8545f23</guid><description>Shaily Engineering Plastics secured a substantial ₹423 crore, four-year manufacturing and supply agreement for pen injectors from an undisclosed domestic pharmaceutical firm. This follows the appointment of Joe Kam as COO (Healthcare) and a planned AED 130-150 million medical device facility in Abu Dhabi. The company's stock closed marginally down on February 25, 2026, at ₹1,941.50.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:51:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India CSR Spending Surge Faces Measurement Dilemmas</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-CSR-Spending-Surge-Faces-Measurement-Dilemmas/699ee1d204a25a58c8545e1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-CSR-Spending-Surge-Faces-Measurement-Dilemmas/699ee1d204a25a58c8545e1e</guid><description>India's Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) expenditure is projected to surpass ₹1.2 lakh crore annually by 2035, signaling a strategic pivot towards 'systemic giving'—funding initiatives that strengthen public systems for scalable, lasting impact. While this approach promises amplified social returns and leveraging corporate funds as risk capital for development, significant challenges persist in rigorously measuring long-term outcomes and mitigating 'impact washing,' necessitating enhanced accountability frameworks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Binance Probed Again: Iran Fund Allegations Spark Regulatory Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Binance-Probed-Again-Iran-Fund-Allegations-Spark-Regulatory-Fears/699ee1c604a25a58c8545df9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Binance-Probed-Again-Iran-Fund-Allegations-Spark-Regulatory-Fears/699ee1c604a25a58c8545df9</guid><description>U.S. Senator Richard Blumenthal has launched an investigation into cryptocurrency exchange Binance over allegations of facilitating over $1.7 billion in transfers to Iran-linked organizations. This probe intensifies scrutiny on Binance's compliance mechanisms, particularly in light of internal investigators who flagged these issues and were subsequently dismissed. The exchange vehemently denies the claims, citing existing KYC procedures. This development re-ignites concerns following Binance's substantial $4.3 billion settlement for past anti-money laundering and sanctions violations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>US Solar Tariffs Hit Indian Stocks; Companies Pivot Strategies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/US-Solar-Tariffs-Hit-Indian-Stocks-Companies-Pivot-Strategies/699edfb204a25a58c8545a41</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/US-Solar-Tariffs-Hit-Indian-Stocks-Companies-Pivot-Strategies/699edfb204a25a58c8545a41</guid><description>US preliminary countervailing duties of 126% on Indian solar imports triggered sharp sell-offs in Waaree Energies, Premier Energies, and Vikram Solar on February 25, 2026. Waaree Energies, with higher export exposure, is leveraging its US manufacturing and diversified supply chains. Premier Energies, largely insulated by its domestic focus, sees minimal direct impact. This event underscores the strategic importance of supply chain resilience and localized production amidst escalating global trade tensions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Himadri Expands Specialty Carbon Black Output, Targets Global Leadership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Himadri-Expands-Specialty-Carbon-Black-Output-Targets-Global-Leadership/699edf9f04a25a58c8545a02</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Himadri-Expands-Specialty-Carbon-Black-Output-Targets-Global-Leadership/699edf9f04a25a58c8545a02</guid><description>Himadri Speciality Chemical has commissioned a new 70,000 tonnes per annum (TPA) specialty carbon black line at its Hooghly facility, elevating its total capacity to 2.50 lakh TPA and making it the world's largest single-location specialty carbon black manufacturing site. This expansion targets high-value applications, signaling a strategic move towards premium segments and enhanced margin potential, as the company seeks to capture rising global demand for customized carbon solutions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Accedere Ltd Pivots to AI-Driven GRC with Controllo.ai Launch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Accedere-Ltd-Pivots-to-AI-Driven-GRC-with-Controlloai-Launch/699edee004a25a58c8545816</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Accedere-Ltd-Pivots-to-AI-Driven-GRC-with-Controlloai-Launch/699edee004a25a58c8545816</guid><description>Accedere Ltd, formerly E.com Infotech India Ltd, is repositioning itself as an AI-driven leader in cybersecurity and regulatory compliance with the launch of its AI-powered Governance, Risk, and Compliance (GRC) platform, "Controllo.ai". This strategic pivot aims to capitalize on evolving IT trends and the growing demand for AI solutions in compliance management, especially with upcoming DPDPA regulations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cricket Fuels Tier-2 Travel Boom for Airbnb</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Cricket-Fuels-Tier-2-Travel-Boom-for-Airbnb/699ede9804a25a58c85456fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Cricket-Fuels-Tier-2-Travel-Boom-for-Airbnb/699ede9804a25a58c85456fc</guid><description>Major cricket tournaments, including the ICC T20 World Cup and IPL, are transforming India's travel patterns. Online accommodation platform Airbnb reports substantial year-on-year growth in searches for match-hosting cities, particularly beyond metropolitan hubs like Ranchi and Thiruvananthapuram. This trend highlights a decentralization of demand, with travelers, especially Gen Z, prioritizing experiential stays and longer durations, extending trips to explore local culture and cuisine, thereby boosting economies in emerging destinations. The surge indicates a broader shift towards experience-led travel, positioning Airbnb to capitalize on event-driven demand in tier-2 and tier-3 cities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>LT Foods Credit Rating Upgraded to AA/Stable by CRISIL on Strong Financials</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/LT-Foods-Credit-Rating-Upgraded-to-AAStable-by-CRISIL-on-Strong-Financials/699ede6c04a25a58c85456cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/LT-Foods-Credit-Rating-Upgraded-to-AAStable-by-CRISIL-on-Strong-Financials/699ede6c04a25a58c85456cd</guid><description>CRISIL has upgraded LT Foods' long-term credit rating to 'AA/Stable' and reaffirmed its short-term rating at 'A1+'. This upgrade reflects the company's sustained improvement in its business risk profile and robust financial health, underpinned by a strong market position, diversified geographic presence, and established distribution network. The total rated bank loan facilities stand at Rs.880 Crore.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ede6c04a25a58c85456cc_1772019773324.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRFC Locks USD 400M Loan From Japanese Banks For Rail Projects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IRFC-Locks-USD-400M-Loan-From-Japanese-Banks-For-Rail-Projects/699ede6c04a25a58c85456b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IRFC-Locks-USD-400M-Loan-From-Japanese-Banks-For-Rail-Projects/699ede6c04a25a58c85456b7</guid><description>Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) has secured an External Commercial Borrowing (ECB) facility of USD 400 million (JPY equivalent) from a consortium of Japanese banks. This marks the company's second such borrowing in FY25-26, following a USD 300 million loan in December 2025. The funds are earmarked for financing railway sector projects, aiming to optimize borrowing costs and expand IRFC's global capital market engagement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ede6c04a25a58c85456b6_1772019503687.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta Ratings Reaffirmed AA (Watch Developing), A1+ by CRISIL</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedanta-Ratings-Reaffirmed-AA-Watch-Developing-A1-by-CRISIL/699eddf604a25a58c85455d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedanta-Ratings-Reaffirmed-AA-Watch-Developing-A1-by-CRISIL/699eddf604a25a58c85455d5</guid><description>CRISIL has reaffirmed Vedanta Limited's long-term credit rating at 'CRISIL AA' and its short-term rating at 'CRISIL A1+'. However, the long-term rating continues to carry a 'Watch Developing' status, signaling potential for future rating changes. This action pertains to the company's bank facilities and Non-Convertible Debentures. The 'Watch Developing' tag indicates uncertainty and ongoing review by CRISIL regarding Vedanta's financial health and business outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Credent Global Finance Q3 Profit Surges 3773% to ₹18 Cr; Raises ₹30 Cr Via QIP</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Credent-Global-Finance-Q3-Profit-Surges-3773percent-to-18-Cr-Raises-30-Cr-Via-QIP/699edd0404a25a58c8545423</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Credent-Global-Finance-Q3-Profit-Surges-3773percent-to-18-Cr-Raises-30-Cr-Via-QIP/699edd0404a25a58c8545423</guid><description>Credent Global Finance Limited has successfully raised ₹30 crore through a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) to bolster its growth capital. The company also reported a stellar Q3FY26 performance, with profit after tax soaring by 3,773% year-on-year to ₹18.02 crore, driven by a 775% surge in revenue. The strengthening of its leadership team with Vikas Kataria's appointment as Executive Director further supports its expansion strategy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bagmane REIT Bets on India's Urbanization Amidst Cautious IPO Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bagmane-REIT-Bets-on-Indias-Urbanization-Amidst-Cautious-IPO-Market/699edc4a04a25a58c85452f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bagmane-REIT-Bets-on-Indias-Urbanization-Amidst-Cautious-IPO-Market/699edc4a04a25a58c85452f0</guid><description>Bagmane Prime Office REIT is pursuing a $3.9 billion IPO, aiming to raise ₹40 billion ($440 million) through a combination of new units and a secondary sale by Blackstone. The move occurs despite a cautious Indian IPO market in early 2026, driven by developer confidence in sustained demand fueled by urbanization. Bagmane REIT's substantial Grade A+ portfolio and Blackstone's extensive experience provide a strong foundation for this contrarian strategy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sutlej Textiles Appoints Narinder Thapa as Protech Business Chief</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sutlej-Textiles-Appoints-Narinder-Thapa-as-Protech-Business-Chief/699edc1004a25a58c8545267</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sutlej-Textiles-Appoints-Narinder-Thapa-as-Protech-Business-Chief/699edc1004a25a58c8545267</guid><description>Sutlej Textiles and Industries Limited announced the appointment of Shri Narinder Thapa as Chief Business Officer for its Protech Business, effective February 25, 2026. Thapa brings over three decades of experience in protective garments marketing, operations, product innovation, and supply chain management. This strategic move aims to bolster the company's expertise in the growing technical textiles sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:25:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699edc1004a25a58c8545266_1772019479363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ather Energy Eyes Premium Segment, Cedes Entry-Level Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ather-Energy-Eyes-Premium-Segment-Cedes-Entry-Level-Share/699edb9f04a25a58c85451b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ather-Energy-Eyes-Premium-Segment-Cedes-Entry-Level-Share/699edb9f04a25a58c85451b2</guid><description>Ather Energy is drawing a line at the ₹1 lakh price point for its electric scooters, signaling a strategic choice to forgo the mass-market entry-level segment. CEO Tarun Mehta views this as a measure to avoid 'bloodletting' from price wars, particularly given Ather's cost disadvantage against competitors benefiting from Production Linked Incentives (PLI). The company is reinvesting heavily in R&amp;D, charging infrastructure, and intellectual property, framing this as long-term investment rather than pure cash burn. Profitability is targeted through gross margins exceeding 20%, with operating leverage from increased volumes expected to drive earnings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699edb9f04a25a58c85451b1_1772019111453.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Veerhealth Care ₹33 Cr Raise for USFDA Push; Revenue Jumps 22%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Veerhealth-Care-33-Cr-Raise-for-USFDA-Push-Revenue-Jumps-22percent/699eda3204a25a58c8544f59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Veerhealth-Care-33-Cr-Raise-for-USFDA-Push-Revenue-Jumps-22percent/699eda3204a25a58c8544f59</guid><description>Veerhealth Care Ltd. reported a 22% rise in FY25 revenue to ₹17.89 crore, though Profit After Tax saw a marginal dip to ₹0.39 crore. The company plans a ₹33 crore fundraising via Rights Issue and Term Loan to fund expansion, including land, building, and machinery. A key development is the USFDA approval for OTC products, paving the way for exports to the US market and signaling a significant growth phase.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:17:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699eda3204a25a58c8544f58_1772018467760.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BLT Logistics ventures into renewables with new subsidiary</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BLT-Logistics-ventures-into-renewables-with-new-subsidiary/699ed9d604a25a58c8544e9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BLT-Logistics-ventures-into-renewables-with-new-subsidiary/699ed9d604a25a58c8544e9e</guid><description>BLT Logistics Limited has established a new wholly-owned subsidiary, BLT Renewable Energy Private Limited, signalling a strategic diversification into the burgeoning renewable energy sector. The subsidiary will focus on Compressed Bio-Gas (CBG), biogas plants, and other sustainable energy projects, leveraging BLT's logistics expertise for this expansion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Market: Sales Soar, Profits Stumble; Large Caps Gain Favor</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Market-Sales-Soar-Profits-Stumble-Large-Caps-Gain-Favor/699ed95d04a25a58c8544d9f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Market-Sales-Soar-Profits-Stumble-Large-Caps-Gain-Favor/699ed95d04a25a58c8544d9f</guid><description>Indian equities are in a prolonged consolidation phase. While Q3FY26 saw record sales growth for NSE500 companies, profit growth moderated significantly, heavily reliant on oil, gas, and financials. Analysts are flagging high EPS downgrade risks for small-caps, shifting preference towards large-caps. Goldman Sachs highlights a global 'HALO effect' favoring capital-intensive companies, a trend aligning with India's manufacturing rebound. New labor codes are also introducing compliance costs impacting profitability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:13:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ed95d04a25a58c8544d9e_1772018118503.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCS Surge Eyed: CLSA Sees 33% Upside Amid SaaS Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Surge-Eyed-CLSA-Sees-33percent-Upside-Amid-SaaS-Boom/699ed94e04a25a58c8544d88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Surge-Eyed-CLSA-Sees-33percent-Upside-Amid-SaaS-Boom/699ed94e04a25a58c8544d88</guid><description>CLSA initiated 'Outperform' on Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) with a ₹3,593 target, projecting a 33.7% upside. The bullish call hinges on robust Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) implementation demand and strong guidance from strategic partner ServiceNow, which forecasts 19.5%-20% growth for FY26. CLSA also factors in a potential share buyback. The IT services sector, however, faces mounting concerns over AI disruption and competitive intensity. TCS's valuation is based on a blended P/E (23x) and DCF approach, with estimated FY26 revenue of ₹2.65 lakh crore.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiger Logistics Q3 FY26: Volume Soars 52% YoY, Revenue Dips Amid Low Freight Rates</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Tiger-Logistics-Q3-FY26-Volume-Soars-52percent-YoY-Revenue-Dips-Amid-Low-Freight-Rates/699ed85104a25a58c8544c45</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Tiger-Logistics-Q3-FY26-Volume-Soars-52percent-YoY-Revenue-Dips-Amid-Low-Freight-Rates/699ed85104a25a58c8544c45</guid><description>Tiger Logistics reported a 52% year-on-year surge in cargo volumes for Q3 FY26, driven by strong demand in sectors like auto and pharma. However, revenue saw a dip due to historically low global freight rates affecting its cost-plus model. New initiatives like the TiGreen solar logistics vertical are performing well, with the CUBOX LCL service reaching break-even, signalling strategic growth avenues despite market headwinds. Management anticipates tailwinds from settling US trade tariffs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:09:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ed85104a25a58c8544c44_1772017896686.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shopsy's Rural Bet: Zero Commission Faces Tough India Market Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Shopsys-Rural-Bet-Zero-Commission-Faces-Tough-India-Market-Test/699ed59c04a25a58c8544636</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Shopsys-Rural-Bet-Zero-Commission-Faces-Tough-India-Market-Test/699ed59c04a25a58c8544636</guid><description>Flipkart's Shopsy is aggressively expanding into India's Tier-2, -3, and -4 cities and rural markets, targeting first-time online shoppers. The platform champions a zero-commission model for sellers, generating revenue through advertising and shipping charges. This strategy aims to capture value-seeking consumers, particularly Gen Z, by offering competitive pricing and quality. However, the expansion faces significant challenges including complex logistics in underserved regions and intense competition from players like Meesho and Amazon, while profitability hinges on advertising uptake and user acquisition costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:57:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ed59c04a25a58c8544635_1772017396959.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Global EV Hub Status Via FTAs, Strategic Sourcing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Eyes-Global-EV-Hub-Status-Via-FTAs-Strategic-Sourcing/699ed51304a25a58c8544485</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Eyes-Global-EV-Hub-Status-Via-FTAs-Strategic-Sourcing/699ed51304a25a58c8544485</guid><description>India is strategically leveraging its expanding network of Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) to propel electric vehicle (EV) exports and establish itself as a global manufacturing hub. This initiative, aligned with national self-reliance goals and net-zero targets, emphasizes industrial strategy, critical mineral sourcing, and building future-proof supply chains. The goal is to capture a significant share of the projected trillion-dollar global EV market through enhanced domestic production and localization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:55:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ed51304a25a58c8544484_1772017588888.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Diversification Study: Unpacking Risk vs. Reward Trade-offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Diversification-Study-Unpacking-Risk-vs-Reward-Trade-offs/699ed4fa04a25a58c85443fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Diversification-Study-Unpacking-Risk-vs-Reward-Trade-offs/699ed4fa04a25a58c85443fd</guid><description>WhiteOak Capital's February 2026 "Chemistry of Investing" study, analyzing data from September 2001 to January 2026, quantifies the impact of asset allocation on portfolio risk and return. Findings show modest equity allocations can enhance risk-adjusted returns without substantially increasing volatility. However, as equity exposure grows, so do both returns and volatility. The inclusion of gold provides downside support and can improve overall portfolio efficiency. The analysis emphasizes that while diversification is key to long-term goals, the dynamic nature of economic cycles necessitates a nuanced approach beyond historical correlations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:54:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ed4fa04a25a58c85443fc_1772018507139.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Capital: Capital Boost Meets Market Skepticism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tata-Capital-Capital-Boost-Meets-Market-Skepticism/699ed4f804a25a58c85443e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tata-Capital-Capital-Boost-Meets-Market-Skepticism/699ed4f804a25a58c85443e6</guid><description>Tata Capital Ltd. reported a strong 19.7% quarter-on-quarter net profit increase to ₹790 crore for Q3 FY26, alongside a 44% surge in net interest income. Concurrently, its housing finance arm, TCHFL, approved a ₹650.02 crore rights issue from its parent. Despite these positive indicators, the company's stock has shown muted performance post-IPO, trading slightly above its issue price, suggesting underlying investor caution amidst evolving regulatory and credit market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Auto Sector Roars: Demand Surge Meets Capacity Wall</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Sector-Roars-Demand-Surge-Meets-Capacity-Wall/699ed4d304a25a58c85443af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Sector-Roars-Demand-Surge-Meets-Capacity-Wall/699ed4d304a25a58c85443af</guid><description>India's automotive sector is experiencing a robust, broad-based demand upcycle anticipated to persist through fiscal year 2027. While passenger vehicles, two-wheelers, commercial vehicles, and tractors are all poised for double-digit growth, significant capacity constraints, particularly at Maruti Suzuki, threaten to cap production. The burgeoning electric vehicle segment continues to see market share shifts, with TVS Motors leading the charge. Upcoming factors like the eighth Pay Commission could further fuel demand, especially for passenger vehicles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>