<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:41 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Silver's Surge Risks Collision With Solar Demand Destruction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silvers-Surge-Risks-Collision-With-Solar-Demand-Destruction/698d582dba46a4833be0f219</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silvers-Surge-Risks-Collision-With-Solar-Demand-Destruction/698d582dba46a4833be0f219</guid><description>Silver prices have surged dramatically, reaching record highs driven by a convergence of speculative buying, its essential role in solar technology, and a broad market deficit. However, this rally is shadowed by the very demand driver that propelled it: the solar industry's relentless pursuit of efficiency. Aggressive efforts to reduce silver content per solar panel, coupled with debates around peak solar installations, point towards a significant potential for demand destruction, creating a stark contrast with current price levels.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Carrier's India Export Play: AI Hype Meets Valuation Doubts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carriers-India-Export-Play-AI-Hype-Meets-Valuation-Doubts/698d57efba46a4833be0f20e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carriers-India-Export-Play-AI-Hype-Meets-Valuation-Doubts/698d57efba46a4833be0f20e</guid><description>Carrier Global is strategically positioning India as a manufacturing base for developed markets, leveraging AI's influence on global supply chains. However, this ambitious pivot is met with a divided analyst consensus, including a recent 'strong sell' rating alongside multiple 'buy' recommendations, and significant operational challenges. Carrier's substantial debt load and the practical integration of AI in HVAC systems add layers of complexity to this strategic shift.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Pushes for IP Watchlist Exit Amid Trade Deal Talks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Pushes-for-IP-Watchlist-Exit-Amid-Trade-Deal-Talks/698d579eba46a4833be0f1e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Pushes-for-IP-Watchlist-Exit-Amid-Trade-Deal-Talks/698d579eba46a4833be0f1e0</guid><description>Indian industry representatives are actively petitioning the U.S. Trade Representative (USTR) to remove India from its Priority Watch List, citing comprehensive IP reforms and strategic cooperation. While India demonstrates robust growth in IP filings, ranking high globally in patent and trademark applications, persistent US concerns regarding patent protection, enforcement effectiveness, and market access remain. These issues, highlighted in annual USTR reports, continue to influence bilateral trade dynamics and India's broader investment appeal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kallam Textiles Faces Insolvency Threat as Union Bank Files NCLT Plea</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Kallam-Textiles-Faces-Insolvency-Threat-as-Union-Bank-Files-NCLT-Plea/698d56fdba46a4833be0eaff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Kallam-Textiles-Faces-Insolvency-Threat-as-Union-Bank-Files-NCLT-Plea/698d56fdba46a4833be0eaff</guid><description>Kallam Textiles Limited disclosed receipt of an application from Union Bank of India to the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), potentially triggering insolvency proceedings. The filing, case number C.P. (IB)/3(AM)2026, marks a significant legal development, with a hearing scheduled for February 11, 2026. The company has assured further updates on material developments, leaving investors to await the outcome of this critical legal challenge.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Surplus Surge Amid Leverage Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Surplus-Surge-Amid-Leverage-Fears/698d565cba46a4833be0e935</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Surplus-Surge-Amid-Leverage-Fears/698d565cba46a4833be0e935</guid><description>India's trade surplus with the United States is projected to expand significantly following a new trade agreement, yet a substantial $500 billion import commitment from India, coupled with lingering US tariffs and asymmetrical trade terms, introduces notable risks. While Indian exports may see a boost, concerns persist regarding potential currency depreciation, a widening trade deficit, and the US retaining strategic leverage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KSH International Revenue Soars 59%, PAT Dips on One-Offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Revenue-Soars-59percent-PAT-Dips-on-One-Offs/698d55fbba46a4833be0e865</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Revenue-Soars-59percent-PAT-Dips-on-One-Offs/698d55fbba46a4833be0e865</guid><description>KSH International reported a robust 59% YoY revenue growth to INR 818 Crores for Q3 FY'26, driven by strong demand in the T&amp;D sector and capacity expansion. However, Profit After Tax (PAT) declined 9% YoY to INR 23 Crores, impacted by INR 8.1 Crores in one-off expenses. Despite the quarterly dip, 9-month PAT surged 53% YoY to INR 75.6 Crores. The company is strategically expanding capacity and diversifying into EVs, with significant deleveraging demonstrated by a Debt-to-Equity ratio improving to 0.42x.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:24:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nuvama's Top Picks: BPCL, Power Grid, SAIL Eye Gains; Nifty Charts Bullish Pattern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nuvamas-Top-Picks-BPCL-Power-Grid-SAIL-Eye-Gains-Nifty-Charts-Bullish-Pattern/698d55f4ba46a4833be0e81f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nuvamas-Top-Picks-BPCL-Power-Grid-SAIL-Eye-Gains-Nifty-Charts-Bullish-Pattern/698d55f4ba46a4833be0e81f</guid><description>Nuvama Professional Clients Group's Aakash K Hindocha has identified BPCL, Power Grid Corporation of India, and Steel Authority of India Ltd (SAIL) as top buy recommendations for February 12, 2026. BPCL targets ₹418, Power Grid ₹320, and SAIL ₹174, driven by sector tailwinds and technical breakouts. Nifty is forming a bullish inverted head and shoulder pattern above 25,940, while Bank Nifty continues its outperformance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tanfac Industries Hits Record FY25 Revenue, Eyes R-32 Gas Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Tanfac-Industries-Hits-Record-FY25-Revenue-Eyes-R-32-Gas-Boom/698d5561ba46a4833be0e79e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Tanfac-Industries-Hits-Record-FY25-Revenue-Eyes-R-32-Gas-Boom/698d5561ba46a4833be0e79e</guid><description>Tanfac Industries has posted its highest-ever revenue from operations for FY25, reaching ₹556.98 Crores, a significant 47% year-on-year increase. Profit After Tax (PAT) also hit a record ₹88.15 Crores, up 68% year-on-year, with EBITDA at ₹128.88 Crores and a 23.14% margin. The company successfully commissioned a new Hydrofluoric Acid (HF) plant and two phases of its Solar Grade Dilute Hydrofluoric Acid (DHF) facility, securing over ₹1,000 Crores in long-term agreements. A major strategic move includes a ₹495 Crores investment in a Refrigerant Gas (R-32) manufacturing facility, backed by a ~₹2,362 Crores supply deal with a Japanese customer. However, Q3FY26 results showed EBITDA margins compressing to 14.94% due to rising input costs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Elgi Equipments Q3 Revenue Jumps 18%, Net Profit Rises Amidst Expense Management</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Elgi-Equipments-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-18percent-Net-Profit-Rises-Amidst-Expense-Management/698d5340ba46a4833be0e5f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Elgi-Equipments-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-18percent-Net-Profit-Rises-Amidst-Expense-Management/698d5340ba46a4833be0e5f9</guid><description>Elgi Equipments Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue surging 18% YoY to ₹10,034 Mn. Profit After Tax (PAT) climbed 18.1% YoY to ₹952 Mn, and Earnings Per Share (EPS) grew 18.4% to ₹3.02. EBITDA saw a 17.1% YoY increase to ₹1,440 Mn, with margins remaining largely stable at 14.4%. The company significantly boosted its net cash position to ₹6,058 Mn, up from ₹3,627 Mn year-on-year, underscoring financial strengthening.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Promoter Sale Hits Netweb Amid AI Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Promoter-Sale-Hits-Netweb-Amid-AI-Growth/698d5246ba46a4833be0e39f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Promoter-Sale-Hits-Netweb-Amid-AI-Growth/698d5246ba46a4833be0e39f</guid><description>Netweb Technologies India Ltd. experienced a significant block trade on February 12, 2026, involving 23.32 lakh shares (3.93% equity) valued at ₹682.3 crore. This large transaction, foreshadowed by earlier promoter sale intentions, introduces a short-term overhang. Despite this, the company's third-quarter financials reveal a substantial 140% revenue increase to ₹804 crore and EBITDA growth to ₹97.5 crore, driven by robust demand for AI systems, even as the stock saw a modest dip.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JPMorgan Downgrades Vodafone Idea to 'Underweight', Cites Funding Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/JPMorgan-Downgrades-Vodafone-Idea-to-Underweight-Cites-Funding-Gap/698d5243ba46a4833be0e372</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/JPMorgan-Downgrades-Vodafone-Idea-to-Underweight-Cites-Funding-Gap/698d5243ba46a4833be0e372</guid><description>JPMorgan has downgraded Vodafone Idea (VIL) to 'Underweight,' setting a ₹9 price target and signaling a 23% downside risk. The brokerage highlights VIL's crucial, yet unreceived, bank funding required for its next capex cycle, essential for stemming subscriber losses. This move comes as VIL's own aggressive targets for EBITDA growth appear increasingly challenging against market leaders Bharti Airtel and Reliance Jio, which continue to gain subscribers and ARPU.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:08:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d5243ba46a4833be0e371_1770869631118.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Stocks Tumble, Market Pauses Rally Amid AI Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IT-Stocks-Tumble-Market-Pauses-Rally-Amid-AI-Shift/698d5151ba46a4833be0e0b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IT-Stocks-Tumble-Market-Pauses-Rally-Amid-AI-Shift/698d5151ba46a4833be0e0b0</guid><description>Benchmark Indian indices opened in the red on Thursday, snapping a recent rally as IT stocks experienced a sharp sell-off. Infosys shed 4%, dragging the broader market lower, amidst concerns over sector outlook and muted FY26 growth forecasts. While near-term headwinds persist, the accelerating adoption of artificial intelligence remains a key long-term driver for the sector's future.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:04:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Zydus Pays $120M for US Generic Myrbetriq Access</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Pays-120M-for-US-Generic-Myrbetriq-Access/698d50eeba46a4833be0e00f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Pays-120M-for-US-Generic-Myrbetriq-Access/698d50eeba46a4833be0e00f</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences and its US subsidiary have agreed to a $120 million upfront settlement with Astellas Pharma, plus ongoing licensing fees until September 2027, to resolve patent litigation over generic Mirabegron (Myrbetriq). This accord allows Zydus to continue marketing its generic in the crucial US market, a move that underscores the high cost of market access and potential margin pressures in the competitive pharmaceutical sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DevX's Landmark Ahmedabad Deal Signals Tier-II Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/DevXs-Landmark-Ahmedabad-Deal-Signals-Tier-II-Shift/698d50edba46a4833be0dfea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/DevXs-Landmark-Ahmedabad-Deal-Signals-Tier-II-Shift/698d50edba46a4833be0dfea</guid><description>DevX Accelerator has finalized a landmark deal for an entire 27-storey office tower in Ahmedabad, valued at over ₹850 crore in total rentals. This transaction, the largest coworking deal in India structured as a Development Management (DM) agreement, signifies a strategic pivot towards Tier-II cities and caters to burgeoning demand from Global Capability Centers (GCCs) and enterprises seeking managed workspace solutions. The 8 lakh sq ft facility is slated for completion in 2.5 to 3 years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:02:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>LG India Profit Plummets 62%, But Analysts See 23% Upside</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Profit-Plummets-62percent-But-Analysts-See-23percent-Upside/698d4fcfba46a4833be0de0d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Profit-Plummets-62percent-But-Analysts-See-23percent-Upside/698d4fcfba46a4833be0de0d</guid><description>LG Electronics India posted a 61.6% net profit decline to ₹89.7 crore in Q3FY26, with revenue falling 6.4% due to subdued demand and margin compression. Despite these operational headwinds, domestic broker Motilal Oswal maintained its 'Buy' rating, projecting a 17% upside, and other analysts show a 'Strong Buy' consensus with higher price targets, anticipating a recovery driven by market leadership and product innovation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Settles Mirabegron Patent Case for $120M</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Settles-Mirabegron-Patent-Case-for-120M/698d4fccba46a4833be0de05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Settles-Mirabegron-Patent-Case-for-120M/698d4fccba46a4833be0de05</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences and its U.S. unit have agreed to a $120 million settlement with Astellas Pharma to resolve patent litigation concerning the bladder disorder drug Mirabegron. The deal also includes ongoing per-unit licensing fees on generic Mirabegron sales in the U.S. through September 2027. This resolution provides market access but introduces significant costs, potentially affecting Zydus's profit margins in the competitive generics market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GRSE's Pipeline Deluge: Growth Risks Amidst Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/GRSEs-Pipeline-Deluge-Growth-Risks-Amidst-Expansion/698d4d87ba46a4833be0db76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/GRSEs-Pipeline-Deluge-Growth-Risks-Amidst-Expansion/698d4d87ba46a4833be0db76</guid><description>Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers (GRSE) posted a robust 74% net profit jump in Q3 FY26, fueled by a 49% revenue increase and improved operating efficiencies. Its order book stands at Rs 18,482 crore, providing strong revenue visibility. However, the company faces a colossal Rs 1.55 lakh crore RFP pipeline over the next 12 months, demanding aggressive capacity expansion and introducing substantial execution risks alongside diversification into new defense hardware.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tax System Shift: Declining Refunds Signal Efficiency</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tax-System-Shift-Declining-Refunds-Signal-Efficiency/698d4cc7ba46a4833be0db42</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tax-System-Shift-Declining-Refunds-Signal-Efficiency/698d4cc7ba46a4833be0db42</guid><description>Income tax refunds in India have seen a notable contraction, declining by approximately 17% in the current fiscal year. This moderation is not indicative of administrative bottlenecks but rather a systemic shift towards greater accuracy in tax collection and a reduction in overpayments. Officials attribute this trend to rationalized TDS provisions, increased adoption of the new tax regime, and sophisticated data analytics flagging incorrect claims earlier in the process. This evolution points to a more efficient tax administration aligning payments more closely with final liabilities, a move consistent with global trends in tax governance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Financial: Strong Earnings Met by Regulatory Storm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Max-Financial-Strong-Earnings-Met-by-Regulatory-Storm/698d4b78ba46a4833be0d8f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Max-Financial-Strong-Earnings-Met-by-Regulatory-Storm/698d4b78ba46a4833be0d8f4</guid><description>Max Financial Services delivered an impressive December quarter with APE growth of 30% and VNB growth of 34%, exceeding market expectations. VNB margins also expanded to 24.1%. However, the company faces significant headwinds from a newly proposed RBI framework set to restrict bank-led distribution of insurance products, potentially impacting its reliance on bancassurance channels. Analysts maintain a 'Buy' rating but the regulatory outlook introduces substantial uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Black Box Q3 PAT Falls 11%, Guidance Cut, Eyes Brazil Buy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Black-Box-Q3-PAT-Falls-11percent-Guidance-Cut-Eyes-Brazil-Buy/698d4b25ba46a4833be0d8eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Black-Box-Q3-PAT-Falls-11percent-Guidance-Cut-Eyes-Brazil-Buy/698d4b25ba46a4833be0d8eb</guid><description>Black Box Limited reported an 11% YoY drop in Q3 FY26 PAT to ₹50 Cr, impacted by a ₹6 Cr exceptional charge. Revenue rose 11% YoY to ₹1,660 Cr. The company revised FY26 revenue, EBITDA, and PAT guidance downwards due to supply chain delays but confirmed its $1 billion order booking target and boosted its exit backlog projection to $800M+. A strategic acquisition of Brazil-based 2S Inovações Tecnológicas was announced to bolster LATAM presence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Black Box Ltd. Revenue Jumps 11%, Eyes Global Expansion via Brazil Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Black-Box-Ltd-Revenue-Jumps-11percent-Eyes-Global-Expansion-via-Brazil-Acquisition/698d4934ba46a4833be0cded</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Black-Box-Ltd-Revenue-Jumps-11percent-Eyes-Global-Expansion-via-Brazil-Acquisition/698d4934ba46a4833be0cded</guid><description>Black Box Limited reported an 11% YoY revenue jump to ₹1,660 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by broad-based growth and a strengthening order book reaching $601 million. Despite an 11% PAT decline, attributed to a ₹6 crore one-off provision, the company is aggressively pursuing global expansion with a planned acquisition of Brazilian firm 2S Inovações Tecnológicas. Management eyes US$2 billion in revenue by 2030, signaling a strategic shift towards high-value opportunities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Bonds Face Global Yield Headwinds Amid Inflation Data</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Bonds-Face-Global-Yield-Headwinds-Amid-Inflation-Data/698d48fdba46a4833be0cde6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Bonds-Face-Global-Yield-Headwinds-Amid-Inflation-Data/698d48fdba46a4833be0cde6</guid><description>Indian government bonds are likely to experience selling pressure as US Treasury yields climb on the back of stronger-than-expected US non-farm payrolls. The domestic market awaits January inflation data, which is projected to return to the Reserve Bank of India's target band. The Reserve Bank of India recently maintained its key policy rate and a neutral stance, while projecting steady economic growth and contained inflation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Climate Crisis: Economic Engine Strained by Heat</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Climate-Crisis-Economic-Engine-Strained-by-Heat/698d4504ba46a4833be0ca41</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Climate-Crisis-Economic-Engine-Strained-by-Heat/698d4504ba46a4833be0ca41</guid><description>India's economy confronts severe headwinds from escalating heatwaves, with forecasts predicting up to 4.5% GDP loss and millions of jobs jeopardized by 2030. While snakebite fatalities remain a global high, climate change amplifies this public health crisis. Despite existing Heat Action Plans, critical deficiencies in data, funding, and implementation leave vulnerable populations, particularly outdoor workers in agriculture and construction, exposed to life-threatening conditions. The inadequacy of current strategies poses a significant systemic risk to national development and human well-being.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:12:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d4504ba46a4833be0ca40_1770866223469.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>M&amp;M Hits Record Revenue Amid Mixed Market Reaction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandM-Hits-Record-Revenue-Amid-Mixed-Market-Reaction/698d44a1ba46a4833be0c807</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandM-Hits-Record-Revenue-Amid-Mixed-Market-Reaction/698d44a1ba46a4833be0c807</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra achieved a landmark ₹50,000 crore in consolidated revenue for Q3 FY26, driven by robust performance across its auto and farm sectors. The company highlighted synchronized execution across diverse business units, including record SUV market share gains and improved profitability in its farm equipment segment. Despite this financial milestone, the stock closed flat, indicating that the market is factoring in potential risks from sector cyclicality and climate events like El Niño.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Disruption Fears Spark Global Tech Sell-off, Indian IT Stocks Hit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Disruption-Fears-Spark-Global-Tech-Sell-off-Indian-IT-Stocks-Hit/698d449bba46a4833be0c7b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Disruption-Fears-Spark-Global-Tech-Sell-off-Indian-IT-Stocks-Hit/698d449bba46a4833be0c7b9</guid><description>Global tech stocks are experiencing a sharp sell-off, driven by escalating fears that artificial intelligence could fundamentally disrupt traditional software services business models. US-listed American Depository Receipts (ADRs) of major Indian IT firms, including Infosys and Wipro, saw significant declines. This sentiment is poised to impact Indian markets, overriding optimism from robust US jobs data and raising concerns for the broader IT sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:10:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d449bba46a4833be0c7b8_1770866160312.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ceigall India Wins ₹2,160 Cr Bihar Highway Project from NHAI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ceigall-India-Wins-2160-Cr-Bihar-Highway-Project-from-NHAI/698d43abba46a4833be0c6d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ceigall-India-Wins-2160-Cr-Bihar-Highway-Project-from-NHAI/698d43abba46a4833be0c6d5</guid><description>Ceigall India Limited, via its subsidiary, secured a ₹2,160 Crore Letter of Award from NHAI for a 78.942 km highway project in Bihar. The contract, awarded under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM), includes a 2-year construction phase and 15 years of Operation &amp; Maintenance, providing substantial revenue visibility and long-term engagement for the infrastructure firm.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:06:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enters Nuclear Arena: High Capital, Tech Hurdles Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Enters-Nuclear-Arena-High-Capital-Tech-Hurdles-Loom/698d43a3ba46a4833be0c6ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Enters-Nuclear-Arena-High-Capital-Tech-Hurdles-Loom/698d43a3ba46a4833be0c6ce</guid><description>Adani Power has launched Adani Atomic Energy Limited, signaling a significant strategic shift into the nuclear power sector. Enabled by the new SHANTI Bill, this move aims to replace existing thermal capacity and contribute to India's ambitious nuclear energy targets. However, the venture faces substantial capital expenditure requirements, complex technological integration, and execution risks, even as competitors also eye the sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:06:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Zydus Pays Astellas $120M, Settles US Patent Case for Generic Drug</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Pays-Astellas-120M-Settles-US-Patent-Case-for-Generic-Drug/698d439dba46a4833be0c6c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Pays-Astellas-120M-Settles-US-Patent-Case-for-Generic-Drug/698d439dba46a4833be0c6c6</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences has reached a settlement with Astellas Pharma, agreeing to pay $120 million plus a prepaid per-unit licensing fee until September 2027. This resolves US patent litigation concerning Astellas's Myrbetriq® (Mirabegron) and allows Zydus to continue marketing its generic version in the United States. The agreement concludes all related legal disputes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:06:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's FTAs: Industry Mandated for Competitive Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indias-FTAs-Industry-Mandated-for-Competitive-Overhaul/698d41ccba46a4833be0c441</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indias-FTAs-Industry-Mandated-for-Competitive-Overhaul/698d41ccba46a4833be0c441</guid><description>India's Commerce Minister has directed exporters to leverage recently signed Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) with developed nations, shifting the onus onto industry to enhance market penetration and product quality. While agreements like the India-EU FTA promise significant preferential access and safeguard sensitive sectors such as agriculture and dairy, their success hinges on Indian businesses overcoming operational hurdles, enhancing global competitiveness, and adapting to stringent international standards. This directive signals a strategic pivot requiring industrial readiness to capitalize on expanded market opportunities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Brokerages Issue Divergent Views on Amber, Titan, Eicher, Star Cement, Lemon Tree</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokerages-Issue-Divergent-Views-on-Amber-Titan-Eicher-Star-Cement-Lemon-Tree/698d41c6ba46a4833be0c439</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokerages-Issue-Divergent-Views-on-Amber-Titan-Eicher-Star-Cement-Lemon-Tree/698d41c6ba46a4833be0c439</guid><description>On February 12, 2026, brokerages presented a mixed scorecard for key Indian stocks. Yes Securities recommends buying Amber Enterprises, citing strong traction and future growth. ICICI Securities maintained an 'add' rating on Titan, noting resilient demand despite gold price concerns. Conversely, Motilal Oswal reiterated a 'sell' on Eicher Motors, pointing to normalized demand and capped margin upside. Star Cement and Lemon Tree Hotels also saw varied analyst sentiment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lenskart Rockets 22% Higher on Jefferies Upgrade Post Strong Q3</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskart-Rockets-22percent-Higher-on-Jefferies-Upgrade-Post-Strong-Q3/698d3ea3ba46a4833be0c104</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskart-Rockets-22percent-Higher-on-Jefferies-Upgrade-Post-Strong-Q3/698d3ea3ba46a4833be0c104</guid><description>Lenskart Solutions reported a robust third quarter, with profit after tax surging to ₹132.7 crore and revenue climbing 38.3% year-on-year. This strong financial performance prompted brokerage firm Jefferies to raise its price target for the stock by 21.6% to ₹575 per share, maintaining a 'buy' rating.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:44:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d3ea3ba46a4833be0c103_1770864569216.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Court Ruling Empowers Employees on Gratuity Claims</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Court-Ruling-Empowers-Employees-on-Gratuity-Claims/698d3dfbba46a4833be0bf76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Court-Ruling-Empowers-Employees-on-Gratuity-Claims/698d3dfbba46a4833be0bf76</guid><description>The Madras High Court has affirmed that employers cannot deny statutory gratuity to employees receiving pensions, unless a specific government exemption is obtained. This ruling emphasizes gratuity as a mandatory, statutory right that cannot be superseded by internal pension schemes. The judgment reinforces employee protections under Indian labor law, compelling employers to ensure compliance and potentially increasing their contingent liabilities for dual benefit structures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kraft Heinz Pauses Split, Pledges $600M Amid Persistent Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kraft-Heinz-Pauses-Split-Pledges-600M-Amid-Persistent-Challenges/698d3de4ba46a4833be0bf52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kraft-Heinz-Pauses-Split-Pledges-600M-Amid-Persistent-Challenges/698d3de4ba46a4833be0bf52</guid><description>Kraft Heinz is shelving its planned two-company split, instead committing $600 million to revitalize core brands and drive profitable growth. This strategic pivot follows a quarter of declining net sales and a significant drop in net income, raising investor apprehension. The company's decision signals a retreat from prior growth strategies amidst intense competitive pressures and a challenging market for consumer staples.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026 GST Overhaul: Stability Over Stimulus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-GST-Overhaul-Stability-Over-Stimulus/698d3d85ba46a4833be0bf47</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-GST-Overhaul-Stability-Over-Stimulus/698d3d85ba46a4833be0bf47</guid><description>Budget 2026's Goods and Services Tax (GST) narrative diverges from rate changes, emphasizing a course correction. Nearly a decade into GST, interpretational ambiguities and structural gaps have spurred disputes and drained working capital. The Finance Bill 2026 targets litigation reduction, cash-flow relief, and restored predictability, formalizing GST Council recommendations to align law with commercial realities and judicial perspectives.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Solar Stocks Rise on Tariffs, But Valuations Remain a Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/India-Solar-Stocks-Rise-on-Tariffs-But-Valuations-Remain-a-Concern/698d3c3aba46a4833be0b7c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/India-Solar-Stocks-Rise-on-Tariffs-But-Valuations-Remain-a-Concern/698d3c3aba46a4833be0b7c9</guid><description>A recent US-India trade agreement, slashing tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, has injected new optimism into India's renewable energy sector. Solar firms like Insolation Energy and Oriana Power have seen significant February gains, recouping prior losses. However, persistent high valuations for giants like Adani Green Energy and JSW Energy, coupled with ongoing execution risks and competition from China, present a complex investment outlook. While export prospects have brightened, analysts urge caution regarding the sustainability of current stock prices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Silver Tumbles: Speculative Frenzy Meets Regulatory Reckoning</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Tumbles-Speculative-Frenzy-Meets-Regulatory-Reckoning/698d3c11ba46a4833be0b4c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Tumbles-Speculative-Frenzy-Meets-Regulatory-Reckoning/698d3c11ba46a4833be0b4c2</guid><description>Silver prices have undergone a dramatic correction, plunging approximately 35-40% from recent peaks near $120 per ounce. This sharp decline was significantly exacerbated by multiple, aggressive margin requirement increases by CME Group, designed to curb extreme volatility and speculative excess. While strong underlying industrial demand and persistent supply deficits provide a structural floor, the recent price action highlights the disruptive impact of speculative fervor and regulatory intervention on commodity markets. Current spot prices hover around $82-$84 per ounce, with MCX futures near Rs 2.62-2.89 lakh per kilogram.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Redefines Liability: Consent No Shield Against Mis-selling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Redefines-Liability-Consent-No-Shield-Against-Mis-selling/698d3aaaba46a4833be09986</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Redefines-Liability-Consent-No-Shield-Against-Mis-selling/698d3aaaba46a4833be09986</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is ushering in stringent new rules effective July 1, 2026, fundamentally altering how financial products are sold. The central bank has redefined mis-selling to prioritize product suitability over customer consent, introducing mandatory refunds and compensation for proven cases. These measures also target deceptive 'dark patterns' in digital interfaces and prohibit compulsory bundling, signaling a significant increase in accountability for regulated entities and a shift towards proactive consumer protection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver: Core Assets or Fleeting Hype?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Core-Assets-or-Fleeting-Hype/698d36e1ba46a4833be096af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Core-Assets-or-Fleeting-Hype/698d36e1ba46a4833be096af</guid><description>Gold and silver are increasingly viewed as strategic portfolio components rather than mere hedges, driven by persistent central bank accumulation, structural industrial demand for silver, and a complex macroeconomic backdrop. This shift has propelled prices to record highs, but divergent economic signals and speculative fervor introduce significant volatility, prompting scrutiny of the long-term sustainability of this bull phase.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Morganite Crucible Profit Plummets 29% Amid Vesuvius Group Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Morganite-Crucible-Profit-Plummets-29percent-Amid-Vesuvius-Group-Acquisition/698d367bba46a4833be096a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Morganite-Crucible-Profit-Plummets-29percent-Amid-Vesuvius-Group-Acquisition/698d367bba46a4833be096a5</guid><description>Morganite Crucible (India) Limited reported a sharp 29.0% year-on-year decline in Profit After Tax (PAT) for Q3 FY26, falling to ₹556.80 Cr from ₹784.65 Cr. This was exacerbated by a significant drop in other income and a ₹277.73 Cr exceptional item related to new labor codes. Concurrently, Foseco India Ltd, part of the Vesuvius Group, acquired a 75% stake for ₹653.94 Cr, signaling a major change in control and a pending name change to Foseco Crucible (India) Limited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech, QSR, and Finance Stocks Diverge: Caution Reigns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Tech-QSR-and-Finance-Stocks-Diverge-Caution-Reigns/698d3169ba46a4833be09323</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Tech-QSR-and-Finance-Stocks-Diverge-Caution-Reigns/698d3169ba46a4833be09323</guid><description>Authum Investment &amp; Infrastructure Ltd (AIIL) presents a high-risk, speculative bounce opportunity near critical support, contrasting sharply with Coforge Ltd and Jubilant Foodworks Ltd. Coforge remains entrenched in a bearish technical pattern, weighed down by sector headwinds and premium valuation. Jubilant Foodworks, despite QSR sector growth, exhibits a persistent downtrend and expensive multiples, signaling caution for investors across these diverse segments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 01:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>