<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:17:33 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Air India in Hot Water: DGCA Slams Airline Over Repeated Dreamliner Snags, Demands Answers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-in-Hot-Water-DGCA-Slams-Airline-Over-Repeated-Dreamliner-Snags-Demands-Answers/69553e344342f77179eef817</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-in-Hot-Water-DGCA-Slams-Airline-Over-Repeated-Dreamliner-Snags-Demands-Answers/69553e344342f77179eef817</guid><description>India's aviation regulator, the DGCA, has issued a show-cause notice to Air India demanding an explanation for operating a Boeing 787-8 Dreamliner (VT-ANI) despite recurring technical issues. The notice highlights safety concerns, including non-compliance with the Minimum Equipment List (MEL) during flights on the Delhi-Tokyo route.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:05:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Fiscal Tightrope: Deficit Hits ₹9.76 Lakh Crore! Are Investors Watching?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Tightrope-Deficit-Hits-976-Lakh-Crore-Are-Investors-Watching/69553de04342f77179eef6f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Tightrope-Deficit-Hits-976-Lakh-Crore-Are-Investors-Watching/69553de04342f77179eef6f0</guid><description>India's fiscal deficit for April-November reached ₹9.76 lakh crore, accounting for 63% of the full fiscal year's budget estimate. This is a significant increase compared to the same period last year, which stood at 53% of the budget estimate. Government receipts are at 55.7% of the estimate, with tax revenues showing mixed performance, while expenditure is at 57.8%, driven by interest payments and subsidies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:02:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553de04342f77179eef6ef_1767194143765.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EU Carbon Tax Looming: Will India's Crucial FTA Talks Collapse or Secure Lifeline for Exporters?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EU-Carbon-Tax-Looming-Will-Indias-Crucial-FTA-Talks-Collapse-or-Secure-Lifeline-for-Exporters/69553df84342f77179eef74a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EU-Carbon-Tax-Looming-Will-Indias-Crucial-FTA-Talks-Collapse-or-Secure-Lifeline-for-Exporters/69553df84342f77179eef74a</guid><description>India is seeking critical exemptions from the European Union's Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (CBAM), set to take effect January 1, 2026. These EU carbon taxes could force Indian steel and aluminium exporters to cut prices by up to 22%, impacting competitiveness. Negotiations for a Free Trade Agreement (FTA) between India and the EU are in their final stages, with India pushing for flexibility on CBAM and other regulations to protect its carbon-intensive industries and ensure market access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553df84342f77179eef749_1767194212478.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mutual Funds Skyrocket: India's AUM Hits Astounding ₹81 Lakh Crore Milestone!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Mutual-Funds-Skyrocket-Indias-AUM-Hits-Astounding-81-Lakh-Crore-Milestone/69553d3e4342f77179eef495</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Mutual-Funds-Skyrocket-Indias-AUM-Hits-Astounding-81-Lakh-Crore-Milestone/69553d3e4342f77179eef495</guid><description>India's mutual fund industry has achieved a significant milestone, with assets under management (AUM) surging 19% year-on-year to reach ₹81 lakh crore by the end of November. Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) played a crucial role, contributing ₹1 lakh crore with a 63% increase year-on-year. Equity schemes hold ₹36 lakh crore, while non-equity schemes manage ₹45 lakh crore, reflecting strong retail investor demand for equity exposure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553d3e4342f77179eef494_1767193997160.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Jobless Claims Plunge to 2024 Lows Amid Holiday Season Volatility!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Jobless-Claims-Plunge-to-2024-Lows-Amid-Holiday-Season-Volatility/69553ab64342f77179eeee0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Jobless-Claims-Plunge-to-2024-Lows-Amid-Holiday-Season-Volatility/69553ab64342f77179eeee0a</guid><description>US unemployment benefit applications dropped significantly to 199,000 during the Christmas week, reaching one of the lowest points this year. Despite typical holiday data volatility, this figure undershot economist expectations and signals a resilient labor market, though overall hiring has been sluggish.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:54:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69553ab64342f77179eeee09_1767193347984.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Sounds Alarm: Are Bank-NBFC Loan Deals Posing Hidden Risks to Your Investments?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Sounds-Alarm-Are-Bank-NBFC-Loan-Deals-Posing-Hidden-Risks-to-Your-Investments/6955382f4342f77179eee656</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Sounds-Alarm-Are-Bank-NBFC-Loan-Deals-Posing-Hidden-Risks-to-Your-Investments/6955382f4342f77179eee656</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Financial Stability Report highlights concerns over banks aggressively buying loans from non-banking finance companies (NBFCs) to boost retail portfolios. The report warns of concentration risks, as banks source nearly 80% of these assets from a few NBFCs, potentially amplifying financial stress and leading to weaker credit performance compared to banks' own loan originations, particularly for public sector lenders.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955382f4342f77179eee655_1767192988084.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Boosts Dollar Bets: Is Rupee Stability at Risk?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Boosts-Dollar-Bets-Is-Rupee-Stability-at-Risk/695538214342f77179eee609</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Boosts-Dollar-Bets-Is-Rupee-Stability-at-Risk/695538214342f77179eee609</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's net short dollar position in the rupee forward market rose to $66.04 billion by end-November, up from $63.6 billion in October. This indicates increased intervention to manage currency volatility. Meanwhile, the Real Effective Exchange Rate (REER) remained stable at 97.51, suggesting potential challenges for export competitiveness if the rupee strengthens significantly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:40:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695538214342f77179eee608_1767192801189.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OYO's Parent PRISM Files Secret IPO Papers: Will India See an $8 Billion Debut?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OYOs-Parent-PRISM-Files-Secret-IPO-Papers-Will-India-See-an-8-Billion-Debut/695538984342f77179eee7eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OYOs-Parent-PRISM-Files-Secret-IPO-Papers-Will-India-See-an-8-Billion-Debut/695538984342f77179eee7eb</guid><description>PRISM, the parent company of OYO, has confidentially filed draft IPO papers with SEBI, aiming for a $7-8 billion valuation. The company seeks shareholder approval to raise up to ₹6,650 crore. ICICI Securities, Axis Capital, Goldman Sachs, and Citibank are among the book running lead managers for the issue, which uses SEBI's confidential pre-filing route.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:40:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695538984342f77179eee7ea_1767193013591.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Piped Gas Price Cut Announced for Delhi-NCR: Big Relief This New Year!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Piped-Gas-Price-Cut-Announced-for-Delhi-NCR-Big-Relief-This-New-Year/6955371e4342f77179eee318</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Piped-Gas-Price-Cut-Announced-for-Delhi-NCR-Big-Relief-This-New-Year/6955371e4342f77179eee318</guid><description>Indraprastha Gas Limited (IGL) has announced a price reduction of ₹0.70 per standard cubic meter (scm) for domestic Piped Natural Gas (PNG) in Delhi and NCR towns. This change, effective January 1, 2026, follows the Petroleum and Natural Gas Regulatory Board's (PNGRB) revised pipeline tariff structure, aiming to make natural gas transportation more cost-effective and accessible for consumers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:38:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955371e4342f77179eee317_1767192446523.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Small Savings: Interest Rates Unchanged for Jan-Mar 2026 - Find Out What It Means for Your Money!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Small-Savings-Interest-Rates-Unchanged-for-Jan-Mar-2026-Find-Out-What-It-Means-for-Your-Money/6955379e4342f77179eee483</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Small-Savings-Interest-Rates-Unchanged-for-Jan-Mar-2026-Find-Out-What-It-Means-for-Your-Money/6955379e4342f77179eee483</guid><description>India's Finance Ministry announced that interest rates for small savings schemes will remain unchanged for the January-March 2026 quarter. Schemes like Public Provident Fund (PPF) will continue at 7.1%, National Savings Certificate (NSC) at 7.7%, while Senior Citizen Savings Scheme (SCSS) and Sukanya Samriddhi Yojana (SSY) will offer the highest 8.2%. Kisan Vikas Patra (KVP) remains at 7.5% and Post Office Monthly Income Scheme (POMIS) at 7.4%.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955379e4342f77179eee482_1767193270520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Bold Prediction: Indian Banks Set for Massive NPA Drop by 2027!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Bold-Prediction-Indian-Banks-Set-for-Massive-NPA-Drop-by-2027/6955366f4342f77179eee108</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Bold-Prediction-Indian-Banks-Set-for-Massive-NPA-Drop-by-2027/6955366f4342f77179eee108</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Financial Stability Report projects a significant improvement in the banking sector, with gross non-performing assets (NPAs) expected to fall to 1.9% by March 2027 from the current 2.1% (as of September 2025). While stress tests indicate potential risks under adverse conditions, the report highlights strong capital buffers across public and private banks. It also notes a decline in large borrower concentration and their contribution to NPAs, despite a slowdown in net interest income growth due to rate cuts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:32:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955366f4342f77179eee107_1767193152149.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets DEFEND Against Global Storm! See How Domestic Investors Are Winning the Battle! 🚀</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-DEFEND-Against-Global-Storm-See-How-Domestic-Investors-Are-Winning-the-Battle/695535504342f77179eedd70</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-DEFEND-Against-Global-Storm-See-How-Domestic-Investors-Are-Winning-the-Battle/695535504342f77179eedd70</guid><description>Indian equities are showing resilience despite global uncertainty and foreign investor (FPI) outflows, according to an RBI report. Domestic institutional investors (DIIs) are driving this stability, with their inflows significantly outpacing FPI outflows for the past five years. While India has underperformed emerging market peers on risk-adjusted returns recently, its long-term performance is better. Valuations have narrowed but remain at the higher end of historical ranges, with future earnings growth facing risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:29:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695535504342f77179eedd6f_1767193101808.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Flags HUGE Risk: Fintech's Unsecured Loan Bubble POPS? What Investors NEED to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Flags-HUGE-Risk-Fintechs-Unsecured-Loan-Bubble-POPS-What-Investors-NEED-to-Know/695531dc4342f77179eed45d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Flags-HUGE-Risk-Fintechs-Unsecured-Loan-Bubble-POPS-What-Investors-NEED-to-Know/695531dc4342f77179eed45d</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Financial Stability Report reveals that unsecured loans, primarily personal and business loans, constitute over 70% of fintechs' total lending books. A significant portion, more than half, has been extended to individuals under 35. While fintech retail lending has grown to 8.9% of the NBFC consumer segment, and overall fintech loan books expanded by 36.1% in the past year driven by personal loans, the RBI noted asset quality has improved. However, risks remain pronounced in small-ticket loans (under ₹50,000) and among borrowers with multiple unsecured loans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:10:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695531dc4342f77179eed45c_1767192321648.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Market Hits 10-Year Win Streak But Trails Global Giants in 2025!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Market-Hits-10-Year-Win-Streak-But-Trails-Global-Giants-in-2025/695533b24342f77179eed92f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Market-Hits-10-Year-Win-Streak-But-Trails-Global-Giants-in-2025/695533b24342f77179eed92f</guid><description>Indian equity markets ended 2025 with a 10.7% gain, marking a decade-long winning streak for the Nifty. However, the year was characterized by resilience rather than outperformance, as India lagged behind global peers like the Dow Jones, Nasdaq, and MSCI Emerging Markets index. Factors such as geopolitical tensions, US trade policy uncertainty, domestic economic headwinds including GST 2.0, significant foreign portfolio investor (FPI) outflows, and a weakening rupee contributed to this underperformance. Precious metals, particularly silver, saw historic rallies, significantly outshining equities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:09:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695533b24342f77179eed92e_1767193011947.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Poised for Major Financial Boost: Promoters Agree to ₹5,836 Crore Recovery Deal!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Poised-for-Major-Financial-Boost-Promoters-Agree-to-5836-Crore-Recovery-Deal/695530d74342f77179eed112</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Poised-for-Major-Financial-Boost-Promoters-Agree-to-5836-Crore-Recovery-Deal/695530d74342f77179eed112</guid><description>Vodafone Idea Limited has inked a revised agreement with its Vodafone Group promoters, set to recover approximately ₹5,836 crore. This recovery, crucial for the company's financial health, will be achieved through a combination of direct cash payments and a strategic allocation of Vodafone Idea shares, improving future cash flow visibility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:09:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695530d74342f77179eed111_1767190831034.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Poised for MAJOR Economic Surge: RBI Governor Reveals Secret Drivers Amid Global Chaos!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Poised-for-MAJOR-Economic-Surge-RBI-Governor-Reveals-Secret-Drivers-Amid-Global-Chaos/6955311c4342f77179eed1e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Poised-for-MAJOR-Economic-Surge-RBI-Governor-Reveals-Secret-Drivers-Amid-Global-Chaos/6955311c4342f77179eed1e1</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India Governor Sanjay Malhotra has projected robust economic growth for India, attributing it to strong domestic consumption and investment despite challenging global conditions. He emphasized the RBI's commitment to financial stability, building resilience against external shocks, and fostering a robust financial system through prudent policy reforms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:08:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955311c4342f77179eed1e0_1767192204360.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai Property Market Shatters Records in 2025: Best Year Ever Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mumbai-Property-Market-Shatters-Records-in-2025-Best-Year-Ever-Revealed/695530484342f77179eecfb8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mumbai-Property-Market-Shatters-Records-in-2025-Best-Year-Ever-Revealed/695530484342f77179eecfb8</guid><description>Mumbai's property market achieved a record-breaking year in 2025, with over 150,300 registrations, a 6% rise from the previous year. Stamp duty collections also hit an all-time high of ₹13,500 crore, up 12%. December was the strongest month ever, seeing 14,400 registrations and ₹1,260 crore in stamp duty. Strong demand, infrastructure development, and improved affordability are key drivers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:04:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695530484342f77179eecfb7_1767190679088.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Britannia's 'Little Hearts' Triumph: Delhi HC Slams Infringer, Protects Iconic Biscuit Shape!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannias-Little-Hearts-Triumph-Delhi-HC-Slams-Infringer-Protects-Iconic-Biscuit-Shape/69552f8f4342f77179eecd42</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannias-Little-Hearts-Triumph-Delhi-HC-Slams-Infringer-Protects-Iconic-Biscuit-Shape/69552f8f4342f77179eecd42</guid><description>The Delhi High Court has issued an interim order restraining Shri Swastik Organics from infringing Britannia Industries Ltd.'s trademark and the distinctive 3D shape of its popular 'Little Hearts' biscuits. The court cited a "triple identity" in marks, products, and trade channels, granting Britannia, the prior user and registered owner, protection against irreparable harm. An e-commerce platform was also ordered to delist the infringing products.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:03:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552f8f4342f77179eecd41_1767192008531.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Consumer Giants Lose Top Leaders: What Does Their Legacy Mean for Your Investments?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Consumer-Giants-Lose-Top-Leaders-What-Does-Their-Legacy-Mean-for-Your-Investments/69552f3f4342f77179eecc3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Consumer-Giants-Lose-Top-Leaders-What-Does-Their-Legacy-Mean-for-Your-Investments/69552f3f4342f77179eecc3b</guid><description>Three leading consumer product executives are retiring in 2025, including leaders from Nestle India, Britannia Industries, and Titan Company, alongside the exit of Hindustan Unilever's MD. Their tenures were marked by strong crisis management, focus on long-term value, and people-centric strategies, leaving a significant cultural imprint on the sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552f3f4342f77179eecc3a_1767192709491.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Casagrand Files Mega IPO: Will ₹1,220 Crore Debt Repayment Drive Real Estate Giant's Comeback?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Casagrand-Files-Mega-IPO-Will-1220-Crore-Debt-Repayment-Drive-Real-Estate-Giants-Comeback/69552f124342f77179eecb5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Casagrand-Files-Mega-IPO-Will-1220-Crore-Debt-Repayment-Drive-Real-Estate-Giants-Comeback/69552f124342f77179eecb5f</guid><description>Chennai-based Casagrand Premier Builder Limited has filed its Draft Red Herring Prospectus (DRHP) with SEBI to raise ₹1,220 crore via an IPO. The primary goal is to prepay outstanding borrowings of ₹4,472 crore. The issue includes a ₹1,200 crore fresh issue and a ₹20 crore Offer for Sale. Despite a net loss of ₹32 crore in Q2 FY25, the company reported ₹2,696 crore revenue and ₹235 crore profit for FY25, supported by a significant project pipeline.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:00:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552f124342f77179eecb5e_1767190366366.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Warns: India's Insurance Growth SHACKLED by Sky-High Distribution Costs! Are You Paying Too Much?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/RBI-Warns-Indias-Insurance-Growth-SHACKLED-by-Sky-High-Distribution-Costs-Are-You-Paying-Too-Much/69552d624342f77179eec645</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/RBI-Warns-Indias-Insurance-Growth-SHACKLED-by-Sky-High-Distribution-Costs-Are-You-Paying-Too-Much/69552d624342f77179eec645</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Financial Stability Report highlights that high distribution costs are embedded in insurance pricing, reducing affordability and hindering coverage expansion. Premium growth is increasingly driven by these costs and spending by existing policyholders, rather than operational efficiency. A conservative investment strategy by insurers also risks making long-term savings products less attractive.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:40:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552d624342f77179eec644_1767191363658.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samvardhana Motherson Surges 17%: German AutoElectric Acquisition and Massive Order Book Drive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Samvardhana-Motherson-Surges-17percent-German-AutoElectric-Acquisition-and-Massive-Order-Book-Drive-Growth/69552e454342f77179eec8cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Samvardhana-Motherson-Surges-17percent-German-AutoElectric-Acquisition-and-Massive-Order-Book-Drive-Growth/69552e454342f77179eec8cf</guid><description>Samvardhana Motherson International's stock has jumped 17% from November lows, driven by strong September quarter results, increased vehicle content, market share gains, and a planned acquisition of German firm AutoElectric. This €207 million deal for a wiring harness maker is expected to expand the company's presence in electric and hybrid vehicles. With a substantial $87 billion order backlog, analysts are bullish, forecasting strong growth through FY28 and reiterating buy ratings with high price targets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:40:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552e454342f77179eec8ce_1767190239258.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Veegaland Developers IPO: Rs 250 Crore Dream for Kerala Real Estate – Will You Invest?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Veegaland-Developers-IPO-Rs-250-Crore-Dream-for-Kerala-Real-Estate-Will-You-Invest/69552c634342f77179eec2ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Veegaland-Developers-IPO-Rs-250-Crore-Dream-for-Kerala-Real-Estate-Will-You-Invest/69552c634342f77179eec2ec</guid><description>Veegaland Developers, part of the V-Guard group, has filed draft papers with India's market regulator Sebi for an Initial Public Offering (IPO) to raise Rs 250 crore. The funds will primarily finance the development of ongoing and upcoming residential projects in Kerala, alongside acquiring new land parcels. This is a completely fresh issue of shares, offering investors a direct stake in the company's expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:39:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552c634342f77179eec2eb_1767189867689.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive Win For Voltas! GST Demand Slashed By 96% From ₹265 Cr To Just ₹11 Cr In Uttarakhand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-Win-For-Voltas-GST-Demand-Slashed-By-96percent-From-265-Cr-To-Just-11-Cr-In-Uttarakhand/69552c3f4342f77179eec1fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-Win-For-Voltas-GST-Demand-Slashed-By-96percent-From-265-Cr-To-Just-11-Cr-In-Uttarakhand/69552c3f4342f77179eec1fb</guid><description>Voltas Ltd has received a significant reprieve as the Central GST Commissionerate in Dehradun drastically reduced a Goods and Services Tax demand. Originally set at ₹265.25 crore, the demand, including interest and penalties, has been lowered to ₹10.77 crore following the company's detailed submissions. This demand pertained to alleged short payments by Universal Comfort Products Ltd, which merged with Voltas. While Voltas is evaluating the order for potential appeals, the company has indicated no material impact on its financials or operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:39:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552c3f4342f77179eec1fa_1767191242349.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zaggle &amp; Visa Forge 7-Year Power Pact: India's Prepaid Card Future Ignites!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Zaggle-and-Visa-Forge-7-Year-Power-Pact-Indias-Prepaid-Card-Future-Ignites/69552c084342f77179eec158</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Zaggle-and-Visa-Forge-7-Year-Power-Pact-Indias-Prepaid-Card-Future-Ignites/69552c084342f77179eec158</guid><description>Fintech firm Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd has signed a significant seven-year growth agreement with Visa Worldwide Pte Ltd. This partnership will see Visa incentivize Zaggle to launch and promote co-branded domestic prepaid cards across the Visa network. This strategic move aims to expand Zaggle's reach and offerings in the burgeoning Indian digital payments market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:39:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552c084342f77179eec157_1767190042779.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹4 Lakh Crore Recovered! India's Debt Resolution Code Delivers Massive Wins for Creditors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/4-Lakh-Crore-Recovered-Indias-Debt-Resolution-Code-Delivers-Massive-Wins-for-Creditors/69552b544342f77179eebef6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/4-Lakh-Crore-Recovered-Indias-Debt-Resolution-Code-Delivers-Massive-Wins-for-Creditors/69552b544342f77179eebef6</guid><description>A Reserve Bank of India report reveals that creditors have recovered ₹4 lakh crore under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC) by September 30, 2025. The IBC has successfully initiated 8,659 corporate insolvency resolution processes (CIRPs), with 78.1% now closed, rescuing 3,865 distressed corporate debtors and significantly exceeding liquidation values.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:39:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552b544342f77179eebef5_1767192808497.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Labour Law Revolution: Draft Rules Released for Millions - Big Changes Coming Soon!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Labour-Law-Revolution-Draft-Rules-Released-for-Millions-Big-Changes-Coming-Soon/69552a764342f77179eebba0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Labour-Law-Revolution-Draft-Rules-Released-for-Millions-Big-Changes-Coming-Soon/69552a764342f77179eebba0</guid><description>India's Ministry of Labour and Employment has unveiled draft rules for four comprehensive labour codes covering wages, industrial relations, social security, and safety. The government aims for nationwide implementation by April 1, 2026, seeking stakeholder feedback during a 30-45 day period. These reforms are designed to enhance worker protections, simplify compliance for businesses, and promote economic growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:39:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552a764342f77179eebb9f_1767189429311.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBL Bank Eyes Foreign Shareholding Cap Amid Emirates NBD Investment Drive!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBL-Bank-Eyes-Foreign-Shareholding-Cap-Amid-Emirates-NBD-Investment-Drive/69552afe4342f77179eebd5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBL-Bank-Eyes-Foreign-Shareholding-Cap-Amid-Emirates-NBD-Investment-Drive/69552afe4342f77179eebd5a</guid><description>RBL Bank has applied to the Reserve Bank of India and the Government of India to temporarily cap foreign shareholding at 24% for a proposed investment by Emirates NBD. While the request has not been approved under current rules, Emirates NBD has sufficient headroom to proceed with a significant stake, subject to regulatory approvals. The bank remains committed to informing the stock exchanges about material developments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552afe4342f77179eebd59_1767189681651.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Stress Test Reveals: Indian Banks' Shocking Resilience Against Economic Shocks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Stress-Test-Reveals-Indian-Banks-Shocking-Resilience-Against-Economic-Shocks/69552b254342f77179eebdfc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Stress-Test-Reveals-Indian-Banks-Shocking-Resilience-Against-Economic-Shocks/69552b254342f77179eebdfc</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's latest Financial Stability Report indicates Indian banks are resilient to macroeconomic shocks. Stress tests show capital buffers (CRAR) will remain above the 9% minimum regulatory requirement even under adverse scenarios. While some banks may touch their Capital Conservation Buffer, the overall system is robust, with GNPA expected to improve in a baseline scenario despite potential rises under stress.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:35:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552b254342f77179eebdfb_1767189600983.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Real Estate's Future is FLEX: 100M Sq Ft Boom &amp; ₹33,000 Cr Opportunity Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Real-Estates-Future-is-FLEX-100M-Sq-Ft-Boom-and-33000-Cr-Opportunity-Unveiled/69552a0a4342f77179eeba77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Real-Estates-Future-is-FLEX-100M-Sq-Ft-Boom-and-33000-Cr-Opportunity-Unveiled/69552a0a4342f77179eeba77</guid><description>Flexible office spaces are leading India's commercial real estate growth in 2025. Major players like WeWork India, Indiqube, and Smartworks are expanding rapidly, partnering with REITs and developers for prime locations. Colliers forecasts the sector to reach 100 million sq ft and account for 20% of total office leasing in India. Ambit Capital projects a ₹33,000 crore opportunity by 2027 and recommends 'buy' for listed players, highlighting agility and capital efficiency over ownership.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:35:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69552a0a4342f77179eeba76_1767189220123.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IGL Slashes Piped Gas Prices for Delhi &amp; NCR Homes This New Year!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IGL-Slashes-Piped-Gas-Prices-for-Delhi-and-NCR-Homes-This-New-Year/695529124342f77179eeb709</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IGL-Slashes-Piped-Gas-Prices-for-Delhi-and-NCR-Homes-This-New-Year/695529124342f77179eeb709</guid><description>Indraprastha Gas Ltd (IGL) has announced a ₹0.70 per standard cubic meter (scm) cut in piped natural gas (PNG) prices for household kitchens in Delhi and NCR towns, effective January 1. The revised rates follow a recent overhaul of pipeline tariffs by the Petroleum and Natural Gas Regulatory Board (PNGRB), aiming to make natural gas transportation more cost-effective. New prices include ₹47.89/scm in Delhi and ₹46.70/scm in Gurugram.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:32:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695529124342f77179eeb708_1767189193348.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Buffett's Big India Exit: Berkshire Hathaway's Paytm Gamble Ends in Loss – What It Means for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Buffetts-Big-India-Exit-Berkshire-Hathaways-Paytm-Gamble-Ends-in-Loss-What-It-Means-for-Investors/6955293c4342f77179eeb7d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Buffetts-Big-India-Exit-Berkshire-Hathaways-Paytm-Gamble-Ends-in-Loss-What-It-Means-for-Investors/6955293c4342f77179eeb7d3</guid><description>Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway has exited its sole Indian investment in fintech firm Paytm, incurring a significant loss of ₹630 crore. The investment, initially around $300 million for a 2.6% stake in One97 Communications (Paytm's parent company) in 2018, marked Berkshire's debut in India. Despite Paytm's recent stock performance and securing a Payment Aggregator license, the firm booked a loss on its exit, concluding a notable chapter in its India strategy as Buffett's era nears its end.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955293c4342f77179eeb7d2_1767189311330.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Roaring Growth &amp; Tata's AI Revolution: Chairman Unveils Bold 2026 Vision!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Roaring-Growth-and-Tatas-AI-Revolution-Chairman-Unveils-Bold-2026-Vision/6955280e4342f77179eeb41a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Roaring-Growth-and-Tatas-AI-Revolution-Chairman-Unveils-Bold-2026-Vision/6955280e4342f77179eeb41a</guid><description>N Chandrasekaran, Chairman of Tata Group, outlines India's path to becoming the world's third-largest economy this decade. He details Tata's 'AI-first' strategy, significant expansion in advanced manufacturing including a semiconductor fab and gigafactories, and milestones in electric vehicles, with Tata Motors leading the charge. The group is also investing heavily in AI data centres and services, aiming for resilience and consistent performance across its diverse companies by 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:29:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955280e4342f77179eeb419_1767188836830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BIG Relief! IGL Slashes PNG Prices Ahead of New Year - Check New Rates NOW!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BIG-Relief-IGL-Slashes-PNG-Prices-Ahead-of-New-Year-Check-New-Rates-NOW/695527c84342f77179eeb2fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BIG-Relief-IGL-Slashes-PNG-Prices-Ahead-of-New-Year-Check-New-Rates-NOW/695527c84342f77179eeb2fd</guid><description>Indraprastha Gas Limited (IGL) has announced a significant price reduction for domestic piped natural gas (PNG) in Delhi and the National Capital Region, effective from January 1st. Consumers will see a decrease of Rs 0.70 per standard cubic metre (SCM), bringing new rates across Delhi, Gurugram, Noida, Greater Noida, and Ghaziabad, offering much-needed relief for households.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695527c84342f77179eeb2fc_1767188735988.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economy Ignites: RBI Governor Unlocks Secret to Stellar Growth Amidst Global Storm!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-Ignites-RBI-Governor-Unlocks-Secret-to-Stellar-Growth-Amidst-Global-Storm/695526db4342f77179eeb031</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-Ignites-RBI-Governor-Unlocks-Secret-to-Stellar-Growth-Amidst-Global-Storm/695526db4342f77179eeb031</guid><description>India's economy is projected to achieve high growth despite global challenges, propelled by robust domestic consumption and investment, according to Reserve Bank of India Governor Sanjay Malhotra. He emphasized the central bank's commitment to maintaining financial stability while fostering innovation and resilience against potential shocks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:24:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695526db4342f77179eeb030_1767188602289.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Stark Warning: Stablecoins Pose Major Risks, India Champions Digital Rupee!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Stark-Warning-Stablecoins-Pose-Major-Risks-India-Champions-Digital-Rupee/695523204342f77179eea7b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Stark-Warning-Stablecoins-Pose-Major-Risks-India-Champions-Digital-Rupee/695523204342f77179eea7b6</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India, in its Financial Stability Report, has flagged significant risks from stablecoins, stating their volatility and potential to disrupt capital flows outweigh their benefits. The central bank strongly advocates for prioritizing Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) over privately issued stablecoins to maintain trust in money, ensure financial stability, and build secure payment infrastructures. India is advancing its own CBDC pilot projects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:08:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695523204342f77179eea7b5_1767187313259.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCC Bags ₹1,237 Cr Orders: Can New Deals Offset Weak Earnings and Stock Dip?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Bags-1237-Cr-Orders-Can-New-Deals-Offset-Weak-Earnings-and-Stock-Dip/695522f64342f77179eea71b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Bags-1237-Cr-Orders-Can-New-Deals-Offset-Weak-Earnings-and-Stock-Dip/695522f64342f77179eea71b</guid><description>NCC Ltd announced securing four new infrastructure orders worth ₹1,237.24 crore in December, split between building (₹704.67 cr) and transportation (₹532.57 cr) segments. This follows a previous large order for Gauhati Medical College. Despite the new contracts, NCC's shares declined 3.47% to ₹160.38 on December 31, impacted by weak Q2 earnings showing a 12.6% revenue drop, although EBITDA margins slightly improved.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:07:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695522f64342f77179eea71a_1767187695490.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Debt Soars: Household Borrowings Hit Record High! But Savings Surge Too – What It Means for Your Money!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Debt-Soars-Household-Borrowings-Hit-Record-High-But-Savings-Surge-Too-What-It-Means-for-Your-Money/695521a84342f77179eea3ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Debt-Soars-Household-Borrowings-Hit-Record-High-But-Savings-Surge-Too-What-It-Means-for-Your-Money/695521a84342f77179eea3ed</guid><description>India's household debt reached 41.3% of GDP by March 2025, up from its five-year average of 38.3%. Non-housing retail loans now form 55.3% of total borrowings, primarily for consumption. Despite the rise in debt, net household financial savings improved significantly to 7.6% of GDP, indicating underlying resilience. The Reserve Bank of India's report also noted an improvement in the quality of household credit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:04:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695521a84342f77179eea3ec_1767187527880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal's Bold Moves: 4 Stocks Picked for Up to 49% Surge! Are You Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Motilal-Oswals-Bold-Moves-4-Stocks-Picked-for-Up-to-49percent-Surge-Are-You-Ready/695520624342f77179eea021</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Motilal-Oswals-Bold-Moves-4-Stocks-Picked-for-Up-to-49percent-Surge-Are-You-Ready/695520624342f77179eea021</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services has issued 'Buy' recommendations for four companies: VA Tech Wabag, V-Mart Retail, Zydus Wellness, and Shriram Finance. Citing strong fundamentals, clear growth paths, and improving profits, the brokerage anticipates potential upside of up to 49% for these stocks. Key factors include robust order books, strategic expansions, margin improvements, and significant investor interest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:58:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695520624342f77179eea020_1767187049057.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Market Revolution: Data Now Dominates Investor Decisions, Reshaping 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Market-Revolution-Data-Now-Dominates-Investor-Decisions-Reshaping-2026/695520844342f77179eea078</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Market-Revolution-Data-Now-Dominates-Investor-Decisions-Reshaping-2026/695520844342f77179eea078</guid><description>The Indian stock market is transforming in 2025, moving from sentiment to data. A massive influx of tech-savvy retail investors, especially Gen Z, prioritizes data-led insights. This trend is maturing the market, enhancing resilience, and shaping investment strategies for 2026 across mutual funds, PMS, and new SIFs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:58:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695520844342f77179eea077_1767186836707.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>