<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:42:49 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Mahindra Lifespace Surges to Profitability, Q3 PAT Jumps 109 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mahindra-Lifespace-Surges-to-Profitability-Q3-PAT-Jumps-109-Cr/69806e2d47db7081af688261</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mahindra-Lifespace-Surges-to-Profitability-Q3-PAT-Jumps-109-Cr/69806e2d47db7081af688261</guid><description>Mahindra Lifespace Developers (MLDL) reported a significant turnaround in Q3 FY26, posting a consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) of ₹109 crore, a stark contrast to a ₹23 crore loss last year. Standalone PAT surged 112% YoY to ₹100.87 crore. The company attributes this strong performance to residential project completions and its Integrated Cities &amp; Industrial Clusters business, maintaining a positive outlook driven by a robust launch pipeline and healthy demand.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:30:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69806e2d47db7081af688260_1770024634486.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India, Ant International in Talks for UPI-Alipay+ Cross-Border Link</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Ant-International-in-Talks-for-UPI-Alipay-Cross-Border-Link/6980698147db7081af6871e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Ant-International-in-Talks-for-UPI-Alipay-Cross-Border-Link/6980698147db7081af6871e0</guid><description>India's finance ministry, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI), and Ant International are reportedly in discussions to link China's Alipay+ payment network with India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI). This collaboration aims to streamline cross-border transactions for Indian tourists, allowing them to use their familiar UPI system with merchants operating on the Alipay+ platform. The move signals a strategic effort by India to enhance the global utility of its digital payment infrastructure, building on UPI's rapid international expansion. Ant International, a global arm of Ant Group, would gain access to India's vast consumer base travelling abroad.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:30:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980698147db7081af6871df_1770024608686.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Boosts Tyre Sector Amidst Duty Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-2026-Boosts-Tyre-Sector-Amidst-Duty-Concerns/698069fc47db7081af687344</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-2026-Boosts-Tyre-Sector-Amidst-Duty-Concerns/698069fc47db7081af687344</guid><description>The Indian tyre industry is set to benefit from the Union Budget 2026-27's substantial Rs 12.2 lakh crore allocation to public capital expenditure, bolstering long-term demand. The Automotive Tyre Manufacturers Association (ATMA) views this infrastructure push as a positive catalyst. However, a persistent issue of the inverted duty structure impacting tyre manufacturing was not addressed, leaving ATMA hopeful for future government intervention.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:28:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698069fc47db7081af687343_1770024478663.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India Posts 7.9% Revenue Growth in Q3; New Plant Operational</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Posts-79percent-Revenue-Growth-in-Q3-New-Plant-Operational/69806d4547db7081af688082</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Posts-79percent-Revenue-Growth-in-Q3-New-Plant-Operational/69806d4547db7081af688082</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India reported a solid Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 7.93% YoY to ₹176,178 Mn and PAT rising 6.35% to ₹12,343 Mn. Nine-month revenues saw modest growth of 1.07%. The company announced its new Talegaon manufacturing facility is operational. However, it flagged potential, unestimatable financial impact from new End-of-Life Vehicle (ELV) rules.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:27:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69806d4547db7081af688081_1770024424427.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra Lifespace Posts Record PAT Surge, Slashes Debt Post Rights Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mahindra-Lifespace-Posts-Record-PAT-Surge-Slashes-Debt-Post-Rights-Issue/69806cc847db7081af687f11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mahindra-Lifespace-Posts-Record-PAT-Surge-Slashes-Debt-Post-Rights-Issue/69806cc847db7081af687f11</guid><description>Mahindra Lifespace Developers reported a stellar Q3 FY25 with standalone PAT soaring 111% YoY to ₹10,087 lakh and consolidated PAT turning profitable. A massive ₹1494.8 crore rights issue significantly deleveraged the balance sheet, reducing consolidated Debt-to-Equity to 0.19. The company also booked substantial gains from acquisitions and NCD modifications, driving the strong financial turnaround.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:26:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69806cc847db7081af687f10_1770024319532.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Campus Activewear Q3 Profit Soars 37% on Strong Sales Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Campus-Activewear-Q3-Profit-Soars-37percent-on-Strong-Sales-Growth/69806c4947db7081af687dbf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Campus-Activewear-Q3-Profit-Soars-37percent-on-Strong-Sales-Growth/69806c4947db7081af687dbf</guid><description>Campus Activewear reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with net profit soaring 37.0% YoY to ₹63.68 crore on a 14.3% revenue jump to ₹588.61 crore. The company also demonstrated significant sequential growth, with PAT up 217.4% QoQ. Nine-month PAT rose 23.0% YoY. Operating margins expanded to 14.6%.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:23:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69806c4947db7081af687dbe_1770024186137.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Insecticides India Stock Dips on Halved FY26 Guidance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Insecticides-India-Stock-Dips-on-Halved-FY26-Guidance/69806bda47db7081af687b54</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Insecticides-India-Stock-Dips-on-Halved-FY26-Guidance/69806bda47db7081af687b54</guid><description>Insecticides (India) Ltd. experienced a significant stock price drop on February 2, 2026, following a sharp reduction in its fiscal year 2026 revenue growth guidance to 5-6% from 10%. The company also lowered its premium product growth forecast to 10% from 20%. This recalibration comes after reporting a 40% year-on-year decline in net profit for the third quarter, despite an 8% rise in revenue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:21:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69806bda47db7081af687b53_1770024070647.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emerald Finance Surges on Strong Q3 Profit; EWA Business Drives Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Emerald-Finance-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-EWA-Business-Drives-Growth/69806be947db7081af687c01</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Emerald-Finance-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-EWA-Business-Drives-Growth/69806be947db7081af687c01</guid><description>Emerald Finance posted a stellar Q3 FY'26, with net profit hitting INR 10.7 Cr and PAT margin around 51%. Driven by its Early Wage Access (EWA) and Gold Loan segments, the company saw total income surge 42% YoY. With a low debt-to-equity ratio of 0.2% and a credit rating upgrade, Emerald Finance is poised for ambitious AUM growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:20:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69806be947db7081af687c00_1770024051296.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's RBI Poised to Hold Rates Amidst Rupee Pressure, Inflation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-RBI-Poised-to-Hold-Rates-Amidst-Rupee-Pressure-Inflation-Concerns/69806b6347db7081af687a07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-RBI-Poised-to-Hold-Rates-Amidst-Rupee-Pressure-Inflation-Concerns/69806b6347db7081af687a07</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee is widely expected to keep the repo rate steady at 5.25% during its February 6, 2026 meeting. This anticipated pause reflects a strategic focus on navigating currency pressures, managing capital flows, and assessing inflation trends, particularly in light of a revised Consumer Price Index series. While domestic growth remains robust, external uncertainties and fiscal borrowing plans are key considerations for policymakers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69806b6347db7081af687a06_1770023957425.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sundaram Finance Delivers Strong Q3, Hikes Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sundaram-Finance-Delivers-Strong-Q3-Hikes-Dividend/69806ae347db7081af6876d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sundaram-Finance-Delivers-Strong-Q3-Hikes-Dividend/69806ae347db7081af6876d8</guid><description>Sundaram Finance reported a significant 18.9% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹541.4 crore for its December quarter. The growth was propelled by a 19% rise in net interest income and steady lending momentum, which saw disbursements climb 14% to ₹8,847 crore. Assets under management grew 16% to ₹58,236 crore. The company declared a 160% interim dividend and confirmed management continuity with reappointment of its MD and JMD.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:16:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69806ae347db7081af6876d7_1770023769556.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Fuels India's Textile Sector Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Budget-2026-Fuels-Indias-Textile-Sector-Growth/69806a7747db7081af6875a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Budget-2026-Fuels-Indias-Textile-Sector-Growth/69806a7747db7081af6875a5</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 signals a robust government commitment to India's textile, handloom, and handicraft sectors. A significant allocation under the Integrated Programme for the Textile Sector, coupled with new initiatives like the National Fibre Scheme and Mega Textile Parks, aims to drive domestic production, upgrade technology, and enhance global competitiveness. This strategic push is expected to foster employment and strengthen the sector's position amidst evolving global trade dynamics, leading to positive market reactions for key industry players.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69806a7747db7081af6875a4_1770023754059.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Noida Airport Nears Inauguration, Eyes Boost for UP Economy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airport-Nears-Inauguration-Eyes-Boost-for-UP-Economy/69806a2a47db7081af687438</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airport-Nears-Inauguration-Eyes-Boost-for-UP-Economy/69806a2a47db7081af687438</guid><description>Noida International Airport is poised for inauguration this month, marking a significant step for Uttar Pradesh's infrastructure. Developed by Flughafen Zürich AG, the greenfield project is expected to become the state's fifth international hub. Despite initial delays from a September 2024 target, the final aerodrome license is anticipated shortly. The airport's launch promises to enhance regional connectivity, stimulate economic activity, and create substantial employment opportunities in the Gautam Buddh Nagar district.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69806a2a47db7081af687437_1770023646301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharat Forge's JS Auto Sells 23% Stake to Premji Invest for ₹300 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Forges-JS-Auto-Sells-23percent-Stake-to-Premji-Invest-for-300-Cr/6980693447db7081af686fff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Forges-JS-Auto-Sells-23percent-Stake-to-Premji-Invest-for-300-Cr/6980693447db7081af686fff</guid><description>Bharat Forge's subsidiary, JS Auto, is selling a 23% stake to PI Opportunities Fund I Scheme II, managed by Premji Invest Group. The transaction is expected to bring ₹300 crore to Bharat Forge and is anticipated to close by March 31, 2026. This strategic investment aims to bolster JS Auto's growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:11:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980693447db7081af686ffe_1770023476004.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Interworld Digital Faces Fraud Allegations, Zero Revenue Amidst BSE Trading Curbs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Interworld-Digital-Faces-Fraud-Allegations-Zero-Revenue-Amidst-BSE-Trading-Curbs/6980690b47db7081af686f47</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Interworld-Digital-Faces-Fraud-Allegations-Zero-Revenue-Amidst-BSE-Trading-Curbs/6980690b47db7081af686f47</guid><description>Interworld Digital is in deep trouble. Allegations suggest the former MD fraudulently transferred the company's business and IP, leading to zero revenue in FY2024-2025. Compounding woes, the BSE has restricted trading to only once a week due to unpaid listing fees since 2018, while significant statutory dues remain outstanding since 2009-2010.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:10:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980690b47db7081af686f46_1770023315553.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki Faces Production Bottleneck Amidst Booming Auto Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Faces-Production-Bottleneck-Amidst-Booming-Auto-Market/6980689247db7081af686db4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Faces-Production-Bottleneck-Amidst-Booming-Auto-Market/6980689247db7081af686db4</guid><description>India's dominant automaker, Maruti Suzuki, is confronting production limitations that are expected to persist for several months. This is causing flat domestic sales for January 2026, contrasting sharply with its strong export numbers and the record performance reported by competitors and the broader Indian automotive sector. The company faces a substantial backlog of 175,000 bookings, with popular models like the Wagon R experiencing extended waiting periods. Maruti Suzuki is actively working to increase capacity, with new lines scheduled to come online in 2026, and is exploring new export opportunities under the India-EU trade agreement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:06:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980689247db7081af686db3_1770023175054.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auditor Flags Fraud, Zero Revenue for Interworld Digital; Results Missing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Auditor-Flags-Fraud-Zero-Revenue-for-Interworld-Digital-Results-Missing/6980681847db7081af686c19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Auditor-Flags-Fraud-Zero-Revenue-for-Interworld-Digital-Results-Missing/6980681847db7081af686c19</guid><description>Interworld Digital's latest filing reveals a severe crisis: its auditor highlights alleged fraud by the former MD, leading to zero revenue in FY24-25. Significant statutory dues dating back to 2009 remain, alongside outstanding BSE listing fees that restrict trading to a Trade-for-Trade basis weekly. Current financial results were notably absent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:05:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980681847db7081af686c18_1770023111545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Grid Surges on Capex Boost and Strong Q3</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Power-Grid-Surges-on-Capex-Boost-and-Strong-Q3/698065f247db7081af686484</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Power-Grid-Surges-on-Capex-Boost-and-Strong-Q3/698065f247db7081af686484</guid><description>Power Grid Corporation of India shares climbed over 4% on February 2, 2026, buoyed by confirmation that its FY26 capital expenditure and capitalization targets are on track to exceed annual guidance. This positive outlook was reinforced by the company's strong third-quarter performance, reporting an 8% year-on-year rise in profit after tax (PAT) to ₹4,185 crore and a 7% increase in total income to ₹12,599 crore. The state-owned utility also announced a second interim dividend of ₹3.25 per share.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698065f247db7081af686483_1770023018318.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Atul Auto Jumps on January Sales Surge; EV Ambitions in Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Atul-Auto-Jumps-on-January-Sales-Surge-EV-Ambitions-in-Focus/6980662547db7081af686604</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Atul-Auto-Jumps-on-January-Sales-Surge-EV-Ambitions-in-Focus/6980662547db7081af686604</guid><description>Atul Auto's stock saw a notable jump on Monday after the company announced a substantial increase in its January sales figures. Combined domestic and export sales rose 30% year-on-year to 3,606 units, primarily propelled by a 40.8% surge in three-wheeler internal combustion engine (ICE) sales. This robust sales performance follows a quarter where the company reported a 69.5% jump in net profit and a 10.2% increase in revenue. The company is navigating the expanding electric vehicle (EV) three-wheeler market amidst growing sector competition and evolving government incentives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:02:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980662547db7081af686603_1770022927400.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bikaji Foods Q3 EBITDA Jumps 77%, Fuels Global JV Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bikaji-Foods-Q3-EBITDA-Jumps-77percent-Fuels-Global-JV-Push/6980672a47db7081af686a16</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bikaji-Foods-Q3-EBITDA-Jumps-77percent-Fuels-Global-JV-Push/6980672a47db7081af686a16</guid><description>Bikaji Foods reported a robust Q3 FY'26 with 11% YoY revenue growth and a remarkable 77% jump in EBITDA, reaching 12.5%. Volume grew 8.4%, led by strong Western snacks (&gt;20%) and Bhujia (16-17%) performance. Strategic expansion is underway with JVs for bakery products in the Middle East and operations in Nepal. Management projects 14-16% core category growth and a 50 bps EBITDA margin improvement next year, targeting double-digit market share in ethnic snacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:01:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980672a47db7081af686a15_1770022867468.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dev Accelerator Surges 53% Revenue, Seals ₹120 Cr Annual Contract</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Dev-Accelerator-Surges-53percent-Revenue-Seals-120-Cr-Annual-Contract/6980664647db7081af686705</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Dev-Accelerator-Surges-53percent-Revenue-Seals-120-Cr-Annual-Contract/6980664647db7081af686705</guid><description>Dev Accelerator Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue up 19% YoY to ₹59.2 Cr and nine-month revenue soaring 53% YoY to ₹166.7 Cr. The company secured India's largest single managed office contract in Ahmedabad, valued at ₹120 Cr annually. Driven by an asset-light Development Management Model and focus on Tier-2 cities, Dev Accelerator operates 28 centres with 88.4% occupancy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:59:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980664647db7081af686704_1770022771921.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lupin Launches US Generic Cancer Drug, Targets $930M Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Launches-US-Generic-Cancer-Drug-Targets-930M-Market/6980666e47db7081af6867fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Launches-US-Generic-Cancer-Drug-Targets-930M-Market/6980666e47db7081af6867fc</guid><description>Lupin Limited has launched its generic version of Dasatinib Tablets in the United States following U.S. FDA approval. The bioequivalent medication, developed with Pharmascience Inc., offers an alternative to Bristol-Myers Squibb's Sprycel®, targeting a market with estimated U.S. sales of $930 million. This launch provides accessible oncology treatments for adults and pediatric patients battling Philadelphia chromosome-positive conditions like CML and ALL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980666e47db7081af6867fb_1770022675115.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: E-commerce Seeks Regulatory Clarity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Budget-2026-E-commerce-Seeks-Regulatory-Clarity/69805cd847db7081af684f3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Budget-2026-E-commerce-Seeks-Regulatory-Clarity/69805cd847db7081af684f3e</guid><description>As India's digital commerce sector matures into a cornerstone of its $5 trillion economic ambition, the Union Budget 2026 is positioned to deliver crucial regulatory certainty. Stakeholders are anticipating reforms addressing ambiguities in Tax Deducted at Source (TDS), Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) for inventory models, social security for gig workers, and leveraging the Open Network for Digital Commerce (ONDC) for enhanced financial inclusion. The budget's focus on balancing ease of doing business with robust safeguards and simplified compliance is expected to drive investor confidence and operational stability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:56:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69805cd847db7081af684f3d_1770022553152.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Grid Soars 5% on Capex Beat, Strong Q3 Results</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Soars-5percent-on-Capex-Beat-Strong-Q3-Results/698064e247db7081af686190</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Soars-5percent-on-Capex-Beat-Strong-Q3-Results/698064e247db7081af686190</guid><description>Power Grid Corporation of India's stock advanced nearly 5% on February 2, 2026, after company disclosures revealed FY26 capital expenditure was on pace to surpass its annual guidance, reaching ₹29,200 crore by January 31 against a ₹28,000 crore target. The utility also reported a significant increase in third-quarter revenue and profit, bolstering investor confidence. A second interim dividend for FY26 was approved, further enhancing shareholder value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:54:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698064e247db7081af68618f_1770022359881.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Launches 4680-Powered BESS in India</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Ola-Electric-Launches-4680-Powered-BESS-in-India/698063d947db7081af685f3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Ola-Electric-Launches-4680-Powered-BESS-in-India/698063d947db7081af685f3e</guid><description>Ola Electric has begun deliveries of its 9.1kWh Ola Shakti residential Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) in Bengaluru. Leveraging indigenous 4680 Bharat cells and secured Bureau of Indian Standards (BIS) certification for its 5.2kWh variant, this launch marks Ola's strategic entry into India's burgeoning clean energy storage sector. The system offers a modern, efficient alternative to conventional power backup, aligning with market growth driven by government support and demand for reliable energy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:53:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698063d947db7081af685f3d_1770022412116.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Bonds Tumble as Tax Rule Shift Hits Secondary Buyers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Gold-Bonds-Tumble-as-Tax-Rule-Shift-Hits-Secondary-Buyers/698064d147db7081af6860f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Gold-Bonds-Tumble-as-Tax-Rule-Shift-Hits-Secondary-Buyers/698064d147db7081af6860f7</guid><description>Sovereign Gold Bonds (SGBs) experienced a sharp sell-off, with several series dropping by 10% on February 2. This market reaction followed the Finance Bill 2026's proposal to restrict capital gains tax exemption on SGB redemptions to original subscribers who hold bonds until maturity. Investors acquiring SGBs in the secondary market will now face taxation on capital gains from April 1, 2026, altering the investment calculus for a significant segment of holders. Specific SGB series like SGBDEC26, SGBSEP31II, and SGBJAN27 saw substantial declines as per National Stock Exchange (NSE) data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698064d147db7081af6860f6_1770022168684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharat Forge Subsidiary JS Auto Raises ₹300 Cr From PI Opportunities Fund</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Forge-Subsidiary-JS-Auto-Raises-300-Cr-From-PI-Opportunities-Fund/698062ef47db7081af685b86</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Forge-Subsidiary-JS-Auto-Raises-300-Cr-From-PI-Opportunities-Fund/698062ef47db7081af685b86</guid><description>Bharat Forge's step-down subsidiary, JS Auto Cast Foundry India Private Limited (JS Auto), has signed definitive agreements to secure an investment of approximately INR 300 crore from PI Opportunities Fund I Scheme II. The investor will acquire a 23% stake in JS Auto on a fully diluted basis. This capital infusion is poised to bolster JS Auto's growth prospects, with the transaction expected to close by March 31, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:49:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698062ef47db7081af685b85_1770022194383.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gateway Distriparks Expands to Central India with ₹150 Cr Indore ICD Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Gateway-Distriparks-Expands-to-Central-India-with-150-Cr-Indore-ICD-Project/6980636747db7081af685cd8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Gateway-Distriparks-Expands-to-Central-India-with-150-Cr-Indore-ICD-Project/6980636747db7081af685cd8</guid><description>Gateway Distriparks Limited is set to develop a new Inland Container Depot (ICD) in Indore, Madhya Pradesh, with an investment of ₹150 crores. This strategic move marks the company's first expansion into Central India, aiming to enhance its multimodal logistics network with two dedicated rail sidings and an annual handling capacity of 120,000 TEUs, connecting regional industries to ports and key corridors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:48:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980636747db7081af685cd7_1770022078394.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Court Blames Public Education Failure for Private School Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Court-Blames-Public-Education-Failure-for-Private-School-Boom/698063a447db7081af685dff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Court-Blames-Public-Education-Failure-for-Private-School-Boom/698063a447db7081af685dff</guid><description>The Jammu and Kashmir High Court has pointed to the "virtual collapse" of the public education system as the primary driver for the proliferation of private schools. In a ruling concerning private school fee regulation, the court observed that citizens are compelled to seek private education due to government's failure to provide adequate public schooling. While affirming the right of private institutions to operate as an occupation and generate reasonable profits, the court cautioned against undue profiteering and directed a more rational approach to fee regulation by the Fee Fixation and Regulation Committee (FFRC).</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:48:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698063a447db7081af685dfe_1770021972435.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Finance Commission Targets Dormant PSEs for Closure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Finance-Commission-Targets-Dormant-PSEs-for-Closure/6980618447db7081af685849</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Finance-Commission-Targets-Dormant-PSEs-for-Closure/6980618447db7081af685849</guid><description>The 16th Finance Commission has recommended the immediate closure of inactive Public Sector Enterprises (PSEs) to alleviate the significant fiscal strain they impose on central and state governments. The panel, chaired by economist Arvind Panagariya, highlighted that valuable land and building assets held by these dormant firms could be repurposed. Persistent losses across many PSEs, coupled with slow privatization progress, underscore the need for decisive action to improve economic growth contributions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:38:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980618447db7081af685848_1770021477851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stroom Secures ₹1 Cr Deal on Shark Tank India, Valuation Revised</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Stroom-Secures-1-Cr-Deal-on-Shark-Tank-India-Valuation-Revised/698061a647db7081af68593c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Stroom-Secures-1-Cr-Deal-on-Shark-Tank-India-Valuation-Revised/698061a647db7081af68593c</guid><description>Protein snack brand Stroom successfully secured ₹1 crore in funding from Shark Tank India Season 5 investors Vineeta Singh and Kunal Bahl. The deal, which included advisory equity, saw the company's valuation adjust to ₹40 crore from its initial ₹50 crore ask. The pitch involved intense scrutiny over product claims, particularly regarding "no refined sugar" labeling, alongside acknowledgment of the brand's ₹2.42 crore in FY24-25 net sales.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:36:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698061a647db7081af68593b_1770021390222.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Borana Weaves Q3 Earnings Surge 42% YoY Amidst Aggressive Capacity Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Borana-Weaves-Q3-Earnings-Surge-42percent-YoY-Amidst-Aggressive-Capacity-Expansion/6980601b47db7081af6854f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Borana-Weaves-Q3-Earnings-Surge-42percent-YoY-Amidst-Aggressive-Capacity-Expansion/6980601b47db7081af6854f6</guid><description>Borana Weaves reported a robust Q3 FY'26 with revenue up 42% YoY to INR 111.36 Cr and PAT surging 63% to INR 18.55 Cr. The company announced plans to double loom capacity by March 2028 via INR 350-400 Cr capex, funded by accruals and debt. A INR 125 Cr renewable energy investment aims for 70-80% power self-sufficiency. Management expects EBITDA margins to reach 25-25.5%.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980601b47db7081af6854f5_1770021305571.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ETFs Hit Circuit Breakers Amid Gold, Silver Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/ETFs-Hit-Circuit-Breakers-Amid-Gold-Silver-Plunge/6980611047db7081af6856b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/ETFs-Hit-Circuit-Breakers-Amid-Gold-Silver-Plunge/6980611047db7081af6856b1</guid><description>Bombay Stock Exchange imposed a 20% circuit limit on gold and silver Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) on Monday, February 2, 2026, following a dramatic sell-off that saw prices plunge by almost 20%. While some ETFs managed to recover a portion of their losses, the market grappled with significant volatility driven by profit-booking and global economic uncertainties. This regulatory action aims to stabilize trading after extreme price swings unnerved investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980611047db7081af6856b0_1770021203878.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Finance Slips on Tax Order Amid Mixed Q3 Results</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Slips-on-Tax-Order-Amid-Mixed-Q3-Results/69805deb47db7081af685289</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Slips-on-Tax-Order-Amid-Mixed-Q3-Results/69805deb47db7081af685289</guid><description>Shriram Finance's stock faced selling pressure, dropping significantly after the company disclosed receiving a tax penalty order from Chennai authorities. This regulatory development coincided with the release of its third-quarter fiscal year 2026 financial results, which showed a 22% year-on-year decline in net profit, despite a 14% increase in total income and robust growth in assets under management.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:32:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69805deb47db7081af685288_1770021122145.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Plunge Amidst Profit-Taking, Fed Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Plunge-Amidst-Profit-Taking-Fed-Fears/69805cf347db7081af685003</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Plunge-Amidst-Profit-Taking-Fed-Fears/69805cf347db7081af685003</guid><description>Precious metals gold and silver suffered severe, historic sell-offs in late January 2026, wiping out trillions in market value after hitting record peaks. The dramatic downturn followed record highs, triggered by aggressive profit-taking, margin hikes, and concerns over potential hawkish shifts in U.S. monetary policy following the Federal Reserve Chair nomination. Despite the volatility, many analysts maintain that underlying fundamentals supporting a long-term bullish trend remain intact.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:24:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69805cf347db7081af685002_1770020641359.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: BFSI Sector Faces Yield Hikes, Digital Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Budget-2026-BFSI-Sector-Faces-Yield-Hikes-Digital-Boost/69805dca47db7081af68519d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Budget-2026-BFSI-Sector-Faces-Yield-Hikes-Digital-Boost/69805dca47db7081af68519d</guid><description>India's 2026 Union Budget introduces a bifurcated outlook for the Banking, Financial Services, and Insurance (BFSI) sector. Elevated government borrowing is set to increase bond yields, potentially straining bank treasury portfolios and raising costs for non-bank finance companies. Conversely, significant boosts to UPI incentive allocations offer a tailwind for digital payment players. The budget also signals structural reviews for the banking sector and introduces targeted measures for MSME financing and infrastructure development, alongside plans to restructure select public sector NBFCs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:22:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69805dca47db7081af68519c_1770020409580.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Auto Sales Surge 11% on Record Despatches</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Auto-Sales-Surge-11percent-on-Record-Despatches/69805af747db7081af68487e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Auto-Sales-Surge-11percent-on-Record-Despatches/69805af747db7081af68487e</guid><description>The Indian automotive sector commenced 2026 with robust momentum, as passenger vehicle wholesales surged by more than 11% year-on-year to approximately 4.50 lakh units in January. This strong performance was underpinned by record-breaking despatches from market leader Maruti Suzuki India, significant growth from Mahindra &amp; Mahindra and Hyundai Motor India, and healthy gains in the two-wheeler segment. Companies are navigating production challenges and commodity price volatility while leveraging sustained consumer demand.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69805af747db7081af68487d_1770020109414.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: Tax Stability, No New Reliefs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Budget-2026-Tax-Stability-No-New-Reliefs/69805b7b47db7081af684c43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Budget-2026-Tax-Stability-No-New-Reliefs/69805b7b47db7081af684c43</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 maintained the status quo for income tax slabs and rates, prioritizing stability over new relief measures for millions of taxpayers. The established choice between the old regime with deductions and the new regime offering lower rates continues, with specific benefits for middle-income earners under the latter. Procedural compliance changes were introduced, including an extended deadline for revised returns.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:14:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69805b7b47db7081af684c42_1770019955587.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Enter Post-Budget Caution Zone</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Enter-Post-Budget-Caution-Zone/69805b4a47db7081af684b17</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Enter-Post-Budget-Caution-Zone/69805b4a47db7081af684b17</guid><description>The Indian stock market is navigating a post-Budget 2026 landscape characterized by caution and profit-taking across major sector indices. Analysts anticipate a period of consolidation as investors digest new fiscal policies, leading to range-bound movements and a heightened focus on individual stock performance. Key indices like Financial Services, Realty, Metal, and Auto are exhibiting signs of near-term weakness, reflecting a broader trend of reduced momentum following the budget announcements.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:09:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69805b4a47db7081af684b16_1770019792159.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apple Bets Big on India: New Stores, Chennai Hub Signal Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apple-Bets-Big-on-India-New-Stores-Chennai-Hub-Signal-Growth/69805a7a47db7081af68458d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apple-Bets-Big-on-India-New-Stores-Chennai-Hub-Signal-Growth/69805a7a47db7081af68458d</guid><description>Apple Inc. is significantly deepening its commitment to India, announcing plans for a second Mumbai retail store and its first dedicated corporate office in Chennai. These moves coincide with Apple's record-breaking first fiscal quarter of 2026, which saw robust revenue growth and an expanding installed base. The expansion signals India's critical role as both a high-growth market and a strategic operational hub for the technology giant.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:07:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69805a7a47db7081af68458c_1770019661413.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asian Paints Q3: Margins Surge on Cost Cuts, Outlook Targets 10% Volume Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Asian-Paints-Q3-Margins-Surge-on-Cost-Cuts-Outlook-Targets-10percent-Volume-Growth/6980591c47db7081af684142</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Asian-Paints-Q3-Margins-Surge-on-Cost-Cuts-Outlook-Targets-10percent-Volume-Growth/6980591c47db7081af684142</guid><description>Asian Paints reported a Q3 FY26 with moderate revenue growth of 2.9% YoY standalone and 4% consolidated, but significant margin improvements driven by cost efficiencies and raw material deflation. Gross margins rose 200 bps YoY to 44.9%, and PBDIT margins also expanded. Despite an exceptional item hitting PAT, the company guides for 8-10% volume growth ahead, fueled by innovation and B2B expansion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:01:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980591c47db7081af684141_1770019312545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>