<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:49:37 +0000</pubDate><item><title>CEAT: Demand Surge Meets Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/CEAT-Demand-Surge-Meets-Margin-Squeeze/699e7bf804a25a58c853b6a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/CEAT-Demand-Surge-Meets-Margin-Squeeze/699e7bf804a25a58c853b6a1</guid><description>CEAT Limited is experiencing robust demand across its segments, fueled by GST rationalization and improved rural liquidity. The company's capacity expansions and strategic acquisition of Camso position it for future growth. However, investors must contend with significant headwinds: escalating raw material prices, particularly rubber and those impacted by a strong USD, are pressuring margins. The integration of the Camso business, while strategically sound, adds another layer of near-term uncertainty, potentially capping earnings momentum despite a positive industry outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:35:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e7bf804a25a58c853b6a0_1771994251936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Polycab's Premium: Growth Fuels Valuation Amidst Input Cost Stabilisation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Polycabs-Premium-Growth-Fuels-Valuation-Amidst-Input-Cost-Stabilisation/699e7ab104a25a58c853b5c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Polycabs-Premium-Growth-Fuels-Valuation-Amidst-Input-Cost-Stabilisation/699e7ab104a25a58c853b5c5</guid><description>Polycab India Ltd. is projected to continue its outperformance, bolstered by robust demand and market share expansion. Stabilizing raw material costs for key inputs like copper and aluminum are expected to support margin improvement in the near term. Significant operating cash flow generation underpins future capital expenditure requirements, reinforcing the company's structural advantages in the cable and wires segment. Despite these strengths, the company trades at a premium valuation compared to its peers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:29:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e7ab104a25a58c853b5c4_1771993882900.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metal Rally Gains Momentum Amidst Growth and Regulatory Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Rally-Gains-Momentum-Amidst-Growth-and-Regulatory-Headwinds/699e79e504a25a58c853b496</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Rally-Gains-Momentum-Amidst-Growth-and-Regulatory-Headwinds/699e79e504a25a58c853b496</guid><description>The Nifty Metal index continues its strong February performance, buoyed by a weaker US dollar and anticipated demand growth, particularly from data centers. Key players like Tata Steel, Adani Enterprises, JSW Steel, Jindal Steel, Vedanta, and SAIL have seen significant gains. However, a looming antitrust investigation by India's Competition Commission of India (CCI) into alleged price collusion among major steel producers, including Tata Steel, JSW Steel, and SAIL, introduces a significant risk factor. Tata Steel also faces environmental litigation in the Netherlands. Despite these concerns, brokerage firms maintain a bullish outlook on select steel stocks, citing strong domestic demand and attractive valuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:26:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e79e504a25a58c853b495_1771993707882.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HAL: CLSA Target Eyes 38% Upside Amid Robust Order Book</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HAL-CLSA-Target-Eyes-38percent-Upside-Amid-Robust-Order-Book/699e79e104a25a58c853b47f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HAL-CLSA-Target-Eyes-38percent-Upside-Amid-Robust-Order-Book/699e79e104a25a58c853b47f</guid><description>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd (HAL) shares saw early gains on Wednesday, Feb 25, snapping a two-day losing streak. Brokerage CLSA reiterated an 'Outperform' rating with a ₹5,436 price target, suggesting 38% potential upside. This optimism stems from a projected $33 billion order pipeline for FY25-30, strong revenue visibility reaching $28 billion by FY27, and HAL's position as the 'cheapest pure-play defense stock,' even as sector peers trade at higher valuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:26:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e79e104a25a58c853b47e_1771993763243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Schaeffler India Q4 FY25 Profit Surges 31.5%; Revenue Up 26.9%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Schaeffler-India-Q4-FY25-Profit-Surges-315percent-Revenue-Up-269percent/699e79e104a25a58c853b468</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Schaeffler-India-Q4-FY25-Profit-Surges-315percent-Revenue-Up-269percent/699e79e104a25a58c853b468</guid><description>Schaeffler India posted robust Q4 FY25 results, with revenue climbing 26.9% year-on-year to ₹26,431 crore and net profit soaring 31.5% to ₹3,280 crore. Improved operating margins, driven by localization and volume gains, boosted earnings quality. The company also recommended a dividend of ₹35 per share, signaling confidence in its sustained growth trajectory and capital efficiency.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:26:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e79e104a25a58c853b467_1771993672669.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Solar Tariffs Force Indian Exporters to Pivot Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/US-Solar-Tariffs-Force-Indian-Exporters-to-Pivot-Strategy/699e78bb04a25a58c853b2ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/US-Solar-Tariffs-Force-Indian-Exporters-to-Pivot-Strategy/699e78bb04a25a58c853b2ed</guid><description>The United States has imposed preliminary countervailing duties of approximately 126% on solar cells and panels from India, citing unfair subsidies. This action has sent shockwaves through the Indian solar sector, with major players like Waaree Energies and Premier Energies experiencing sharp stock price declines. The move compels Indian manufacturers to reassess their export reliance, explore strategies like domestic US production, and diversify into alternative global markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:21:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e78bb04a25a58c853b2ec_1771993490742.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks Rebound: AI Fears Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Rebound-AI-Fears-Linger/699e78bb04a25a58c853b2d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Rebound-AI-Fears-Linger/699e78bb04a25a58c853b2d6</guid><description>The Indian IT sector witnessed a sharp rebound on February 25, 2026, with the Nifty IT index climbing 2.23% following a significant decline the previous day. This recovery tracked global tech stocks and eased immediate AI disruption concerns, with Tech Mahindra, HCL Technologies, and TCS among the top gainers. However, persistent worries about AI's long-term impact on service models and pricing power continue to cast a shadow over the sector's valuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:21:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e78bb04a25a58c853b2d5_1771993412965.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T PT&amp;D Secures Major EPC Orders in India, Middle East</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-PTandD-Secures-Major-EPC-Orders-in-India-Middle-East/699e775004a25a58c853b1b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-PTandD-Secures-Major-EPC-Orders-in-India-Middle-East/699e775004a25a58c853b1b2</guid><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro's Power Transmission &amp; Distribution (PT&amp;D) vertical has announced the securing of "Major" Engineering, Procurement, and Construction (EPC) orders for power infrastructure projects in India and the Middle East. The projects, valued in the ₹5,000 Cr to ₹10,000 Cr classification, involve the design and construction of substations and transmission lines, significantly contributing to L&amp;T's order pipeline and reinforcing its market leadership.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:15:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e775004a25a58c853b1b1_1771993012593.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coforge Rallies on Near-Doubling Target Amid AI Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-Rallies-on-Near-Doubling-Target-Amid-AI-Ambitions/699e74f404a25a58c853b010</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-Rallies-on-Near-Doubling-Target-Amid-AI-Ambitions/699e74f404a25a58c853b010</guid><description>Centrum has set a ₹2,405 target for Coforge, implying a 96% rise from its current ₹1,221 share price, citing diversified growth and a robust deal pipeline. The firm's $2.35 billion Encora acquisition bolsters its AI capabilities. While the outlook is bullish, concerns persist regarding AI disruption, integration success, and competitive positioning against larger IT players. Coforge's valuation reflects high growth expectations, exceeding industry averages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:05:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e74f404a25a58c853b00f_1771992451958.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Omnitech IPO: Growth Ambition Clashes with Financial Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Omnitech-IPO-Growth-Ambition-Clashes-with-Financial-Strain/699e74e404a25a58c853afd6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Omnitech-IPO-Growth-Ambition-Clashes-with-Financial-Strain/699e74e404a25a58c853afd6</guid><description>Omnitech Engineering is launching a ₹583 crore IPO to fund expansion and debt reduction, backed by a robust order book and strong export revenue. Despite robust growth, its elevated debt-to-equity ratio of 1.60x and stretched working capital present significant financial risks, contrasting sharply with more conservatively leveraged peers. The IPO's valuation of approximately 50x FY26 earnings reflects this tension between growth prospects and financial stability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:04:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e74e404a25a58c853afd5_1771992390440.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Healthcare Sector Booms: Valuations &amp; Expansion Risks Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Healthcare-Sector-Booms-Valuations-and-Expansion-Risks-Emerge/699e731504a25a58c853aec2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Healthcare-Sector-Booms-Valuations-and-Expansion-Risks-Emerge/699e731504a25a58c853aec2</guid><description>India's hospitals and diagnostic chains reported a robust third quarter for FY26, with revenue and EBITDA climbing significantly year-over-year. Improved average revenue per occupied bed and strategic price adjustments fueled hospital growth, while diagnostics chains prioritized network expansion and operational efficiency over steep price hikes. Top picks like Fortis Healthcare, Metropolis Healthcare, and Thyrocare Technologies are noted for their momentum. However, significant capacity additions loom, alongside competitive pressures and inflation, raising questions about long-term margin sustainability and valuation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 03:57:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e731504a25a58c853aec1_1771991959312.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fears Sink Indian IT to 18-Month Low</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fears-Sink-Indian-IT-to-18-Month-Low/699e722d04a25a58c853ad68</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fears-Sink-Indian-IT-to-18-Month-Low/699e722d04a25a58c853ad68</guid><description>Indian IT shares are in a steep sell-off, with the Nifty IT index down 21% in February to an 18-month low. Generative AI tools, particularly for coding, are sparking fears of substantial revenue erosion in Application Development and Maintenance (ADM), a key business segment. Global analysts like Jefferies have downgraded major Indian IT firms, citing AI-driven cost efficiencies and the potential for accelerating contract cancellations. Technical indicators confirm a bearish trend, shifting sentiment from "buy on dips" to "sell on rise."</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 03:53:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e722d04a25a58c853ad67_1771991726284.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ambitious Fiscal Promises Clash With Economic Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Ambitious-Fiscal-Promises-Clash-With-Economic-Reality/699e722904a25a58c853ad51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Ambitious-Fiscal-Promises-Clash-With-Economic-Reality/699e722904a25a58c853ad51</guid><description>President Donald Trump has outlined a bold fiscal agenda, proposing a new retirement savings option for private-sector workers and claiming "no tax on Social Security." However, his assertion that tariffs can replace income tax faces significant economic hurdles. Analysis suggests tariffs are mathematically incapable of fully replacing income tax revenue and historically lead to higher consumer prices and trade retaliation. The Social Security tax claims also carry specific, limited exclusions. The proposals arrive amid heightened market sensitivity to fiscal policy, with investors weighing ambitious promises against economic feasibility and historical precedent.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 03:53:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e722904a25a58c853ad50_1771991730436.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India EMS Sector: Leaders Leverage Specialization Amidst Growth Tailwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-EMS-Sector-Leaders-Leverage-Specialization-Amidst-Growth-Tailwinds/699e722804a25a58c853ad3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-EMS-Sector-Leaders-Leverage-Specialization-Amidst-Growth-Tailwinds/699e722804a25a58c853ad3a</guid><description>India's Electronics Manufacturing Services (EMS) sector is poised for significant expansion, projected to reach $155 billion by 2030. Driven by government incentives like the PLI scheme and strategic diversification into high-margin verticals, companies are experiencing strong revenue and EBITDA growth. However, the path to sustained profitability will increasingly depend on specialized capabilities and navigating import dependencies, rather than relying solely on broad sector tailwinds. Current high valuations across the sector warrant a closer look at execution and differentiation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 03:53:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e722804a25a58c853ad39_1771991724720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Year-End Tax Rush: Market Faces Liquidity Crunch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Year-End-Tax-Rush-Market-Faces-Liquidity-Crunch/699e710d04a25a58c853ac51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Year-End-Tax-Rush-Market-Faces-Liquidity-Crunch/699e710d04a25a58c853ac51</guid><description>As India's fiscal year-end approaches on March 31, a wave of tax harvesting is set to impact markets. Investors strategically book gains and losses, creating potential for liquidity shifts and price volatility. Navigating complex tax codes, particularly Section 112A for equities and Section 50AA for debt instruments, is crucial, as common execution errors and regulatory nuances present significant risks. Historical seasonal patterns suggest increased activity around this period, amplifying its market influence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 03:48:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e710d04a25a58c853ac50_1771991423001.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bernstein Bullish on Swiggy &amp; Eternal Amidst Stock Declines</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Bernstein-Bullish-on-Swiggy-and-Eternal-Amidst-Stock-Declines/699e6a2c04a25a58c853a993</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Bernstein-Bullish-on-Swiggy-and-Eternal-Amidst-Stock-Declines/699e6a2c04a25a58c853a993</guid><description>Brokerage firm Bernstein has maintained 'Outperform' ratings for food delivery and quick commerce platforms Swiggy Ltd. and Eternal Ltd., setting price targets of ₹500 and ₹370 respectively. Despite this bullish outlook, both stocks have experienced significant recent declines, Swiggy dropping for four consecutive sessions and Eternal for six. Analysts remain largely positive, with a strong majority recommending 'Buy' for both companies. However, investor sentiment appears more cautious, driven by factors such as Eternal's elevated valuation multiples and past controversies surrounding Swiggy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 03:19:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e6a2c04a25a58c853a992_1771989683593.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BoFA Elevates Vedanta to Buy, Cites Commodity Surge &amp; Deleveraging</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BoFA-Elevates-Vedanta-to-Buy-Cites-Commodity-Surge-and-Deleveraging/699e6a2a04a25a58c853a97c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BoFA-Elevates-Vedanta-to-Buy-Cites-Commodity-Surge-and-Deleveraging/699e6a2a04a25a58c853a97c</guid><description>BoFA Securities upgraded Vedanta Ltd. to 'Buy,' significantly increasing its price target to ₹840. The upgrade is underpinned by a strong positive outlook on aluminum and silver prices, a healthy dividend yield, and strategic deleveraging at the parent company. This move aligns with a generally bullish analyst consensus and a robust recent stock performance, though historical controversies and ESG concerns remain salient risks for the mining conglomerate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 03:19:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e6a2a04a25a58c853a97b_1771989677657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market Pulse: Airtel's NBFC Play, ITC's Tax Woes, Zomato's Valuation Gambit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Market-Pulse-Airtels-NBFC-Play-ITCs-Tax-Woes-Zomatos-Valuation-Gambit/699e66e804a25a58c853a72d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Market-Pulse-Airtels-NBFC-Play-ITCs-Tax-Woes-Zomatos-Valuation-Gambit/699e66e804a25a58c853a72d</guid><description>Bharti Airtel is expanding into the NBFC sector, a strategic move analysts believe is a natural growth engine, supported by strong free cash flow. ITC faces significant headwinds from a recent cigarette tax increase, potentially impacting volumes and earnings in FY27, though a recovery is anticipated by FY28. ABB India, despite robust order inflows, trades at a premium valuation (63x P/E) that analysts find optimistic given margin pressures. Urban Company's growth initiatives, like Instahelp, continue, but near-term profitability remains under pressure as it targets breakeven by Q3F28. Zomato's food delivery segment shows resilience, but intense quick-commerce competition and a high valuation raise concerns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 03:05:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e66e804a25a58c853a72c_1771989146081.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metals Stabilize Amidst Conflicting Economic Forces</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metals-Stabilize-Amidst-Conflicting-Economic-Forces/699e62b304a25a58c853a592</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metals-Stabilize-Amidst-Conflicting-Economic-Forces/699e62b304a25a58c853a592</guid><description>Precious metals showed signs of stabilization on February 25, 2026, a delicate equilibrium born from conflicting market pressures. Anticipated Federal Reserve rate cuts offer a theoretical tailwind, yet this is significantly countered by a firming U.S. dollar. Geopolitical uncertainties and the pervasive optimism in AI-driven equity markets further complicate the demand for safe-haven assets, suggesting a volatile period ahead rather than a true market calm.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:47:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e62b304a25a58c853a591_1771987767481.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Reassesses US Trade Talks, Eases China FDI Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Reassesses-US-Trade-Talks-Eases-China-FDI-Scrutiny/699e605d04a25a58c853a3f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Reassesses-US-Trade-Talks-Eases-China-FDI-Scrutiny/699e605d04a25a58c853a3f6</guid><description>India has deferred trade discussions with the United States following a U.S. Supreme Court ruling that invalidated previous tariff structures, leading to immediate, broad-based tariff impositions. Concurrently, India is exploring a calibrated easing of 'Press Note 3,' which governs investments from countries sharing land borders, including China. This review aims to balance national security with attracting essential foreign investment and technology, potentially introducing a tiered approval system for Chinese capital inflows.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:37:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e605d04a25a58c853a3f5_1771987222238.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mindspace REIT ₹350 Cr Hyderabad Hotel Deal: 5.3 Lakh Sq.Ft. Leased to Chalet Hotels</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mindspace-REIT-350-Cr-Hyderabad-Hotel-Deal-53-Lakh-SqFt-Leased-to-Chalet-Hotels/699e5e7504a25a58c85388b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mindspace-REIT-350-Cr-Hyderabad-Hotel-Deal-53-Lakh-SqFt-Leased-to-Chalet-Hotels/699e5e7504a25a58c85388b8</guid><description>Mindspace Business Parks REIT has pre-leased approximately 5.3 lakh sq.ft. at its Hyderabad campus to Chalet Hotels Limited for a luxury hotel. The ₹350 crore development is slated for completion by Q4FY28. This move diversifies Mindspace REIT's tenant base beyond traditional office spaces, adding hospitality to its portfolio and enhancing the campus ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:29:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e5e7504a25a58c85388b7_1771986678975.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India MFs Hit ₹81L Cr: Passive Surge Masks Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-MFs-Hit-81L-Cr-Passive-Surge-Masks-Margin-Squeeze/699e5b4a04a25a58c85385f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-MFs-Hit-81L-Cr-Passive-Surge-Masks-Margin-Squeeze/699e5b4a04a25a58c85385f5</guid><description>India's mutual fund industry reached ₹81.01 lakh crore in Assets Under Management (AUM) by January 2026, propelled by a 37.7% year-on-year surge in passive fund AUM to ₹15.02 lakh crore, now representing 19% of total assets. Retail investors account for 60% of this AUM, with Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) contributing ₹31,002 crore monthly. Despite robust growth, this shift signals increasing fee compression for asset managers and highlights a potential structural vulnerability tied to sustained retail inflows absorbing market liquidity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:15:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e5b4a04a25a58c85385f4_1771986194345.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Sentiment Swing: India IT Faces Volatility, Nifty Eyes Open Higher</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Sentiment-Swing-India-IT-Faces-Volatility-Nifty-Eyes-Open-Higher/699e5a3804a25a58c8538488</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Sentiment-Swing-India-IT-Faces-Volatility-Nifty-Eyes-Open-Higher/699e5a3804a25a58c8538488</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks are poised for a positive opening on February 25, following gains in GIFT Nifty and a strong rebound in US tech stocks fueled by AI optimism. However, the domestic information technology sector remains under pressure, facing significant investor concerns over AI-driven disruption to its core services, leading to a sharp sell-off. Domestic institutional investors provided support on February 24, offsetting foreign outflows, but sector-specific anxieties persist.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:11:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e5a3804a25a58c8538487_1771985962509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AXISCADES inks France deal at Embassy for India's Space Awareness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AXISCADES-inks-France-deal-at-Embassy-for-Indias-Space-Awareness/699e567904a25a58c8538123</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AXISCADES-inks-France-deal-at-Embassy-for-Indias-Space-Awareness/699e567904a25a58c8538123</guid><description>AXISCADES Technologies Limited has signed a strategic agreement with the Embassy of France in New Delhi on February 25, 2026. The pact aims to significantly enhance India's capabilities in Space Situational Awareness (SSA). This collaboration marks a key step in bolstering national security and technological prowess in the space domain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:55:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e567904a25a58c8538122_1771984633021.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Re-prices: Fiscal Stress &amp; Geopolitics Drive $5K+ Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Re-prices-Fiscal-Stress-and-Geopolitics-Drive-5K-Rally/699e53b304a25a58c8537e1d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Re-prices-Fiscal-Stress-and-Geopolitics-Drive-5K-Rally/699e53b304a25a58c8537e1d</guid><description>Gold has entered a structural repricing phase, breaking past $5,000 per ounce. This ascent is driven by persistent global fiscal stress, record sovereign debt, and escalating geopolitical uncertainties, diminishing trust in policy-driven yields. Central bank diversification and tight physical supply provide underlying support, positioning gold as a strategic reserve asset rather than a mere inflation hedge. Analysts foresee continued strength, signaling a long-term shift in global financial architecture.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:43:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e53b304a25a58c8537e1c_1771983965176.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US-India Trade Deal Slashes Solar Tariffs, Shifting Export Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/US-India-Trade-Deal-Slashes-Solar-Tariffs-Shifting-Export-Outlook/699e53ac04a25a58c8537e03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/US-India-Trade-Deal-Slashes-Solar-Tariffs-Shifting-Export-Outlook/699e53ac04a25a58c8537e03</guid><description>New US-India trade pact slashed reciprocal tariffs on Indian solar goods from up to 50% to 18%, a sharp reversal from earlier preliminary duties of 126% on Indian solar imports announced just prior. This move offers significant relief and reshapes export prospects for Waaree Energies and Premier Energies, while Vikram Solar navigates its post-IPO market performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:43:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e53ac04a25a58c8537e02_1771984107334.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Growth-Eco Tightrope: Resource Scarcity vs. Green Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Eco-Tightrope-Resource-Scarcity-vs-Green-Ambition/699e52a204a25a58c8537c46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Eco-Tightrope-Resource-Scarcity-vs-Green-Ambition/699e52a204a25a58c8537c46</guid><description>India's ambitious drive for economic dominance and high-income status faces a critical juncture. Achieving nearly 9% annual GDP growth and reclaiming 18% of global GDP by 2050 requires simultaneous, rapid decarbonization. However, severe import dependency for essential critical minerals, particularly from China, coupled with a tight climate window, creates significant execution risks. This dual imperative necessitates a strategic balancing act between growth imperatives and environmental sustainability, with substantial implications for market valuations and investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:38:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e52a204a25a58c8537c45_1771983647448.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MatX Secures $500M to Challenge Nvidia with Ambitious AI Chip Claims</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MatX-Secures-500M-to-Challenge-Nvidia-with-Ambitious-AI-Chip-Claims/699e4f4804a25a58c8537946</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MatX-Secures-500M-to-Challenge-Nvidia-with-Ambitious-AI-Chip-Claims/699e4f4804a25a58c8537946</guid><description>MatX, a startup featuring former Google TPU engineers, has secured $500 million in Series B funding, co-led by Jane Street and Leopold Aschenbrenner's Situational Awareness fund. The company aims to deliver AI processors ten times more effective than Nvidia's GPUs for LLM training and inference by 2027. This infusion of capital underscores significant investor confidence in specialized AI hardware, though MatX faces a formidable challenge against incumbents and a crowded startup ecosystem. The funding follows a $100 million Series A, which valued the company at over $300 million.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:24:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e4f4804a25a58c8537945_1771982956609.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Biocon Q3 FY26 Profit Surges 475% on Integration Push; Revenue Up 11%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biocon-Q3-FY26-Profit-Surges-475percent-on-Integration-Push-Revenue-Up-11percent/699e4d1c04a25a58c85377b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biocon-Q3-FY26-Profit-Surges-475percent-on-Integration-Push-Revenue-Up-11percent/699e4d1c04a25a58c85377b9</guid><description>Biocon reported a robust Q3 FY26, with reported net profit soaring 475% year-on-year to ₹144 crore on an 11% rise in total revenue to ₹4,290 crore. The company is actively integrating Biocon Biologics as a wholly-owned subsidiary, a move aimed at simplifying its structure and unlocking synergies. Growth was led by strong performances in its Generics and Biosimilars segments, though the CRDMO segment saw a revenue dip.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:15:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e4d1c04a25a58c85377b8_1771983193597.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Prices Surge on Geopolitics, Fundamentals Lag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Surge-on-Geopolitics-Fundamentals-Lag/699e4c6904a25a58c85376ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Surge-on-Geopolitics-Fundamentals-Lag/699e4c6904a25a58c85376ef</guid><description>Geopolitical tensions surrounding US-Iran nuclear talks and significant military deployments have propelled oil prices to six-month peaks. Brent crude hovers near $71 and WTI around $66 per barrel. However, this rally appears increasingly disconnected from underlying fundamentals, with analysts forecasting a substantial supply surplus for 2026. The market's focus on the Strait of Hormuz chokepoint risk may be overpricing potential disruptions, masking growing inventory levels and bearish EIA price targets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e4c6904a25a58c85376ee_1771983677165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Capex Rally Faces Reality: Execution Woes Plague Smaller EPC Players</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capex-Rally-Faces-Reality-Execution-Woes-Plague-Smaller-EPC-Players/699e4a3304a25a58c8537419</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capex-Rally-Faces-Reality-Execution-Woes-Plague-Smaller-EPC-Players/699e4a3304a25a58c8537419</guid><description>India's capital expenditure sector, energized by a 9% budget allocation hike to ₹12.2 lakh crore for FY27, is seeing investors look beyond large players like L&amp;T and ABB India towards smaller EPC firms. However, these smaller companies face significant headwinds. The December 2025 quarter highlighted project implementation delays and land acquisition issues, compounded by rising input costs for cement and steel, which are compressing operating margins. While order books remain robust, the ability to execute these projects efficiently amidst these challenges is a critical concern for investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:02:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e4a3304a25a58c8537418_1771983443450.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dhawan's Contrarian Bets: Bluspring &amp; AGI - Value Trap or Rebound?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhawans-Contrarian-Bets-Bluspring-and-AGI-Value-Trap-or-Rebound/699e49e204a25a58c85373ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhawans-Contrarian-Bets-Bluspring-and-AGI-Value-Trap-or-Rebound/699e49e204a25a58c85373ae</guid><description>Veteran investor Ashish Dhawan is doubling down on infrastructure services firm Bluspring Enterprises and packaging solutions provider AGI Greenpac, significantly increasing his stake in both. While Bluspring grapples with consistent net losses despite revenue growth, AGI Greenpac faces regulatory hurdles after a Supreme Court ruling, despite strong operational metrics. This aggressive accumulation signals a high-conviction play against prevailing market skepticism, raising questions about whether these are deep-value opportunities or potential value traps.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:01:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e49e204a25a58c85373ad_1771981849070.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>WTO Faces Geopolitical Reckoning on Industrial Policy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/WTO-Faces-Geopolitical-Reckoning-on-Industrial-Policy/699e49d104a25a58c853738a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/WTO-Faces-Geopolitical-Reckoning-on-Industrial-Policy/699e49d104a25a58c853738a</guid><description>The upcoming 14th WTO Ministerial Conference (MC-14) will confront escalating global industrial policy interventions, export controls, and subsidy disputes, highlighted by China's challenges to India's manufacturing incentives. This battleground reflects a broader geopolitical shift where national security and supply chain resilience supersede traditional trade liberalization, challenging the WTO's foundational principles and capacity to mediate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:01:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e49d104a25a58c8537389_1771981413747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Incentive Maze Risks Stifling True Innovation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Incentive-Maze-Risks-Stifling-True-Innovation/699e496804a25a58c85372a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Incentive-Maze-Risks-Stifling-True-Innovation/699e496804a25a58c85372a1</guid><description>Recent revelations from the India AI Impact Summit 2026 highlight a critical disconnect: a surge in patent filings, particularly from private universities, is driven by reimbursement and ranking incentives rather than demonstrable innovation or commercial success. This 'innovation theater' risks undermining India's ambition to be an AI powerhouse, as low patent grant rates and limited market translation contrast sharply with global benchmarks and the nation's growing talent pool and investment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:59:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e496804a25a58c85372a0_1771982719299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks' NIM Squeeze Deepens as Deposit Flight Fuels Costly Funding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-NIM-Squeeze-Deepens-as-Deposit-Flight-Fuels-Costly-Funding/699e495b04a25a58c8537282</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-NIM-Squeeze-Deepens-as-Deposit-Flight-Fuels-Costly-Funding/699e495b04a25a58c8537282</guid><description>Indian banks are grappling with a significant squeeze on Net Interest Margins (NIMs) as a structural shift sees low-cost retail deposits migrate to alternative investments. This outflow compels banks to seek expensive wholesale funding, widening the gap between asset yields and liability costs. Compounding this are permanent liquidity leaks from tax payments, physical cash withdrawals, and RBI currency mop-ups. Banks must urgently recalibrate business models beyond reactive rate hikes to manage heightened funding costs and structural liquidity mismatches.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e495b04a25a58c8537281_1771981612877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jonjua Overseas: Promoter entity sells 2.98% stake via off-market trade</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jonjua-Overseas-Promoter-entity-sells-298percent-stake-via-off-market-trade/699e434104a25a58c8536e2b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jonjua-Overseas-Promoter-entity-sells-298percent-stake-via-off-market-trade/699e434104a25a58c8536e2b</guid><description>Jonjua Air Limited, a promoter group entity of Jonjua Overseas Limited, has divested 4.43 lakh shares, representing 2.98% of the total equity. The off-market transaction on February 24, 2026, reduces Jonjua Air's stake to 9.18%. This follows a previous stake sale by the same entity in early January.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:33:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e434104a25a58c8536e2a_1771983721706.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Prioritizes Stability in Coal Exchange Reform</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Prioritizes-Stability-in-Coal-Exchange-Reform/699e3da604a25a58c85369fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Prioritizes-Stability-in-Coal-Exchange-Reform/699e3da604a25a58c85369fb</guid><description>Coal India Limited is advocating for a phased introduction of the proposed coal exchange mechanism, prioritizing stability in electricity tariffs and national energy security. The company, while aligning with reformist agendas, stresses the need for calibrated implementation to protect long-term power assets from excessive market volatility. Executive Director V.S. Maharaj articulated this position at the Indian Coal Markets Conference, noting that modernization must be carefully managed. Mjunction Services Limited, a joint venture between Tata Steel and SAIL, has expressed strong interest in developing India's coal exchange, leveraging two decades of experience in coal auctions. The coal ministry has initiated public consultation on draft rules for the coal exchange, following amendments to the Mines and Minerals (Development and Regulation) Act.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:09:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e3da604a25a58c85369fa_1771979362379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TANFAC EGM Approves ₹500Cr Fundraise, Share Sub-division</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/TANFAC-EGM-Approves-500Cr-Fundraise-Share-Sub-division/699e3cb504a25a58c85368cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/TANFAC-EGM-Approves-500Cr-Fundraise-Share-Sub-division/699e3cb504a25a58c85368cd</guid><description>TANFAC Industries' Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on February 23, 2026, saw shareholders approve a significant ₹500 crore equity fundraising plan and the sub-division of equity shares. The meeting also sanctioned leadership changes, appointing Mr. Afzal Harunbhai Malkani as Managing Director and Mrs. Sandhya Venugopal Sharma as a Director. These moves signal potential strategic shifts and enhanced shareholder accessibility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:05:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e3cb504a25a58c85368cc_1771979119517.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>