<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:53 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Auto Stocks Surge as December Sales Jump 67%! SML Mahindra Leads Charge – Is Your Portfolio Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Stocks-Surge-as-December-Sales-Jump-67percent-SML-Mahindra-Leads-Charge-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/6955eeac4342f77179f3dba8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Stocks-Surge-as-December-Sales-Jump-67percent-SML-Mahindra-Leads-Charge-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/6955eeac4342f77179f3dba8</guid><description>December auto sales for 2025 showed robust growth, with SML Mahindra reporting a 67% year-on-year increase to 1,044 units, driven by strong cargo and passenger vehicle sales. VAHAN data indicated a 9% overall registration rise in December, though two-wheelers lagged. Key players like Maruti Suzuki and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra are set to launch new models in January 2026, while the Nifty Auto index ended 2025 with a significant 21.8% gain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:42:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955eeac4342f77179f3dba7_1767239415384.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Shut, But India's Dalal Street OPEN on New Year's Day 2026! Traders Rejoice!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Global-Markets-Shut-But-Indias-Dalal-Street-OPEN-on-New-Years-Day-2026-Traders-Rejoice/6955ee624342f77179f3db05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Global-Markets-Shut-But-Indias-Dalal-Street-OPEN-on-New-Years-Day-2026-Traders-Rejoice/6955ee624342f77179f3db05</guid><description>Indian stock markets, including the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) and National Stock Exchange (NSE), will operate as usual on New Year's Day, January 1, 2026. This contrasts sharply with most global equity markets which will remain closed. Commodity markets will also be functional during daytime hours, though evening sessions are suspended. Investors can plan accordingly, as exchanges have released the full 2026 holiday calendar listing 15 trading holidays.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:39:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955ee624342f77179f3db04_1767239341510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Factories Roar Back: Will November's Record Surge Ignite a 2026 Turnaround?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Factories-Roar-Back-Will-Novembers-Record-Surge-Ignite-a-2026-Turnaround/6955edc74342f77179f3d9ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Factories-Roar-Back-Will-Novembers-Record-Surge-Ignite-a-2026-Turnaround/6955edc74342f77179f3d9ea</guid><description>India's industrial production surged 6.7% year-on-year in November 2025, its highest since October 2023, with manufacturing up 8%. Capital goods and consumer goods also showed strong growth, and only three manufacturing sectors contracted. However, consumer durables show long-term stagnation, and the sustainability of consumption demand and capital expenditure is key. A new IIP series in 2026 will provide a clearer picture of India's industrial future.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:37:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955edc74342f77179f3d9e9_1767239181473.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Giants Unleash $15 Trillion: Tech's Next Big Boom Ignited!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-Giants-Unleash-15-Trillion-Techs-Next-Big-Boom-Ignited/6955e99d4342f77179f3cd96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-Giants-Unleash-15-Trillion-Techs-Next-Big-Boom-Ignited/6955e99d4342f77179f3cd96</guid><description>Global sovereign wealth funds (SWFs) reached a record $15 trillion in assets under management in 2025. They significantly increased technology investments, ploughing $66 billion into artificial intelligence and digitalization. Middle Eastern SWFs, including Abu Dhabi's Mubadala Investment Co., Kuwait Investment Authority, and Qatar Investment Authority, led this surge. The United States emerged as the primary destination for these substantial state-owned investments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:10:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e99d4342f77179f3cd95_1767238168317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New Year Stock Surge Alert! Top Companies Making Waves on Jan 1st - Don't Miss Out!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/New-Year-Stock-Surge-Alert-Top-Companies-Making-Waves-on-Jan-1st-Dont-Miss-Out/6955e8ad4342f77179f3cb6f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/New-Year-Stock-Surge-Alert-Top-Companies-Making-Waves-on-Jan-1st-Dont-Miss-Out/6955e8ad4342f77179f3cb6f</guid><description>The Indian stock market is poised for a higher opening on January 1, 2026, with GIFT Nifty futures showing gains. Investors are watching Vodafone Idea for clarifications on AGR dues and promoter funding, while RBL Bank seeks to cap foreign shareholding. Jindal Poly reported a Q2 net loss. Auto stocks like Maruti Suzuki and Tata Motors will be in focus for December sales data. NCC and NBCC secured new orders. Updates also include leadership changes at Hyundai Motor India, Jio Financial Services' investment, Zaggle's partnership, Dr. Reddy's FDA update, Blue Dart's tax revision, Adani Enterprises' acquisition, and Tata Steel's subsidiary investment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:10:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e8ad4342f77179f3cb6e_1767237896659.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto's 2026 Future: Stability, Growth, and US-Led Integration Predicted Amidst Regulatory Clarity!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cryptos-2026-Future-Stability-Growth-and-US-Led-Integration-Predicted-Amidst-Regulatory-Clarity/6955e8e94342f77179f3cbfb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cryptos-2026-Future-Stability-Growth-and-US-Led-Integration-Predicted-Amidst-Regulatory-Clarity/6955e8e94342f77179f3cbfb</guid><description>Analysts are optimistic about cryptocurrencies in 2026, forecasting increased stability and growth due to clearer regulations and greater institutional involvement. The US is set to lead with initiatives like the Crypto Strategic Reserve and the GENIUS Act. India remains a global adoption leader, though regulatory clarity is crucial for its continued growth. Stablecoins and AI-blockchain convergence are key future drivers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:10:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e8e94342f77179f3cbfa_1767238015089.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Bond Investors Set for Massive Windfall: Sovereign Gold Bond 2018-19 Series IV Offers 400%+ Returns!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Gold-Bond-Investors-Set-for-Massive-Windfall-Sovereign-Gold-Bond-2018-19-Series-IV-Offers-400percent-Returns/6955e7a94342f77179f3c908</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Gold-Bond-Investors-Set-for-Massive-Windfall-Sovereign-Gold-Bond-2018-19-Series-IV-Offers-400percent-Returns/6955e7a94342f77179f3c908</guid><description>Investors in Sovereign Gold Bond (SGB) 2018-19 Series IV are poised for significant gains as premature redemption begins January 1, 2026. The Reserve Bank of India has set the redemption price at ₹13,486 per unit, marking over a four-fold return from the issue price of ₹3,119 per gram (effective price potentially lower with online discount). This payout, plus an annual 2.5% interest and tax-exempt capital gains, makes it a highly rewarding investment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:09:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e7a94342f77179f3c907_1767237786926.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zomato CEO Deepinder Goyal Set to Invest $25 Million in Space Tech Startup Pixxel's Mega Funding Round!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Zomato-CEO-Deepinder-Goyal-Set-to-Invest-25-Million-in-Space-Tech-Startup-Pixxels-Mega-Funding-Round/6955e79a4342f77179f3c890</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Zomato-CEO-Deepinder-Goyal-Set-to-Invest-25-Million-in-Space-Tech-Startup-Pixxels-Mega-Funding-Round/6955e79a4342f77179f3c890</guid><description>Zomato founder and CEO Deepinder Goyal is reportedly investing $25 million personally in space technology startup Pixxel's latest funding round. Pixxel is aiming to raise between $55 million and $60 million, potentially up to $100 million, in what would be its largest funding round to date. This significant capital infusion highlights growing investor interest in India's deep tech and space sectors, marking Goyal's first major investment in space technology.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:05:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e79a4342f77179f3c88f_1767237644243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Bond Investors Rejoice: RBI Redemption Yields Staggering 387% Returns!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Bond-Investors-Rejoice-RBI-Redemption-Yields-Staggering-387percent-Returns/6955e75a4342f77179f3c7d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Bond-Investors-Rejoice-RBI-Redemption-Yields-Staggering-387percent-Returns/6955e75a4342f77179f3c7d3</guid><description>Investors in the Reserve Bank of India's (RBI) Sovereign Gold Bond (SGB) 2017-18 Series XIV are set for a major payout on January 1, 2026. The bond matures after an eight-year tenure, offering investors approximately 387% in total returns. This includes significant price appreciation and a fixed 2.5% annual interest, with capital gains on redemption being tax-free for individuals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:05:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e75a4342f77179f3c7d2_1767237554222.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Surprise Looms: India's GDP Growth Slowdown Threatens Fiscal Targets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Surprise-Looms-Indias-GDP-Growth-Slowdown-Threatens-Fiscal-Targets/6955e6d04342f77179f3c5cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Surprise-Looms-Indias-GDP-Growth-Slowdown-Threatens-Fiscal-Targets/6955e6d04342f77179f3c5cd</guid><description>India's nominal GDP growth is slowing down, potentially falling short of the 10.5 percent assumption for FY26. This deceleration, driven by low inflation, directly impacts government revenue estimates and the fiscal deficit target. If the actual growth is lower, the government may need to adjust spending or face a wider deficit, which could concern markets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:05:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e6d04342f77179f3c5cc_1767237404106.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Spam Call Crisis: Indian Telecom Giants Demand Big Hike in International Call Rates!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Spam-Call-Crisis-Indian-Telecom-Giants-Demand-Big-Hike-in-International-Call-Rates/6955e6f64342f77179f3c686</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Spam-Call-Crisis-Indian-Telecom-Giants-Demand-Big-Hike-in-International-Call-Rates/6955e6f64342f77179f3c686</guid><description>Leading Indian telecom operators, including Reliance Jio, Bharti Airtel, and Vodafone Idea, are urging the Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI) to significantly increase international call termination charges (ITCs). They argue that the current low rates of ₹0.65 per minute, compared to global benchmarks, create a 'spam arbitrage' opportunity for fraudsters. The proposal seeks to raise ITCs to ₹4.5 per minute to curb unsolicited and fraudulent calls entering India.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:03:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e6f64342f77179f3c685_1767237667650.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo's 2026 Vision: Stability &amp; Global Routes Unveiled! New Jet Debut Sparks Excitement!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-2026-Vision-Stability-and-Global-Routes-Unveiled-New-Jet-Debut-Sparks-Excitement/6955e6784342f77179f3c4c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-2026-Vision-Stability-and-Global-Routes-Unveiled-New-Jet-Debut-Sparks-Excitement/6955e6784342f77179f3c4c6</guid><description>IndiGo is prioritizing operational reliability for 2026, balancing network densification with limited international expansion. The airline will launch non-stop flights to Athens on January 23, 2026, marking the debut of the Airbus A321XLR, expected to enable new international markets. IndiGo is also preparing to operate from Noida International Airport (Jewar) and is fully cooperating with the Directorate General of Civil Aviation's review following recent disruptions. While long-term fleet ambitions remain, the near-term outlook is measured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:03:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e6784342f77179f3c4c5_1767237424001.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Films &amp; Shows: Publish Books First? Legal Shield Trend Takes Over!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indian-Films-and-Shows-Publish-Books-First-Legal-Shield-Trend-Takes-Over/6955e6384342f77179f3c3df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indian-Films-and-Shows-Publish-Books-First-Legal-Shield-Trend-Takes-Over/6955e6384342f77179f3c3df</guid><description>Indian film producers and streaming platforms are increasingly asking writers to publish non-fiction ideas as books before developing them into web series or films. This trend helps protect intellectual property rights and avoid potential legal issues and controversies, while also benefiting publishers with added publicity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:02:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e6384342f77179f3c3de_1767237453521.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>WhatsApp India Billing SHIFT! Rupees Instead of Dollars Coming Soon - HUGE Cost Savings for Businesses!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/WhatsApp-India-Billing-SHIFT-Rupees-Instead-of-Dollars-Coming-Soon-HUGE-Cost-Savings-for-Businesses/6955e5ff4342f77179f3c322</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/WhatsApp-India-Billing-SHIFT-Rupees-Instead-of-Dollars-Coming-Soon-HUGE-Cost-Savings-for-Businesses/6955e5ff4342f77179f3c322</guid><description>WhatsApp will introduce local billing in Indian Rupees for businesses in India by the second half of 2026. This change aims to significantly reduce foreign exchange costs, eliminate cross-border transaction issues, and enable faster settlements for Indian startups and enterprises currently billed in US dollars. The move is expected to streamline operations, improve cost predictability, and potentially accelerate WhatsApp adoption among businesses. Additionally, WhatsApp plans to increase rates for marketing messages starting January 1, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:02:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e5ff4342f77179f3c321_1767237183176.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Nuclear Revolution Ignites! SHANTI Act Unleashes Private Sector &amp; Climate Goals!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Nuclear-Revolution-Ignites-SHANTI-Act-Unleashes-Private-Sector-and-Climate-Goals/6955e0354342f77179f3b85c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Nuclear-Revolution-Ignites-SHANTI-Act-Unleashes-Private-Sector-and-Climate-Goals/6955e0354342f77179f3b85c</guid><description>India's new SHANTI Act marks a major reform in the nuclear sector, aiming to boost clean energy and energy security. It opens the door for private participation, crucial for meeting the 2070 net-zero target. However, significant challenges remain regarding substantial capital investment, long payback periods, and preventing foreign technology lock-in, posing questions about the legislation's full implementation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 02:36:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e0354342f77179f3b85b_1767235730837.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Autos Roaring Ahead? Tax Cuts &amp; Rural Push Signal Major 2026 Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Autos-Roaring-Ahead-Tax-Cuts-and-Rural-Push-Signal-Major-2026-Boom/6955dd6f4342f77179f3b03d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Autos-Roaring-Ahead-Tax-Cuts-and-Rural-Push-Signal-Major-2026-Boom/6955dd6f4342f77179f3b03d</guid><description>India's automobile industry anticipates strong demand growth across all segments, including entry-level, by 2026. This optimism is fueled by rising rural incomes and recent Goods and Services Tax (GST) rationalization, which has significantly improved vehicle affordability. Society of Indian Automobile Manufacturers (SIAM) President Shailesh Chandra noted that GST cuts on vehicles and two-wheelers are being passed on through price corrections, widening the market and boosting consumer confidence. Positive economic indicators and strong order books are prompting automakers to ramp up production.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 02:26:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955dd6f4342f77179f3b03c_1767234999379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Future Investment Picks: Expert Reveals Top 3 Stocks for January 1, 2026 - Will These Soar?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Future-Investment-Picks-Expert-Reveals-Top-3-Stocks-for-January-1-2026-Will-These-Soar/6955dbb14342f77179f39331</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Future-Investment-Picks-Expert-Reveals-Top-3-Stocks-for-January-1-2026-Will-These-Soar/6955dbb14342f77179f39331</guid><description>Nuvama's Aakash K Hindocha identifies Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation, Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd, and Indian Oil Corporation as top stock picks for January 1, 2026. He notes Nifty and Bank Nifty showing positive signs, with potential for rallies if key resistance levels are breached. GMDC, BHEL, and IOC are recommended with specific buy levels, stop losses, and targets, showing strong technical indicators and potential for upside momentum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 02:20:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955dbb14342f77179f39330_1767234648450.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Stocks EXPLODE in 2025! Top Performers &amp; Shocking Reversals Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-Stocks-EXPLODE-in-2025-Top-Performers-and-Shocking-Reversals-Revealed/6955d7ed4342f77179f38d18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-Stocks-EXPLODE-in-2025-Top-Performers-and-Shocking-Reversals-Revealed/6955d7ed4342f77179f38d18</guid><description>While the Nifty delivered modest gains in 2025, individual stocks delivered record-breaking performances and sharp reversals. Reliance Industries and Eicher Motors surged, HDFC Bank showed consistent growth, and Shriram Finance made a strong comeback. Conversely, Trent and Tata Consultancy Services faced significant downturns, highlighting intense stock-specific action for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 02:01:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955d7ed4342f77179f38d17_1767233591048.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Religare Analyst's Top Picks: BPCL, Tata Consumer, Manappuram Finance Revealed for Big Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Religare-Analysts-Top-Picks-BPCL-Tata-Consumer-Manappuram-Finance-Revealed-for-Big-Gains/6955ce924342f77179f37f06</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Religare-Analysts-Top-Picks-BPCL-Tata-Consumer-Manappuram-Finance-Revealed-for-Big-Gains/6955ce924342f77179f37f06</guid><description>Religare Broking's Ajit Mishra highlights Bharat Petroleum Corporation, Tata Consumer Products, and Manappuram Finance as 'Buy' recommendations. The market ended the calendar year positively, with Nifty nearing 26,200 resistance. Mishra favors banking, auto, and metal stocks, emphasizing a sector-specific approach. BPCL shows a strong uptrend with a new breakout, Tata Consumer is accumulating near its record high, and Manappuram Finance is set for further upside after a consolidation band breakout.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:24:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955ce924342f77179f37f05_1767231182071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2026 'Goldilocks Moment': 5 Portfolio Checks to Unlock Massive Wealth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-2026-Goldilocks-Moment-5-Portfolio-Checks-to-Unlock-Massive-Wealth/6955ccd34342f77179f37bc2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-2026-Goldilocks-Moment-5-Portfolio-Checks-to-Unlock-Massive-Wealth/6955ccd34342f77179f37bc2</guid><description>Indian investors should prepare for India's 2026 'Goldilocks moment' characterized by high growth and low inflation, according to RBI Governor Sanjay Malhotra. With Nifty 50 targeting 30,000 and SIP flows nearing ₹40,000 crore monthly, five key portfolio checks are vital: assess small-cap allocation with an 86% rebound probability, evaluate exposure to domestic-focused sectors benefiting from the ₹2 lakh crore 8th Pay Commission, ensure large caps have a 15% earnings growth path, lock in yields around 5.25% in debt funds, and explore AI infrastructure opportunities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:14:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955ccd34342f77179f37bc1_1767230809369.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹44,700 Cr Shipbuilding Push: 3 Indian Defence Giants Set to Soar!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-44700-Cr-Shipbuilding-Push-3-Indian-Defence-Giants-Set-to-Soar/6955ccbd4342f77179f37b8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-44700-Cr-Shipbuilding-Push-3-Indian-Defence-Giants-Set-to-Soar/6955ccbd4342f77179f37b8d</guid><description>India's Ministry of Ports, Shipping, and Waterways has launched two shipbuilding programs worth ₹44,700 crore to boost domestic capacity and global competitiveness through FY36. The schemes offer 15-25% financial assistance for ship construction and fund infrastructure development. Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders, Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers, and Cochin Shipyard are the primary beneficiaries, benefiting from substantial order books and future project pipelines in both defence and commercial sectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:14:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955ccbd4342f77179f37b8c_1767230802014.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Trade War: India's Export Lifeline Under Threat Amid US Tariffs &amp; Geopolitical Shifts!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Trade-War-Indias-Export-Lifeline-Under-Threat-Amid-US-Tariffs-and-Geopolitical-Shifts/6955cbc14342f77179f37995</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Trade-War-Indias-Export-Lifeline-Under-Threat-Amid-US-Tariffs-and-Geopolitical-Shifts/6955cbc14342f77179f37995</guid><description>India faces a challenging trade environment in 2026, with merchandise exports expected to remain flat around $438 billion due to weak global demand and US tariffs. Services exports may reach $400 billion, falling short of the $1 trillion target. Exporters are diversifying markets away from the US, while the EU's Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism, new deforestation rules, and China's growing trade surplus pose further risks. Navigating these geopolitical and regulatory hurdles is crucial for India's competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:11:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955cbc14342f77179f37994_1767230675098.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Energy Revolution: Storage &amp; Nuclear Power Set to Dominate Post-2025!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Revolution-Storage-and-Nuclear-Power-Set-to-Dominate-Post-2025/6955c8624342f77179f3741f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Revolution-Storage-and-Nuclear-Power-Set-to-Dominate-Post-2025/6955c8624342f77179f3741f</guid><description>India is shifting its energy transition focus from just adding solar and wind capacity to building crucial energy storage and diversifying into nuclear power. Despite reaching 50% non-fossil fuel generation, erratic renewable sources limit output. Policymakers are targeting 2026 for significant progress in grid integration, storage solutions, and opening nuclear power to private investment to ensure reliable, round-the-clock clean energy supply and meet ambitious national goals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:52:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c8624342f77179f3741e_1767229615615.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Year-End Rally Ignites Indian Markets! Discover 2 Must-Buy Stocks from MarketSmith India</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Year-End-Rally-Ignites-Indian-Markets-Discover-2-Must-Buy-Stocks-from-MarketSmith-India/6955c8884342f77179f374af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Year-End-Rally-Ignites-Indian-Markets-Discover-2-Must-Buy-Stocks-from-MarketSmith-India/6955c8884342f77179f374af</guid><description>Indian stock markets closed 2025 on a high note, with Nifty 50 and Sensex advancing. The metal sector surged on government import tariffs, boosting JSW Steel and Tata Steel. MarketSmith India has recommended two stocks: Hindalco Industries Ltd and Fertilizers and Chemicals Travancore Ltd, citing strong fundamentals and growth potential. Investors are now looking towards Q3 earnings and auto sales data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:52:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c8884342f77179f374ae_1767229763227.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sebi's New Rules Cool SME IPO Frenzy: What Investors MUST Know About This Major Market Shift!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sebis-New-Rules-Cool-SME-IPO-Frenzy-What-Investors-MUST-Know-About-This-Major-Market-Shift/6955c8084342f77179f373b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sebis-New-Rules-Cool-SME-IPO-Frenzy-What-Investors-MUST-Know-About-This-Major-Market-Shift/6955c8084342f77179f373b7</guid><description>The pace of small and medium enterprise (SME) Initial Public Offerings (IPOs) has slowed down significantly this year, moving from 31% growth in 2024 to just 12.5% in the current period. This slowdown is largely due to stringent new regulations introduced by the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) aimed at curbing speculation and ensuring better governance. Alongside these policy changes, unfavorable macroeconomic conditions also played a role in dampening investor enthusiasm for new listings. Despite the slower growth, experts suggest these measures are improving the quality of companies listing on SME platforms, leading to larger average issue sizes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:52:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c8084342f77179f373b6_1767229614586.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCS Explores Gig Work for AI Talent: Is This the Future of IT Jobs in India?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Explores-Gig-Work-for-AI-Talent-Is-This-the-Future-of-IT-Jobs-in-India/6955c77e4342f77179f372ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Explores-Gig-Work-for-AI-Talent-Is-This-the-Future-of-IT-Jobs-in-India/6955c77e4342f77179f372ca</guid><description>Tata Consultancy Services is considering a new hiring model, offering gig-like arrangements for hard-to-retain AI specialists such as data architects and scientists. This move aims to address the talent crunch in India's $283 billion IT sector, allowing these experts to work flexible hours and potentially elsewhere, a significant shift from traditional full-time employment. The plan, still under development, aims to boost efficiency and manage costs while navigating data privacy concerns and margin pressures faced by the company.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:52:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c77e4342f77179f372c9_1767229640301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haier India Deal: Chinese Giant Cedes Control in $1.5B Transaction, Signaling Key Global Trend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Haier-India-Deal-Chinese-Giant-Cedes-Control-in-15B-Transaction-Signaling-Key-Global-Trend/6955c56c4342f77179f36fda</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Haier-India-Deal-Chinese-Giant-Cedes-Control-in-15B-Transaction-Signaling-Key-Global-Trend/6955c56c4342f77179f36fda</guid><description>Chinese appliance maker Haier has sold a 49% stake in its Indian subsidiary, Haier India, to a Bharti-Warburg Pincus consortium for $1.5 billion. Haier now holds a minority stake, reflecting a growing trend where Chinese firms relinquish control for market access. The deal, involving two manufacturing plants and a significant market share in appliances, underscores the ambition of Chinese companies in India despite geopolitical challenges and highlights the role of private equity as a buffer in international deal-making.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c56c4342f77179f36fd9_1767228874488.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Minimum Wage Hike Looms? India Unveils Draft Labour Rules, Set to Reshape Worker Pay!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Minimum-Wage-Hike-Looms-India-Unveils-Draft-Labour-Rules-Set-to-Reshape-Worker-Pay/6955c4804342f77179f36ed5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Minimum-Wage-Hike-Looms-India-Unveils-Draft-Labour-Rules-Set-to-Reshape-Worker-Pay/6955c4804342f77179f36ed5</guid><description>India's government has released draft rules for its four new labour codes, proposing significant changes to minimum wage calculations, working hours, and worker welfare. Minimum daily wages will be determined by family needs, including specific calorie intake, housing costs, and other essentials, signalling a potential upward revision. Weekly working hours are capped at 48. Gratuity provisions will also see changes, becoming prospective from November 21, 2025, with fixed-term employees gaining eligibility after just one year of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:42:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c4804342f77179f36ed4_1767228616145.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IREDA Skyrockets on Stellar Q3: Loan Book Nears ₹90,000 Cr as Disbursements Surge 44%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Skyrockets-on-Stellar-Q3-Loan-Book-Nears-90000-Cr-as-Disbursements-Surge-44percent/6955c2234342f77179f36c96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Skyrockets-on-Stellar-Q3-Loan-Book-Nears-90000-Cr-as-Disbursements-Surge-44percent/6955c2234342f77179f36c96</guid><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd. (IREDA) reported a strong Q3, with loan sanctions up 29% to ₹40,100 crore and disbursements soaring 44% to ₹24,903 crore year-on-year. The outstanding loan book expanded 28% to ₹87,975 crore, signaling robust growth in India's renewable energy financing sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:32:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c2234342f77179f36c95_1767228004903.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Warren Buffett's Secret Weapon: The Skill That Outlasts Him &amp; Why You Need It Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Warren-Buffetts-Secret-Weapon-The-Skill-That-Outlasts-Him-and-Why-You-Need-It-Now/6955c0784342f77179f36ae0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Warren-Buffetts-Secret-Weapon-The-Skill-That-Outlasts-Him-and-Why-You-Need-It-Now/6955c0784342f77179f36ae0</guid><description>Warren Buffett's enduring success wasn't built on innovation but on unparalleled patience. He consistently bought quality businesses at fair prices, holding them for decades to let compounding work its magic. This article reveals why patience, often seen as a weakness today, was Buffett's strategic advantage. It explores how this disciplined approach, despite market speed and technological shifts, remains the most powerful, yet overlooked, edge for investors seeking long-term wealth creation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:23:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955c0784342f77179f36adf_1767227578438.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>