<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:41:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>JCT Limited CIRP Extended 60 Days; Creditors Start Negotiations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/JCT-Limited-CIRP-Extended-60-Days-Creditors-Start-Negotiations/698f6dd59418faa08c170787</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/JCT-Limited-CIRP-Extended-60-Days-Creditors-Start-Negotiations/698f6dd59418faa08c170787</guid><description>JCT Limited, currently under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), has seen its creditors decide to commence commercial negotiations with Resolution Applicants. The Ninth Committee of Creditors (CoC) meeting on February 10, 2026, also resolved to seek a further 60-day extension for the CIRP period, highlighting the ongoing complexities and financial distress faced by the company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:30:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6dd59418faa08c170786_1771007591337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Astron Paper: 97% Revenue Collapse, IBC Threaten Survival</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astron-Paper-97percent-Revenue-Collapse-IBC-Threaten-Survival/698f6dbe9418faa08c170759</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astron-Paper-97percent-Revenue-Collapse-IBC-Threaten-Survival/698f6dbe9418faa08c170759</guid><description>Astron Paper reported Q3 FY26 results, showing a modest 6.36% YoY revenue increase to ₹1.45 Cr. However, this masks a catastrophic 97.13% YoY revenue plunge to ₹2.73 Cr for the nine-month period. The company faces ongoing insolvency proceedings under IBC and SARFAESI, with lenders taking symbolic asset possession, alongside a vacant Company Secretary role.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:30:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6dbe9418faa08c170758_1771007611757.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Electronics Sector: Growth Surge Meets Value-Add Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Electronics-Sector-Growth-Surge-Meets-Value-Add-Gap/698f6d899418faa08c1705ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Electronics-Sector-Growth-Surge-Meets-Value-Add-Gap/698f6d899418faa08c1705ae</guid><description>India's electronics sector is on a robust growth trajectory, with demand expanding at a 17.2% CAGR and exports surging nearly fivefold to $42.1 billion since 2016. Electronics has become the second-largest export item. However, the sector's future competitiveness hinges on transitioning from assembly to high-value component manufacturing and overcoming structural cost disabilities. Government initiatives like the ₹40,000 crore Electronics Components Manufacturing Scheme aim to deepen domestic capabilities, but India still lags behind East Asian competitors in integrated value chains, facing challenges in component ecosystems and higher capital costs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:29:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6d899418faa08c1705ad_1771007457917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fuels Cybercrime Surge, Boosting Security Spend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fuels-Cybercrime-Surge-Boosting-Security-Spend/698f6d759418faa08c1704df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fuels-Cybercrime-Surge-Boosting-Security-Spend/698f6d759418faa08c1704df</guid><description>Generative AI is not creating novel cyberattacks but significantly enhancing existing ones, making them faster, more personalized, and harder to detect. This evolution is driving a substantial increase in global cybersecurity spending and a market shift towards AI-powered defense solutions. Cybercrime's economic incentives are improving for attackers, necessitating a strategic re-evaluation of corporate security postures and investments to counter increasingly sophisticated threats.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:29:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6d759418faa08c1704de_1771007481319.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auditor Flags Asset Impairment Miss in Q3 Results; Governance Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Auditor-Flags-Asset-Impairment-Miss-in-Q3-Results-Governance-Concern/698f6cc29418faa08c16facd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Auditor-Flags-Asset-Impairment-Miss-in-Q3-Results-Governance-Concern/698f6cc29418faa08c16facd</guid><description>The Company's board approved unaudited Q3 and nine-month FY26 results. However, auditors issued a qualified report, noting the company's failure to assess impairment on an ENA plant, a repeat issue from FY25. With no financial figures provided, the key investor takeaway is this significant governance and reporting concern.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:26:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6cc29418faa08c16facc_1771007337709.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Solana Biofuels Q3 Loss Widens 26.7% as Revenue Tumbles YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Solana-Biofuels-Q3-Loss-Widens-267percent-as-Revenue-Tumbles-YoY/698f6c929418faa08c16fa43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Solana-Biofuels-Q3-Loss-Widens-267percent-as-Revenue-Tumbles-YoY/698f6c929418faa08c16fa43</guid><description>Solana Biofuels reported a grim Q3 FY26, with net losses ballooning YoY to ₹2.76 Cr on a 26.7% revenue drop. Nine-month losses surged to ₹9.56 Cr. The Bio Diesel segment's sharp turn to loss highlights critical operational challenges and significant investor risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:25:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6c929418faa08c16fa42_1771007464772.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fedders Holding Audit Flags Discrepancies; Standalone Plunges, Consolidated Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Fedders-Holding-Audit-Flags-Discrepancies-Standalone-Plunges-Consolidated-Soars/698f6c5c9418faa08c16f890</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Fedders-Holding-Audit-Flags-Discrepancies-Standalone-Plunges-Consolidated-Soars/698f6c5c9418faa08c16f890</guid><description>Fedders Holding's Q3 results show a stark divergence: standalone income plunged 98% to ₹0.75 Lacs with a net loss, while consolidated net profit soared 809% to ₹3,669.64 Lacs. However, auditors issued a qualified conclusion due to significant documentation discrepancies, compliance issues, and unquantifiable financial impacts, raising serious governance concerns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:24:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f6c5c9418faa08c16f88f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>M M Forgings Q3 Profit Dives 33% YoY Despite Revenue Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/M-M-Forgings-Q3-Profit-Dives-33percent-YoY-Despite-Revenue-Rise/698f6c429418faa08c16f7d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/M-M-Forgings-Q3-Profit-Dives-33percent-YoY-Despite-Revenue-Rise/698f6c429418faa08c16f7d4</guid><description>M M Forgings reported mixed Q3 FY26 results. Standalone revenue grew 11.39% YoY to ₹403.94 Cr, but PAT fell 18.79% YoY to ₹25.75 Cr. Consolidated revenue rose 10.68% YoY to ₹412.25 Cr, while consolidated PAT plunged 33.82% YoY to ₹17.57 Cr. Nine-month standalone and consolidated PAT also saw significant year-on-year declines. Management attributes challenges to global economic volatility and trade uncertainties, emphasizing operational efficiency and cost optimization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:24:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6c429418faa08c16f7d3_1771007214678.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Spectrum Foods Profit Plummets 59% Despite Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Spectrum-Foods-Profit-Plummets-59percent-Despite-Revenue-Surge/698f6b869418faa08c16f51f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Spectrum-Foods-Profit-Plummets-59percent-Despite-Revenue-Surge/698f6b869418faa08c16f51f</guid><description>Spectrum Foods reported a strong 35.63% YoY revenue jump to ₹7.69 Cr in Q3 FY26. However, net profit saw a sharp 59.35% decline to ₹0.63 Cr. Alarmingly, the cost of materials consumed (₹10.96 Cr) surpassed total revenue, signaling severe margin compression and operational challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:20:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6b869418faa08c16f51e_1771007004617.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dhruv Consultancy Reports Massive Loss Amidst Accounting Change, NHAI Stay</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhruv-Consultancy-Reports-Massive-Loss-Amidst-Accounting-Change-NHAI-Stay/698f6b529418faa08c16f422</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhruv-Consultancy-Reports-Massive-Loss-Amidst-Accounting-Change-NHAI-Stay/698f6b529418faa08c16f422</guid><description>Dhruv Consultancy Services plunged into a substantial consolidated net loss of ₹31.01 Cr in Q3 FY26, a sharp reversal from profit, driven by a significant revenue decline of 124.7% YoY. The results are heavily impacted by a change in revenue recognition accounting methodology, flagged by auditors, which reduced revenue by ₹24.97 Cr. The company also secured an interim stay on an NHAI debarment order.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:20:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6b529418faa08c16f421_1771007020228.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jeena Sikho Lifecare Surges 92% YoY on Blockbuster Q3, Eyes Global Ayurveda Leadership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Jeena-Sikho-Lifecare-Surges-92percent-YoY-on-Blockbuster-Q3-Eyes-Global-Ayurveda-Leadership/698f6b209418faa08c16f39e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Jeena-Sikho-Lifecare-Surges-92percent-YoY-on-Blockbuster-Q3-Eyes-Global-Ayurveda-Leadership/698f6b209418faa08c16f39e</guid><description>Jeena Sikho Lifecare reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue soaring 92% YoY to ₹221.7 Cr and PAT jumping 405% to ₹66.7 Cr. The company outlined ambitious plans, including expanding bed capacity to 7,000-10,000, launching 6-8 new products, and venturing into international markets like the US. Management aims to become the number one Ayurveda company globally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:19:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6b209418faa08c16f39d_1771006855549.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Lead Bank Scheme Overhaul: Increased Burden on Banks?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Lead-Bank-Scheme-Overhaul-Increased-Burden-on-Banks/698f6a8d9418faa08c16f1a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Lead-Bank-Scheme-Overhaul-Increased-Burden-on-Banks/698f6a8d9418faa08c16f1a3</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has proposed significant revisions to its Lead Bank Scheme (LBS), aiming to streamline credit flow and enhance financial inclusion. The updated guidelines, open for feedback until March 6, 2026, will increase operational coordination and reporting responsibilities for designated Lead Banks and State Level Bankers' Committees (SLBCs). These changes come as the Indian banking sector navigates economic growth dynamics and evolving regulatory expectations, with potential implications for bank profitability and operational efficiency, particularly concerning priority sector lending targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:16:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6a8d9418faa08c16f1a2_1771006729266.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aban Offshore: Auditor Issues Disclaimer Conclusion Amidst CIRP Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Aban-Offshore-Auditor-Issues-Disclaimer-Conclusion-Amidst-CIRP-Uncertainty/698f6a659418faa08c16f176</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Aban-Offshore-Auditor-Issues-Disclaimer-Conclusion-Amidst-CIRP-Uncertainty/698f6a659418faa08c16f176</guid><description>Aban Offshore Limited, already undergoing Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), has filed its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. However, independent auditors issued a 'Disclaimer Conclusion' on both standalone and consolidated statements, citing a lack of sufficient and appropriate audit evidence. This severely undermines the reliability of the reported financials and heightens concerns for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:16:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6a659418faa08c16f175_1771006732385.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IEL Ltd Plunges 91% YoY Revenue, Faces Promoter Reclassification Questions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/IEL-Ltd-Plunges-91percent-YoY-Revenue-Faces-Promoter-Reclassification-Questions/698f69fa9418faa08c16eec9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/IEL-Ltd-Plunges-91percent-YoY-Revenue-Faces-Promoter-Reclassification-Questions/698f69fa9418faa08c16eec9</guid><description>IEL Limited reported a catastrophic Q3 FY26, with revenue from operations plummeting 90.96% year-on-year to ₹55.00 Lakhs. Total expenses surged 846.75% to ₹531.71 Lakhs, resulting in a net loss of ₹474.07 Lakhs, a stark contrast to a profit last year. The company also approved reclassifying three promoter group individuals to the public category, a move raising governance concerns as these individuals currently hold zero equity shares.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f69fa9418faa08c16eec8_1771006613502.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Virgo Polymers: Revenue Surges 827%, But Profit Plummets 65%, EPS Crashes 99%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Virgo-Polymers-Revenue-Surges-827percent-But-Profit-Plummets-65percent-EPS-Crashes-99percent/698f69309418faa08c16ec8b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Virgo-Polymers-Revenue-Surges-827percent-But-Profit-Plummets-65percent-EPS-Crashes-99percent/698f69309418faa08c16ec8b</guid><description>Virgo Polymers (India) Ltd. unveiled its Q3 FY26 results, showing an astonishing 827.51% YoY revenue increase to ₹40.50 Cr. However, profitability faltered, with profit before tax plunging 64.80% YoY to ₹0.04 Cr, and EPS collapsing by 99.21% to ₹0.11. QoQ performance also declined. Significant mathematical discrepancies between revenue, expenses, and profit raise serious investor concerns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:10:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f69309418faa08c16ec8a_1771006422657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kitex Garments Posts Consolidated Loss, Auditor Flags US Investment Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Kitex-Garments-Posts-Consolidated-Loss-Auditor-Flags-US-Investment-Risk/698f69029418faa08c16eac9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Kitex-Garments-Posts-Consolidated-Loss-Auditor-Flags-US-Investment-Risk/698f69029418faa08c16eac9</guid><description>Kitex Garments announced a Q3 FY26 consolidated net loss of ₹17 Cr, a sharp reversal from a ₹40.52 Cr profit last year, despite standalone revenue growth. The company's auditor issued a qualified conclusion, unable to comment on the recoverability of its ₹2776 lakh investment in Kitex USA LLC.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:10:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f69029418faa08c16eac8_1771006420554.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Poddar Pigments Plunges: Profits Tumble 64% Amid Data Inconsistencies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Poddar-Pigments-Plunges-Profits-Tumble-64percent-Amid-Data-Inconsistencies/698f681c2e554c89b6a40206</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Poddar-Pigments-Plunges-Profits-Tumble-64percent-Amid-Data-Inconsistencies/698f681c2e554c89b6a40206</guid><description>Poddar Pigments reported a steep 64.34% year-on-year decline in net profit for Q3 FY26, alongside a 39.46% drop in profit before tax. Quarter-on-quarter, net profit fell 20.33%. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, net profit decreased 56.10% YoY. Crucially, the reported revenue figures for both quarterly and nine-month periods show significant inconsistencies and apparent typos, raising serious concerns about data integrity and making reliable analysis difficult. Finance costs also saw an increase.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:06:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f681c2e554c89b6a40205_1771006211611.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Balgopal Commercial: Q3 Profit Skews on Other Income as Revenue Tumbles 86%, Governance Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Balgopal-Commercial-Q3-Profit-Skews-on-Other-Income-as-Revenue-Tumbles-86percent-Governance-Shifts/698f681b2e554c89b6a401ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Balgopal-Commercial-Q3-Profit-Skews-on-Other-Income-as-Revenue-Tumbles-86percent-Governance-Shifts/698f681b2e554c89b6a401ff</guid><description>Balgopal Commercial reported a Q3 FY26 profit turnaround on standalone ₹5.87 Cr and consolidated ₹7.53 Cr, driven by a sharp 402% YoY surge in 'Other Income'. However, core 'Revenue from Operations' plummeted 86.5% YoY to ₹0.24 Cr. The nine-month Net Profit saw a significant decline YoY. The company also announced governance changes, including the resignation of its Chairperson and appointment of new directors, amid concerns over data integrity and profit sustainability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:06:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f681b2e554c89b6a401fe_1771006275268.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Empower India Q3 Revenue Surges 101%, But Auditor Report Faces Delay</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Empower-India-Q3-Revenue-Surges-101percent-But-Auditor-Report-Faces-Delay/698f67272e554c89b6a3edc7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Empower-India-Q3-Revenue-Surges-101percent-But-Auditor-Report-Faces-Delay/698f67272e554c89b6a3edc7</guid><description>Empower India Limited announced its Q3 FY26 results, reporting a 101.54% YoY jump in consolidated revenue to ₹4781.25 L. However, the company disclosed an inability to obtain its statutory auditor's Limited Review Report due to the auditor's critical illness, delaying final submission. Standalone profit before tax declined 36.61% YoY.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:02:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f67272e554c89b6a3edc6_1771006220808.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Minal Industries Faces Auditor's Scare Amidst Deepening Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Minal-Industries-Faces-Auditors-Scare-Amidst-Deepening-Losses/698f671a2e554c89b6a3ed70</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Minal-Industries-Faces-Auditors-Scare-Amidst-Deepening-Losses/698f671a2e554c89b6a3ed70</guid><description>Minal Industries Limited has reported its quarterly and nine-month financial results, but the accompanying limited review report from statutory auditors RH Modi &amp; Co. raises significant concerns. The auditors issued a 'Qualified Conclusion' and highlighted 'Material Uncertainty Related to Going Concern' for both standalone and consolidated statements, citing substantial accumulated losses and issues with a subsidiary. A significant provision for investment impairment in Minal Infojewels Limited further adds to investor apprehension.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:02:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f671a2e554c89b6a3ed6f_1771006207650.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vivimed Labs Files Insolvency, Faces ₹512 Cr Default</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Vivimed-Labs-Files-Insolvency-Faces-512-Cr-Default/698f670c2e554c89b6a3e918</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Vivimed-Labs-Files-Insolvency-Faces-512-Cr-Default/698f670c2e554c89b6a3e918</guid><description>Vivimed Labs Limited has filed an application for Pre-pack Insolvency Resolution Process (PPIRP) with the NCLT Bengaluru Bench. The company reported a staggering default amount of ₹512.53 Crores as of January 31, 2026, triggering these significant insolvency proceedings and raising major investor concerns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:01:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f670c2e554c89b6a3e917_1771006048880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rico Auto Posts 14% Revenue Jump, Eyes Double-Digit Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rico-Auto-Posts-14percent-Revenue-Jump-Eyes-Double-Digit-Growth/698f66a52e554c89b6a3d707</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rico-Auto-Posts-14percent-Revenue-Jump-Eyes-Double-Digit-Growth/698f66a52e554c89b6a3d707</guid><description>Rico Auto Industries Limited posted a robust Q3 FY'26, with consolidated revenue soaring 14.1% year-on-year to INR 632 Crores. EBITDA saw a significant 33.2% jump, pushing margins to 10%. For the nine-month period, PAT more than tripled. The company is optimistic about FY'27, guiding for double-digit revenue growth and targeting a 13% EBITDA margin, driven by new programs, localization, and export recovery.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f66a52e554c89b6a3d706_1771005796862.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Carraro India Faces ₹89 Cr Tax Notice; Shares Under Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carraro-India-Faces-89-Cr-Tax-Notice-Shares-Under-Scrutiny/698f66522e554c89b6a3d5c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carraro-India-Faces-89-Cr-Tax-Notice-Shares-Under-Scrutiny/698f66522e554c89b6a3d5c3</guid><description>Carraro India Limited has been served an Initial Show Cause Notice (SCN) by the Income Tax Department for Assessment Year 2023-24. The notice proposes a substantial variation of ₹89.37 Crores to its total income, citing issues related to transfer pricing and ad-hoc disallowances of expenditures. While the company is confident in securing favourable relief, the SCN poses a significant risk for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:58:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f66522e554c89b6a3d5c2_1771005810954.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Advance Petrochemicals Turns Loss-Making as Expenses Surge 63% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Advance-Petrochemicals-Turns-Loss-Making-as-Expenses-Surge-63percent-YoY/698f65c12e554c89b6a39047</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Advance-Petrochemicals-Turns-Loss-Making-as-Expenses-Surge-63percent-YoY/698f65c12e554c89b6a39047</guid><description>Advance Petrochemicals Ltd. reported a significant turnaround from profit to a net loss of ₹0.03 crore in Q3 FY26, a stark contrast to a ₹3.04 crore profit in Q3 FY25. While revenue from operations jumped 39.97% YoY to ₹72.65 crore, total expenses escalated by a steep 63.08% YoY to ₹72.68 crore, leading to a loss before tax of ₹0.00 crore. The company also noted a non-recurring loss from investment sale impacting other expenses. QoQ, the net loss narrowed from ₹0.31 crore to ₹0.03 crore. Nine-month FY26 also shows a loss of ₹0.02 crore against a profit of ₹3.02 crore in FY25.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:56:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f65c12e554c89b6a39046_1771005930638.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amalgamated Electricity Loss Widens; Auditors Warn of Going Concern Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Amalgamated-Electricity-Loss-Widens-Auditors-Warn-of-Going-Concern-Risk/698f65392e554c89b6a38f66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Amalgamated-Electricity-Loss-Widens-Auditors-Warn-of-Going-Concern-Risk/698f65392e554c89b6a38f66</guid><description>Amalgamated Electricity Company Limited posted a sharp increase in net loss to ₹0.1550 Cr in Q3 FY26, from ₹0.0193 Cr YoY, as total income plunged 69.6%. The nine-month period saw losses widen to ₹0.2545 Cr. Critically, statutory auditors issued a 'Material uncertainty on Going Concern' warning, citing current liabilities exceeding total assets by ₹0.6473 Cr.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:54:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f65392e554c89b6a38f65_1771005548801.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Deliveries Plummet 61%, Revenue Halved, Losses Deepen</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Deliveries-Plummet-61percent-Revenue-Halved-Losses-Deepen/698f64fc2e554c89b6a38dac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Deliveries-Plummet-61percent-Revenue-Halved-Losses-Deepen/698f64fc2e554c89b6a38dac</guid><description>Ola Electric Mobility Limited reported a dismal Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue plunging 55% YoY to ₹470 Cr and vehicle deliveries falling 61% to 32,680 units. Despite improved gross margins, the company widened its operating EBITDA loss QoQ to ₹(271) Cr and PAT loss to ₹(487) Cr, signaling significant performance challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f64fc2e554c89b6a38dab_1771005503320.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stylam Industries Board Shakeup: Directors Exit Amid Control Change</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Stylam-Industries-Board-Shakeup-Directors-Exit-Amid-Control-Change/698f64e72e554c89b6a38d17</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Stylam-Industries-Board-Shakeup-Directors-Exit-Amid-Control-Change/698f64e72e554c89b6a38d17</guid><description>Stylam Industries announced significant board changes, including three director resignations attributed to a change in company control. A new Chairman has been appointed, and multiple board committees reconstituted. AICA Kogyo Company, Limited, has been granted special acquirer rights, signaling a pivotal governance and ownership shift.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:52:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f64e72e554c89b6a38d16_1771005300589.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KIFS Financial Services Posts Robust 32% YoY Revenue Growth in Q3 FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KIFS-Financial-Services-Posts-Robust-32percent-YoY-Revenue-Growth-in-Q3-FY26/698f64dc2e554c89b6a38c96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KIFS-Financial-Services-Posts-Robust-32percent-YoY-Revenue-Growth-in-Q3-FY26/698f64dc2e554c89b6a38c96</guid><description>KIFS Financial Services announced strong Q3 FY26 results, with revenue climbing 32.41% YoY to ₹7.15 Cr and Net Profit rising 30.67% YoY to ₹2.31 Cr. EPS grew 31.29% YoY to ₹2.14. Quarter-over-quarter, revenue saw a modest 1.42% increase while Net Profit grew 8.96%, indicating controlled expenses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:52:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f64dc2e554c89b6a38c95_1771005370966.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PPAP Automotive Profit Plummets 96% on Divestment, EPS Turns Negative</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PPAP-Automotive-Profit-Plummets-96percent-on-Divestment-EPS-Turns-Negative/698f64cc2e554c89b6a38c2e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PPAP-Automotive-Profit-Plummets-96percent-on-Divestment-EPS-Turns-Negative/698f64cc2e554c89b6a38c2e</guid><description>PPAP Automotive's Q3 consolidated net profit plummeted 95.9% YoY to ₹0.07 Cr, with EPS turning negative at ₹(1.39). Standalone revenue dipped 5.0% and profit fell 76.2%. The company received ₹100 Cr cash from divesting its 50% stake in PPAP Tokai India Rubber Private Limited. For the nine months, consolidated net profit is a loss of ₹2.25 Cr.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:52:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f64cc2e554c89b6a38c2d_1771005429811.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vikas WSP Faces Insolvency; Auditor Flags Going Concern Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Vikas-WSP-Faces-Insolvency-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Risk/698f645a2e554c89b6a38a97</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Vikas-WSP-Faces-Insolvency-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Risk/698f645a2e554c89b6a38a97</guid><description>Vikas WSP Limited announced unaudited standalone results for Q3 FY26, revealing it's under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) since February 2022. The auditor has flagged material uncertainty regarding the company's ability to continue as a going concern, citing continuous losses, current liabilities exceeding assets, and significant verification issues with fixed assets, receivables, and payables due to lack of documentation. A resolution plan is pending NCLT approval.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:50:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f645a2e554c89b6a38a96_1771005185693.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Investment &amp; Precision Castings Secures Major Defence Order from DRDO</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Investment-and-Precision-Castings-Secures-Major-Defence-Order-from-DRDO/698f60a4cf63a6ff289c5281</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Investment-and-Precision-Castings-Secures-Major-Defence-Order-from-DRDO/698f60a4cf63a6ff289c5281</guid><description>Investment &amp; Precision Castings Limited has landed a substantial supply order from GTRE DRDO for HP Turbine Component Super alloy Castings for a critical defence application. While the exact financial value is confidential, the deal significantly bolsters the company's order book and reinforces its standing in the high-value aerospace and defence sector, promising positive financial contributions during execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f60a4cf63a6ff289c5280_1771004147060.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Inox Wind Posts Stellar Q3: Revenue Jumps 24%, EBITDA Soars 39%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Inox-Wind-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-24percent-EBITDA-Soars-39percent/698f6098cf63a6ff289c4982</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Inox-Wind-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-24percent-EBITDA-Soars-39percent/698f6098cf63a6ff289c4982</guid><description>Inox Wind reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue jumping 24% YoY to ₹1,238 Cr and EBITDA soaring 39% to ₹313 Cr. The company also posted strong 9M FY26 performance, with revenue up 36% and EBITDA up 42%. Inox Wind guided for FY26 revenue exceeding ₹5,000 Cr and EBITDAM of 20-22%, underpinned by new plant ramp-ups and upcoming turbine launches.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:34:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6098cf63a6ff289c4981_1771004105931.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Camlin Fine Sciences Faces Fire, Unreviewed Subs Raise Investor Alert</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Camlin-Fine-Sciences-Faces-Fire-Unreviewed-Subs-Raise-Investor-Alert/698f6031cf63a6ff289c3fc6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Camlin-Fine-Sciences-Faces-Fire-Unreviewed-Subs-Raise-Investor-Alert/698f6031cf63a6ff289c3fc6</guid><description>Camlin Fine Sciences Limited announced the approval of its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. However, the announcement highlighted significant concerns: a fire incident at its Brazilian subsidiary has suspended operations, with financial impact yet undetermined. Additionally, auditors relied on unreviewed financial results for several subsidiaries, raising governance and transparency questions for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:32:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f6031cf63a6ff289c3fc5_1771004009644.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Utique Enterprises Q3 Profit Turns Around, But EPS Discrepancy Sparks Governance Alarm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Utique-Enterprises-Q3-Profit-Turns-Around-But-EPS-Discrepancy-Sparks-Governance-Alarm/698f601bcf63a6ff289c3efe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Utique-Enterprises-Q3-Profit-Turns-Around-But-EPS-Discrepancy-Sparks-Governance-Alarm/698f601bcf63a6ff289c3efe</guid><description>Utique Enterprises Limited has turned profitable in Q3 FY26, posting a net profit of ₹11.78 Lakh compared to a loss last year, with revenue surging 47.44% YoY. However, a significant accounting anomaly has been identified, showing a large discrepancy between reported net profit and net profit derived from EPS calculations. The company also saw a 5.46% YoY decline in nine-month revenue and a reduced net loss.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:32:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f601bcf63a6ff289c3efd_1771003985708.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UGRO Capital Shifts Strategy, Aims INR 220 Cr Savings, Boosts MSME Lending</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UGRO-Capital-Shifts-Strategy-Aims-INR-220-Cr-Savings-Boosts-MSME-Lending/698f5fa8cf63a6ff289c3ce0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UGRO-Capital-Shifts-Strategy-Aims-INR-220-Cr-Savings-Boosts-MSME-Lending/698f5fa8cf63a6ff289c3ce0</guid><description>UGRO Capital announced a strategic pivot focusing on annuity-led income from two core MSME segments: Emerging Market LAP and Embedded Merchant Financing. The company aims to achieve annualized cost rationalization of INR 220 crore and expects future growth to be funded by internal accruals. Consolidated Assets Under Management (AUM) grew 40% YoY to INR 15,454 Cr, with PAT rising 23% YoY to INR 46 Cr, signaling a move towards improved earnings quality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:30:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f5fa8cf63a6ff289c3cdf_1771003871922.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRB Infra Okays 1:1 Bonus, Dividend; Asset Monetization Fuels Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRB-Infra-Okays-11-Bonus-Dividend-Asset-Monetization-Fuels-Growth/698f5eb9cf63a6ff289c359a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRB-Infra-Okays-11-Bonus-Dividend-Asset-Monetization-Fuels-Growth/698f5eb9cf63a6ff289c359a</guid><description>IRB Infrastructure Developers announced a 1:1 bonus share issue and a 3rd interim dividend for FY26. While consolidated income dipped 8.5% YoY to ₹1,912 Cr, EBITDA rose 1.3% to ₹1,063 Cr. Profit After Tax (PAT) saw a significant YoY decline to ₹211 Cr due to prior year exceptional gains, but PAT before exceptional items grew 14% to ₹253 Cr. The company is actively recycling assets, unlocking capital for ₹14,000 Cr in new TOT project acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f5eb9cf63a6ff289c3599_1771003656678.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPL Ltd: Standalone Profit Surges 187%, Consolidated Dips Amidst CEO Change</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/EPL-Ltd-Standalone-Profit-Surges-187percent-Consolidated-Dips-Amidst-CEO-Change/698f2e948360adfdbac994f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/EPL-Ltd-Standalone-Profit-Surges-187percent-Consolidated-Dips-Amidst-CEO-Change/698f2e948360adfdbac994f9</guid><description>EPL Limited reported a dramatic surge in standalone Net Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹126.4 Cr, up 187% YoY, fueled by significant other income and exceptional gains. However, consolidated PAT dipped 11.7% YoY to ₹83.1 Cr due to a ₹12 Cr exceptional loss. Revenue showed YoY growth both standalone and consolidated, but consolidated revenue saw a QoQ decline. The company also announced the appointment of Hemani Bakshi as MD &amp; Global CEO, effective January 1, 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:00:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f2e948360adfdbac994f8_1770991397022.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Home Loan Surge: Youthful Buyers Drive Digital Push Amidst Sector Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Home-Loan-Surge-Youthful-Buyers-Drive-Digital-Push-Amidst-Sector-Headwinds/698f2e2b8360adfdbac99147</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Home-Loan-Surge-Youthful-Buyers-Drive-Digital-Push-Amidst-Sector-Headwinds/698f2e2b8360adfdbac99147</guid><description>India's home loan market is fundamentally reshaped by Millennials and Gen Z, who now constitute 90-95% of homebuyers, driving a surge in digital applications. The market, valued at $329.9 billion in 2024, is projected for significant growth. Public sector banks lead, but private players and NBFCs are adapting. Despite digital gains, borrowers grapple with excessive documentation, mis-selling, and rising NPAs in affordable housing, signaling underlying structural issues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f2e2b8360adfdbac99146.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anuh Pharma Q3: Profit Surges QoQ, But YoY Earnings Dip; USFDA Cleared</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Anuh-Pharma-Q3-Profit-Surges-QoQ-But-YoY-Earnings-Dip-USFDA-Cleared/698f2d998360adfdbac98cb1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Anuh-Pharma-Q3-Profit-Surges-QoQ-But-YoY-Earnings-Dip-USFDA-Cleared/698f2d998360adfdbac98cb1</guid><description>Anuh Pharma reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue up 6.08% QoQ to ₹197.18 Cr, and PAT soaring 76.70% QoQ to ₹13.45 Cr, driven by margin expansion. However, for the nine-month period, revenue grew 22.91% YoY to ₹569.54 Cr, while EBITDA and PAT saw declines of 5.66% and 15.85% respectively. The company's USFDA inspection concluded successfully with zero observations. Management guides for 15-16% annual growth and margin improvement.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:56:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698f2d998360adfdbac98cb0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prudential Sugar: Auditor Flags Non-Compliance, Revenue Anomaly; Stock Faces Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Prudential-Sugar-Auditor-Flags-Non-Compliance-Revenue-Anomaly-Stock-Faces-Scrutiny/698f2d7d8360adfdbac98c29</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Prudential-Sugar-Auditor-Flags-Non-Compliance-Revenue-Anomaly-Stock-Faces-Scrutiny/698f2d7d8360adfdbac98c29</guid><description>Prudential Sugar Corporation's Q3 results are overshadowed by a critical auditor's report flagging non-compliance with IND AS, uncertain balances, and pending litigation. A significant anomaly sees nine-month revenues lower than the third quarter's revenue. While 9M PAT jumped YoY, the auditor notes an 'unascertainable impact' from these issues, raising serious governance and reporting concerns for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:56:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698f2d7d8360adfdbac98c28_1770991369820.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>