<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:29:06 +0000</pubDate><item><title>PSU Bank Stocks Tumble for 4th Day: Is 2026 Your Buying Window or Warning Sign?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Bank-Stocks-Tumble-for-4th-Day-Is-2026-Your-Buying-Window-or-Warning-Sign/69521ef14342f77179dc247a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Bank-Stocks-Tumble-for-4th-Day-Is-2026-Your-Buying-Window-or-Warning-Sign/69521ef14342f77179dc247a</guid><description>Public Sector Bank (PSB) stocks continued their decline for the fourth consecutive session on December 29, pulling the Nifty PSU Bank index down by 0.3 percent. Analysts foresee near-term volatility, suggesting a stock-specific approach due to market consolidation after a recent rally. While fundamentals like asset quality and profitability have improved, investors are advised to be selective, focusing on banks with consistent earnings growth and strong capital buffers for potential long-term compounding.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:14:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69521ef14342f77179dc2479_1766989615658.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Housing Market Diverges: Fewer Homes Sold, More Money Made! Will 2026 Bring a Comeback?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Housing-Market-Diverges-Fewer-Homes-Sold-More-Money-Made-Will-2026-Bring-a-Comeback/69521e004342f77179dc22cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Housing-Market-Diverges-Fewer-Homes-Sold-More-Money-Made-Will-2026-Bring-a-Comeback/69521e004342f77179dc22cd</guid><description>India's real estate market saw sales volume drop 14% in 2025, marking the second consecutive annual decline due to high prices. However, total sales value increased by 6%, driven by strong price appreciation and a shift towards luxury residences. Commercial real estate performed strongly, attracting record institutional investments of $10.4 billion. Developers hope for demand revival in 2026 through lower mortgage rates and potential budget support, while affordable housing segments remain under pressure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:11:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69521e004342f77179dc22cc_1766989383336.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Prices Dip Slightly! Is This a Buying Opportunity Before the Next Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Dip-Slightly-Is-This-a-Buying-Opportunity-Before-the-Next-Surge/69521cfa4342f77179dc20f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Dip-Slightly-Is-This-a-Buying-Opportunity-Before-the-Next-Surge/69521cfa4342f77179dc20f3</guid><description>Gold prices experienced a minor drop on December 29, 2025, with 24K gold at ₹139,940 and 22K at ₹128,278 per 10 grams. Despite this small decline, factors like anticipated US Federal Reserve rate cuts and global geopolitical tensions continue to support gold's safe-haven appeal. Indian prices remain higher than Dubai's. Analysts suggest monitoring global trends for investment decisions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:09:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69521cfa4342f77179dc20f2_1766989125169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Expert Reveals Top Stock Picks &amp; Nifty Outlook: Your Investing Guide for the Week!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Expert-Reveals-Top-Stock-Picks-and-Nifty-Outlook-Your-Investing-Guide-for-the-Week/69521bf64342f77179dc1ea8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Expert-Reveals-Top-Stock-Picks-and-Nifty-Outlook-Your-Investing-Guide-for-the-Week/69521bf64342f77179dc1ea8</guid><description>SBI Securities expert Sudeep Shah has named Karur Vysya Bank and Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation (GMDC) as top stock recommendations for the week starting December 29, 2025. He also provided an outlook on Nifty and Bank Nifty, noting Nifty's recent narrow trading range and low volatility. Key support and resistance levels for both indices were highlighted, alongside specific buy zones and targets for the recommended stocks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 06:03:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69521bf64342f77179dc1ea7_1766988993104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty IT Skyrockets: 'Golden Cross' Signals Major Bull Run Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nifty-IT-Skyrockets-Golden-Cross-Signals-Major-Bull-Run-Ahead/695219034342f77179dc1a5e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nifty-IT-Skyrockets-Golden-Cross-Signals-Major-Bull-Run-Ahead/695219034342f77179dc1a5e</guid><description>The Nifty IT index has surged 15% in three months, recently hitting 39,530 and outperforming Nifty 50 in December. Analysts cite valuation comfort after a 30% fall, a reversal in the global AI trade, and supportive US H1B visa policies as key drivers. With IT hiring rebounding and GenAI investments expected, the sector shows a favourable risk-reward scenario, underpinned by a bullish 'Golden Cross' technical pattern indicating a potential sustained recovery.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:43:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695219034342f77179dc1a5d_1766988210013.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BLS International Surges Ahead: 20-25% Growth Target Revealed, M&amp;A and Digital Boom on Horizon!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BLS-International-Surges-Ahead-20-25percent-Growth-Target-Revealed-MandA-and-Digital-Boom-on-Horizon/695217384342f77179dc174f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BLS-International-Surges-Ahead-20-25percent-Growth-Target-Revealed-MandA-and-Digital-Boom-on-Horizon/695217384342f77179dc174f</guid><description>BLS International aims for steady 20-25% annual organic growth over the next five years, supported by mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;A) and digital services expansion through BLS E-Services. The company reported strong Q2 financials, with revenue up 48.8% to ₹736 crore and EBITDA up 30% to ₹212 crore. Key developments include a ₹2,000 crore Aadhaar contract win and relief from the Delhi High Court, allowing eligibility for Ministry of External Affairs (MEA) tenders.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695217384342f77179dc174e_1766987684218.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titan's Daring Diamond Leap: New LGD Brand 'be Yon' Sparks Market Intrigue! What Investors MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titans-Daring-Diamond-Leap-New-LGD-Brand-be-Yon-Sparks-Market-Intrigue-What-Investors-MUST-Know/695216234342f77179dc1540</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titans-Daring-Diamond-Leap-New-LGD-Brand-be-Yon-Sparks-Market-Intrigue-What-Investors-MUST-Know/695216234342f77179dc1540</guid><description>Titan Company, India's largest jewelry player, has entered the lab-grown diamond (LGD) market with its new exclusive brand, 'be Yon'. This move capitalizes on the growing acceptance of affordable, visually identical diamonds. While LGDs are gaining traction, analysts expect minimal immediate impact on Titan's natural diamond sales in India due to the market's gold-centric nature and lower diamond penetration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:38:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695216234342f77179dc153f_1766987452802.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump's 2025 Trade War: Tariffs Ignored Economics, Triggering Global Chaos &amp; Policy U-Turn!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trumps-2025-Trade-War-Tariffs-Ignored-Economics-Triggering-Global-Chaos-and-Policy-U-Turn/695215ba4342f77179dc1447</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trumps-2025-Trade-War-Tariffs-Ignored-Economics-Triggering-Global-Chaos-and-Policy-U-Turn/695215ba4342f77179dc1447</guid><description>Former President Trump's 'Liberation Day' reciprocal tariffs announced in April 2025 have been criticized for ignoring basic economic principles and creating trade chaos. The policy, which imposed tariffs of up to 32% on imports from nations like India and Taiwan, aimed to eliminate trade deficits but relied on flawed assumptions about exports and price pass-through. Despite promises of swift trade deals, negotiations stalled, leading to escalations with China and India. Political pressure over rising prices prompted a partial rollback on food items, while a Supreme Court challenge questions the presidential authority to impose such taxes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:38:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695215ba4342f77179dc1446_1766987336931.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axis Bank Growth Rebuilding: What Motilal Oswal Sees Ahead! Margins to Bottom Q4FY26/Q1FY27? Neutral Rating &amp; ₹1,300 Target Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-Growth-Rebuilding-What-Motilal-Oswal-Sees-Ahead-Margins-to-Bottom-Q4FY26Q1FY27-Neutral-Rating-and-1300-Target-Revealed/69520ffa4342f77179dc09c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-Growth-Rebuilding-What-Motilal-Oswal-Sees-Ahead-Margins-to-Bottom-Q4FY26Q1FY27-Neutral-Rating-and-1300-Target-Revealed/69520ffa4342f77179dc09c2</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services has reiterated a 'Neutral' rating on Axis Bank with a target price of ₹1,300. Key takeaways indicate loan growth is in a 'repair phase' with advances up 12% year-on-year, focusing on granular portfolios. Net interest margins (NIMs) are expected to bottom out by Q4FY26 or Q1FY27. Asset quality is deemed stable with seasonal blips, not structural stress. The bank maintains strong capital buffers, and FY27 is projected to be a 'tailwind' year for return on assets (RoA).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:06:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69520ffa4342f77179dc09c1_1766986037901.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Rockets Past ₹50,000 Cr Mark: Stock Surges 48% in 7 Days on Copper Price Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Copper-Rockets-Past-50000-Cr-Mark-Stock-Surges-48percent-in-7-Days-on-Copper-Price-Boom/69520ea54342f77179dc0723</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Copper-Rockets-Past-50000-Cr-Mark-Stock-Surges-48percent-in-7-Days-on-Copper-Price-Boom/69520ea54342f77179dc0723</guid><description>Hindustan Copper Ltd.'s market capitalization has crossed ₹50,000 crore, marking a significant milestone. The company's shares have surged for seven consecutive days, gaining 48% and reaching ₹516.3. This rally is propelled by soaring global copper prices, nearing $13,000 per ton on the London Metal Exchange, and concerns over potential US import tariffs and supply disruptions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:06:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69520ea54342f77179dc0722_1766985457140.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Plunges! Foreign Funds Exodus Drains Indian Currency to Record Lows - Urgent Investor Alert!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Plunges-Foreign-Funds-Exodus-Drains-Indian-Currency-to-Record-Lows-Urgent-Investor-Alert/69520ea94342f77179dc0754</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Plunges-Foreign-Funds-Exodus-Drains-Indian-Currency-to-Record-Lows-Urgent-Investor-Alert/69520ea94342f77179dc0754</guid><description>The Indian rupee weakened by 5 paise to trade at 89.95 against the US dollar on Monday. This decline is primarily driven by continued foreign portfolio investor (FPI) outflows from domestic equities and a subdued opening in Indian stock markets. The rupee remains the worst-performing currency in emerging and Asian markets over recent months, raising concerns for investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:06:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69520ea94342f77179dc0753_1766985507464.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Smashes $90,000! Oil Surges as Russia-Ukraine Peace Hopes Shatter</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Smashes-90000-Oil-Surges-as-Russia-Ukraine-Peace-Hopes-Shatter/69520e524342f77179dc0648</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Smashes-90000-Oil-Surges-as-Russia-Ukraine-Peace-Hopes-Shatter/69520e524342f77179dc0648</guid><description>Bitcoin surged past $90,000 on Monday, boosting the broader market sentiment. The leading cryptocurrency saw gains alongside major altcoins like Ether and Solana. This rally coincided with a rise in oil prices, as weakened hopes for a Russia-Ukraine peace deal followed recent attacks on energy infrastructure in both nations. Asian stocks traded cautiously, with South Korea's KOSPI index being an exception.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:02:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69520e524342f77179dc0647_1766985465361.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>8th Pay Commission Looms: Will Central Govt Employees See DA Reset or Continued Hikes?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8th-Pay-Commission-Looms-Will-Central-Govt-Employees-See-DA-Reset-or-Continued-Hikes/69520de34342f77179dc050a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8th-Pay-Commission-Looms-Will-Central-Govt-Employees-See-DA-Reset-or-Continued-Hikes/69520de34342f77179dc050a</guid><description>The 8th Pay Commission is set to be implemented from January 1, 2026, but a key concern for central government employees is the Dearness Allowance (DA) merger. Traditionally, accumulated DA is merged with basic pay, resetting DA to zero. Employee unions propose an alternative where a portion of DA continues, aiming to protect purchasing power. The decision will significantly impact employee salaries and future arrears.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:01:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69520de34342f77179dc0509_1766985375428.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Debt Clock Ticking Down? Government Reveals Bold Plan to Slash Debt Ratio!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Debt-Clock-Ticking-Down-Government-Reveals-Bold-Plan-to-Slash-Debt-Ratio/69520db04342f77179dc0495</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Debt-Clock-Ticking-Down-Government-Reveals-Bold-Plan-to-Slash-Debt-Ratio/69520db04342f77179dc0495</guid><description>The Indian government is considering a significant fiscal move, aiming to lower the country's debt-to-GDP ratio to around 54.5-55% by FY27. This strategic shift, moving away from the fiscal deficit as the primary benchmark, signals a calibrated approach to fiscal consolidation. The final decision will depend on the economic growth outlook. The International Monetary Fund has also weighed in, suggesting more ambitious debt reduction targets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:01:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69520db04342f77179dc0494_1766985295551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Stocks 2026: Will AI Boom Fade? FPI Exodus &amp; Retail Power! 5 Key Questions Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Stocks-2026-Will-AI-Boom-Fade-FPI-Exodus-and-Retail-Power-5-Key-Questions-Ahead/69520cb44342f77179dc01f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Stocks-2026-Will-AI-Boom-Fade-FPI-Exodus-and-Retail-Power-5-Key-Questions-Ahead/69520cb44342f77179dc01f9</guid><description>As the Indian stock market navigates 2026, investors face five critical questions. After a narrow-range 2025 where the BSE Sensex gained 8%, the focus shifts to AI's sustainability, market discernment amid rich valuations, the potential return of foreign investors versus continued mutual fund inflows, retail investor sentiment, and the future of the IPO market. These factors will dictate market direction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 05:00:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69520cb44342f77179dc01f8_1766985170089.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Arvind Fashions to Buy Flipkart's Flying Machine Stake for ₹135 Cr: Full Control Gained!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Arvind-Fashions-to-Buy-Flipkarts-Flying-Machine-Stake-for-135-Cr-Full-Control-Gained/69520d164342f77179dc02b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Arvind-Fashions-to-Buy-Flipkarts-Flying-Machine-Stake-for-135-Cr-Full-Control-Gained/69520d164342f77179dc02b0</guid><description>Arvind Fashions announced it will acquire Flipkart India's 31.25% stake in its denim brand unit, Arvind Youth Brands Private Limited, for ₹135 crore. This move grants Arvind Fashions full ownership of the Flying Machine brand, a popular casualwear label. The transaction reflects Flipkart's strategy to divest non-core assets and concentrate on its main e-commerce operations. Flying Machine reported ₹432.16 crore in turnover last fiscal year.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:57:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69520d164342f77179dc02af_1766985085226.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking ₹2,434 Crore Fraud Uncovered: Punjab National Bank Shares Tumble - What Investors MUST Know Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shocking-2434-Crore-Fraud-Uncovered-Punjab-National-Bank-Shares-Tumble-What-Investors-MUST-Know-Now/69520d4f4342f77179dc033d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shocking-2434-Crore-Fraud-Uncovered-Punjab-National-Bank-Shares-Tumble-What-Investors-MUST-Know-Now/69520d4f4342f77179dc033d</guid><description>Punjab National Bank's shares dropped over 3% after the lender disclosed a ₹2,434 crore fraud linked to former promoters of SREI Equipment Finance and SREI Infrastructure Finance. The bank confirmed full provisioning for the outstanding exposure in both accounts, which have been resolved under the corporate insolvency resolution process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:56:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69520d4f4342f77179dc033c_1766985185055.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 10-Minute Delivery Revolution: From Groceries to Gadgets, 2025 Rewrites Retail!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-10-Minute-Delivery-Revolution-From-Groceries-to-Gadgets-2025-Rewrites-Retail/69520b464342f77179dbff5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-10-Minute-Delivery-Revolution-From-Groceries-to-Gadgets-2025-Rewrites-Retail/69520b464342f77179dbff5b</guid><description>In 2025, quick commerce fundamentally transformed India's retail landscape, evolving from experimental grocery delivery to a multi-billion-dollar sector moving everything from electronics to appliances in minutes. Reaching 33 million users across 150+ cities, it's projected to command 10% of branded retail sales by 2030. Major e-commerce players launched rapid delivery services, while large dark stores expanded capacity. However, this growth triggered a "Kirana Conflict," prompting regulatory actions on pricing, and intensified focus on gig worker welfare, culminating in new labor codes recognizing delivery partners under social security. The industry now heads towards consolidation and category expansion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:53:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69520b464342f77179dbff5a_1766984591677.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PAN-Aadhaar Deadline Approaching: Link Now to Avoid ₹1000 Penalty &amp; Inoperative Card!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PAN-Aadhaar-Deadline-Approaching-Link-Now-to-Avoid-1000-Penalty-and-Inoperative-Card/6952097a4342f77179dbfcc5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PAN-Aadhaar-Deadline-Approaching-Link-Now-to-Avoid-1000-Penalty-and-Inoperative-Card/6952097a4342f77179dbfcc5</guid><description>The deadline to link your Permanent Account Number (PAN) with Aadhaar is December 31, 2025. Failing to do so will result in a ₹1,000 penalty and your PAN becoming inoperative from January 1, 2026. This can severely impact your ability to file income tax returns, receive refunds, and conduct financial transactions. You can check your linking status and link your documents online via the Income Tax e-filing portal, SMS, or at a PAN service centre.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952097a4342f77179dbfcc4_1766984165597.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Banks: Q3 Earnings Set to Surge? Elara Securities Reveals Top Picks &amp; Looming NIM Risks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Q3-Earnings-Set-to-Surge-Elara-Securities-Reveals-Top-Picks-and-Looming-NIM-Risks/6952070d4342f77179dbf9dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Q3-Earnings-Set-to-Surge-Elara-Securities-Reveals-Top-Picks-and-Looming-NIM-Risks/6952070d4342f77179dbf9dd</guid><description>Elara Securities anticipates an improved Q3FY26 for India's banking sector, with public and top private banks expected to post strong results driven by loan growth over 11%. However, the report cautions about potential Net Interest Margin (NIM) pressures in FY27 due to rising funding costs and competition, prompting a need to monitor funding and investment yields. Top picks include ICICI Bank, State Bank of India, Karur Vysya Bank, and AU Small Finance Bank.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:33:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952070d4342f77179dbf9dc_1766983512734.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2025 Stock Forecast! Brokerages Reveal Top Buy, Sell, Hold Picks for Apollo Tyres, Coforge, Titan – Are You Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/2025-Stock-Forecast-Brokerages-Reveal-Top-Buy-Sell-Hold-Picks-for-Apollo-Tyres-Coforge-Titan-Are-You-Ready/6952069c4342f77179dbf8f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/2025-Stock-Forecast-Brokerages-Reveal-Top-Buy-Sell-Hold-Picks-for-Apollo-Tyres-Coforge-Titan-Are-You-Ready/6952069c4342f77179dbf8f0</guid><description>Brokerage firms Motilal Oswal, Citi, Investec, and Morgan Stanley have issued their 2025 outlooks for Apollo Tyres, Coforge, and Titan Company. Recommendations range from Buy to Hold, with target prices set between ₹600 and ₹4,248. Key factors influencing these calls include strong domestic demand, strategic acquisitions like Coforge's Encora deal, and Titan's entry into the lab-grown diamond market with its 'beYon' brand.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952069c4342f77179dbf8ef_1766983497564.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Mania! Top Stocks Surge, Others Plummet - See Who Made the Biggest Moves Today!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Mania-Top-Stocks-Surge-Others-Plummet-See-Who-Made-the-Biggest-Moves-Today/6952068d4342f77179dbf8a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Mania-Top-Stocks-Surge-Others-Plummet-See-Who-Made-the-Biggest-Moves-Today/6952068d4342f77179dbf8a3</guid><description>Indian stock markets saw significant activity today, December 29, 2025. Tata Steel Ltd and Hindalco Industries Ltd were among the top gainers, showing sharp surges attributed to positive sector trends and market sentiment. Conversely, Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone Ltd and Axis Bank Ltd featured among the top losers, experiencing declines due to profit booking or adverse global cues. Investors are advised to monitor these market movers for potential opportunities and risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952068d4342f77179dbf8a2_1766983375239.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Veteran Investor Ramesh Damani Buys Stake in John Cockerill India – Shares Skyrocket!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Veteran-Investor-Ramesh-Damani-Buys-Stake-in-John-Cockerill-India-Shares-Skyrocket/695205e74342f77179dbf757</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Veteran-Investor-Ramesh-Damani-Buys-Stake-in-John-Cockerill-India-Shares-Skyrocket/695205e74342f77179dbf757</guid><description>Shares of John Cockerill India jumped nearly 10% over two days after renowned investor Ramesh Damani purchased a stake via block deals. Damani acquired approximately 27,500 shares for around ₹13 crore from the company's promoter, John Cockerill SA. John Cockerill India is an industrial component manufacturer. The stock is up 3.6% today and 22% year-to-date.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:32:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695205e74342f77179dbf756_1766983210206.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Prices Soar Past $4,516: Geopolitical Fears &amp; Fed Policy Hints Fuel Safe-Haven Demand!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Soar-Past-4516-Geopolitical-Fears-and-Fed-Policy-Hints-Fuel-Safe-Haven-Demand/695205ce4342f77179dbf718</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Soar-Past-4516-Geopolitical-Fears-and-Fed-Policy-Hints-Fuel-Safe-Haven-Demand/695205ce4342f77179dbf718</guid><description>Gold prices are surging, holding strong above $4,516 per ounce due to heightened geopolitical tensions and expectations of future Federal Reserve easing. Spot prices gained 1.6% in a week, reaching a peak of $4,546. Domestic futures on MCX are also up, trading around Rs 1,38,209 per 10 grams of 24K purity. Analysts foresee continued momentum, with targets around $4,900-$5,000 by late 2026, driven by safe-haven demand amid macro uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:27:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695205ce4342f77179dbf717_1766983279402.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Bombshell $30 Billion Claim Against Reliance &amp; BP: What It Means for Energy Giants!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Bombshell-30-Billion-Claim-Against-Reliance-and-BP-What-It-Means-for-Energy-Giants/695204ac4342f77179dbf461</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Bombshell-30-Billion-Claim-Against-Reliance-and-BP-What-It-Means-for-Energy-Giants/695204ac4342f77179dbf461</guid><description>India is demanding over $30 billion in compensation from Reliance Industries and BP concerning gas underproduction from the KG-D6 offshore fields. An arbitration tribunal has been hearing the dispute since 2016, with final arguments concluded and a verdict anticipated by mid-2026. The government alleges mismanagement led to significant reserve loss, a claim Reliance and BP dispute. This represents the largest claim ever made by India against a corporation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:24:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695204ac4342f77179dbf460_1766982898234.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>States Poised for ₹17,000 Crore Windfall Under New Rural Job Act, SBI Report Signals Despite Funding Shift!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/States-Poised-for-17000-Crore-Windfall-Under-New-Rural-Job-Act-SBI-Report-Signals-Despite-Funding-Shift/695204344342f77179dbf398</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/States-Poised-for-17000-Crore-Windfall-Under-New-Rural-Job-Act-SBI-Report-Signals-Despite-Funding-Shift/695204344342f77179dbf398</guid><description>A State Bank of India report projects that Indian states will collectively gain approximately ₹17,000 crore under the proposed Viksit Bharat Guarantee for Rozgar and Ajeevika Mission (VB-G RAM G) Act. Despite a revised 60:40 Centre-state funding ratio, the report argues that fears of increased financial burden are unfounded, as the new framework improves fund distribution based on objective criteria. Uttar Pradesh and Maharashtra are identified as top beneficiaries of the act, which guarantees 125 days of wage employment per rural household.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:23:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695204344342f77179dbf397_1766982767607.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PM Modi Unveils India's 'Reform Express': Youth Powering Next-Gen Growth to Global Dominance!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PM-Modi-Unveils-Indias-Reform-Express-Youth-Powering-Next-Gen-Growth-to-Global-Dominance/695203a44342f77179dbf1af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PM-Modi-Unveils-Indias-Reform-Express-Youth-Powering-Next-Gen-Growth-to-Global-Dominance/695203a44342f77179dbf1af</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi announced India is on the "Reform Express," with its youth driving "next-generation reforms." Speaking at a chief secretaries' conference themed "Human capital for Viksit Bharat," he emphasized empowering the poor, boosting 'Made in India' quality, enhancing ease of doing business, and aiming for India to become a global services and food export giant. The focus is on leveraging demography for national development and quality in governance and manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:22:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695203a44342f77179dbf1ae_1766982637602.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty, Sensex Open Higher! Expert Sees India Outperforming in 2026 Amidst Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Sensex-Open-Higher-Expert-Sees-India-Outperforming-in-2026-Amidst-Consolidation/695202664342f77179dbef9a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Sensex-Open-Higher-Expert-Sees-India-Outperforming-in-2026-Amidst-Consolidation/695202664342f77179dbef9a</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks Nifty50 and BSE Sensex opened in the green on Monday, with Nifty50 trading above 26,050 and Sensex near 85,100. Geojit Investments' Dr. VK Vijayakumar predicts India will outperform in 2026 due to strong fundamentals and recovering earnings, despite current consolidation. Investors are advised to accumulate quality largecap stocks during this period. Market volatility is expected this week due to year-end and derivatives expiry, with key domestic data releases also on watch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:15:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695202664342f77179dbef99_1766982401411.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Year of Turmoil &amp; Triumph: Tariffs, Rupee Crash, and Market Records Exposed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Year-of-Turmoil-and-Triumph-Tariffs-Rupee-Crash-and-Market-Records-Exposed/6951ff854342f77179dbebe8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Year-of-Turmoil-and-Triumph-Tariffs-Rupee-Crash-and-Market-Records-Exposed/6951ff854342f77179dbebe8</guid><description>India's 2025 was a year of significant economic shifts. US tariffs impacted exports, while the Indian Rupee hit historic lows against the dollar. Despite trade tensions, India secured new free trade agreements and saw its equity markets, including the BSE Sensex and Nifty 50, reach record highs. Major reforms in taxation (GST, Income Tax) and SEBI regulations aimed to boost investor confidence and simplify processes. Tech giants pledged substantial investments, and the RBI cut interest rates. However, disruptions like IndiGo's flight cancellations and corporate governance issues at Tata Trusts highlighted ongoing challenges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:58:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ff854342f77179dbebe7_1766981577717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VA Tech Wabag Surges as Saudi Arabia Awards Massive Repeat Water Treatment Contract!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VA-Tech-Wabag-Surges-as-Saudi-Arabia-Awards-Massive-Repeat-Water-Treatment-Contract/6951fdd64342f77179dbea1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VA-Tech-Wabag-Surges-as-Saudi-Arabia-Awards-Massive-Repeat-Water-Treatment-Contract/6951fdd64342f77179dbea1e</guid><description>VA Tech Wabag Ltd. shares climbed after announcing a significant repeat order from the Saudi Water Authority. The EPC contract is for an advanced brackish water reverse osmosis (BWRO) plant with a capacity of 50 million liters per day in Aljouf, Saudi Arabia. Orders in the $30 million to $75 million range are classified as 'large' by the company. The project involves design, supply, and commissioning over 14 months, showcasing VA Tech Wabag's expertise in specialized water treatment technologies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:57:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951fdd64342f77179dbea1d_1766981148565.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Investing Revolution: SIPs &amp; Tech Make Markets Accessible to All!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Indian-Investing-Revolution-SIPs-and-Tech-Make-Markets-Accessible-to-All/6951fdd64342f77179dbe9f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Indian-Investing-Revolution-SIPs-and-Tech-Make-Markets-Accessible-to-All/6951fdd64342f77179dbe9f0</guid><description>Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) are transforming Indian retail investing, moving it beyond traditional deposits and gold. Technology, mobile platforms, and UPI payments have made investing as simple as online shopping, bringing markets closer to the masses. HSBC Mutual Fund CEO Kailash Kulkarni notes future innovations will expand SIP offerings to include thematic, ESG, and customized goal-based products, further deepening market participation and stability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:57:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951fdd64342f77179dbe9ef_1766981158209.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock Tax Savings: Adjust Share/Derivative Losses Against Mutual Fund Gains in FY26!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Tax-Savings-Adjust-ShareDerivative-Losses-Against-Mutual-Fund-Gains-in-FY26/6951fd2d4342f77179dbe8a4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Tax-Savings-Adjust-ShareDerivative-Losses-Against-Mutual-Fund-Gains-in-FY26/6951fd2d4342f77179dbe8a4</guid><description>Indian investors can adjust losses from selling shares or derivatives against capital gains from mutual funds in the financial year 2025-26. According to income tax rules, while speculative losses are restricted, losses from derivative transactions, treated as non-speculative business income, can be set off against capital gains (short-term or long-term). Similarly, share transaction losses can be adjusted against capital gains, depending on their classification. This advice helps optimize tax liabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:52:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951fd2d4342f77179dbe8a3_1766980990573.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Bond Market Shift: Goldilocks Era Ends, Investors Brace for New 'Accrual &amp; Carry' Strategy in 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Bond-Market-Shift-Goldilocks-Era-Ends-Investors-Brace-for-New-Accrual-and-Carry-Strategy-in-2026/6951fc634342f77179dbe730</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Bond-Market-Shift-Goldilocks-Era-Ends-Investors-Brace-for-New-Accrual-and-Carry-Strategy-in-2026/6951fc634342f77179dbe730</guid><description>India enjoyed a 'Goldilocks' economic year in 2025 with low inflation and high growth, prompting the RBI to cut rates. However, 2026 may see monetary policy tightening, signaling the end of the rate-cut cycle. Fixed income investors should transition from a rate-cut strategy to an 'accrual &amp; carry' approach, focusing on generating income rather than capital gains from falling rates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:52:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951fc634342f77179dbe72f_1766980814817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Market Supremacy Fading? Tech's Reign and Debt Woes Spark Investor Alarm – The Shocking Truth Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Market-Supremacy-Fading-Techs-Reign-and-Debt-Woes-Spark-Investor-Alarm-The-Shocking-Truth-Revealed/6951fcda4342f77179dbe821</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Market-Supremacy-Fading-Techs-Reign-and-Debt-Woes-Spark-Investor-Alarm-The-Shocking-Truth-Revealed/6951fcda4342f77179dbe821</guid><description>The United States has dominated global markets since 2008, driven by its strong technology sector and stable institutions. However, recent events like a 'triple red' market signal potential instability. Rising US debt levels, with interest payments exceeding defense spending, and concerns over institutional resilience pose risks. Despite these challenges, investors continue to pour capital into the U.S., largely due to the exceptional returns offered by its technology giants, seeking growth amidst a world of limited alternatives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:52:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951fcda4342f77179dbe820_1766981022545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Analysts Reveal Top 2 Stocks to Buy This Week: Midwest &amp; Ambuja Cement Surge Potential!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Analysts-Reveal-Top-2-Stocks-to-Buy-This-Week-Midwest-and-Ambuja-Cement-Surge-Potential/6951f9b14342f77179dbe47f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Analysts-Reveal-Top-2-Stocks-to-Buy-This-Week-Midwest-and-Ambuja-Cement-Surge-Potential/6951f9b14342f77179dbe47f</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services Ltd has identified Midwest and Ambuja Cement as top stock picks for the week commencing December 29, 2025. Midwest, a leading Black Galaxy granite exporter, is poised for growth through diversification into high-purity quartz and heavy mineral sands. Ambuja Cement is set to expand its footprint and improve profitability through the acquisition of Jaiprakash Associates' cement assets and significant cost reduction initiatives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:40:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f9b14342f77179dbe47e_1766980077932.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Rupee Teeters Near 90! Bonds Brace for Quarter-End Storm - Are You Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Rupee-Teeters-Near-90-Bonds-Brace-for-Quarter-End-Storm-Are-You-Ready/6951f7994342f77179dbe1a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Rupee-Teeters-Near-90-Bonds-Brace-for-Quarter-End-Storm-Are-You-Ready/6951f7994342f77179dbe1a7</guid><description>The Indian rupee is under pressure, facing potential headwinds from maturing non-deliverable forward (NDF) positions, with traders expecting it could slip past 90 per dollar again. Persistent corporate hedging and significant foreign portfolio outflows, tracking record redemptions from local stocks, are weighing on the currency despite Reserve Bank of India (RBI) interventions. Meanwhile, bond traders are closely watching demand-supply dynamics and foreign investor activity, with the 10-year benchmark yield influenced by RBI's bond purchase program and ongoing selling by foreign investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:24:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f7994342f77179dbe1a6_1766979550389.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Investment Bets: Are PSU Banks &amp; IT Your Next Goldmine? Defence Stocks Sky-High!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-Investment-Bets-Are-PSU-Banks-and-IT-Your-Next-Goldmine-Defence-Stocks-Sky-High/6951f7044342f77179dbe016</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-Investment-Bets-Are-PSU-Banks-and-IT-Your-Next-Goldmine-Defence-Stocks-Sky-High/6951f7044342f77179dbe016</guid><description>As 2025 concludes with strong market gains, analysts are strategizing for 2026. They identify PSU banks, IT, and financials as 'undervalued' sectors ripe for entry, citing valuations below historical averages. Conversely, defence, healthcare, and consumer discretionary stocks are flagged as 'overvalued' and potentially overheated after significant rallies this year. Energy and engineering sectors also present future opportunities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:24:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f7044342f77179dbe015_1766979408861.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹1,100 Crore Highway Win: Ceigall India's Shares Set to Soar!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-1100-Crore-Highway-Win-Ceigall-Indias-Shares-Set-to-Soar/6951f6184342f77179dbdf05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-1100-Crore-Highway-Win-Ceigall-Indias-Shares-Set-to-Soar/6951f6184342f77179dbdf05</guid><description>Ceigall India has secured a significant Letter of Award (LoA) from the Madhya Pradesh government for a highway project valued at ₹1,089 crore. Awarded to its subsidiary Ceigall Infra Projects Pvt. Ltd., the project involves constructing the 'Indore Ujjain Greenfield' highway, spanning 48.10 kilometers on a Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM). This win boosts Ceigall India's robust order book, which now stands at ₹14,237 crore, having already surpassed its fiscal year 2026 order inflow target.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:22:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f6184342f77179dbdf04_1766979218817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Sector Roars in December: Four-Wheelers Lead Surge, Two-Wheelers Still Finding Footing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Sector-Roars-in-December-Four-Wheelers-Lead-Surge-Two-Wheelers-Still-Finding-Footing/6951f6094342f77179dbdeda</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Sector-Roars-in-December-Four-Wheelers-Lead-Surge-Two-Wheelers-Still-Finding-Footing/6951f6094342f77179dbdeda</guid><description>Domestic auto demand showed resilience in December 2025, with overall registrations rising 9% year-on-year. Passenger vehicles and commercial vehicles spearheaded this growth with robust double-digit increases, alongside a remarkable surge in three-wheelers. However, the two-wheeler segment experienced only modest growth, indicating a gradual recovery in rural and mass-market demand. The divergence between four-wheeler strength and two-wheeler lag was a key feature of the month's performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:22:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f6094342f77179dbded9_1766979191558.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Brace: Bank of Japan Signals Aggressive Rate Hikes as Real Rate Plummets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Brace-Bank-of-Japan-Signals-Aggressive-Rate-Hikes-as-Real-Rate-Plummets/6951f5ca4342f77179dbdd3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Brace-Bank-of-Japan-Signals-Aggressive-Rate-Hikes-as-Real-Rate-Plummets/6951f5ca4342f77179dbdd3e</guid><description>Bank of Japan officials indicated potential further interest rate hikes due to Japan's real interest rate being the lowest globally. The benchmark rate was recently raised to 0.75%, a 30-year high. Discussions also covered adjusting monetary accommodation and managing currency fluctuations, with markets anticipating the next policy move.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:22:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f5ca4342f77179dbdd3d_1766979142257.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>