<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:43:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Overhauls GDP Stats Today: Clarity Amidst New Ambiguities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Overhauls-GDP-Stats-Today-Clarity-Amidst-New-Ambiguities/69a0f365fa7d0695d1aafd64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Overhauls-GDP-Stats-Today-Clarity-Amidst-New-Ambiguities/69a0f365fa7d0695d1aafd64</guid><description>On February 27, 2026, India unveils a revamped Gross Domestic Product (GDP) series, a critical statistical overhaul designed to enhance economic measurement accuracy. The revision, set to be released today, aims to address persistent data quality issues, particularly concerning the unorganized sector and the reconciliation of production and expenditure approaches. While promising greater economic clarity, the continued reliance on single deflators in certain sectors may still obscure precise real growth figures, presenting a nuanced picture for market participants.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:29:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0f365fa7d0695d1aafd63_1772155935387.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FCI Pivot: From Overstock to Export Goldmine</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/FCI-Pivot-From-Overstock-to-Export-Goldmine/69a0f1d1fa7d0695d1aafc62</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/FCI-Pivot-From-Overstock-to-Export-Goldmine/69a0f1d1fa7d0695d1aafc62</guid><description>The Food Corporation of India (FCI) is hampered by costly, open-ended procurement practices that result in massive stock overhangs, inflating carrying costs and fiscal burdens. As of July 1, 2025, reserves far exceeded norms. This inefficient model, costing ₹22,347.62 per tonne compared to modern operators' ₹534 per tonne, necessitates a pivot. By delinking procurement volumes from storage capacity and embracing modern, rule-based interventions via advanced silo infrastructure, FCI can unlock significant savings, enhance food security resilience against climate variability, and bolster India's ambition for $100 billion in agricultural exports by 2030.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:22:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0f1d1fa7d0695d1aafc61_1772155658927.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paramount-Warner Bros. Discovery Deal: A Debt-Fueled Gamble?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Paramount-Warner-Bros-Discovery-Deal-A-Debt-Fueled-Gamble/69a0ed4cfa7d0695d1aafa66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Paramount-Warner-Bros-Discovery-Deal-A-Debt-Fueled-Gamble/69a0ed4cfa7d0695d1aafa66</guid><description>Paramount Global is nearing a potential acquisition of Warner Bros. Discovery (WBD) after Netflix withdrew its offer. Paramount's bid, valued at approximately $31 per share and backed by billions in debt, faces considerable antitrust scrutiny from the U.S. Department of Justice and potential regulatory hurdles. This deal, if successful, would reshape Hollywood but carries substantial financial risk for Paramount, with backing from Skydance Media and foreign sovereign wealth funds. Meanwhile, WBD's board has deemed Paramount's proposal superior to Netflix's initial bid.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:03:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0ed4cfa7d0695d1aafa65_1772154475520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Stocks: Technical Revival Signals Tested by Debt Overhang</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Stocks-Technical-Revival-Signals-Tested-by-Debt-Overhang/69a0eb0efa7d0695d1aaf79b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Stocks-Technical-Revival-Signals-Tested-by-Debt-Overhang/69a0eb0efa7d0695d1aaf79b</guid><description>Select Adani Group stocks, including Adani Enterprises, Adani Energy Solutions, and Adani Power, are exhibiting technical patterns suggestive of accumulation and a potential revival, following the Hindenburg-induced downturn. Adani Enterprises and Adani Energy Solutions display Wyckoff accumulation structures, while Adani Power shows a pattern of reclaiming key moving averages. However, these optimistic technical signals are juxtaposed against high valuations and the group's substantial debt, presenting a mixed outlook for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:53:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0eb0efa7d0695d1aaf79a_1772153769649.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kacholia's Bets: Agarwal Industrial &amp; Infinium Face Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kacholias-Bets-Agarwal-Industrial-and-Infinium-Face-Margin-Squeeze/69a0eb05fa7d0695d1aaf77d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kacholias-Bets-Agarwal-Industrial-and-Infinium-Face-Margin-Squeeze/69a0eb05fa7d0695d1aaf77d</guid><description>Veteran investor Ashish Kacholia is holding firm on Agarwal Industrial Corporation and Infinium Pharmachem despite significant price drops. While Kacholia bets on long-term potential, Agarwal Industrial grapples with a sharp decline in operating margins and cash flow, while Infinium Pharmachem, listed on an SME exchange, faces inherent liquidity challenges, promoter stake reduction, and eroding profitability, raising questions about the sustainability of these investments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:53:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0eb05fa7d0695d1aaf77c_1772153763764.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Specialty Chemicals: DII Bets On Privi, Styrenix Amidst Sector Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Specialty-Chemicals-DII-Bets-On-Privi-Styrenix-Amidst-Sector-Shift/69a0eaf0fa7d0695d1aaf746</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Specialty-Chemicals-DII-Bets-On-Privi-Styrenix-Amidst-Sector-Shift/69a0eaf0fa7d0695d1aaf746</guid><description>Domestic institutional investors are increasing stakes in niche Indian specialty chemical players like Privi Speciality Chemicals and Styrenix Performance Materials, signaling confidence in the sector's structural transformation. While Privi commands a premium valuation with strong growth momentum in aroma chemicals, Styrenix offers a more conservative valuation despite a recent profit downturn, underpinned by its engineering polymer leadership and global expansion. Both companies are executing strategic growth initiatives, but potential investors must weigh Privi's premium against Styrenix's mixed financial signals and conflicting analyst sentiment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0eaf0fa7d0695d1aaf745_1772153788914.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Securities Bill Sparks Debate Over PSU Regulatory Exemptions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Securities-Bill-Sparks-Debate-Over-PSU-Regulatory-Exemptions/69a0ea9afa7d0695d1aaf678</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Securities-Bill-Sparks-Debate-Over-PSU-Regulatory-Exemptions/69a0ea9afa7d0695d1aaf678</guid><description>India's proposed Securities Market Code Bill, 2025, aims to modernize financial laws but includes Section 65(2), which permits central government exemptions for listed public sector companies (PSCs) from core regulations. Critics argue this provision risks establishing a dual regulatory framework, undermining competitive neutrality and investor confidence, and could reverse decades of economic reform by reintroducing ownership-based regulatory disparities. The move potentially jeopardizes India's goal of attracting global capital by signaling a departure from uniform market discipline.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:51:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0ea9afa7d0695d1aaf677_1772154066067.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Debt Burden Mounts: Interest Costs Soar, Dollar's Role Tested</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Debt-Burden-Mounts-Interest-Costs-Soar-Dollars-Role-Tested/69a0ea7dfa7d0695d1aaf657</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Debt-Burden-Mounts-Interest-Costs-Soar-Dollars-Role-Tested/69a0ea7dfa7d0695d1aaf657</guid><description>The United States faces a critical juncture as its public debt-to-GDP ratio exceeds 120%, with annual interest payments now surpassing military expenditure. Decades of quantitative easing and regulatory support for Treasury markets are waning, coinciding with decreased foreign demand and the introduction of expansive fiscal legislation. These factors are intensifying pressure on the U.S. dollar's global reserve currency status, while the fundamental need for deficit reduction remains unaddressed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:51:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0ea7dfa7d0695d1aaf656_1772153670367.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pivots to IP-Driven Chip Ecosystem with ISM 2.0</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Pivots-to-IP-Driven-Chip-Ecosystem-with-ISM-20/69a0ea7afa7d0695d1aaf640</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Pivots-to-IP-Driven-Chip-Ecosystem-with-ISM-20/69a0ea7afa7d0695d1aaf640</guid><description>India's Budget 2026-27 signals a major strategic shift with the rollout of India Semiconductor Mission (ISM) 2.0 and an expanded Electronics Components Manufacturing Scheme (ECMS) with a ₹40,000 crore outlay. This new phase prioritizes the development of indigenous intellectual property (IP), semiconductor equipment, and materials, moving beyond ISM 1.0's primary focus on fabrication capacity. The initiative aims to build a comprehensive, IP-driven ecosystem to bolster India's position in the global semiconductor value chain amid surging demand from AI, automotive, and telecommunications sectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:51:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0ea7afa7d0695d1aaf63f_1772154024471.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Consolidation: Technical Trades Emerge Amidst Sector Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Consolidation-Technical-Trades-Emerge-Amidst-Sector-Strength/69a0e4defa7d0695d1aaf428</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Consolidation-Technical-Trades-Emerge-Amidst-Sector-Strength/69a0e4defa7d0695d1aaf428</guid><description>Equity benchmarks concluded February 26, 2026, with flat performance amid volatility and neutral market breadth. Analysts identified several short-term trading opportunities driven by technical patterns, particularly in the resilient auto, banking, and strong pharma sectors. While Nifty 50 and Sensex saw marginal movements, specific counters like Delhivery, Eicher Motors, IndusInd Bank, and Lupin showed potential based on chart formations and momentum indicators. However, high valuations and divergent analyst outlooks present notable risks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:27:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0e4defa7d0695d1aaf427_1772152155167.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>