<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:42:24 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Shriram Finance's MUFG Deal Fuels Bajaj Finance Rivalry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finances-MUFG-Deal-Fuels-Bajaj-Finance-Rivalry/6982a0adf5a3f0ebac98552b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finances-MUFG-Deal-Fuels-Bajaj-Finance-Rivalry/6982a0adf5a3f0ebac98552b</guid><description>Shriram Finance has secured a pivotal Rs 39,617 crore investment from MUFG Bank, significantly bolstering its competitive position against market leader Bajaj Finance. Both non-banking financial companies (NBFCs) demonstrated robust loan book expansion in the December 2025 quarter. Shriram Finance's retail lending strategy enhanced its Net Interest Margin (NIM), while Bajaj Finance managed higher provisions to reveal strong underlying profit growth, intensifying their market rivalry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:30:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982a0adf5a3f0ebac98552a_1770168608156.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tech Talent Gap: Industry Apathy Risks Future Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tech-Talent-Gap-Industry-Apathy-Risks-Future-Dominance/69829b10f5a3f0ebac9851aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tech-Talent-Gap-Industry-Apathy-Risks-Future-Dominance/69829b10f5a3f0ebac9851aa</guid><description>India's tech sector confronts a persistent skill gap, exacerbated by industry's abandonment of historical talent development models for 'day-one productivity.' Despite the National Education Policy (NEP) 2020's call for partnerships, corporate engagement remains superficial. This strategic shift, driven by complex new roles and attrition fears, risks undermining India's competitive advantage in the global technology arena, necessitating urgent policy intervention and genuine industry commitment to human capital investment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:06:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69829b10f5a3f0ebac9851a9_1770167172727.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alphabet Bets Big on India for AI Talent</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Bets-Big-on-India-for-AI-Talent/69829135f5a3f0ebac984cd3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Bets-Big-on-India-for-AI-Talent/69829135f5a3f0ebac984cd3</guid><description>Alphabet Inc. is dramatically expanding its presence in India, leasing and optioning millions of square feet of office space in Bengaluru. This strategic move aims to capture critical artificial intelligence talent and bolster its Global Capability Centers (GCCs) as India emerges as a key hub for AI development. The expansion could more than double its India workforce, signaling a major push in the global race for AI expertise against rivals like Microsoft and OpenAI.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:24:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69829135f5a3f0ebac984cd2_1770164647102.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>