<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:29:58 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Growth: Resilience Tested by Trade Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Resilience-Tested-by-Trade-Volatility/699e10a604a25a58c8534a38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Resilience-Tested-by-Trade-Volatility/699e10a604a25a58c8534a38</guid><description>India's economic outlook remains strong, with forecasts predicting it to be the fastest-growing major economy. Key drivers include domestic demand, policy continuity, and a growing workforce. However, escalating global trade tensions, particularly US tariff uncertainties, and the need to absorb a large young population pose significant risks to this optimistic trajectory. Major trade deals with the EU and a framework agreement with the US are in place, but their full impact is yet to be realized amidst evolving geopolitical and trade dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Semaglutide Patent Expiry: Indian Pharma Faces Price War</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Semaglutide-Patent-Expiry-Indian-Pharma-Faces-Price-War/699e104604a25a58c8534998</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Semaglutide-Patent-Expiry-Indian-Pharma-Faces-Price-War/699e104604a25a58c8534998</guid><description>The March 2026 patent expiry for semaglutide, the active ingredient in blockbuster weight-loss drugs, is poised to trigger an aggressive price war among Indian pharmaceutical companies. At least six to seven players, including Sun Pharma, Dr. Reddy's, and Zydus Lifesciences, are preparing for day-one launches of affordable generic versions. This influx is anticipated to slash prices by up to 75% over time, dramatically expanding patient access and potentially doubling the market size from its current ₹1,400 crore valuation within a year. The move signals a major disruption for innovator brands and intensified competition among domestic manufacturers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India IT Sector: AI Fuels Growth but Risks Margin Erosion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-IT-Sector-AI-Fuels-Growth-but-Risks-Margin-Erosion/699e0fb604a25a58c85348a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-IT-Sector-AI-Fuels-Growth-but-Risks-Margin-Erosion/699e0fb604a25a58c85348a9</guid><description>India's technology sector is projected to reach $315 billion in FY26, with AI-led services expected to contribute $10-12 billion. Despite this expansion, the industry faces a "painful transition" as AI automation threatens traditional revenue streams, leading to significant market sell-offs and analyst concerns over margin compression and competitive displacement. The focus shifts from scale to value-added AI integration, but the pace of adaptation remains a critical challenge.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Group Chair: Nerves Jittery as Finance Pressure Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tata-Group-Chair-Nerves-Jittery-as-Finance-Pressure-Mounts/699e0fb504a25a58c8534892</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tata-Group-Chair-Nerves-Jittery-as-Finance-Pressure-Mounts/699e0fb504a25a58c8534892</guid><description>Tata Trusts is scrutinizing the performance and tenure extension of Tata Group Chairman N. Chandrasekaran, citing criteria tied to improving losses in aviation and digital services, and managing capital expenditure in high-risk sectors like semiconductors and batteries. This comes as Tata Sons faces limitations on debt raising due to RBI norms, and a recent market capitalization decline across the group, forcing a more rigorous evaluation of leadership and financial stewardship. The ongoing talks for Shapoorji Pallonji Group's exit from Tata Sons also add a layer of complexity to the conglomerate's leadership continuity plans.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Broadcast Sector Battles Piracy; Regulatory Pace Lags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Broadcast-Sector-Battles-Piracy-Regulatory-Pace-Lags/699e039f04a25a58c8533ffc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Broadcast-Sector-Battles-Piracy-Regulatory-Pace-Lags/699e039f04a25a58c8533ffc</guid><description>India's broadcast industry is grappling with a sharp rise in DTH signal piracy, leading to billions in revenue losses and impacting legitimate operators. Despite industry demands for mandatory technological safeguards like forensic watermarking, regulatory movement has been slow, with a government task force still gaining traction. This ongoing battle underscores a critical need for faster enforcement to protect the integrity of the media sector and its future growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Q3 GDP Surges to 8.1%, Driven by Domestic Might</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Q3-GDP-Surges-to-81percent-Driven-by-Domestic-Might/699e036504a25a58c8533f60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Q3-GDP-Surges-to-81percent-Driven-by-Domestic-Might/699e036504a25a58c8533f60</guid><description>India's economy demonstrated robust resilience in the third quarter of fiscal year 2026, with the State Bank of India projecting a significant 8.1% Gross Domestic Product expansion. This forecast is primarily fueled by strong rural and urban consumption, underpinned by fiscal stimulus and positive agricultural and non-farm sector activity. However, this impressive domestic performance occurs as the nation prepares for a crucial revision of its GDP base year, introducing potential complexities in historical data interpretation and facing persistent global economic uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IndiaRevampsCANorms:CreditTradingUnlocksNewAutoMarketDynamics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/IndiaRevampsCANormsCreditTradingUnlocksNewAutoMarketDynamics/699e030c04a25a58c8533ed6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/IndiaRevampsCANormsCreditTradingUnlocksNewAutoMarketDynamics/699e030c04a25a58c8533ed6</guid><description>IndiaislauchingacredittradingsystemforautomakerstomeetstringentCAFEIIIfuel-efficiencystandards.Thismechanismallowsompaniesexceedingtargetstosellsurpluscreditsthosefallingshort,fosteringamarket-drivenapproachtoemissionsreduction.Thereformsaimtoencourigeinivestmentincleanertechnologiessignificantlyaltercompliancestrategiesformanufacturers,withpotentialimpactsonvehicleaffordabilityandmarketcompetition.Electricandhybridvehiclesreceivepreferentialcredittreatment,furtherincentivizingtheiradoption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Fuels Hyper-Growth, But Durability Trumps Speed for Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/AI-Fuels-Hyper-Growth-But-Durability-Trumps-Speed-for-Investors/699e00b404a25a58c8533c86</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/AI-Fuels-Hyper-Growth-But-Durability-Trumps-Speed-for-Investors/699e00b404a25a58c8533c86</guid><description>AI is dramatically accelerating startup revenue, with Stripe reporting a surge in businesses reaching multi-million dollar Annual Recurring Revenue (ARR) milestones within months. This surge, particularly among international firms leveraging tools like Stripe Atlas, contrasts sharply with previous growth rates. However, venture capitalists are increasingly scrutinizing the sustainability of this rapid expansion, emphasizing durable growth and profitability over velocity alone, especially amid rising interest rates and a maturing investment landscape.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:49:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's BOT Road Projects: Risk Sharing to Fuel Private Investment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-BOT-Road-Projects-Risk-Sharing-to-Fuel-Private-Investment/699df7fb04a25a58c853363a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-BOT-Road-Projects-Risk-Sharing-to-Fuel-Private-Investment/699df7fb04a25a58c853363a</guid><description>The Indian Ministry of Road Transport and Highways has updated its model concession agreement for Build-Operate-Transfer (BOT) road projects. This revision introduces profit and loss sharing mechanisms tied to traffic data, aims to enhance project viability, and is set to unlock approximately ₹2 lakh crore in new projects. The move seeks to de-risk infrastructure development for private concessionaires, potentially attracting increased private capital into the sector. The changes also address road safety and operational efficiency.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:11:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699df7fb04a25a58c8533639_1771965352253.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wondrlab Eyes IPO Post ₹1,000 Cr Madison World Buyout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Wondrlab-Eyes-IPO-Post-1000-Cr-Madison-World-Buyout/699df75f04a25a58c85334fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Wondrlab-Eyes-IPO-Post-1000-Cr-Madison-World-Buyout/699df75f04a25a58c85334fd</guid><description>Marketing technology firm Wondrlab is reportedly in the final stages of acquiring Madison World for approximately ₹1,000 crore. This deal, set to be India's largest acquisition of an independent ad agency by a domestic player, would significantly bolster Wondrlab's media planning and buying capabilities. The move aims to create a full-stack marketing entity and potentially pave the way for Wondrlab's initial public offering, while founder Sam Balsara is expected to exit Madison World after nearly four decades.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:09:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699df75f04a25a58c85334fc_1771963251328.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ESR Bets ₹900 Cr on India's AI Data Boom in Navi Mumbai</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ESR-Bets-900-Cr-on-Indias-AI-Data-Boom-in-Navi-Mumbai/699df75804a25a58c85334d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ESR-Bets-900-Cr-on-Indias-AI-Data-Boom-in-Navi-Mumbai/699df75804a25a58c85334d5</guid><description>Asia-Pacific real asset manager ESR commits ₹900 crore to its Indian data center debut in Navi Mumbai, securing a 60 MW hyperscale facility with a pre-lease agreement. This move capitalizes on India's AI and cloud growth, but intensifies a market crowded with global players investing billions. The venture signals maturity in India's digital infrastructure, though challenges around power, connectivity, and regulatory compliance persist.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:09:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699df75804a25a58c85334d4_1771962232944.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Jewelry Market Shifts: Diamonds Rise, 9K Gold Gains Amid Price Flux</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Jewelry-Market-Shifts-Diamonds-Rise-9K-Gold-Gains-Amid-Price-Flux/699df70604a25a58c8533392</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Jewelry-Market-Shifts-Diamonds-Rise-9K-Gold-Gains-Amid-Price-Flux/699df70604a25a58c8533392</guid><description>India's jewelry sector is undergoing a significant transformation. Solitaire diamond demand is surging, propelled by a 30% price correction from recent peaks. Concurrently, record-high gold prices are fueling a pivot towards 9-carat and 14-carat gold jewelry, alongside studded designs, appealing to value-conscious consumers. Millennials and Gen Z are driving this shift, prioritizing affordability, individuality, and modern aesthetics, prompting jewelers to diversify their offerings. International trade pressures, notably US tariffs on diamonds, add complexity to market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Venezuela Ups Exports via VLCCs, Eyes India amid Sanctions Easing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Venezuela-Ups-Exports-via-VLCCs-Eyes-India-amid-Sanctions-Easing/699df6da04a25a58c853333b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Venezuela-Ups-Exports-via-VLCCs-Eyes-India-amid-Sanctions-Easing/699df6da04a25a58c853333b</guid><description>Venezuela is set to ramp up crude oil exports significantly by chartering Very Large Crude Carriers (VLCCs) for the first time since a U.S.-Venezuela supply deal began. This strategic shift, expected to accelerate shipments from March, targets increased deliveries to India. Trading firms Vitol and Trafigura are spearheading these operations under recently eased U.S. sanctions, aiming to optimize delivery costs and access key Asian markets. This move signals a potential resurgence for Venezuelan oil, albeit from historical lows, as the country navigates a complex global energy market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:07:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699df6da04a25a58c853333a_1771960342689.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tredence Bets on GCC AI Shift Amid Tech Sector Flux</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tredence-Bets-on-GCC-AI-Shift-Amid-Tech-Sector-Flux/699df66b04a25a58c85331d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tredence-Bets-on-GCC-AI-Shift-Amid-Tech-Sector-Flux/699df66b04a25a58c85331d5</guid><description>Data analytics firm Tredence is launching a dedicated GCC business unit designed to transform Global Capability Centers into AI-driven innovation hubs. The company aims to leverage India's specialized talent in GenAI and Agentic AI, seeing opportunities amidst current IT sector volatility. Tredence plans strategic hiring to meet this growing demand for advanced AI solutions, positioning itself as a premium player in a shifting industry landscape that favors specialized expertise over traditional service models.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India REITs/InvITs: Debt Surge Fuels Growth Amidst Regulatory Tightening</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-REITsInvITs-Debt-Surge-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Regulatory-Tightening/699deddf04a25a58c8523243</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-REITsInvITs-Debt-Surge-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Regulatory-Tightening/699deddf04a25a58c8523243</guid><description>Specialized investment vehicles in India's real estate and infrastructure sectors are on track for record debt fundraising in FY26, raising ₹37,742 crore. The Reserve Bank of India's proposal to allow direct bank lending aims to lower borrowing costs. However, this surge in leverage is met with enhanced regulatory oversight and potential valuation concerns for high-performing trusts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kotak AMC Crosses ₹6 Trillion; IPO Market Shows Mixed Investor Signals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Kotak-AMC-Crosses-6-Trillion-IPO-Market-Shows-Mixed-Investor-Signals/699dedc004a25a58c8522c48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Kotak-AMC-Crosses-6-Trillion-IPO-Market-Shows-Mixed-Investor-Signals/699dedc004a25a58c8522c48</guid><description>Kotak Mahindra Asset Management Company (AMC) has surpassed ₹6 trillion in assets under management (AUM), driven significantly by its equity portfolio and consistent Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) inflows exceeding ₹1,500 crore monthly. Meanwhile, India's IPO market shows a bifurcated investor response: Gaudium IVF's IPO garnered strong demand at 7.27 times subscription, positioning it as a pioneer in the fertility sector's public market debut, while Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions' IPO secured 45% subscription on its second day, indicating cautious interest in the renewable energy space.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:28:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dedc004a25a58c8522c47_1771958478958.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Grid Narela Commissions 8.1 GW Rajasthan Solar Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Narela-Commissions-81-GW-Rajasthan-Solar-Project/699ded8f04a25a58c8521727</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Narela-Commissions-81-GW-Rajasthan-Solar-Project/699ded8f04a25a58c8521727</guid><description>POWERGRID Narela Transmission Limited, a subsidiary of Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd., has successfully commissioned its 8.1 GW transmission project in Rajasthan. The project is key to evacuating solar power and strengthens India's renewable energy infrastructure. This milestone aligns with national green energy targets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:27:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ded8f04a25a58c8521726_1771959626700.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exide Industries Invests ₹100 Cr in EV Battery Arm; Total Stake ₹4,352 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Exide-Industries-Invests-100-Cr-in-EV-Battery-Arm-Total-Stake-4352-Cr/699ded2004a25a58c851e05d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Exide-Industries-Invests-100-Cr-in-EV-Battery-Arm-Total-Stake-4352-Cr/699ded2004a25a58c851e05d</guid><description>Exide Industries Limited has infused an additional ₹100 crore into its wholly-owned subsidiary, Exide Energy Solutions Limited (EESL). This capital injection for EESL's greenfield lithium-ion battery project brings Exide's total investment in the subsidiary to ₹4,352.23 crore. Despite EESL reporting a net loss of ₹209.12 crore on a turnover of ₹116.89 crore in FY2024-25, Exide continues to back its strategic expansion into the burgeoning EV battery market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IOL Chemicals gets Europe nod for Cardiovascular API Clopidogrel Besilate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/IOL-Chemicals-gets-Europe-nod-for-Cardiovascular-API-Clopidogrel-Besilate/699ded1b04a25a58c851e031</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/IOL-Chemicals-gets-Europe-nod-for-Cardiovascular-API-Clopidogrel-Besilate/699ded1b04a25a58c851e031</guid><description>IOL Chemicals and Pharmaceuticals Limited announced it has received a Certificate of Suitability (CEP) from the European Directorate for the Quality of Medicines &amp; Health Care (EDQM) for its active pharmaceutical ingredient (API) 'Clopidogrel Besilate'. This pivotal certification, effective February 23, 2026, significantly enhances the company's market access for this key cardiovascular drug ingredient within Europe, complementing its existing CEP for 'Clopidogrel Bisulphate'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Infrastructure Fuels Crypto Miner Surge, Tech Adapts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Infrastructure-Fuels-Crypto-Miner-Surge-Tech-Adapts/699decd204a25a58c851cbd0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Infrastructure-Fuels-Crypto-Miner-Surge-Tech-Adapts/699decd204a25a58c851cbd0</guid><description>Bitcoin surpassed $64,000, mirroring a broader rebound in risk assets, largely propelled by advancements in artificial intelligence. Software companies demonstrated resilience by integrating AI through strategic partnerships, while select Bitcoin miners, directly benefiting from AI data center infrastructure demands, saw significant gains. This rally highlights a growing bifurcation, with AI infrastructure plays outperforming broader crypto sentiment and creating distinct opportunities and risks across the technology and digital asset sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sumuka Agro Sets March 9 Record Date for Gujjubhai Foods Merger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sumuka-Agro-Sets-March-9-Record-Date-for-Gujjubhai-Foods-Merger/699decce04a25a58c851cbae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sumuka-Agro-Sets-March-9-Record-Date-for-Gujjubhai-Foods-Merger/699decce04a25a58c851cbae</guid><description>Sumuka Agro Industries Limited has fixed March 9, 2026, as the record date to determine the eligibility of Gujjubhai Foods Private Limited shareholders for the merger. The approved share exchange ratio is 7 Sumuka Agro shares for every 4 Gujjubhai Foods shares. This corporate action follows the NCLT's sanction of the merger, paving the way for operational consolidation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>YES BANK FY25 ESG Score Hits 80.5; Governance Strong Amid Compliance Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/YES-BANK-FY25-ESG-Score-Hits-805-Governance-Strong-Amid-Compliance-Risks/699debfb04a25a58c851bcc6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/YES-BANK-FY25-ESG-Score-Hits-805-Governance-Strong-Amid-Compliance-Risks/699debfb04a25a58c851bcc6</guid><description>YES BANK has received an ESG score of 80.5 for FY 2024-25 from SES ESG Research, an improvement from the previous year. The bank highlights strong governance and environmental scores. However, the rating comes alongside disclosures of ongoing governance concerns, including board non-compliance, regulatory penalties, and a notable number of data privacy and sexual harassment complaints during the fiscal year.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sumuka Agro Industries: Gujjubhai Foods Merger Effective Feb 23, 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sumuka-Agro-Industries-Gujjubhai-Foods-Merger-Effective-Feb-23-2026/699debf504a25a58c851bc2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sumuka-Agro-Industries-Gujjubhai-Foods-Merger-Effective-Feb-23-2026/699debf504a25a58c851bc2a</guid><description>Sumuka Agro Industries Limited has announced the merger with Gujjubhai Foods Private Limited is now effective from February 23, 2026. This consolidation, following approval from the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) and completion of Ministry of Corporate Affairs filings, integrates Gujjubhai Foods into Sumuka Agro. The move is aimed at streamlining operations and strengthening the combined entity's market presence in the FMCG sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:20:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699debf504a25a58c851bc29_1771958121494.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Iykot Hitech Promoters Sell 34.58% Stake; Open Offer Triggered</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Iykot-Hitech-Promoters-Sell-3458percent-Stake-Open-Offer-Triggered/699debf004a25a58c851bc12</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Iykot-Hitech-Promoters-Sell-3458percent-Stake-Open-Offer-Triggered/699debf004a25a58c851bc12</guid><description>Iykot Hitech Toolroom is set for a change in control as its promoters execute a Share Purchase Agreement to sell 34.58% stake to Aspect Global Ventures Private Limited for ₹8 per share. This transaction mandates an open offer to public shareholders at ₹8.50 per share. Concurrently, the company approved the forfeiture of over 99 lakh partly paid-up equity shares due to unpaid call money, signalling recent financial pressure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:20:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699debf004a25a58c851bc11_1771959270913.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>T.T. Limited: Promoter Buys Shares, Stake Dilutes Sharply to 24.02%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/TT-Limited-Promoter-Buys-Shares-Stake-Dilutes-Sharply-to-2402percent/699deb8704a25a58c851b941</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/TT-Limited-Promoter-Buys-Shares-Stake-Dilutes-Sharply-to-2402percent/699deb8704a25a58c851b941</guid><description>T.T. Limited's promoter group, T T Brands Limited, acquired 43,138 shares for ₹4.16 lakh on February 24, 2026. However, the promoter's stake percentage sharply fell from 34.0308% to 24.02%. This substantial dilution, despite a purchase, points to a significant increase in the company's total outstanding shares, likely due to recent corporate actions like a rights issue and share split, impacting existing shareholders' proportional ownership.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindalco's Novelis Secures $200M Investment from AV Minerals, Bolstering IPO Prospects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindalcos-Novelis-Secures-200M-Investment-from-AV-Minerals-Bolstering-IPO-Prospects/699deaf504a25a58c851b597</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindalcos-Novelis-Secures-200M-Investment-from-AV-Minerals-Bolstering-IPO-Prospects/699deaf504a25a58c851b597</guid><description>Novelis Inc., a subsidiary of Hindalco Industries, has entered into a subscription agreement with AV Minerals (Netherlands) N.V. for the purchase of 13,33,333 common shares valued at approximately $200 million. This significant capital infusion comes as Novelis continues to navigate its path towards a potential initial public offering (IPO), signalling continued investor confidence in the global aluminum leader.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Schaeffler India FY25 Profit Jumps 22%; Declares ₹35 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Schaeffler-India-FY25-Profit-Jumps-22percent-Declares-35-Dividend/699dead704a25a58c851b48c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Schaeffler-India-FY25-Profit-Jumps-22percent-Declares-35-Dividend/699dead704a25a58c851b48c</guid><description>Schaeffler India reported robust FY25 results with a 22.4% rise in net profit to ₹11,962 crore and 16.3% revenue growth to ₹9,395 crore, driven by strong automotive sector demand. The company also declared a dividend of ₹35 per share, signalling financial health. A minor impact on Q4 PBT margin was noted due to the labour code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:15:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dead704a25a58c851b48b_1771957218129.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Akme Fintrade: Acquirer Group Lifts Stake to 6.78% via Open Market Buys</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-Acquirer-Group-Lifts-Stake-to-678percent-via-Open-Market-Buys/699deaad04a25a58c851b340</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-Acquirer-Group-Lifts-Stake-to-678percent-via-Open-Market-Buys/699deaad04a25a58c851b340</guid><description>AKME FINTRADE (INDIA) LTD. disclosed a significant shareholding increase under SEBI's SAST regulations. A group of acquirers, led by Subhash Phootarmal Rathod, collectively bought 1.253% of the company's voting capital via open market transactions between February 20-24, 2026. Their total holding now stands at 6.783%. This move signifies sustained interest from the acquirer group in the non-banking financial company.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:15:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699deaad04a25a58c851b33f_1771957093832.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Onix Solar Energy Clarifies Bank Guarantee Allegations; Operations Unaffected</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Onix-Solar-Energy-Clarifies-Bank-Guarantee-Allegations-Operations-Unaffected/699dea1204a25a58c851af2b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Onix-Solar-Energy-Clarifies-Bank-Guarantee-Allegations-Operations-Unaffected/699dea1204a25a58c851af2b</guid><description>Onix Solar Energy Limited has issued a clarification regarding media reports alleging fraudulent bank guarantee issues for its Maharashtra solar projects. The company stated it is not named as an accused in the FIR, that discrepancies in bank guarantees were rectified before the FIR filing, and confirmed its ongoing operations and financial position remain unaffected. The clarification comes amid reports of FIRs filed against associated entities for forged guarantees.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:12:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dea1204a25a58c851af2a_1771956987482.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Orient Electric: KYC Update Mandate for Physical Shareholders; Dividend Hold Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Orient-Electric-KYC-Update-Mandate-for-Physical-Shareholders-Dividend-Hold-Looms/699de86504a25a58c8515686</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Orient-Electric-KYC-Update-Mandate-for-Physical-Shareholders-Dividend-Hold-Looms/699de86504a25a58c8515686</guid><description>Orient Electric has issued a crucial update for shareholders holding physical securities, emphasizing mandatory KYC, PAN, and nomination details. Citing SEBI mandates, the company will withhold dividend payments for non-compliant shareholders from April 1, 2024. A special one-year window (Feb 5, 2026 - Feb 4, 2027) is also open for transferring physical securities sold before April 1, 2019.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:05:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de86504a25a58c8515685_1771958683826.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>WPIL Ltd: INR 1,300Cr+ Revenue; Global Push Targets 20% Product Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/WPIL-Ltd-INR-1300Cr-Revenue-Global-Push-Targets-20percent-Product-Growth/699de85b04a25a58c8514d66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/WPIL-Ltd-INR-1300Cr-Revenue-Global-Push-Targets-20percent-Product-Growth/699de85b04a25a58c8514d66</guid><description>WPIL Limited has reported over INR 1,300 crore in revenue for the first nine months of FY26, driven by its engineered flow solutions business. The company is aggressively expanding its global footprint through strategic acquisitions and joint ventures, targeting approximately 20% year-over-year growth in its product business over the next five years. While facing temporary moderation in its project business due to domestic funding, WPIL is focusing on high-margin international markets and exports to fuel future growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks Plunge on AI Disruption and Sovereign Risk Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Plunge-on-AI-Disruption-and-Sovereign-Risk-Fears/699de77104a25a58c850f5f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Plunge-on-AI-Disruption-and-Sovereign-Risk-Fears/699de77104a25a58c850f5f2</guid><description>The Indian IT sector is in distress following a Citrini Research report detailing AI-driven contract cancellations and risks to consumption-driven economies. The Nifty IT Index plummeted 4.74% to a 30-month low, entering bear-market territory with a 22% drop since February 4th. Benchmark indices also fell, wiping out ₹3.55 lakh crore in market capitalization. Concerns extend beyond job losses to potential sovereign economic vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Quintegra Solutions Seeks NCLT Nod for Capital Reduction to Write Off Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Quintegra-Solutions-Seeks-NCLT-Nod-for-Capital-Reduction-to-Write-Off-Losses/699de74304a25a58c850f563</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Quintegra-Solutions-Seeks-NCLT-Nod-for-Capital-Reduction-to-Write-Off-Losses/699de74304a25a58c850f563</guid><description>Quintegra Solutions Limited has applied to the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), Chennai, to reduce its share capital. The move, approved by shareholders, aims to write off accumulated losses of ₹178.12 crore by adjusting reserves, thereby improving the company's financial presentation and attracting investors. The face value of shares will be reduced from ₹10 to ₹1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>P&amp;G Hygiene's Legal Head Hegde to Oversee India, MEA Regional Operations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PandG-Hygienes-Legal-Head-Hegde-to-Oversee-India-MEA-Regional-Operations/699de74004a25a58c850f54d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PandG-Hygienes-Legal-Head-Hegde-to-Oversee-India-MEA-Regional-Operations/699de74004a25a58c850f54d</guid><description>Procter &amp; Gamble Hygiene &amp; Health Care Limited announced on February 24, 2026, that Mr. Ghanashyam Hegde, Legal Head, Executive Director, and Company Secretary, will assume a new regional role. Effective July 1, 2026, he will become Vice President &amp; Associate General Counsel – Market Operations, overseeing India, Middle East, Turkey, and Africa. This move signifies a broadening of responsibilities for key legal oversight within P&amp;G's expansive emerging markets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de74004a25a58c850f54c_1771956137566.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys Q3 FY26: AI Revenue Hits 5.5%; 90% Workforce AI-Enabled</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Q3-FY26-AI-Revenue-Hits-55percent-90percent-Workforce-AI-Enabled/699de6ff04a25a58c850f450</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Q3-FY26-AI-Revenue-Hits-55percent-90percent-Workforce-AI-Enabled/699de6ff04a25a58c850f450</guid><description>Infosys is aggressively integrating AI, with 5.5% of Q3 FY26 revenue now from AI and 90% of its workforce AI-enabled. Management forecasts a $300-$400 billion AI services market and reaffirms margin guidance, reinvesting AI-driven cost savings. Key challenges include the deployment gap and execution at scale.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:59:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de6ff04a25a58c850f44f_1771956107386.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SAMHI Subsidiary Gets Go-Ahead for 235-Room Hotel Expansion in Bangalore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SAMHI-Subsidiary-Gets-Go-Ahead-for-235-Room-Hotel-Expansion-in-Bangalore/699de6ca04a25a58c850f3cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SAMHI-Subsidiary-Gets-Go-Ahead-for-235-Room-Hotel-Expansion-in-Bangalore/699de6ca04a25a58c850f3cf</guid><description>SAMHI Hotels' subsidiary, ITHPL, has secured KIADB sanctioned layout plans for a second hotel development in Whitefield, Bangalore. This expansion will add approximately 235 rooms to its existing 142-room Westin-branded hotel, bringing the total inventory at the complex to around 377 rooms, reinforcing its presence in a key commercial hub.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:58:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de6ca04a25a58c850f3ce_1771956024089.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kome-On Communication Ltd AGM March 19; Delisting Proceedings Continue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kome-On-Communication-Ltd-AGM-March-19-Delisting-Proceedings-Continue/699de67504a25a58c850f30c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kome-On-Communication-Ltd-AGM-March-19-Delisting-Proceedings-Continue/699de67504a25a58c850f30c</guid><description>Kome-On Communication Limited has scheduled its 30th Annual General Meeting (AGM) for March 19, 2026, to adopt FY 2022-23 audited financials and appoint directors. The company appointed Mr. Shankar Kokane and Mrs. Renu Beniwal as Non-Executive Independent Directors. However, BSE Limited issued a delisting order on December 11, 2025, with ongoing proceedings until April 10, 2026, regarding the potential compulsory delisting of its equity shares, creating significant uncertainty for its trading status.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:57:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de67504a25a58c850f30b_1771955973092.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Subsidiary Wins 300 MW Gujarat Wind Project from SECI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Waaree-Energies-Subsidiary-Wins-300-MW-Gujarat-Wind-Project-from-SECI/699de66d04a25a58c850f2f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Waaree-Energies-Subsidiary-Wins-300-MW-Gujarat-Wind-Project-from-SECI/699de66d04a25a58c850f2f5</guid><description>Waaree Energies' subsidiary, Waaree Forever Energies, has been awarded a 300 MW wind power project in Dwarka, Gujarat, by the Solar Energy Corporation of India (SECI). This significant win includes a 25-year Power Purchase Agreement (PPA), providing long-term revenue visibility and reinforcing Waaree's expanding footprint in India's renewable energy sector, particularly in wind power development.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:57:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de66d04a25a58c850f2f4_1771956903092.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>H.G. Infra Wins ₹1,582 Cr NHAI Odisha Road Project as L-1 Bidder</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HG-Infra-Wins-1582-Cr-NHAI-Odisha-Road-Project-as-L-1-Bidder/699de5b304a25a58c850f0d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HG-Infra-Wins-1582-Cr-NHAI-Odisha-Road-Project-as-L-1-Bidder/699de5b304a25a58c850f0d1</guid><description>H.G. Infra Engineering Limited has been declared the Lowest (L-1) bidder by the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for a significant road project in Odisha. The bid is valued at ₹1,582.11 crore for the construction of a new six-lane access-controlled Capital Region Ring Road, Package-III. This marks a substantial addition to the company's order book, reinforcing its position in the infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:53:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de5b304a25a58c850f0d0_1771955749000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lux Industries Ratings Affirmed: AA Stable for ₹464Cr Debt by Acuite</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lux-Industries-Ratings-Affirmed-AA-Stable-for-464Cr-Debt-by-Acuite/699de4bb04a25a58c850ec80</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lux-Industries-Ratings-Affirmed-AA-Stable-for-464Cr-Debt-by-Acuite/699de4bb04a25a58c850ec80</guid><description>Lux Industries Limited's long-term bank facilities worth ₹464.18 crore have been reaffirmed at 'AA (Stable)' by Acuite Ratings &amp; Research Limited. Short-term facilities of ₹1.50 crore also retain an 'A1+ (Stable)' rating. This reaffirmation signals continued financial stability for the Kolkata-based apparel manufacturer, despite recent pressures on its profitability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:49:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de4bb04a25a58c850ec7f_1771955541476.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>