<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:54:19 +0000</pubDate><item><title>INOXGFL's 1900 Cr Bid Targets Distressed Wind World Assets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/INOXGFLs-1900-Cr-Bid-Targets-Distressed-Wind-World-Assets/6995b364d25eafd9cdfd810d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/INOXGFLs-1900-Cr-Bid-Targets-Distressed-Wind-World-Assets/6995b364d25eafd9cdfd810d</guid><description>INOXGFL Group has submitted a ₹1,800-1,900 crore bid for distressed assets of Wind World India under insolvency proceedings. The bid is strategically split between Inox Clean Energy (for generation capacity) and Inox Green Energy (for O&amp;M services). This move accelerates INOXGFL's aggressive renewable energy expansion targets, aiming to secure critical infrastructure and service capabilities amidst a competitive sector. The acquisition signifies a consolidation play, leveraging group entities to absorb a significant bankrupt player.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:41:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995b364d25eafd9cdfd810c_1771418618517.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cement Sector: Demand Rebounds, But Margin Squeeze Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Sector-Demand-Rebounds-But-Margin-Squeeze-Looms/6995b2ebd25eafd9cdfd804c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Sector-Demand-Rebounds-But-Margin-Squeeze-Looms/6995b2ebd25eafd9cdfd804c</guid><description>The Indian cement sector navigated a mixed Q3 FY26, with volumes up approximately 7% year-on-year, driven by price corrections that boosted demand. Despite operational cost savings, EBITDA per tonne saw a sequential decline. Looking ahead, strong infrastructure spending from the Union Budget 2026-27 promises sustained demand, yet rising pet coke prices and significant capacity additions cast a shadow over future margin expansion and competitive pricing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:39:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995b2ebd25eafd9cdfd804b_1771418472646.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MM Forgings: Margin Squeeze Amidst Growth Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MM-Forgings-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Growth-Hopes/6995b1fbd25eafd9cdfd7f16</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MM-Forgings-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Growth-Hopes/6995b1fbd25eafd9cdfd7f16</guid><description>MM Forgings posted Q3FY26 results showing an 11% revenue increase to ₹405 crore, driven by exports and domestic sales. However, consolidated profit after tax plunged 33.82% year-on-year to ₹17.57 crore, and gross margins contracted by 440 basis points due to an unfavorable product mix. Despite these headwinds, analysts foresee a robust revenue and EBITDA CAGR of 13% and 18% respectively over FY26-28E, supported by an anticipated M&amp;HCV sector recovery and GST reforms. The company's stock trades at a P/E of approximately 22-26x, appearing more conservatively valued than peers Ramkrishna Forgings (39-48x) and Bharat Forge (64-74x).</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:35:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995b1fbd25eafd9cdfd7f15_1771418387122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ipca Labs: Margin Gains Mask API Woes, Premium Valuation Questioned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ipca-Labs-Margin-Gains-Mask-API-Woes-Premium-Valuation-Questioned/6995b1fbd25eafd9cdfd7eff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ipca-Labs-Margin-Gains-Mask-API-Woes-Premium-Valuation-Questioned/6995b1fbd25eafd9cdfd7eff</guid><description>Ipca Laboratories posted a 19% year-on-year EBITDA increase to ₹530 crore, significantly exceeding estimates, driven by a 400 bps gross margin expansion. Revenues reached ₹2,400 crore, a 6.6% rise. However, this performance is tempered by a 14% decline in domestic API sales and flat overall API revenue, contrasting with robust formulation growth. The company's valuation now trades at a premium to peers and industry averages, prompting a cautious outlook from some analysts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:35:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995b1fbd25eafd9cdfd7efe_1771418276160.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Qualcomm Bets $150M on India's Edge AI for Future Chip Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Bets-150M-on-Indias-Edge-AI-for-Future-Chip-Dominance/6995b180d25eafd9cdfd7e6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Bets-150M-on-Indias-Edge-AI-for-Future-Chip-Dominance/6995b180d25eafd9cdfd7e6d</guid><description>Qualcomm Incorporated is injecting up to $150 million into India's technology and AI startup ecosystem through its venture arm, Qualcomm Ventures. This strategic move focuses on advancing edge AI in automotive, IoT, robotics, and mobile sectors. The investment deepens Qualcomm's nearly two-decade commitment to India, aiming to secure future innovation and market positions beyond traditional mobile markets, while competitors like NVIDIA, Microsoft, and Google are also aggressively expanding their AI presence in the region.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:33:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995b180d25eafd9cdfd7e6c_1771418125019.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tejas Networks Gets ₹69.96 Cr Boost From Govt PLI Scheme</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tejas-Networks-Gets-6996-Cr-Boost-From-Govt-PLI-Scheme/6995b017d25eafd9cdfd7dc5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tejas-Networks-Gets-6996-Cr-Boost-From-Govt-PLI-Scheme/6995b017d25eafd9cdfd7dc5</guid><description>Tejas Networks Limited has received a significant payment of ₹69.96 Crore from the Department of Telecommunications under the Production Linked Incentive (PLI) Scheme. This financial inflow for FY 2024-2025 is expected to positively impact the company's cash position and working capital, supporting its role in boosting India's telecom manufacturing capabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:27:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995b017d25eafd9cdfd7dc4_1771417747033.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nephrocare Health Services Sees 32% Revenue Jump, Expands Global Footprint</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Nephrocare-Health-Services-Sees-32percent-Revenue-Jump-Expands-Global-Footprint/6995adc2d25eafd9cdfd7c51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Nephrocare-Health-Services-Sees-32percent-Revenue-Jump-Expands-Global-Footprint/6995adc2d25eafd9cdfd7c51</guid><description>Nephrocare Health Services has reported a robust financial performance for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 (Q3 FY26). Consolidated revenue surged by 32% year-on-year to ₹260 crore, driven by strong treatment volumes and increased revenue per treatment. The company also highlighted significant growth in its international operations and reiterated its long-term revenue CAGR guidance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:17:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995adc2d25eafd9cdfd7c50_1771417133133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jindal Saw Faces API License Suspension: What Investors Need to Know</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Saw-Faces-API-License-Suspension-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6995adc1d25eafd9cdfd7c3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Saw-Faces-API-License-Suspension-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6995adc1d25eafd9cdfd7c3b</guid><description>Jindal Saw Limited has had its American Petroleum Institute (API) license for seamless pipes suspended following an audit that identified non-conformances. This critical suspension prohibits the company from affixing the API monogram, a key mark of quality for oil and gas clients. While management suggests the financial impact may not be material due to fungible capacity, this event introduces significant operational and reputational risks, potentially affecting long-term supply contracts and positioning the company at a disadvantage against peers maintaining their certifications. The company is actively engaging with API to resolve the issue and expects to provide updates on remediation efforts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995adc1d25eafd9cdfd7c3a_1771417225867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sarvam AI's LLMs: India's AI Leap or Costly Bet?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sarvam-AIs-LLMs-Indias-AI-Leap-or-Costly-Bet/6995ad4cd25eafd9cdfd7b5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sarvam-AIs-LLMs-Indias-AI-Leap-or-Costly-Bet/6995ad4cd25eafd9cdfd7b5c</guid><description>Bengaluru-based Sarvam AI has launched 30B and 105B parameter LLMs, leveraging efficient MoE architecture to challenge global leaders like Google's Gemini and DeepSeek. Backed by significant government subsidies under IndiaAI Mission for crucial GPU access, the startup aims to spearhead India's sovereign AI drive. However, the complex nature of MoE at scale and intense global competition present considerable commercialization risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:15:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995ad4cd25eafd9cdfd7b5b_1771417086225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCC Ltd Debarred by NHAI: Legal Battle Clouds Future Bids</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NCC-Ltd-Debarred-by-NHAI-Legal-Battle-Clouds-Future-Bids/6995ad48d25eafd9cdfd7b45</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NCC-Ltd-Debarred-by-NHAI-Legal-Battle-Clouds-Future-Bids/6995ad48d25eafd9cdfd7b45</guid><description>NCC Ltd and its subsidiary OB Infrastructure Ltd received a two-year debarment order from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) effective February 17, 2026, due to ongoing project disputes and arbitration. Despite NCC stating no immediate financial impact on its current order book, the action restricts participation in future NHAI tenders. The company plans to challenge the order, which stems from delays allegedly caused by NHAI on the Orai–Bhognipur and Bhognipur–Barah highway projects. Shares fell 1.77% on the news.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:15:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995ad48d25eafd9cdfd7b44_1771417071324.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICE Builds Pune Hub: Talent &amp; Tech Drive GCC Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/ICE-Builds-Pune-Hub-Talent-and-Tech-Drive-GCC-Expansion/6995ad27d25eafd9cdfd7b0f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/ICE-Builds-Pune-Hub-Talent-and-Tech-Drive-GCC-Expansion/6995ad27d25eafd9cdfd7b0f</guid><description>Intercontinental Exchange (ICE) Mortgage Technology has secured nearly 2 lakh sq ft of office space in Pune's Magarpatta Cybercity via a long-term lease. This expansion signals a strategic push into India to support advanced product engineering and technology operations, leveraging Pune's deep talent pool and competitive costs. The move underscores Pune's rapid ascent as a key destination for global capability centers (GCCs) in the financial services and technology sectors, joining established hubs like Bengaluru and Hyderabad. ICE, a significant player in digital infrastructure for global financial markets, is expected to enhance its India operations with this new facility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:14:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995ad27d25eafd9cdfd7b0e_1771416966899.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FedEx Bets Big: ₹2,500 Cr Hub to Boost India's Logistics Gateway</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/FedEx-Bets-Big-2500-Cr-Hub-to-Boost-Indias-Logistics-Gateway/6995ac88d25eafd9cdfd7a49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/FedEx-Bets-Big-2500-Cr-Hub-to-Boost-Indias-Logistics-Gateway/6995ac88d25eafd9cdfd7a49</guid><description>FedEx has initiated construction on a substantial ₹2,500 crore, 300,000 sq. ft. automated air cargo hub at Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA). This strategic investment, a partnership with Adani Airport Holdings, aims to significantly bolster Western India's logistics infrastructure, create over 6,000 jobs, and position the region as a key international trade gateway. The facility will leverage advanced automation to improve efficiency for high-value sectors and contribute to India's rapidly expanding air cargo market, which is projected for significant growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:11:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995ac88d25eafd9cdfd7a48_1771416801222.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ZF India Seeks Shareholder Nod for Rs 2,500 Crore Deal with Sister Firm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/ZF-India-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-Rs-2500-Crore-Deal-with-Sister-Firm/6995abe1d25eafd9cdfd7963</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/ZF-India-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-Rs-2500-Crore-Deal-with-Sister-Firm/6995abe1d25eafd9cdfd7963</guid><description>ZF Commercial Vehicle Control Systems India Limited has announced a postal ballot seeking shareholder approval for significant related party transactions (RPT) with its fellow subsidiary, ZF CV Systems Global GmbH. The proposed transactions, valued up to ₹2,500 crore for FY 2026-27, represent a substantial portion of the company's turnover, raising questions about financial transparency and deal terms for investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:09:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995abe1d25eafd9cdfd7962_1771416686988.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPL: Nomura Sees 60% Upside Amidst Sustainability Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EPL-Nomura-Sees-60percent-Upside-Amidst-Sustainability-Race/6995ab6bd25eafd9cdfd78e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EPL-Nomura-Sees-60percent-Upside-Amidst-Sustainability-Race/6995ab6bd25eafd9cdfd78e0</guid><description>Nomura initiated coverage on packaging firm EPL Limited with a 'Buy' rating and a Rs 350 target price, signaling approximately 60% potential upside. The firm's optimism stems from EPL's 13.3% Q3FY26 revenue growth, led by the Beauty &amp; Cosmetics segment, and strategic expansion in emerging markets. A key focus on sustainability and stable operating margins (around 20.1%) bolsters the outlook. While EPL's current valuation appears supportive, trading below its long-term average and at a P/E of approximately 17x, its projected growth rate may trail industry peers. The report also highlights EPL's comparatively weaker financial stability against competitors and a declining mutual fund holding.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:07:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995ab6bd25eafd9cdfd78df_1771416618824.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vervesemi Secures $10M Series A to Scale ML Analog ICs Amidst India's Deep Tech Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Vervesemi-Secures-10M-Series-A-to-Scale-ML-Analog-ICs-Amidst-Indias-Deep-Tech-Surge/6995aaf2d25eafd9cdfd785e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Vervesemi-Secures-10M-Series-A-to-Scale-ML-Analog-ICs-Amidst-Indias-Deep-Tech-Surge/6995aaf2d25eafd9cdfd785e</guid><description>Fabless semiconductor startup Vervesemi has secured $10 million in Series A funding, co-led by Ashish Kacholia and Unicorn India Ventures. The capital infusion is crucial for scaling its ML-enhanced analog signal chain ICs, including data converters and intelligent power solutions, targeting industrial, smart energy, and avionics markets. This funding marks a transition from technology validation to large-scale deployment, benefiting from India's rapidly maturing deep tech ecosystem and government support for foundational technologies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:05:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995aaf2d25eafd9cdfd785d_1771416476686.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Surges Amidst Demand, Silver Outpaces Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-Amidst-Demand-Silver-Outpaces-Gains/6995aa09d25eafd9cdfd77a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-Amidst-Demand-Silver-Outpaces-Gains/6995aa09d25eafd9cdfd77a3</guid><description>Gold prices surged on Wednesday, with April futures on MCX reaching Rs 1,52,715 per 10 grams, a 0.86% increase, fueled by strong spot demand and speculator buying. Globally, spot gold rose 0.8% to $4,915.90 per ounce. Notably, silver prices demonstrated a more aggressive rally, with spot silver jumping 2.8%. City-level prices across India showed minor variations, with Chennai recording slightly higher rates. The divergence in precious metal performance hints at underlying market sentiment beyond simple gold accumulation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:01:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995aa09d25eafd9cdfd77a2_1771416230516.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prostarm Info Systems Surges on Strong Sales, Debt Cleared</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Prostarm-Info-Systems-Surges-on-Strong-Sales-Debt-Cleared/6995a911d25eafd9cdfd76fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Prostarm-Info-Systems-Surges-on-Strong-Sales-Debt-Cleared/6995a911d25eafd9cdfd76fc</guid><description>Prostarm Info Systems Limited posted stellar Q3 results, with revenue soaring 110% year-on-year to ₹161 Cr. The company also significantly reduced its debt, becoming effectively net debt-free. Management is optimistic about future growth, driven by expansions in Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) and UPS segments, aiming for 20-25% revenue growth in FY'26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:57:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a911d25eafd9cdfd76fb_1771415929178.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mamaearth Parent Honasa Consumer Posts Record Revenue, Eyes Margin Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mamaearth-Parent-Honasa-Consumer-Posts-Record-Revenue-Eyes-Margin-Growth/6995a89cd25eafd9cdfd769a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mamaearth-Parent-Honasa-Consumer-Posts-Record-Revenue-Eyes-Margin-Growth/6995a89cd25eafd9cdfd769a</guid><description>Honasa Consumer Limited, the parent company of Mamaearth, reported its highest-ever quarterly revenue of ₹602 crores in Q3 FY'26, a 21.7% year-on-year jump. Profit After Tax (PAT) nearly doubled, reaching its highest point. The company also announced the acquisition of Reginald Men, bolstering its presence in the growing men's skincare segment. Management is confident in sustaining growth and expects annual EBITDA margin expansion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:55:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a89cd25eafd9cdfd7699_1771415821389.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godavari Biorefineries Posts Strong Q3 Profit Jump, Plans Ethanol Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Godavari-Biorefineries-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Jump-Plans-Ethanol-Expansion/6995a803d25eafd9cdfd7607</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Godavari-Biorefineries-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Jump-Plans-Ethanol-Expansion/6995a803d25eafd9cdfd7607</guid><description>Godavari Biorefineries Limited reported a strong financial performance for Q3 FY26, with Profit Before Tax (PBT) before exceptional items soaring by 152.2% year-on-year to ₹21.4 crore. The company saw its EBITDA grow by 13.8% to ₹45.1 crore, with margins improving to 9.8%. This turnaround was driven by better performance in Bio-based Chemicals and Sugar &amp; Cogeneration segments, alongside significant reduction in finance costs due to IPO proceeds being used for debt repayment. The company is also planning a new 200 KLPD grain/maize distillery for ethanol production, expected to commission in Q1 FY27.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:52:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a803d25eafd9cdfd7606_1771415657283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kirloskar Ferrous Sees Production Rise Amidst Price Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kirloskar-Ferrous-Sees-Production-Rise-Amidst-Price-Pressures/6995a750d25eafd9cdfd74af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kirloskar-Ferrous-Sees-Production-Rise-Amidst-Price-Pressures/6995a750d25eafd9cdfd74af</guid><description>Kirloskar Ferrous Industries Limited (KFIL) posted solid operational gains in Q3 FY26 with higher production across pig iron, casting, tubes, and steel segments. However, the company grappled with margin pressures due to falling product prices and rising input costs. Management expresses optimism for Q4, anticipating margin recovery from increased prices, and is focused on strategic growth projects like the Oliver Foundry merger and expanding green energy capacity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:49:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a750d25eafd9cdfd74ae_1771415456833.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Deep-Tech Surges Amidst LP Hype, Lacks Global Unicorns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indian-Deep-Tech-Surges-Amidst-LP-Hype-Lacks-Global-Unicorns/6995a72ad25eafd9cdfd7416</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indian-Deep-Tech-Surges-Amidst-LP-Hype-Lacks-Global-Unicorns/6995a72ad25eafd9cdfd7416</guid><description>Investor and LP appetite for Indian deep-tech and AI startups has surged, fueled by successful IPOs and increased family office participation. A $2.5 billion IDTA fund and government R&amp;D initiatives aim to accelerate growth. However, the sector struggles with a global lack of a recognized innovation leader, potentially impacting long-term international capital flows and creating valuation risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:48:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a72ad25eafd9cdfd7415_1771415473227.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor's Indonesia Hub Hits 1M Units, Fuels ASEAN EV Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motors-Indonesia-Hub-Hits-1M-Units-Fuels-ASEAN-EV-Ambitions/6995a6d6d25eafd9cdfd737b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motors-Indonesia-Hub-Hits-1M-Units-Fuels-ASEAN-EV-Ambitions/6995a6d6d25eafd9cdfd737b</guid><description>TVS Motor achieved a landmark 1 million vehicle production in Indonesia, underscoring its Indonesian facility's role as a vital global manufacturing and export base. This milestone, representing 19 years of operation, supports the company's strategic push into the ASEAN market, particularly its electric vehicle ambitions, leveraging local capacity for regional distribution. The production mix is 95% two-wheelers and 5% three-wheelers, serving markets across multiple continents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:47:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a6d6d25eafd9cdfd737a_1771415477955.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CDMOs Shift: Strategic Partnerships Mask Growing Sector Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CDMOs-Shift-Strategic-Partnerships-Mask-Growing-Sector-Volatility/6995a6d1d25eafd9cdfd735a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CDMOs-Shift-Strategic-Partnerships-Mask-Growing-Sector-Volatility/6995a6d1d25eafd9cdfd735a</guid><description>Indian contract development and manufacturing organizations (CDMOs) are transitioning from tactical manufacturing to strategic partnerships with global pharmaceutical firms. This evolution, driven by geopolitical shifts and a focus on supply chain resilience, promises a multi-year growth cycle. However, this strategic embrace masks inherent revenue volatility from product mix shifts and inventory cycles, while prompting close valuation scrutiny as companies invest heavily in capacity and technology. Sai Life Sciences highlights this industry investment phase, emphasizing long-term relationships over short-term metrics.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:47:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a6d1d25eafd9cdfd7359_1771415415476.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Frontier Warehousing eyes Kesoram Industries with ₹5.48 per share open offer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Frontier-Warehousing-eyes-Kesoram-Industries-with-548-per-share-open-offer/6995a6c7d25eafd9cdfd733e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Frontier-Warehousing-eyes-Kesoram-Industries-with-548-per-share-open-offer/6995a6c7d25eafd9cdfd733e</guid><description>Frontier Warehousing Limited is making a mandatory open offer to buy 26% of Kesoram Industries Limited at ₹5.48 per share. This follows Frontier's agreement to purchase a 42.80% stake from Kesoram's promoters. The offer opens on February 26, 2026. Kesoram Industries, historically a cement producer, has faced significant operational losses in recent years, with its recent profit boosted by a demerger. Frontier Warehousing, involved in warehousing and real estate, has substantial borrowings relative to its equity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:47:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a6c7d25eafd9cdfd733d_1771415371931.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>S&amp;P 500 Tests Support Amid Tech Exodus, Breadth Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/SandP-500-Tests-Support-Amid-Tech-Exodus-Breadth-Divergence/6995a66dd25eafd9cdfd7227</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/SandP-500-Tests-Support-Amid-Tech-Exodus-Breadth-Divergence/6995a66dd25eafd9cdfd7227</guid><description>The S&amp;P 500 is under pressure, testing critical support levels including its 100-day moving average. This comes as investors rotate out of high-valuation technology stocks into defensive sectors. While the index struggles, market breadth indicators suggest underlying resilience, creating a complex dynamic. The performance of mega-cap tech stocks, particularly the "Magnificent Seven," continues to heavily influence the broader market's direction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:45:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a66dd25eafd9cdfd7226_1771415297004.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dr. Reddy's Semaglutide Push: Canada Launch Amidst Fierce Generic Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Semaglutide-Push-Canada-Launch-Amidst-Fierce-Generic-Race/6995a66ad25eafd9cdfd7210</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Semaglutide-Push-Canada-Launch-Amidst-Fierce-Generic-Race/6995a66ad25eafd9cdfd7210</guid><description>Dr. Reddy's Laboratories is poised to launch its generic semaglutide in Canada, targeting a May timeline following minimal regulatory queries. This move positions the company to capitalize on early market entry ahead of significant competition from players like Biocon, Sandoz, and Lupin. While promising substantial revenue, the launch occurs within a fiercely competitive and rapidly commoditizing GLP-1 market, raising questions about long-term pricing power and sustainable growth. Dr. Reddy's, valued at approximately ₹1.07 trillion with a P/E of around 19x, aims to offset pressures in other markets but faces an uphill battle for sustained profitability in the face of aggressive price erosion projections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:45:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a66ad25eafd9cdfd720f_1771415446792.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BL Kashyap Bags ₹300 Cr Housing Order; Analysts Eye Execution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BL-Kashyap-Bags-300-Cr-Housing-Order-Analysts-Eye-Execution/6995a662d25eafd9cdfd71f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BL-Kashyap-Bags-300-Cr-Housing-Order-Analysts-Eye-Execution/6995a662d25eafd9cdfd71f6</guid><description>BL Kashyap and Sons Ltd announced a significant ₹300 crore work order for a group housing project in Greater Noida, slated for execution over 42 months. This addition further strengthens the company's already robust order book, which includes substantial contracts secured late last year. However, the stock's modest 0.30% gain suggests investors are now scrutinizing execution timelines and competitive positioning within the Indian construction sector, which faces ongoing cost pressures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:45:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a662d25eafd9cdfd71f5_1771415255575.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jinkushal Standalone Profit Soars, Consolidated Sees Loss Due to Big Inventory Build</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jinkushal-Standalone-Profit-Soars-Consolidated-Sees-Loss-Due-to-Big-Inventory-Build/6995a5fed25eafd9cdfd7118</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jinkushal-Standalone-Profit-Soars-Consolidated-Sees-Loss-Due-to-Big-Inventory-Build/6995a5fed25eafd9cdfd7118</guid><description>Jinkushal Industries reported a strong standalone profit of ₹4.17 Cr for Q3 FY26, up 34% YoY. However, the consolidated results showed a loss of ₹9.87 Cr, primarily due to a strategic build-up of ₹70 Cr in overseas inventory. The company is shifting towards direct retail sales and higher-margin refurbished machines, utilizing IPO funds for global expansion and brand building.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:43:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a5fed25eafd9cdfd7117_1771415092887.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PAN-Aadhaar Linking: Decoding Data Mismatch Errors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PAN-Aadhaar-Linking-Decoding-Data-Mismatch-Errors/6995a5e6d25eafd9cdfd70f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PAN-Aadhaar-Linking-Decoding-Data-Mismatch-Errors/6995a5e6d25eafd9cdfd70f0</guid><description>Navigating the 'data mismatch' error when linking PAN and Aadhaar cards is a common hurdle for Indian taxpayers. This issue typically stems from minor, often overlooked, inconsistencies in names, spellings, or incomplete birth dates. A rigorous, side-by-side comparison of both official documents is essential to pinpoint these discrepancies. Resolving them requires updating the incorrect information on either the Aadhaar or PAN record, followed by a waiting period for system reflection before re-attempting the linking process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:43:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a5e6d25eafd9cdfd70ef_1771415194936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Midwest Ltd Surges on Strong Q3 Results and Diversification Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Midwest-Ltd-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Results-and-Diversification-Push/6995a553d25eafd9cdfd6ff3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Midwest-Ltd-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Results-and-Diversification-Push/6995a553d25eafd9cdfd6ff3</guid><description>Midwest Limited has posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue rising 10% year-on-year to ₹128 Crores. The company significantly improved its standalone EBITDA margin to 23.7%, up from 20% last year, and used IPO funds to repay ₹54 Crores in loans. Management is optimistic about future growth, detailing aggressive expansion plans across granite, quartz, heavy mineral sands, electric vehicles, and rare earth materials, aiming for sustained double-digit growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:41:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a553d25eafd9cdfd6ff2_1771415000886.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vadhvan Port Land Costs Soar Amidst Acquisition Payouts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Vadhvan-Port-Land-Costs-Soar-Amidst-Acquisition-Payouts/6995a552d25eafd9cdfd6fdd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Vadhvan-Port-Land-Costs-Soar-Amidst-Acquisition-Payouts/6995a552d25eafd9cdfd6fdd</guid><description>Landowners within the Vadhvan Port project zone in Maharashtra are set to receive over ₹2 crore per hectare, a package comprising double the market value plus a 100% solatium. This substantial compensation, mandated by the National Highways Act, 1956, adds considerable weight to the project's ₹76,220 crore capital expenditure. The elevated acquisition costs raise questions about financial prudence and competitive positioning within India's rapidly expanding port infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:41:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a552d25eafd9cdfd6fdc_1771415010500.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Max Financial Profit Dips Despite Strong Insurance Growth; Amalgamation Plan Revealed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Max-Financial-Profit-Dips-Despite-Strong-Insurance-Growth-Amalgamation-Plan-Revealed/6995a471d25eafd9cdfd6e96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Max-Financial-Profit-Dips-Despite-Strong-Insurance-Growth-Amalgamation-Plan-Revealed/6995a471d25eafd9cdfd6e96</guid><description>Max Financial Services (MFSL) reported strong 18% YoY revenue growth for 9 months FY'26, driven by its subsidiary Axis Max Life's impressive 30% APE growth. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) fell due to one-off impacts and GST expenses at the parent level. The company announced an in-principle board approval for the amalgamation of Axis Max Life and MFSL, signalling a major strategic shift.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:37:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a471d25eafd9cdfd6e95_1771414739233.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Muthoot Finance Posts Record Profit, Eyes Expansion as RBI Eases Branch Rules</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Posts-Record-Profit-Eyes-Expansion-as-RBI-Eases-Branch-Rules/6995a469d25eafd9cdfd6e7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Posts-Record-Profit-Eyes-Expansion-as-RBI-Eases-Branch-Rules/6995a469d25eafd9cdfd6e7f</guid><description>Muthoot Finance reported record-breaking standalone Assets Under Management (AUM) and Profit After Tax (PAT) for the nine months ending December 31, 2025. The company saw a 50% YoY growth in its core gold loan portfolio and a 91% jump in PAT. This strong performance is boosted by positive anticipation of new RBI draft regulations that could allow easier branch expansion for NBFCs. Subsidiaries also showed turnarounds, with Belstar Microfinance achieving profitability in Q3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:37:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a469d25eafd9cdfd6e7e_1771414772666.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MTAR Technologies Seeks Shareholder Nod to Boost Borrowing Limit to ₹900 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MTAR-Technologies-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-to-Boost-Borrowing-Limit-to-900-Cr/6995a462d25eafd9cdfd6e65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MTAR-Technologies-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-to-Boost-Borrowing-Limit-to-900-Cr/6995a462d25eafd9cdfd6e65</guid><description>MTAR Technologies has initiated a postal ballot to get shareholder approval for significant financial moves. The company wants to raise its borrowing limit to ₹800 Crores on a standalone basis and ₹900 Crores consolidated. Shareholders will also vote on allowing the creation of charges on company assets to secure these borrowings, alongside approving remuneration for Independent Directors. This move is intended to fuel future growth and operational expansion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:37:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a462d25eafd9cdfd6e64_1771414771360.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCC &amp; Subsidiary Debarred by NHAI for 2 Years, Future Projects Affected</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/NCC-and-Subsidiary-Debarred-by-NHAI-for-2-Years-Future-Projects-Affected/6995a401d25eafd9cdfd6db7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/NCC-and-Subsidiary-Debarred-by-NHAI-for-2-Years-Future-Projects-Affected/6995a401d25eafd9cdfd6db7</guid><description>NCC Limited and its step-down subsidiary OBIL have been debarred by the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for two years, effective February 17, 2026. This prohibition prevents them from participating in any NHAI tenders or bids. While the company states no financial impact on current projects, future business opportunities with NHAI will be curtailed. The debarment stems from a dispute related to an OBIL project, where an arbitration award favoured OBIL, but NHAI has challenged it. NCC plans to contest the debarment order.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:35:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a401d25eafd9cdfd6db6_1771414609181.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NDA Securities faces confusion over share sale amount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NDA-Securities-faces-confusion-over-share-sale-amount/6995a2f8d25eafd9cdfd6ce7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NDA-Securities-faces-confusion-over-share-sale-amount/6995a2f8d25eafd9cdfd6ce7</guid><description>NDA Securities Limited's board has approved a preferential issue of equity shares. However, significant numerical discrepancies in the total issue size, ranging from ₹63.05 crore to ₹3640.5 crore, have raised serious governance and transparency concerns among investors and analysts. The company plans to seek member approval via an EGM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a2f8d25eafd9cdfd6ce6_1771414377207.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aban Offshore NCLAT Order: Settlement Talks Adjourned, Future Uncertain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Aban-Offshore-NCLAT-Order-Settlement-Talks-Adjourned-Future-Uncertain/6995a119d25eafd9cdfd6bee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Aban-Offshore-NCLAT-Order-Settlement-Talks-Adjourned-Future-Uncertain/6995a119d25eafd9cdfd6bee</guid><description>Aban Offshore Limited's Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) is ongoing. The National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT), Chennai, has adjourned a hearing concerning an appeal related to this process to March 27, 2026. This adjournment is to allow for potential settlement discussions between the appellant and Punjab National Bank (PNB). An interim order from January 21, 2026, remains in effect until the next hearing, highlighting the deep financial distress and prolonged uncertainty surrounding the company.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:23:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a119d25eafd9cdfd6bed_1771413922923.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Himalaya Foods Expands to US Market Via US Foods Partnership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Himalaya-Foods-Expands-to-US-Market-Via-US-Foods-Partnership/6995a0a1d25eafd9cdfd6b3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Himalaya-Foods-Expands-to-US-Market-Via-US-Foods-Partnership/6995a0a1d25eafd9cdfd6b3d</guid><description>Himalaya Food International Ltd. has officially entered the United States market by securing product registration and becoming a 'Regular Approved Vendor' with US Foods, a major American foodservice distributor. This strategic move is expected to significantly boost the company's market visibility and pave the way for accelerated growth in North America.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:21:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a0a1d25eafd9cdfd6b3c_1771413778860.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Orient Green Power Boosts Profit, Eyes 1 GW Capacity with New Projects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Orient-Green-Power-Boosts-Profit-Eyes-1-GW-Capacity-with-New-Projects/6995a09fd25eafd9cdfd6b27</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Orient-Green-Power-Boosts-Profit-Eyes-1-GW-Capacity-with-New-Projects/6995a09fd25eafd9cdfd6b27</guid><description>Orient Green Power Company Limited saw its net profit surge by 54% year-on-year to ₹88.13 Crores for the first nine months of FY2026. This growth was significantly boosted by a one-time interest refund. The company is actively expanding its renewable energy portfolio, currently at 389 MW, with plans to add new solar and wind capacity and repower older wind turbines. Management aims to reach 1 GW of capacity and is targeting to unpledge promoter shares by March 2026, signalling confidence in future performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:21:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a09fd25eafd9cdfd6b26_1771413803023.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mufin Green Finance Gets Green Light for Share Sale from BSE, NSE</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Mufin-Green-Finance-Gets-Green-Light-for-Share-Sale-from-BSE-NSE/6995a028d25eafd9cdfd6ab5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Mufin-Green-Finance-Gets-Green-Light-for-Share-Sale-from-BSE-NSE/6995a028d25eafd9cdfd6ab5</guid><description>Mufin Green Finance Limited has received in-principle approval from stock exchanges BSE and NSE for a preferential issue, planning to issue over 3.43 crore equity shares and 76.5 lakh warrants. This move aims to bolster its capital base for expanding its green finance operations. The approval, however, comes with conditions from SEBI and NSE, including strengthening internal controls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:19:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995a028d25eafd9cdfd6ab4_1771413690603.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>