<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:53:18 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Airtel: ARPU Soars, but AI Investments Weigh on Profit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airtel-ARPU-Soars-but-AI-Investments-Weigh-on-Profit/69849026bf48f011a29cdc8a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airtel-ARPU-Soars-but-AI-Investments-Weigh-on-Profit/69849026bf48f011a29cdc8a</guid><description>Bharti Airtel posted a healthy 3.5% sequential revenue increase to ₹53,982 crore and a 4% EBITDA rise to ₹30,782 crore in the December quarter, lifting margins to 57%. However, net profit saw a marginal 2.4% decline to ₹6,630.5 crore. This mixed performance reflects sustained operational momentum across India and Africa, coupled with significant strategic investments in AI and digital services, signaling a long-term growth trajectory. The Homes business continued its strong outperformance with 32.6% YoY revenue growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RERA Insurance Mandate: Developer Scrutiny &amp; Sector Bifurcation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RERA-Insurance-Mandate-Developer-Scrutiny-and-Sector-Bifurcation/69848febbf48f011a29cdb14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RERA-Insurance-Mandate-Developer-Scrutiny-and-Sector-Bifurcation/69848febbf48f011a29cdb14</guid><description>A Karnataka RERA tribunal ruling that builders must provide mandatory Section 16 insurance or cover repair costs highlights increasing regulatory demands on developers. This mandatory insurance requirement, intended to safeguard homebuyers, is set to elevate project compliance standards, potentially bifurcating developers based on their financial robustness and operational discipline. The stricter enforcement could influence cost structures, access to capital, and overall market competitiveness within India's real estate sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Q3 Loss Widens on JLR Cyber Attack; Domestic Sales Shine</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Q3-Loss-Widens-on-JLR-Cyber-Attack-Domestic-Sales-Shine/69848fb6bf48f011a29cda31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Q3-Loss-Widens-on-JLR-Cyber-Attack-Domestic-Sales-Shine/69848fb6bf48f011a29cda31</guid><description>Tata Motors posted a Rs 3,483 crore consolidated loss for Q3 FY26, a stark reversal from profit due to Jaguar Land Rover's severe production disruptions following a cyber incident that impacted global volumes and revenue by 26%. Despite these headwinds, the company's domestic passenger and electric vehicle business demonstrated resilience, achieving 22% volume growth and record wholesale sales. This dichotomy highlights the critical dependence on JLR's recovery for overall financial health.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Posts Stellar Q3 Earnings, Profit Soars 90%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Earnings-Profit-Soars-90percent/69848f10bf48f011a29cd7eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Earnings-Profit-Soars-90percent/69848f10bf48f011a29cd7eb</guid><description>Hitachi Energy India reported a robust Q3 FY25-26, with revenue up 29.6% YoY to ₹2,168 Cr. Profit After Tax (PAT) surged 90.3% YoY to ₹261.4 Cr, driven by a significant EBITDA margin expansion to 15.6%. For the nine months, PAT leaped 228.5% YoY. Management highlighted strategic shifts towards Export, Service, and Digital offerings, alongside growth in Data Centers and BESS, signaling a positive outlook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IHCL Acquires 51% of Brij Hotels for Up to ₹225 Crore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/IHCL-Acquires-51percent-of-Brij-Hotels-for-Up-to-225-Crore/69848efabf48f011a29cd70b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/IHCL-Acquires-51percent-of-Brij-Hotels-for-Up-to-225-Crore/69848efabf48f011a29cd70b</guid><description>The Indian Hotels Company Limited (IHCL) is set to acquire a 51% stake in Brij Hospitality, a luxury boutique hotel operator, for up to ₹225 crore. Antares Legal guided IHCL through deal structuring and due diligence, while Shardul Amarchand Mangaldas &amp; Co represented Brij Hotels and its promoters. This move signals a strategic expansion for IHCL and continues the trend of consolidation in India's hospitality market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharti Airtel's Underlying Strength Shines Despite Q3 Profit Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtels-Underlying-Strength-Shines-Despite-Q3-Profit-Dip/69848e96bf48f011a29cd5b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtels-Underlying-Strength-Shines-Despite-Q3-Profit-Dip/69848e96bf48f011a29cd5b4</guid><description>Bharti Airtel posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenues climbing 19.6% YoY to ₹53,982 crore and EBITDA growing 25.2% to ₹31,144 crore, driven by a 57.7% EBITDA margin. Average Revenue Per User (ARPU) rose to ₹259. The reported net profit after exceptional items fell 55% to ₹6,630.5 crore, primarily due to a high base from a prior year's exceptional gain related to Indus Towers. The company's overall customer base expanded to approximately 645 million.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Power Targets Global Solar Markets, Bets Big on Nuclear Power</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Tata-Power-Targets-Global-Solar-Markets-Bets-Big-on-Nuclear-Power/69848e59bf48f011a29cd46c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Tata-Power-Targets-Global-Solar-Markets-Bets-Big-on-Nuclear-Power/69848e59bf48f011a29cd46c</guid><description>Tata Power is charting an aggressive expansion, targeting solar cell and module exports to the US and Europe by fiscal year 2027, leveraging recent trade agreements that reduce tariffs to 18%. Concurrently, the company is advancing its entry into nuclear energy, identifying land for potential projects, and preparing its 4,000 MW Mundra coal plant for recommencement. This multi-pronged approach aims to diversify revenue streams beyond its established domestic power generation, transmission, and distribution businesses, even as market sentiment remains cautiously bearish.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Surges on Record Order Book &amp; Profit Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Surges-on-Record-Order-Book-and-Profit-Boom/69848e42bf48f011a29cd3e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Surges-on-Record-Order-Book-and-Profit-Boom/69848e42bf48f011a29cd3e3</guid><description>Hitachi Energy India reported a stellar third quarter for FY26, with revenue climbing 29.6% year-on-year to ₹2,168 crore and profit after tax soaring 90.3% to ₹261.4 crore. The company achieved its highest-ever order backlog of ₹29,872 crore, signaling strong future revenue visibility. Margins also expanded significantly, with operational EBITDA reaching 15.6%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NCC Ltd: Revenue Dip Hits Q3, But PAT Jumps Amid Amalgamation Plans</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Ltd-Revenue-Dip-Hits-Q3-But-PAT-Jumps-Amid-Amalgamation-Plans/69848e01bf48f011a29cd270</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Ltd-Revenue-Dip-Hits-Q3-But-PAT-Jumps-Amid-Amalgamation-Plans/69848e01bf48f011a29cd270</guid><description>NCC Limited posted mixed Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue declining 17.2% YoY to ₹4,454.29 crore, while consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) rose 8.15% to ₹122.46 crore. Standalone PAT saw a sharp 57.57% fall to ₹82.01 crore. The company also announced the amalgamation of NCC Infrastructure Holdings Limited, effective February 28, 2026, and maintained a robust order book of ₹79,571 crore.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Alphabet Exceeds $400B Revenue, Investment Gains Fuel Profit Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Exceeds-400B-Revenue-Investment-Gains-Fuel-Profit-Surge/69848dccbf48f011a29cd0fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Exceeds-400B-Revenue-Investment-Gains-Fuel-Profit-Surge/69848dccbf48f011a29cd0fe</guid><description>Alphabet reported record annual revenue of $402.84 billion for 2025, marking a 15% increase fueled by strong performance in Google Search, YouTube, and Google Cloud. Net income surged to $132.17 billion, with a significant portion attributed to a more than threefold increase in "Other income (expense), net" to $29.79 billion, indicating substantial investment gains played a critical role alongside operational growth. CEO Sundar Pichai highlighted the success of Gemini 3 and advancing AI model capabilities. The company maintained a steady operating margin of 32% throughout the year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India to Source $500B US Goods as Trade Deal Slashes Tariffs to 18%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-to-Source-500B-US-Goods-as-Trade-Deal-Slashes-Tariffs-to-18percent/69848d93bf48f011a29ccf52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-to-Source-500B-US-Goods-as-Trade-Deal-Slashes-Tariffs-to-18percent/69848d93bf48f011a29ccf52</guid><description>India has clarified it made no direct investment commitments to the US, but its 'Viksit Bharat 2047' goals will drive $500 billion in US goods sourcing over five years. The initial phase of a bilateral trade agreement, set for imminent rollout, will slash US tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, a significant reduction from previous highs. This pact aims to more than double bilateral trade to $500 billion by 2030, boosting Indian exports and competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Unichem Labs PAT Surges 357% on Land Sale, Core Business Shrinks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Unichem-Labs-PAT-Surges-357percent-on-Land-Sale-Core-Business-Shrinks/69848d6fbf48f011a29cce9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Unichem-Labs-PAT-Surges-357percent-on-Land-Sale-Core-Business-Shrinks/69848d6fbf48f011a29cce9e</guid><description>Unichem Laboratories reported a Q3 FY26 consolidated PAT of ₹264.29 crore, a staggering 356.86% YoY increase, propelled by a ₹275.52 crore gain from the sale of land and buildings. However, this exceptional item masked a significant operational downturn. Consolidated revenue declined 2.24% YoY to ₹521.17 crore, while standalone revenue plummeted by 29.69% YoY to ₹314.90 crore. The nine-month period also showed mixed performance, with consolidated revenue up 6.76% but standalone revenue down 17.14%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Posts 90% PAT Surge, Record Order Backlog</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Posts-90percent-PAT-Surge-Record-Order-Backlog/69848d2dbf48f011a29ccd0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Posts-90percent-PAT-Surge-Record-Order-Backlog/69848d2dbf48f011a29ccd0b</guid><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd. reported robust Q3 FY26 results with revenue climbing 29.6% year-on-year to ₹2,168.0 crore and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 90.3% to ₹261.4 crore. Operational EBITDA margin expanded significantly to 15.6% from 10.1% YoY. The company achieved a record order backlog of ₹29,872.2 crore, driven by strong demand in transformers, GIS/AIS, data centers, and renewables. An exceptional item of ₹54.24 crore due to new Labour Codes impacted QoQ PAT slightly.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indowind Energy Returns to Profit, Posts Strong 9-Month Growth and Solar Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indowind-Energy-Returns-to-Profit-Posts-Strong-9-Month-Growth-and-Solar-Push/69848d12bf48f011a29ccc75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indowind-Energy-Returns-to-Profit-Posts-Strong-9-Month-Growth-and-Solar-Push/69848d12bf48f011a29ccc75</guid><description>Indowind Energy Limited returned to profitability in Q3 FY26 with INR 0.35 crore PAT on INR 6.19 crore revenue. For the nine months ended FY26, revenue surged 21.61% to INR 35.49 crore, EBITDA grew 29.39% to INR 16.98 crore, and net profit rose 24.32% to INR 7.5 crore, driven by better wind season and cost control. The company also completed a INR 49.42 crore rights issue, secured approval for a 4MW solar project, and is planning strategic investments and overseas fundraising up to USD 70 million to fuel future growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:29:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Aavas Financiers Posts 16% PAT Rise Amidst Data Anomalies and Rising Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aavas-Financiers-Posts-16percent-PAT-Rise-Amidst-Data-Anomalies-and-Rising-Costs/69848c80bf48f011a29cca5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aavas-Financiers-Posts-16percent-PAT-Rise-Amidst-Data-Anomalies-and-Rising-Costs/69848c80bf48f011a29cca5b</guid><description>Aavas Financiers reported a strong 16.1% YoY rise in Q3 FY26 Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹1,700.5 million, driven by 18.2% growth in Net Interest Income (NII). Assets Under Management (AUM) increased by 16% YoY. However, operating expenses climbed 20% and credit costs rose 29.3%. Notably, reported Net Worth figures closely mirror AUM, and a significant discrepancy exists between Q3 and 9MFY26 AUM figures, raising data integrity concerns for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Groww IPO Windfall Sparks Partner Exodus at Peak XV</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Groww-IPO-Windfall-Sparks-Partner-Exodus-at-Peak-XV/69848ba7bf48f011a29cc848</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Groww-IPO-Windfall-Sparks-Partner-Exodus-at-Peak-XV/69848ba7bf48f011a29cc848</guid><description>Key partners Ashish Agrawal, Ishaan Mittal, and Tejeshwi Sharma have exited Peak XV Partners. Disputes over payouts and carried interest stemming from Groww's successful IPO, which yielded a significant return, reportedly fueled the departures. This adds to recent leadership churn at India's largest venture capital firm post-Sequoia split.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Banks Press RBI on State Bond Valuation, Risking Market Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Press-RBI-on-State-Bond-Valuation-Risking-Market-Strain/69848b75bf48f011a29cc7aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Press-RBI-on-State-Bond-Valuation-Risking-Market-Strain/69848b75bf48f011a29cc7aa</guid><description>Indian lenders are intensifying calls for the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to reform how state government bonds are valued on their books. Current standardized yield-based accounting practices are reportedly creating significant 'paper losses' for banks, particularly on debt from fiscally stronger states. This situation is dampening demand for new state debt issuance, which is projected to hit record levels, potentially leading to higher borrowing costs for states and broader market instability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:22:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nykaa's Profit Doubles: Can Margin Gains Sustain Amidst High Valuation?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nykaas-Profit-Doubles-Can-Margin-Gains-Sustain-Amidst-High-Valuation/69848b17bf48f011a29cc627</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nykaas-Profit-Doubles-Can-Margin-Gains-Sustain-Amidst-High-Valuation/69848b17bf48f011a29cc627</guid><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd. (Nykaa) announced a robust third quarter for FY26, with net profit more than doubling to ₹63 crore on revenue growth of 27% to ₹2,873 crore. Earnings Before Interest, Taxes, Depreciation, and Amortisation (EBITDA) surged 63.2%, driving EBITDA margins to 8% from 6.2% year-on-year. This performance highlights operational efficiencies and increasing demand in its core beauty segment. However, the company's market valuation, coupled with intensifying competition and evolving consumer spending patterns in India's expansive retail sector, presents a critical juncture for sustained growth and profitability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Power Secures AA+/Stable Rating; ₹2000 Cr NCD Issue Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Secures-AAStable-Rating-2000-Cr-NCD-Issue-Looms/69848aebbf48f011a29cc4f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Secures-AAStable-Rating-2000-Cr-NCD-Issue-Looms/69848aebbf48f011a29cc4f3</guid><description>India Ratings has assigned an 'IND AA+/Stable' rating to Torrent Power's proposed ₹2000 Crore NCDs and reaffirmed existing ratings. The company showcases robust financials with improved leverage and interest coverage, driven by its strong distribution business. TPL is set for significant growth, planning ₹65,000-₹70,000 Crore capex for renewable and thermal power projects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Varroc Engineering Hits Record Revenue on EV Boom, India Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Varroc-Engineering-Hits-Record-Revenue-on-EV-Boom-India-Growth/69848acfbf48f011a29cc42d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Varroc-Engineering-Hits-Record-Revenue-on-EV-Boom-India-Growth/69848acfbf48f011a29cc42d</guid><description>Varroc Engineering reported its highest-ever quarterly revenue of ₹22,875 million, up 10.2% YoY, fueled by robust India operations and a 50% surge in EV segment revenue. Consolidated EBITDA margins improved slightly to 9.3%, while PBT margins rose to 4.4% on improved operational performance. The company secured substantial new business wins worth ₹20,636 million annualized peak revenue. Despite challenges in overseas markets, management eyes a turnaround by H2 FY27, focusing on cost efficiencies and EV opportunities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Thomas Cook India Revenue Up 4%, But One-Offs Hit Profit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Thomas-Cook-India-Revenue-Up-4percent-But-One-Offs-Hit-Profit/69848aa7bf48f011a29cc360</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Thomas-Cook-India-Revenue-Up-4percent-But-One-Offs-Hit-Profit/69848aa7bf48f011a29cc360</guid><description>Thomas Cook India posted a 4% YoY revenue growth in Q3 FY26, reaching ₹21,457 million. While PBT before exceptional items surged 20%, reported PBT and PAT declined due to ₹301 million provisions under the new Labour Code. The company remains optimistic about the upcoming travel season, anticipating momentum from reduced TCS on overseas tour packages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Shreeji Shipping's Post-IPO PAT Surges 135% Driven by Exceptional Item Reversal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Shreeji-Shippings-Post-IPO-PAT-Surges-135percent-Driven-by-Exceptional-Item-Reversal/69848a2fbf48f011a29cc166</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Shreeji-Shippings-Post-IPO-PAT-Surges-135percent-Driven-by-Exceptional-Item-Reversal/69848a2fbf48f011a29cc166</guid><description>Shreeji Shipping Global Limited reported a significant year-on-year boost in its Q4 FY25 consolidated results, posting a 30% revenue increase to ₹1979.26 million and a 135.5% surge in Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹324.66 million. This PAT jump was largely attributed to the absence of a ₹317.80 million exceptional item from the prior year. Post-IPO, the company is utilizing proceeds for expansion, including new vessel construction and a GIFT City subsidiary, while managing contingent liabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cochin Malabar Estates Faces Going Concern Doubt on Eroded Net Worth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Cochin-Malabar-Estates-Faces-Going-Concern-Doubt-on-Eroded-Net-Worth/69848a0cbf48f011a29cc08c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Cochin-Malabar-Estates-Faces-Going-Concern-Doubt-on-Eroded-Net-Worth/69848a0cbf48f011a29cc08c</guid><description>The Cochin Malabar Estates and Industries Limited reported severe financial distress, with its net worth fully eroded and current liabilities surpassing current assets. Auditors have raised substantial uncertainty about the company's ability to continue as a going concern. Quarterly net loss widened by 50% to ₹50.15 Lakhs, while nine-month losses ballooned 185% to ₹105.45 Lakhs, driven by soaring finance costs and depreciation. Management plans to utilize land assets in Goa to address the crisis.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>LIC PAT Surges 16.68% on Higher Margins, AUM Grows to Rs 59.17 Lakh Crore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/LIC-PAT-Surges-1668percent-on-Higher-Margins-AUM-Grows-to-Rs-5917-Lakh-Crore/698489b7bf48f011a29cbf23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/LIC-PAT-Surges-1668percent-on-Higher-Margins-AUM-Grows-to-Rs-5917-Lakh-Crore/698489b7bf48f011a29cbf23</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) posted a robust 16.68% year-on-year rise in Profit After Tax (PAT) to Rs 33,998 crore for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. The insurer achieved this with a significant 27.96% surge in Value of New Business (VNB) and a 170-basis point expansion in Net VNB Margin to 18.8%, driven by a strategic pivot to Non-Par products. Assets Under Management (AUM) grew 8.01% to Rs 59.17 lakh crore. However, the company saw a marginal dip in individual policies sold and persistency ratios, alongside a slight decline in market share.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GNG Electronics Posts Stellar Q3 Profit Growth, Boosts Subsidiary Guarantees</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GNG-Electronics-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Profit-Growth-Boosts-Subsidiary-Guarantees/69848974bf48f011a29cbdae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GNG-Electronics-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Profit-Growth-Boosts-Subsidiary-Guarantees/69848974bf48f011a29cbdae</guid><description>GNG Electronics Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 financial results, with standalone PAT jumping 259.1% YoY to ₹98.48 million and consolidated PAT up 102.8% to ₹386.87 million. Revenue also saw significant YoY increases. Alongside this strong performance, the company approved enhancements to corporate guarantees for its subsidiary, Electronics Bazaar (FZC), totalling an additional AED 38 million across multiple banks. No specific management guidance for future performance was provided.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SETL's Integration Drive: Valuation Premium Meets Execution Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SETLs-Integration-Drive-Valuation-Premium-Meets-Execution-Risk/6984894dbf48f011a29cbcb5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SETLs-Integration-Drive-Valuation-Premium-Meets-Execution-Risk/6984894dbf48f011a29cbcb5</guid><description>Standard Engineering Technology Limited (SETL) is pivoting from specialized manufacturing to a 'concept-to-commissioning' engineering platform via strategic acquisitions. While Q3 FY26 and 9M FY26 results show robust income growth (up 37.1% and 23.6% respectively) and PAT increases (up 28.3% and 18.8%), the company's valuation commands a premium. This expansion strategy, while promising broader solutions, introduces integration complexities and execution risks that warrant scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Suyog Telematics Q3 Profit Dips Amidst Revenue Growth &amp; Key Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Suyog-Telematics-Q3-Profit-Dips-Amidst-Revenue-Growth-and-Key-Acquisition/698488f9bf48f011a29cbb32</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Suyog-Telematics-Q3-Profit-Dips-Amidst-Revenue-Growth-and-Key-Acquisition/698488f9bf48f011a29cbb32</guid><description>Suyog Telematics Limited reported a 14.5% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹559 Mn for Q3 FY26, with EBITDA up 15.9% to ₹395 Mn and margins improving. However, Net Profit declined 14.8% YoY to ₹146 Mn, impacting EPS to ₹12.57, down 20.9%. This was attributed to higher employee costs and depreciation. The company highlighted the successful acquisition of Lotus Tele Infra for ₹13.5 Cr, now holding a 95% stake, enhancing its national footprint in the Delhi &amp; NCR region. The outlook remains positive, focusing on India's telecom capex upswing and 5G expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:11:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698488f9bf48f011a29cbb31_1770295969651.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aavas Financiers Posts Strong Q3 Growth, Margins Expand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aavas-Financiers-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Margins-Expand/698488d8bf48f011a29cba24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aavas-Financiers-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Margins-Expand/698488d8bf48f011a29cba24</guid><description>Aavas Financiers Limited has announced strong unaudited financial results for Q3 FY26. The company reported a 16% year-on-year growth in Net Profit to Rs 1,700 million (Rs 1.70 bn), fueled by a 17% YoY increase in Net Interest Income (NII). Key profitability metrics improved, with Net Interest Margins (NIM) rising 27 basis points YoY to 8.01% and borrowing costs declining. Operational efficiency saw sequential gains, and asset quality remained strong with improving DPD and GNPA figures. The company also surpassed Rs 20,000 crore in balance sheet size and successfully raised Rs 975 crore via NCDs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:11:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698488d8bf48f011a29cba23_1770295765633.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors PV: JLR Woes, Margin Squeeze Dominate Q3 Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-PV-JLR-Woes-Margin-Squeeze-Dominate-Q3-Loss/698488b0bf48f011a29cb922</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-PV-JLR-Woes-Margin-Squeeze-Dominate-Q3-Loss/698488b0bf48f011a29cb922</guid><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd. (TMPVL) posted a ₹3,486 crore net loss for Q3 FY26, a stark reversal from prior year profits, primarily due to operational disruptions at Jaguar Land Rover (JLR) following a cyber incident. Revenue growth of 25% to ₹15,268 crore missed analyst forecasts, and EBITDA margins narrowed significantly to 4.5%, signaling persistent profitability challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:10:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698488b0bf48f011a29cb921_1770295821348.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>QSR Recovery Signals Emerge; Elara Capital Names Top Stocks to Watch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/QSR-Recovery-Signals-Emerge-Elara-Capital-Names-Top-Stocks-to-Watch/6984882ebf48f011a29cb798</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/QSR-Recovery-Signals-Emerge-Elara-Capital-Names-Top-Stocks-to-Watch/6984882ebf48f011a29cb798</guid><description>The Indian quick service restaurant (QSR) sector is displaying early recovery indicators, boosted by improving same-store sales growth and lower input costs. However, sustained expansion hinges on reviving dine-in demand and maintaining delivery strength. Elara Capital's Karan Taurani notes that companies with higher delivery revenue shares are better positioned, while merger benefits for Devyani International and Sapphire Foods are expected to drive cost synergies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:08:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984882ebf48f011a29cb797_1770295628863.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Office Market Surges on GCC Demand; REIT Potential Unmet</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Office-Market-Surges-on-GCC-Demand-REIT-Potential-Unmet/698487d0bf48f011a29cb615</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Office-Market-Surges-on-GCC-Demand-REIT-Potential-Unmet/698487d0bf48f011a29cb615</guid><description>India's commercial real estate sector achieved record office leasing in 2025, propelled by Global Capability Centres (GCCs) which now drive over 40% of demand. Despite this booming occupier market and evolving GCC roles, the nation's Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT) segment remains significantly under-penetrated compared to global benchmarks, signaling a potential capital market disconnect. This structural growth is supported by favorable policies and India's macro resilience, with GCCs increasingly becoming strategic value-creation hubs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:06:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698487d0bf48f011a29cb614_1770295515408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unichem Labs' Profit Soars on One-Offs Amidst Steep Margin Erosion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Unichem-Labs-Profit-Soars-on-One-Offs-Amidst-Steep-Margin-Erosion/69848788bf48f011a29cb498</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Unichem-Labs-Profit-Soars-on-One-Offs-Amidst-Steep-Margin-Erosion/69848788bf48f011a29cb498</guid><description>Unichem Laboratories posted a net profit of ₹264.3 crore for Q3 FY26, heavily influenced by an exceptional item of ₹2.75 billion, likely related to the European Commission fine. This contrasts sharply with a 47.4% drop in EBITDA to ₹45 crore and a 2.2% revenue decline to ₹521.2 crore, compressing EBITDA margins to 8.6%. The board also approved the appointment of Dr. Swati Patankar as a Non-Executive Independent Director, adding governance oversight.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:05:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69848788bf48f011a29cb497_1770295312933.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors Slumps on JLR Cyber Chaos, But Domestic PV Shines</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Slumps-on-JLR-Cyber-Chaos-But-Domestic-PV-Shines/69848746bf48f011a29cb38b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Slumps-on-JLR-Cyber-Chaos-But-Domestic-PV-Shines/69848746bf48f011a29cb38b</guid><description>Tata Motors posted a significant consolidated revenue drop of 25.8% YoY to ₹70,108 Cr in Q3 FY26, driven by a severe cyber incident at Jaguar Land Rover (JLR). JLR reported a £(1.5)bn free cash flow outflow and a £(310)m loss. However, the domestic Tata Passenger Vehicles (PV) business demonstrated resilience, with revenue growing 24.0% YoY to ₹15,317 Cr and achieving record wholesale volumes. The EV segment also saw robust 50% volume growth. Management reaffirms FY26 guidance amidst plans to recover sharply in Q4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69848746bf48f011a29cb38a_1770295311658.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-GCC FTA Talks Revive: Trade Deficit Lingers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GCC-FTA-Talks-Revive-Trade-Deficit-Lingers/69848702bf48f011a29cb1fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GCC-FTA-Talks-Revive-Trade-Deficit-Lingers/69848702bf48f011a29cb1fa</guid><description>India and the six-nation Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) have formally revived negotiations for a Free Trade Agreement (FTA), a move stalled since 2011. Despite substantial existing trade volume, India faces a persistent trade deficit, importing significantly more goods than it exports to the bloc. The revived talks aim to unlock new investment, boost exports in sectors like food processing and IT, and secure energy supply chains, while the GCC seeks diversification and access to India's consumer market. The success hinges on navigating complex trade-offs and addressing the existing imbalance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:03:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69848702bf48f011a29cb1f9_1770295094730.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yatharth Hospital Surges 46% in Q3 on New Units, Acquires Agra Facility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Yatharth-Hospital-Surges-46percent-in-Q3-on-New-Units-Acquires-Agra-Facility/698486c0bf48f011a29cb021</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Yatharth-Hospital-Surges-46percent-in-Q3-on-New-Units-Acquires-Agra-Facility/698486c0bf48f011a29cb021</guid><description>Yatharth Hospital &amp; Trauma Care Services Limited delivered a robust Q3 FY26 performance, with revenues surging 46% year-on-year to Rs 3,205 million. Profit After Tax (PAT) also climbed 41% YoY to Rs 431 million. The growth was propelled by the successful ramp-up of new facilities in Delhi and Faridabad, and the company has strengthened its expansion pipeline with the acquisition of a 250-bed hospital in Agra.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:02:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698486c0bf48f011a29cb020_1770294936689.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Varroc Engineering posts 10% revenue jump, EV sales surge, PAT hit by one-offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Varroc-Engineering-posts-10percent-revenue-jump-EV-sales-surge-PAT-hit-by-one-offs/698486a8bf48f011a29caee8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Varroc-Engineering-posts-10percent-revenue-jump-EV-sales-surge-PAT-hit-by-one-offs/698486a8bf48f011a29caee8</guid><description>Varroc Engineering reported a robust 10.2% YoY revenue growth to Rs. 22,875 million in Q3 FY26, fueled by strong Indian operations and a 53% surge in EV model sales. The company secured record net new order wins worth Rs. 20,636 million, predominantly for EVs. Despite pre-exceptional item profitability improvements, Q3 PAT stood at Rs. -113 million due to Rs. 1,049 million in exceptional costs, including VRS expenses. Net debt rose to Rs. 4,405 million.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:01:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698486a8bf48f011a29caee7_1770294926156.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharti Hexacom Profit Soars 81% on Tax Credit, Revenue Grows Modestly</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Hexacom-Profit-Soars-81percent-on-Tax-Credit-Revenue-Grows-Modestly/69848692bf48f011a29cae35</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Hexacom-Profit-Soars-81percent-on-Tax-Credit-Revenue-Grows-Modestly/69848692bf48f011a29cae35</guid><description>Bharti Hexacom reported a robust 81.56% YoY profit increase to ₹4,737 million in Q3 FY26, significantly boosted by a ₹487 million exceptional tax credit from a favourable tribunal judgment. Revenue grew 4.87% YoY to ₹23,598 million. For the nine months, profit rose 25.50% to ₹12,865 million on 10.88% revenue growth, with finance costs also declining.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:01:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69848692bf48f011a29cae34_1770294716885.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharti Hexacom Profit Soars 81% on Tax Credit, Revenue Grows Modestly</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Hexacom-Profit-Soars-81percent-on-Tax-Credit-Revenue-Grows-Modestly/6984857cbf48f011a29cabab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Hexacom-Profit-Soars-81percent-on-Tax-Credit-Revenue-Grows-Modestly/6984857cbf48f011a29cabab</guid><description>Bharti Hexacom reported a robust 81.56% YoY profit increase to ₹4,737 million in Q3 FY26, significantly boosted by a ₹487 million exceptional tax credit from a favourable tribunal judgment. Revenue grew 4.87% YoY to ₹23,598 million. For the nine months, profit rose 25.50% to ₹12,865 million on 10.88% revenue growth, with finance costs also declining.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:56:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984857cbf48f011a29cabaa_1770294770180.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nykaa Q3 Sees 27% Revenue Growth, 156% Profit Jump; Partners Nike India.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Nykaa-Q3-Sees-27percent-Revenue-Growth-156percent-Profit-Jump-Partners-Nike-India/6984855cbf48f011a29caaab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Nykaa-Q3-Sees-27percent-Revenue-Growth-156percent-Profit-Jump-Partners-Nike-India/6984855cbf48f011a29caaab</guid><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) reported a robust Q3 FY26, with revenues climbing 27% YoY to ₹2,873 Cr and PAT surging 156% to ₹68 Cr. EBITDA grew 63% YoY to ₹230 Cr, with margins improving significantly. The company also announced a major strategic partnership to operate Nike.in in India, signaling aggressive expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:56:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984855cbf48f011a29caaaa_1770294511631.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharti Airtel Posts Stellar Q3 FY26: Revenue Surges 19.6%, Debt Falls</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtel-Posts-Stellar-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Surges-196percent-Debt-Falls/69848490bf48f011a29ca85c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtel-Posts-Stellar-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Surges-196percent-Debt-Falls/69848490bf48f011a29ca85c</guid><description>Bharti Airtel delivered a robust Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenues leaping 19.6% YoY to ₹53,982 crore and EBITDA climbing 25.2% to ₹31,144 crore. Margins strengthened across segments. The company significantly deleveraged, with Net Debt to EBITDA falling to 1.47x. Strategic partnerships, including an AI hub with Google and a cybersecurity deal with Indian Railways, signal future growth avenues.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>