<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:03:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Rupee Edges Higher, Corporate Demand Caps Rise on Tuesday</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Edges-Higher-Corporate-Demand-Caps-Rise-on-Tuesday/698b5427757d40c781871aff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Edges-Higher-Corporate-Demand-Caps-Rise-on-Tuesday/698b5427757d40c781871aff</guid><description>The Indian rupee strengthened on Tuesday, following Asian currency trends. However, significant dollar demand from large corporations limited its advance, with the local unit closing at 90.58 against the dollar. The dollar index's dip below 97 provided some support to the rupee. Analysts point to the 90.00-90.20 zone as key support.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:52:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b5427757d40c781871afe_1770738864245.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titan's Jewellery Power Fuels Q3 Profit; Watch Segment Faces Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titans-Jewellery-Power-Fuels-Q3-Profit-Watch-Segment-Faces-Challenges/698b52c2757d40c781871949</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titans-Jewellery-Power-Fuels-Q3-Profit-Watch-Segment-Faces-Challenges/698b52c2757d40c781871949</guid><description>Titan Company announced a robust Q3FY26 with net profit jumping 61% to ₹1,684 crore and revenue climbing 43% to ₹25,416 crore. The stellar performance was primarily fueled by its jewellery division, which saw a 42% revenue increase, driven by strong festive demand and effective campaigns despite elevated gold prices. While the watches and eyewear segments posted growth, a notable 27% year-on-year volume decline in smartwatches indicates segment-specific headwinds. The company's P/E ratio stands significantly above industry averages, signaling investor confidence in its premium positioning and continued growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:46:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b52c2757d40c781871948.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Cyber Threat Escalation Hits MNCs, Investment Risks Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Cyber-Threat-Escalation-Hits-MNCs-Investment-Risks-Rise/698b524f757d40c7818717df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Cyber-Threat-Escalation-Hits-MNCs-Investment-Risks-Rise/698b524f757d40c7818717df</guid><description>Union Home Minister Amit Shah's stark warning about India's data being pilfered highlights a growing cybersecurity crisis impacting the nation's digital ambitions. With cybercrime cases and financial losses surging, multinational corporations operating within India face heightened operational risks and increased compliance burdens. The escalating threat landscape, coupled with the expansive digital economy, could pose a drag on foreign investment, necessitating a decisive shift towards robust enforcement over awareness campaigns.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:44:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b524f757d40c7818717de_1770738317536.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata AutoComp Expands with Future-Ready EV Plants in Gujarat</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-AutoComp-Expands-with-Future-Ready-EV-Plants-in-Gujarat/698b51da757d40c781871690</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-AutoComp-Expands-with-Future-Ready-EV-Plants-in-Gujarat/698b51da757d40c781871690</guid><description>Tata AutoComp Systems has inaugurated two advanced manufacturing facilities in Sanand, Gujarat, on January 30, 2026. These plants, for TM Automotive Seating Systems and TACO Air International Thermal Systems, are designed to bolster support for Original Equipment Manufacturers (OEMs) and align with the evolving requirements of next-generation mobility platforms, particularly in the electric vehicle sector. This expansion underscores a strategic commitment to sustainability and advanced automotive component solutions, reinforcing Tata AutoComp's position as a key supplier within India's rapidly growing automotive ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:42:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b51da757d40c78187168f_1770738724809.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Forces CRA Operational Splits: Investor Clarity or Costly Complexity?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SEBI-Forces-CRA-Operational-Splits-Investor-Clarity-or-Costly-Complexity/698b50e3757d40c7818714e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SEBI-Forces-CRA-Operational-Splits-Investor-Clarity-or-Costly-Complexity/698b50e3757d40c7818714e2</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has imposed stringent new regulations on credit rating agencies (CRAs) that rate financial instruments falling under the purview of other regulators. Effective 60 days from February 10, 2026, CRAs must implement segregated digital footprints, maintain unimpaired net worth, and provide explicit client disclosures regarding the absence of SEBI's investor protection mechanisms for such ratings. A 12-month grace period is allocated for changes to grievance handling and client notification processes. This move aims to enhance investor awareness and protect market integrity by clearly delineating regulatory oversight.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:38:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b50e3757d40c7818714e1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hitech Corp Posts Q3 Loss, Profit Slides 80% for 9 Months</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitech-Corp-Posts-Q3-Loss-Profit-Slides-80percent-for-9-Months/698b5068757d40c781871372</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitech-Corp-Posts-Q3-Loss-Profit-Slides-80percent-for-9-Months/698b5068757d40c781871372</guid><description>Hitech Corporation reported a sharp downturn in profitability for Q3 FY26, swinging to a net loss on both standalone and consolidated bases despite revenue growth. Standalone revenue rose 6.9% YoY to ₹131.54 Cr, but net profit plunged to a ₹3.27 Cr loss from a ₹1.43 Cr profit last year. For the nine-month period, standalone PAT fell 80.4% to ₹1.65 Cr. The company also announced the retirement of its CFO.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Auditor Flags Massive ₹483M Unrecognised Loss at Advance Lifestyles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Auditor-Flags-Massive-483M-Unrecognised-Loss-at-Advance-Lifestyles/698b500c757d40c78187119f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Auditor-Flags-Massive-483M-Unrecognised-Loss-at-Advance-Lifestyles/698b500c757d40c78187119f</guid><description>Advance Lifestyles Limited reported a substantial 51.94% YoY revenue jump to ₹10.3 million for Q3 FY26. However, the company faces a severe accounting challenge as its auditor issued a qualified opinion, highlighting the failure to recognise an impairment loss of ₹483.76 crore on an inter-corporate advance. This massive unrecognised loss overshadows revenue growth, raises critical questions about financial reporting integrity, and signals potential future write-offs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:34:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b500c757d40c78187119e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Allcargo Terminals Q3 PAT Jumps 27.6%, But 9-Month Standalone Profit Dips 40%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Allcargo-Terminals-Q3-PAT-Jumps-276percent-But-9-Month-Standalone-Profit-Dips-40percent/698b4ff2757d40c7818710f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Allcargo-Terminals-Q3-PAT-Jumps-276percent-But-9-Month-Standalone-Profit-Dips-40percent/698b4ff2757d40c7818710f2</guid><description>Allcargo Terminals reported a robust 27.6% year-on-year rise in consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹15.03 crore for Q3 FY26. Standalone PAT also climbed 30.2% YoY. However, the nine-month period ended December 31, 2025, saw a significant 40.1% year-on-year decline in standalone PAT to ₹24.94 crore, despite an 8.6% consolidated PAT increase. The company also disclosed an ongoing Income Tax search and approved a ₹100 crore corporate guarantee for its subsidiary.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HEG PAT Soars 43% YoY To ₹206 Cr, But Exceptional Losses Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HEG-PAT-Soars-43percent-YoY-To-206-Cr-But-Exceptional-Losses-Surge/698b4fb4757d40c781870f7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HEG-PAT-Soars-43percent-YoY-To-206-Cr-But-Exceptional-Losses-Surge/698b4fb4757d40c781870f7b</guid><description>HEG Limited reported a robust 43.26% year-on-year (YoY) surge in consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹205.97 crore for Q3 FY26, driven by a 36.99% YoY increase in revenue to ₹655.33 crore. Standalone PAT also grew 43.67% YoY. However, consolidated results were significantly impacted by a sharp rise in exceptional item losses, increasing from ₹7.26 crore to ₹55.14 crore, leading to a decline in consolidated profit before tax. Standalone EPS for the quarter also saw a YoY decrease. The company also approved a ₹400 crore investment in subsidiary TACC Limited and a corporate guarantee for its credit facilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gandhi Special Tubes Posts Strong Q3 Results, Revenue Up 21.8% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gandhi-Special-Tubes-Posts-Strong-Q3-Results-Revenue-Up-218percent-YoY/698b4f98757d40c781870e5e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gandhi-Special-Tubes-Posts-Strong-Q3-Results-Revenue-Up-218percent-YoY/698b4f98757d40c781870e5e</guid><description>Gandhi Special Tubes reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue climbing 21.82% YoY to ₹48.44 Cr and PAT surging 29.94% to ₹19.70 Cr. For the nine months, revenue grew 33.92% and PAT increased 26.27%. The company recognized an exceptional item of ₹1.18 Cr related to new labor codes, impacting pre-tax profit.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Allcargo Terminals Q3 Profit Jumps, YTD Standalone Dips Amid Tax Scan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Allcargo-Terminals-Q3-Profit-Jumps-YTD-Standalone-Dips-Amid-Tax-Scan/698b4f7a757d40c781870d7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Allcargo-Terminals-Q3-Profit-Jumps-YTD-Standalone-Dips-Amid-Tax-Scan/698b4f7a757d40c781870d7b</guid><description>Allcargo Terminals reported a robust 30.18% year-on-year rise in standalone net profit to ₹13.07 Crore for Q3 FY26, with consolidated profit up 10.61% to ₹13.03 Crore. Standalone revenue also grew 17.07% YoY to ₹147.16 Crore. However, the nine-month standalone profit declined 40.08% YoY to ₹24.94 Crore. The company is cooperating with Income Tax searches and contesting GST demand notices, for which an interim stay is in place for the holding company. The Board also approved enhancing a corporate guarantee by ₹100 Crore for Speedy Multimodes Limited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Advance Lifestyles Auditor Flags ₹48 Cr Loss; Profit, EPS Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Advance-Lifestyles-Auditor-Flags-48-Cr-Loss-Profit-EPS-Plunge/698b4f03757d40c781870c2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Advance-Lifestyles-Auditor-Flags-48-Cr-Loss-Profit-EPS-Plunge/698b4f03757d40c781870c2c</guid><description>Advance Lifestyles reported a significant 51.9% YoY revenue growth to ₹1032.57 Cr in Q3 FY26, with PAT up 29.5% to ₹169.32 Cr. However, EPS saw a steep fall from ₹2.30 to ₹0.27. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, revenue grew 39.5% to ₹2789.48 Cr, but PAT plummeted 63.6% to ₹422.88 Cr and EPS dropped to ₹0.68. Margins compressed drastically to 15.2% from 58.1%. Critically, the auditor's qualified conclusion over non-recognition of a ₹48.37 Cr impairment loss, citing potential Ind AS 109 violation, casts a significant shadow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Calcom Vision Q3 Revenue Jumps 23%, Yet Profit Turns To Loss Amidst Higher Expenses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Calcom-Vision-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-23percent-Yet-Profit-Turns-To-Loss-Amidst-Higher-Expenses/698b4ebb757d40c781870abf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Calcom-Vision-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-23percent-Yet-Profit-Turns-To-Loss-Amidst-Higher-Expenses/698b4ebb757d40c781870abf</guid><description>Calcom Vision Limited saw its Q3 FY26 revenue climb 23.4% YoY to ₹5,513.21 Lakhs. However, the company posted a net loss of ₹85.09 Lakhs, reversing a profit of ₹30.85 Lakhs in the prior year quarter. This quarterly dip, despite strong revenue, was attributed to significant increases in total expenses and exceptional items. Conversely, the nine-month period ending December 31, 2025, showed robust growth, with revenue up 54.9% to ₹15,027.27 Lakhs and net profit after tax surging 697% to ₹194.11 Lakhs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:28:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b4ebb757d40c781870abe.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anupam Finserv Q3 Profit Surges 790% on Margin Expansion, Bank Account Unfrozen</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Anupam-Finserv-Q3-Profit-Surges-790percent-on-Margin-Expansion-Bank-Account-Unfrozen/698b4e88757d40c7818709a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Anupam-Finserv-Q3-Profit-Surges-790percent-on-Margin-Expansion-Bank-Account-Unfrozen/698b4e88757d40c7818709a8</guid><description>Anupam Finserv reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with Profit Before Tax (PBT) soaring 790% year-on-year to ₹539.25 Crore. This surge drove PBT margins to an impressive 43.1% from approximately 6.3% quarter-on-quarter. However, for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, total income declined 38% YoY to ₹1776.95 Crore, though PBT still grew 84% to ₹1193.33 Crore with margins at a strong 67.1% YoY. The company also saw a significant bank account, frozen since 2021, unfrozen with ₹28.20 Crore.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Roto Pumps Q3 PAT Surges 77%, But 9-Month Revenue Dips; Amalgamation Approved</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Roto-Pumps-Q3-PAT-Surges-77percent-But-9-Month-Revenue-Dips-Amalgamation-Approved/698b4dfb757d40c7818707c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Roto-Pumps-Q3-PAT-Surges-77percent-But-9-Month-Revenue-Dips-Amalgamation-Approved/698b4dfb757d40c7818707c8</guid><description>Roto Pumps reported a strong third quarter for FY26, with standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 77.0% YoY to ₹632.70 Lakhs, and consolidated PAT rising 69.07% to ₹677.56 Lakhs. However, the cumulative nine-month period showed a revenue decline of 8.28% (standalone) and 5.38% (consolidated), with PAT also falling YoY. The company also approved the amalgamation of its wholly-owned subsidiary, Roto Energy Systems Limited, to streamline operations and reduce costs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Primary Ventures Drops $625M Fund V, Redefining Seed Stage</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Primary-Ventures-Drops-625M-Fund-V-Redefining-Seed-Stage/698b4dec757d40c78187071b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Primary-Ventures-Drops-625M-Fund-V-Redefining-Seed-Stage/698b4dec757d40c78187071b</guid><description>Primary Ventures has launched Fund V with $625 million, signaling a dramatic increase in seed-stage investment capital. This substantial fund aims for average checks of $5-$10 million across 40-50 companies nationwide. The move reflects a trend of escalating early-stage valuations, particularly within the AI sector, and intensifies competition among VCs seeking top-tier opportunities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:25:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b4dec757d40c78187071a_1770737197612.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eldeco Housing Q3 Profit Surges 137% On Margin Boost &amp; ₹55 Cr Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Eldeco-Housing-Q3-Profit-Surges-137percent-On-Margin-Boost-and-55-Cr-Recovery/698b4d93757d40c781870468</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Eldeco-Housing-Q3-Profit-Surges-137percent-On-Margin-Boost-and-55-Cr-Recovery/698b4d93757d40c781870468</guid><description>Eldeco Housing &amp; Industries reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with net profit soaring 137.0% YoY to ₹13.7 crore, driven by a significant EBITDA margin expansion to 43.7% and a ₹55 crore recovery from the Bareilly project. Nine-month operational metrics also showed strong growth in bookings and collections, though specific forward guidance was absent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:24:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b4d93757d40c781870467.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Archean Chemical Signs Gujarat MOU for Mega Salt Jetty Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Archean-Chemical-Signs-Gujarat-MOU-for-Mega-Salt-Jetty-Project/698b4d5d757d40c7818702f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Archean-Chemical-Signs-Gujarat-MOU-for-Mega-Salt-Jetty-Project/698b4d5d757d40c7818702f9</guid><description>Archean Chemical Industries has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) with the Government of Gujarat to develop a substantial captive salt jetty. The proposed facility will boast a significant throughput capacity of 7 million metric tonnes per annum (MMTPA), enhancing the company's salt logistics infrastructure along Gujarat's coastline. The state government will facilitate the acquisition of all necessary permits and approvals for this strategic development.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dixon's February Surge: Betting on PLI Over Q3 Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixons-February-Surge-Betting-on-PLI-Over-Q3-Woes/698b4d2a757d40c781870208</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixons-February-Surge-Betting-on-PLI-Over-Q3-Woes/698b4d2a757d40c781870208</guid><description>Dixon Technologies shares have climbed 13% since February 1st, defying a challenging December quarter marked by 2% sales growth and a 10% drop in consumer electronics. Mobile phone segment growth hit a 16-quarter low, leading to reduced FY26 smartphone volume guidance. While some reports indicated muted profit, later disclosures showed substantial net profit increases. Analysts are split, with some upgrading on the back of Production Linked Incentive (PLI) benefits and non-mobile segment strength, while others express caution due to JV delays and input cost pressures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kinetic Engineering Unit Secures ₹42 Cr Maharashtra EV Subsidy Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Kinetic-Engineering-Unit-Secures-42-Cr-Maharashtra-EV-Subsidy-Boost/698b4cae757d40c781870092</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Kinetic-Engineering-Unit-Secures-42-Cr-Maharashtra-EV-Subsidy-Boost/698b4cae757d40c781870092</guid><description>Kinetic Watts &amp; Volts, a subsidiary of Kinetic Engineering Limited, secured approval for ₹42 crore in Maharashtra EV policy incentives. This 10-year benefit supports domestic manufacturing, particularly for the localized Kinetic DX EV. Funds will scale production, enhance technical capabilities including robotics and battery assembly, and strengthen the supply chain, aiming to accelerate EV rollout and reduce import dependency.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Unemployment Rate Dips; Job Growth Sees Uptick</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Unemployment-Rate-Dips-Job-Growth-Sees-Uptick/698b4c5b757d40c78186fee1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Unemployment-Rate-Dips-Job-Growth-Sees-Uptick/698b4c5b757d40c78186fee1</guid><description>India's job market showed signs of improvement in the October-December 2025 quarter. The unemployment rate for individuals aged 15 and above declined to 6.7% in urban areas and 4% in rural areas. Total employment saw an increase, with 57.4 crore people employed, up from 56.2 crore in the previous quarter. The Labour Force Participation Rate also edged up, particularly for women.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:18:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b4c5b757d40c78186fee0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NIIF Plans Ather Energy Stake Sale Amid Strong Q3 Turnaround</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/NIIF-Plans-Ather-Energy-Stake-Sale-Amid-Strong-Q3-Turnaround/698b4c36757d40c78186fdfd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/NIIF-Plans-Ather-Energy-Stake-Sale-Amid-Strong-Q3-Turnaround/698b4c36757d40c78186fdfd</guid><description>National Investment and Infrastructure Fund (NIIF) is reportedly preparing to divest up to 1.92% of its stake in Ather Energy Ltd. through a block deal, potentially raising approximately ₹533.5 crore. This move by a key investor comes as Ather Energy posted a narrower net loss of ₹83.6 crore for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025, a significant improvement from ₹197.6 crore a year prior. Revenue surged 50% year-on-year to ₹953.6 crore, driven by robust sales volumes and increased non-vehicle revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:18:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AFCOM Holdings Soars 208% Revenue, Eyes Aircraft MRO Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AFCOM-Holdings-Soars-208percent-Revenue-Eyes-Aircraft-MRO-Expansion/698b4bb8757d40c78186fd22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AFCOM-Holdings-Soars-208percent-Revenue-Eyes-Aircraft-MRO-Expansion/698b4bb8757d40c78186fd22</guid><description>AFCOM Holdings reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with revenue surging 207.84% YoY to ₹15,258.39 lakhs and PAT soaring 325.57% to ₹3,847.14 lakhs. The company's board approved establishing a greenfield aircraft Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul (MRO) subsidiary and raised significant capital through preference shares and warrants. AFCOM also successfully transitioned to the BSE main board.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pace Digitek Secures ₹1,775 Cr Solar Project with Battery Storage</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Pace-Digitek-Secures-1775-Cr-Solar-Project-with-Battery-Storage/698b4b7a757d40c78186fbbc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Pace-Digitek-Secures-1775-Cr-Solar-Project-with-Battery-Storage/698b4b7a757d40c78186fbbc</guid><description>Pace Digitek Limited has secured a significant award from Karnataka Renewable Energy Development Limited (KREDL) for a 250 MWAC Solar PV Project, complemented by a 250 MW/1100 MWh Battery Energy Storage System (BESS). The project, located in Pavagada Solar Park, is estimated at ₹1,775 Crore and will operate for 25 years under a tariff of ₹5.51 per unit. This development marks a substantial expansion for the company in India's renewable energy sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Creative Eye Delays Financial Results, Faces Trading Window Breach</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Creative-Eye-Delays-Financial-Results-Faces-Trading-Window-Breach/698b4b6a757d40c78186faef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Creative-Eye-Delays-Financial-Results-Faces-Trading-Window-Breach/698b4b6a757d40c78186faef</guid><description>Creative Eye Limited has announced a delay in approving its unaudited financial results for Q2 and Q3 FY26. Citing "exceptional and unavoidable circumstances," the company postponed its board meeting. Alarmingly, the company also failed to comply with mandatory trading window closure norms for its directors and designated persons for these quarters, raising significant governance and disclosure concerns. No financial figures or outlook were provided.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:14:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b4b6a757d40c78186faee.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NPPA Forces Drug Price Cuts Post-Budget Duty Exemptions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/NPPA-Forces-Drug-Price-Cuts-Post-Budget-Duty-Exemptions/698b4b4a757d40c78186f9d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/NPPA-Forces-Drug-Price-Cuts-Post-Budget-Duty-Exemptions/698b4b4a757d40c78186f9d2</guid><description>The National Pharmaceuticals Pricing Authority (NPPA) has directed pharmaceutical firms to slash the Maximum Retail Price (MRP) of 17 cancer and life-saving drugs, citing customs duty exemptions from Budget 2026-27. This directive, rooted in the Drugs (Prices Control) Order, 2013, mandates that duty benefits be passed to consumers. While aiming for affordability, the move introduces compliance challenges and potential margin pressures, mirroring historical regulatory interventions that have influenced sector profitability and market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India EV Push: From Policy to Execution Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-EV-Push-From-Policy-to-Execution-Challenges/698b4ae6757d40c78186f7d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-EV-Push-From-Policy-to-Execution-Challenges/698b4ae6757d40c78186f7d5</guid><description>India's electric mobility strategy is moving into a large-scale execution phase, prioritizing industrial strategy, climate commitments, and economic growth. Union Minister H.D. Kumaraswamy highlighted the shift from policy signaling to practical implementation, focusing on strengthening the EV value chain, from vehicle manufacturing to charging infrastructure. Commercial vehicles and public transport are identified as critical segments for electrification due to their impact on urban pollution. This transition, however, faces significant challenges in scaling, supply chain development, financing, and ensuring widespread adoption across diverse vehicle types.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Brokers Navigate STT Hike: Diversification Proves Resilience</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Brokers-Navigate-STT-Hike-Diversification-Proves-Resilience/698b4ad1757d40c78186f753</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Brokers-Navigate-STT-Hike-Diversification-Proves-Resilience/698b4ad1757d40c78186f753</guid><description>Indian broking firms are confronting a challenging environment driven by a proposed hike in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) and ongoing regulatory interventions. A Crisil analysis reveals that entities with diversified revenue streams, including wealth management and distribution fees, are better positioned to absorb market fluctuations. Conversely, firms heavily reliant on transaction broking fees and proprietary trading are experiencing significant revenue contractions as trading volumes decline.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DII Surge Fuels India Market; Textile Sector Faces Trade Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/DII-Surge-Fuels-India-Market-Textile-Sector-Faces-Trade-Headwinds/698b4a5b757d40c78186f63b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/DII-Surge-Fuels-India-Market-Textile-Sector-Faces-Trade-Headwinds/698b4a5b757d40c78186f63b</guid><description>Indian equities advanced for a third straight session, with benchmark indices buoyed by strong performances in metal and auto sectors. Domestic institutional investors (DIIs) have solidified their dominant position, now holding more Nifty50 equity than foreign counterparts. This structural shift is underpinned by consistent inflows from retail investors. However, the textile sector faces emerging headwinds from a new US-Bangladesh trade agreement, contrasting with broader market optimism. Investors are now awaiting key US employment data for further directional cues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sterling Holidays Posts Record Q3 FY26 Revenue, EBITDA, and PBT</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sterling-Holidays-Posts-Record-Q3-FY26-Revenue-EBITDA-and-PBT/698b490f757d40c78186f460</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sterling-Holidays-Posts-Record-Q3-FY26-Revenue-EBITDA-and-PBT/698b490f757d40c78186f460</guid><description>Sterling Holiday Resorts Limited reported a record-breaking third quarter for FY26, achieving its highest-ever quarterly Revenue, EBITDA, and Profit Before Tax. The company posted ₹1,582 million in revenue, a 10% year-on-year increase, and maintained a strong 36% EBITDA margin. Sterling remains debt-free with a 54% year-on-year surge in cash reserves. Management expressed confidence in continued momentum driven by network expansion and digital initiatives.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:04:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b490f757d40c78186f45f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Popular Vehicles Q3 PAT Turns Positive as Revenue Surges 31% on Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Popular-Vehicles-Q3-PAT-Turns-Positive-as-Revenue-Surges-31percent-on-Demand/698b48fa757d40c78186f34d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Popular-Vehicles-Q3-PAT-Turns-Positive-as-Revenue-Surges-31percent-on-Demand/698b48fa757d40c78186f34d</guid><description>Popular Vehicles and Services Ltd reported a robust Q3 FY26, with revenue jumping 30.9% YoY to ₹1,791.8 Cr and EBITDA rising 68.5% to ₹58.2 Cr. Profit After Tax (PAT) turned positive at ₹0.7 Cr, a significant rebound from a ₹-9.8 Cr loss last year. This strong quarterly performance, driven by improved demand across vehicle segments, contrasts with a loss in the nine-month period. The company aims for 5% EBITDA margins, supported by strategic acquisitions and network expansion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:04:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Popular Vehicles Rebounds: Q3 Profit Turns Positive on Strong Volume Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Popular-Vehicles-Rebounds-Q3-Profit-Turns-Positive-on-Strong-Volume-Surge/698b48ec757d40c78186f296</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Popular-Vehicles-Rebounds-Q3-Profit-Turns-Positive-on-Strong-Volume-Surge/698b48ec757d40c78186f296</guid><description>Popular Vehicles and Services Ltd (PVSL) announced a significant turnaround in Q3 FY26, posting a net profit of ₹0.7 Cr against a loss last year. Total income surged 30.9% YoY to ₹1,791.8 Cr, driven by a 43.7% jump in new vehicle volumes. EBITDA improved 68.5% YoY to ₹58.2 Cr with margins expanding to 3.3%. The company also bolstered its strategic footprint with the acquisition of Audi dealerships and a new distributorship agreement, anticipating further growth despite near-term cost pressures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:04:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b48ec757d40c78186f295.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KFIL Navigates Low Prices, Boosts Margins on Cost Cuts; Awaits Tube Order Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KFIL-Navigates-Low-Prices-Boosts-Margins-on-Cost-Cuts-Awaits-Tube-Order-Boost/698b4872757d40c78186f19f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KFIL-Navigates-Low-Prices-Boosts-Margins-on-Cost-Cuts-Awaits-Tube-Order-Boost/698b4872757d40c78186f19f</guid><description>Kirloskar Ferrous Industries Limited (KFIL) reported a challenging third quarter for FY26, with revenues declining YoY and QoQ due to five-year lows in pig iron and steel realisations. Despite this, strategic cost optimization measures, including enhanced coal injection and solar power commissioning, led to improved EBITDA margins to 11.5% on both standalone and consolidated levels. The company successfully completed maintenance shutdowns and looks ahead to executing a substantial tubes order, which is expected to improve order book visibility.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Amrapali Fincap Board to Consider Merger/Restructuring on Feb 13</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Amrapali-Fincap-Board-to-Consider-MergerRestructuring-on-Feb-13/698b480c757d40c78186f04d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Amrapali-Fincap-Board-to-Consider-MergerRestructuring-on-Feb-13/698b480c757d40c78186f04d</guid><description>Amrapali Fincap Limited has announced a crucial Board Meeting scheduled for Friday, February 13, 2026. The primary agenda is to deliberate and approve a potential Scheme of Arrangement, including amalgamation, merger, or reconstruction. In line with its Insider Trading Code, the company has enforced a trading window closure for designated persons from February 10, 2026, until 48 hours post-announcement, signalling significant corporate restructuring activities ahead.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GHV Infra Wins Rs 135 Crore Haryana Water Project Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GHV-Infra-Wins-Rs-135-Crore-Haryana-Water-Project-Order/698b47f7757d40c78186ef63</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GHV-Infra-Wins-Rs-135-Crore-Haryana-Water-Project-Order/698b47f7757d40c78186ef63</guid><description>GHV Infra Projects Limited announced on February 10, 2026, a significant Rs. 135 crore work order from MHK Buildcon LLP for constructing a water storage pond and associated works in Haryana. The project is slated for completion within 22 months, marking a substantial addition to the company's business pipeline and demonstrating its infrastructure development capabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Power Equipment Wins Rs 14.86 Crore Transformer Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Supreme-Power-Equipment-Wins-Rs-1486-Crore-Transformer-Order/698b4781757d40c78186ee0d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Supreme-Power-Equipment-Wins-Rs-1486-Crore-Transformer-Order/698b4781757d40c78186ee0d</guid><description>Supreme Power Equipment Limited secured a Rs 14.86 crore contract to supply six 20MVA, 66/11KV power transformers to a Karnataka-based EPC firm. The order, to be executed over eight months, reinforces the company's presence in the regional energy infrastructure sector and follows its recent IPO listing on NSE Emerge.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:58:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b4781757d40c78186ee0c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Firms Eye Record $4.4B Foreign Debt Amid Currency Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Firms-Eye-Record-44B-Foreign-Debt-Amid-Currency-Risks/698b4739757d40c78186ec51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Firms-Eye-Record-44B-Foreign-Debt-Amid-Currency-Risks/698b4739757d40c78186ec51</guid><description>Indian companies filed for $4.43 billion in external commercial borrowings and foreign currency convertible bonds in December 2025, the highest monthly total for fiscal year 2026. This surge, driven by infrastructure and NBFC sectors, indicates strong corporate demand for capital. However, it also magnifies risks related to currency depreciation and increased financial leverage, particularly for highly indebted entities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Waterways Surge: ODC Moves to Tata's Assam Chip Plant, Signaling Logistics Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Waterways-Surge-ODC-Moves-to-Tatas-Assam-Chip-Plant-Signaling-Logistics-Shift/698b471d757d40c78186eb6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Waterways-Surge-ODC-Moves-to-Tatas-Assam-Chip-Plant-Signaling-Logistics-Shift/698b471d757d40c78186eb6e</guid><description>The Inland Waterways Authority of India (IWAI) successfully transported a 189.260 metric tonne Over Dimensional Cargo (ODC) to the upcoming Tata Semiconductor Assembly facility in Morigaon, Assam. Utilising National Waterway-2 (Brahmaputra) and the Indo-Bangladesh Protocol Route (IBPR), this movement underscores the growing strategic importance of inland waterways for large-scale industrial projects. The shipment is critical for bolstering Assam's semiconductor ecosystem, a key component of India's 'Make in India' and 'Atmanirbhar Bharat' initiatives, which aims to build domestic chip manufacturing capabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sugs Lloyd Surges: 60% Revenue Jump Fuels Ambitious FY28 Targets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sugs-Lloyd-Surges-60percent-Revenue-Jump-Fuels-Ambitious-FY28-Targets/698b470b757d40c78186eabf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sugs-Lloyd-Surges-60percent-Revenue-Jump-Fuels-Ambitious-FY28-Targets/698b470b757d40c78186eabf</guid><description>Sugs Lloyd Limited posted a robust Q3 FY26 with 60.62% YoY revenue growth to INR 185.6 crores for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported INR 17.92 crores PAT and aims for INR 1,000 crores revenue by FY28, supported by expansion into EHV transmission and increased debt facilities. A resolved land dispute deferred INR 20 crores revenue in Q3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:56:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b470b757d40c78186eabe_1770735446841.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiQube Spaces Surges on 45% Revenue Growth and Major Debt Reduction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/IndiQube-Spaces-Surges-on-45percent-Revenue-Growth-and-Major-Debt-Reduction/698b463d757d40c78186e91a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/IndiQube-Spaces-Surges-on-45percent-Revenue-Growth-and-Major-Debt-Reduction/698b463d757d40c78186e91a</guid><description>IndiQube Spaces reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue climbing 45% YoY to ₹395 Crore and Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 214% YoY to ₹40 Crore. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, revenue grew 37% to ₹1063 Crore, and PAT surged 284% to ₹95 Crore. The company significantly deleveraged, slashing its Debt-to-Equity ratio to 0.15 from 0.80 YoY. Operational expansion included adding 1.5 Million sq. ft. AUM and 21 new centers across three new cities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:52:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b463d757d40c78186e919.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>