<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:25:30 +0000</pubDate><item><title>SBFC Finance Q3 PAT Surges 34% Amidst Macro Concerns &amp; Regional Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBFC-Finance-Q3-PAT-Surges-34percent-Amidst-Macro-Concerns-and-Regional-Woes/697e449846be08bbe62f44a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBFC-Finance-Q3-PAT-Surges-34percent-Amidst-Macro-Concerns-and-Regional-Woes/697e449846be08bbe62f44a8</guid><description>SBFC Finance reported a strong Q3 FY'26 with Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 34% year-on-year to INR 118 crore, driven by a 29% rise in Assets Under Management (AUM) to INR 10,478 crore. However, management flagged concerns over hardening interest rates and rising household debt, alongside regional disbursement challenges due to bureau scores. The company also announced a leadership transition with MD &amp; CEO Aseem Dhru moving to Non-Executive Vice Chairman.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e449846be08bbe62f44a7_1769882870952.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Climate Disrupts Travel: Industry Adapts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Climate-Disrupts-Travel-Industry-Adapts/697e433046be08bbe62f43b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Climate-Disrupts-Travel-Industry-Adapts/697e433046be08bbe62f43b8</guid><description>Extreme weather events are fundamentally altering global travel, transforming weather from casual chat to critical planning. Past disruptions are compelling travelers and operators toward greater adaptability, meticulous planning, and increased emphasis on sustainable practices. The tourism sector faces mounting pressure to mitigate its environmental impact and build resilience against climate volatility, redefining the future of holidays.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:01:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e433046be08bbe62f43b7_1769882515444.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Dual Tax Drag: Budget 2026 Scrutiny Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Dual-Tax-Drag-Budget-2026-Scrutiny-Intensifies/697e40da46be08bbe62f42a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Dual-Tax-Drag-Budget-2026-Scrutiny-Intensifies/697e40da46be08bbe62f42a6</guid><description>Indian stock market participants grapple with a dual taxation system combining Securities Transaction Tax (STT) and Capital Gains Tax (CGT). Recent increases in STCG (to 20%) and LTCG (to 12.5%) rates, alongside a limited exemption threshold, are impacting investor sentiment and participation. With the Union Budget 2026 imminent, policymakers face pressure to address these tax burdens, which critics argue stifle market vibrancy and deter long-term investment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:52:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e40da46be08bbe62f42a5_1769881950380.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Looms: Tax Debate Ignites Over Capital Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Looms-Tax-Debate-Ignites-Over-Capital-Gains/697d55875fc43f26c54f2eef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Looms-Tax-Debate-Ignites-Over-Capital-Gains/697d55875fc43f26c54f2eef</guid><description>With India's annual Budget imminent, investor attention is fixated on potential tax relief, particularly concerning capital gains. Prominent investor Samir Arora, founder of Helios Capital, has ignited debate by contrasting how different investment incomes are taxed. He argues that the government's net tax collection is significantly impacted by whether transactions involve offsetting gains and losses, suggesting a fundamental difference between equity capital gains, interest income, and derivatives trading.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d55875fc43f26c54f2eee_1769880487028.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Stake Rethink: Survey Seeks 26% Floor Amid Disinvestment Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PSU-Stake-Rethink-Survey-Seeks-26percent-Floor-Amid-Disinvestment-Woes/697d58cd5fc43f26c54f30ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PSU-Stake-Rethink-Survey-Seeks-26percent-Floor-Amid-Disinvestment-Woes/697d58cd5fc43f26c54f30ce</guid><description>The Economic Survey has proposed amending the Companies Act to reduce the government's minimum shareholding in state-owned enterprises to 26%. Chief Economic Adviser V. Anantha Nageswaran cited this as a strategy to augment non-tax capital receipts and improve managerial efficiency, particularly relevant given the government's historically subdued privatization record and stalled divestment plans for major entities like BPCL and CONCOR. This proposal aligns with ongoing calls from NITI Aayog and industry bodies like CII to increase disinvestment for infrastructure funding.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d58cd5fc43f26c54f30cd_1769880365380.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Olympic Cards Defaults on HDFC Bank Loan, Faces Liquidity Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Olympic-Cards-Defaults-on-HDFC-Bank-Loan-Faces-Liquidity-Crisis/697e3a44adca9f39e27ee89f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Olympic-Cards-Defaults-on-HDFC-Bank-Loan-Faces-Liquidity-Crisis/697e3a44adca9f39e27ee89f</guid><description>Olympic Cards Limited has officially informed the BSE about a default in repaying its term loan facility to HDFC Bank Ltd. The company failed to pay Rs. 15.17 lakhs (principal and interest) by December 31, 2025. This signals potential financial distress and liquidity challenges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:25:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e3a44adca9f39e27ee89e_1769880338273.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quantum Threat: Systemic Risk &amp; Crypto Migration Urgency</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Quantum-Threat-Systemic-Risk-and-Crypto-Migration-Urgency/697d594c5fc43f26c54f314c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Quantum-Threat-Systemic-Risk-and-Crypto-Migration-Urgency/697d594c5fc43f26c54f314c</guid><description>The impending advent of quantum computing poses a systemic risk to global cybersecurity, threatening to shatter current encryption standards and unleash widespread chaos across financial systems, critical infrastructure, and sensitive data repositories. The "harvest now, decrypt later" tactic is actively stockpiling encrypted data for future decryption, making proactive migration to post-quantum cryptography (PQC) an immediate necessity. Organizations and regulators face a critical juncture, with projections indicating significant cybersecurity impacts within five years, necessitating urgent strategic planning and cryptographic infrastructure upgrades.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d594c5fc43f26c54f314b_1769880066615.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Investor Bets Fuel India's Green Energy Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Investor-Bets-Fuel-Indias-Green-Energy-Ambitions/697d55975fc43f26c54f2f21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Investor-Bets-Fuel-Indias-Green-Energy-Ambitions/697d55975fc43f26c54f2f21</guid><description>Super-investors Ashish Kacholia and Mukul Agrawal are placing high-conviction bets on two small-cap Indian companies, Concord Control Systems and Vikran Engineering, identified as vital components in the nation's ambitious Net Zero 2070 energy transition. Concord is pioneering green hydrogen locomotive technology, while Vikran Engineering is expanding its footprint in the solar EPC sector. Both companies present strong growth narratives alongside specific market and operational challenges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d55975fc43f26c54f2f20_1769880012509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goa Beer Industry Seeks DRS Delay Amid Revenue &amp; Supply Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Goa-Beer-Industry-Seeks-DRS-Delay-Amid-Revenue-and-Supply-Fears/697e36855fc43f26c5515bf8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Goa-Beer-Industry-Seeks-DRS-Delay-Amid-Revenue-and-Supply-Fears/697e36855fc43f26c5515bf8</guid><description>The Brewers Association of India (BAI) has formally petitioned the Goa government to postpone the April 2, 2026, implementation of its Deposit Refund System (DRS). BAI cites significant operational hurdles and fears the rule will cause severe supply disruptions during the crucial summer tourist season, potentially costing the state ₹50-55 crore in beer excise revenue alone. Manufacturers highlight unresolved technical specifications and lengthy upgrade timelines as key impediments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:08:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e36855fc43f26c5515bf7_1769879300640.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AVI Polymers Soars on Strong Q3 Profit, Eyes Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/AVI-Polymers-Soars-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-Eyes-Expansion/697e360e5fc43f26c55158c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/AVI-Polymers-Soars-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-Eyes-Expansion/697e360e5fc43f26c55158c0</guid><description>AVI Polymers Ltd. posted a robust net profit of ₹7.02 crore for the December quarter, a sharp increase from prior periods, fueled by a 348% sequential revenue surge to ₹132.32 crore. The specialty chemicals firm secured BSE's in-principle approval for a ₹90 crore rights issue, signaling a strategic move to secure growth capital for volume expansion and strategic opportunities. This performance positions the company for further development within the expanding Indian specialty chemicals market.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:06:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e360e5fc43f26c55158bf_1769879164119.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai Rail &amp; Metro Synergy: Capacity Boost Underway</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbai-Rail-and-Metro-Synergy-Capacity-Boost-Underway/697e34405fc43f26c550e08f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbai-Rail-and-Metro-Synergy-Capacity-Boost-Underway/697e34405fc43f26c550e08f</guid><description>Vivek Kumar Gupta, Member (Infrastructure) of the Railway Board, has clarified that Mumbai's Metro and suburban railway systems are complementary, not competing, elements of the city's public transport. The Metro addresses east-west connectivity gaps while the suburban network remains the city's lifeline, handling 70-80 lakh daily passengers. Significant capacity enhancements, including the expansion of train rakes to 15-car configurations and the planned introduction of non-AC closed-door services, are in progress to combat overcrowding and improve safety. Infrastructure upgrades focus on accident-prone zones and integrated station development with the MMRDA.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e34405fc43f26c550e08e_1769878808393.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Export Vision: Strong Rupee, Stronger Exports Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Export-Vision-Strong-Rupee-Stronger-Exports-Ahead/697e34585fc43f26c550e116</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Export-Vision-Strong-Rupee-Stronger-Exports-Ahead/697e34585fc43f26c550e116</guid><description>Chief Economic Advisor V. Anantha Nageswaran has articulated a vision for India's export sector: to achieve a level of competitiveness where a strengthening rupee does not undermine global sales. This ambition is detailed in the Economic Survey 2025-26, which also highlights the need for proactive domestic reforms in tax simplicity and predictability to attract foreign capital. Nageswaran referenced countries like Switzerland, Germany, and Japan as examples of export powerhouses with strong currencies, attributing their success to price-inelastic products and manufacturing prowess. The Economic Survey notes India's growing FDI inflows and the nation's positioning as an 'oasis of stability' amidst global volatility.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e34585fc43f26c550e115_1769878745108.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: AI, Capex Drive India's Economic Agenda</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-AI-Capex-Drive-Indias-Economic-Agenda/697e33bc5fc43f26c550df54</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-AI-Capex-Drive-Indias-Economic-Agenda/697e33bc5fc43f26c550df54</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman presents the Union Budget 2026, targeting sustained economic growth through significant capital expenditure and AI-driven innovation. The budget addresses sector-specific needs in semiconductors, telecom, and green energy. However, it navigates challenges of fiscal discipline, global trade frictions, and restoring investor confidence amid a weak rupee.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e33bc5fc43f26c550df53_1769878614364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Documents: India's Fiscal Secrets Unveiled</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Documents-Indias-Fiscal-Secrets-Unveiled/697e34325fc43f26c550e03a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Documents-Indias-Fiscal-Secrets-Unveiled/697e34325fc43f26c550e03a</guid><description>Detailed Union Budget documents are crucial for understanding India's fiscal policy, offering granular data on spending, revenue, and targets that shape market sentiment and investment decisions. Beyond the Finance Minister's speech, these papers, including the Annual Financial Statement and Finance Bill, provide the critical insights investors need to assess economic health and policy direction.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nvidia-OpenAI $100B Deal Talks Collapse</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-OpenAI-100B-Deal-Talks-Collapse/697d6b8c5fc43f26c54f5a64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-OpenAI-100B-Deal-Talks-Collapse/697d6b8c5fc43f26c54f5a64</guid><description>Negotiations between Nvidia Corp. and OpenAI for a potential $100 billion investment have reportedly collapsed, according to The Wall Street Journal. Citing internal concerns at Nvidia and unidentified sources, the breakdown signals a potential strategic divergence between the AI hardware giant and the leading AI research firm. The deal, aimed at bolstering AI infrastructure and data centers, was announced as a letter of intent in September, targeting 10 gigawatts of computing power.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d6b8c5fc43f26c54f5a63_1769878507880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apple India Surge: Record Q1 Fueled by Strong iPhone, Mac Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apple-India-Surge-Record-Q1-Fueled-by-Strong-iPhone-Mac-Growth/697d5d805fc43f26c54f32b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apple-India-Surge-Record-Q1-Fueled-by-Strong-iPhone-Mac-Growth/697d5d805fc43f26c54f32b2</guid><description>Apple Inc. achieved a record-breaking first fiscal quarter of 2026, highlighted by significant growth in India. CEO Tim Cook reported "terrific" results, with quarterly revenue records set for iPhone, Mac, and iPad, alongside an all-time record for services. India contributed robust double-digit revenue and installed base growth, underscoring its increasing strategic importance for the tech giant. Apple's modest but expanding market share in India's vast smartphone and PC markets presents a substantial future opportunity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d5d805fc43f26c54f32b1_1769878103402.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Gold Rally, Household Holdings Scrutinized</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Budget-2026-Gold-Rally-Household-Holdings-Scrutinized/697d5f615fc43f26c54f33ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Budget-2026-Gold-Rally-Household-Holdings-Scrutinized/697d5f615fc43f26c54f33ae</guid><description>India's gold and silver markets are bracing for Budget 2026 proposals, following a reported 100% surge in gold and 250% in silver prices since the previous budget. Indian households reportedly hold over 34,600 tonnes of gold, valued at $3.8 trillion, a figure exceeding global central bank reserves. Existing tax laws permit unlimited gold holdings from explained sources, with specific seizure limits. Experts anticipate budget changes may focus on enhanced reporting and disclosure mechanisms rather than outright holding limits, potentially simplifying existing tax rules on gold sales.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:46:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d5f615fc43f26c54f33ad_1769877975495.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Srit India Files IPO to Fund Growth, Targets Capex &amp; Working Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Srit-India-Files-IPO-to-Fund-Growth-Targets-Capex-and-Working-Capital/697d60c45fc43f26c54f348b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Srit-India-Files-IPO-to-Fund-Growth-Targets-Capex-and-Working-Capital/697d60c45fc43f26c54f348b</guid><description>Bengaluru-based Srit India has filed for an Initial Public Offering (IPO) to raise funds primarily for capital expenditure and working capital. The company plans to allocate ₹15.3 crore for product modernization and ₹124 crore towards working capital. In the fiscal year 2025, Srit India reported a revenue of ₹389.3 crore and a profit of ₹33.65 crore, marking significant year-over-year growth. The company operates in digital solutions and automation for key sectors like healthcare and e-governance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:46:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d60c45fc43f26c54f348a_1769877959643.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Tax Simplification to Drive Consumption, Not Big Fiscal Giveaways</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Tax-Simplification-to-Drive-Consumption-Not-Big-Fiscal-Giveaways/697d61bc5fc43f26c54f353e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Tax-Simplification-to-Drive-Consumption-Not-Big-Fiscal-Giveaways/697d61bc5fc43f26c54f353e</guid><description>India's upcoming Budget 2026-27 is poised to bolster consumption demand through tax simplification and targeted relief, steering clear of broad fiscal handouts. Policymakers aim for continuity and execution, emphasizing private capital expenditure, innovation-driven growth, and enhanced PPP frameworks. The strategy relies on domestic growth engines amidst global volatility, signaling a focus on stable growth visibility and execution credibility.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d61bc5fc43f26c54f353d_1769877762096.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Seabed Mining: Critical Mineral Race or Ocean Peril?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Seabed-Mining-Critical-Mineral-Race-or-Ocean-Peril/697d6c0b5fc43f26c54f5adf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Seabed-Mining-Critical-Mineral-Race-or-Ocean-Peril/697d6c0b5fc43f26c54f5adf</guid><description>The escalating global demand for critical minerals essential to energy transitions and technological advancement positions deep-sea mining as a contentious policy option. Proponents highlight potential supply diversification and reduced reliance on geopolitically concentrated sources. However, significant concerns persist regarding irreversible damage to fragile marine ecosystems, the slow pace of recovery from disturbances, and the uncertain effectiveness of proposed governance frameworks. Experts debate the true necessity of seabed exploitation, pointing to alternatives like enhanced terrestrial mining, material substitution, and circular economy strategies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:39:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d6c0b5fc43f26c54f5ade_1769877579813.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Bolsters Agriculture: New Laws, Record Rice Output</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-Bolsters-Agriculture-New-Laws-Record-Rice-Output/697e2f7d5fc43f26c5508c31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-Bolsters-Agriculture-New-Laws-Record-Rice-Output/697e2f7d5fc43f26c5508c31</guid><description>The Indian agriculture sector is experiencing robust growth, averaging 4.45% annually, driven by strong performance in allied sectors and a record rice output, surpassing China. Union Minister Shivraj Singh Chouhan announced new legislation to combat spurious seeds and pesticides, alongside reforms to rural employment schemes like the VB G-RAM-G Act. The focus remains on modern farming techniques, diversification, and sustainable practices to enhance farmer welfare and national food security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e2f7d5fc43f26c5508c30_1769877449643.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Finolex Q3: Revenue Dips, PAT Surges 55% YoY; 9-Month Profit Skewed by Prior Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Finolex-Q3-Revenue-Dips-PAT-Surges-55percent-YoY-9-Month-Profit-Skewed-by-Prior-Gains/697e2d295fc43f26c55085a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Finolex-Q3-Revenue-Dips-PAT-Surges-55percent-YoY-9-Month-Profit-Skewed-by-Prior-Gains/697e2d295fc43f26c55085a5</guid><description>Finolex Industries posted mixed Q3 FY26 results, with YoY revenue declining 10.35% but standalone PAT soaring 55% YoY to ₹109.99 Cr. Nine-month standalone PAT surged 220.70% YoY to ₹326.12 Cr, largely due to a significant exceptional gain recorded in the prior year, which also caused a sharp drop in nine-month consolidated PAT. The company now reports as a single business segment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:36:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e2d295fc43f26c55085a4_1769877414329.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GPIL Secures Green Nod for Iron Ore Mine Expansion, Tripling Capacity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GPIL-Secures-Green-Nod-for-Iron-Ore-Mine-Expansion-Tripling-Capacity/697e2e8e5fc43f26c5508b7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GPIL-Secures-Green-Nod-for-Iron-Ore-Mine-Expansion-Tripling-Capacity/697e2e8e5fc43f26c5508b7d</guid><description>Godawari Power and Ispat Limited (GPIL) has secured crucial Environmental Clearance from the Ministry of Environment, Forest and Climate Change for its Ari Dongri Iron Ore Mines expansion. The clearance allows a near tripling of capacity from 2.35 MTPA to 6 MTPA, significantly bolstering raw material security for its steel manufacturing. This move is poised to enhance operational efficiency and drive future revenue and profit growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:34:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e2e8e5fc43f26c5508b7c_1769877247889.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Jobs &amp; Skills Drive Economic Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Jobs-and-Skills-Drive-Economic-Strategy/697d811d5fc43f26c54f6cca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Jobs-and-Skills-Drive-Economic-Strategy/697d811d5fc43f26c54f6cca</guid><description>As India's Union Budget 2026 approaches, policymakers face the dual task of sustaining robust GDP growth while addressing critical employment generation and workforce skilling needs. Despite economic expansion, the quality and distribution of jobs remain under scrutiny for the nation's young workforce. Budgetary measures are expected to focus on formalizing employment, enhancing employability, and supporting labor-intensive sectors, crucial for converting economic gains into durable prosperity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d811d5fc43f26c54f6cc9_1769877225818.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Developed Status: Manufacturing Key to $13 Trillion Goal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Developed-Status-Manufacturing-Key-to-13-Trillion-Goal/697e2d9d5fc43f26c55086aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Developed-Status-Manufacturing-Key-to-13-Trillion-Goal/697e2d9d5fc43f26c55086aa</guid><description>India's ambition to become a developed nation by 2047 hinges on a significant economic expansion, targeting a $13 trillion Gross Domestic Product from its current $3.7 trillion. Department of Financial Services Secretary Nagaraju M emphasized that bolstering the manufacturing sector is crucial for this transformation, noting its current contribution to GDP lags behind comparable Asian economies. State Bank of India Chairman CS Setty highlighted eight sunrise sectors as foundational to this industrial resurgence, supported by the launch of SBI's 'CHAKRA' Centre of Excellence.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:32:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e2d9d5fc43f26c55086a9_1769877067836.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Finolex Industries Q3 PAT Surges 55% Amidst Revenue Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Finolex-Industries-Q3-PAT-Surges-55percent-Amidst-Revenue-Dip/697e2da35fc43f26c55086d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Finolex-Industries-Q3-PAT-Surges-55percent-Amidst-Revenue-Dip/697e2da35fc43f26c55086d2</guid><description>Finolex Industries posted a strong 55.01% YoY rise in standalone Q3 FY26 Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹109.99 crore, driven by margin expansion, despite a 10.35% dip in revenue to ₹897.66 crore. The nine-month PAT saw a significant YoY decline due to a prior year's exceptional gain from leasehold land rights transfer. Consolidated PAT also grew YoY in Q3. Segment reporting has been discontinued.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:29:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e2da35fc43f26c55086d1_1769876992069.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Defence Budget Surge to Fuel Domestic Arms Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Defence-Budget-Surge-to-Fuel-Domestic-Arms-Race/697d77c55fc43f26c54f6394</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Defence-Budget-Surge-to-Fuel-Domestic-Arms-Race/697d77c55fc43f26c54f6394</guid><description>India's upcoming defence budget is poised for a substantial capital infusion, with projections indicating a nearly 20% surge in acquisition funding for FY27. This strategic shift heavily favors domestic manufacturers and modernization initiatives, channeling incremental funds away from imports. Key areas slated for accelerated contracting include aviation fleets, missile systems, and advanced C4ISR/drone capabilities, directly benefiting major players like Solar Industries, BEL, HAL, and MDL.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d77c55fc43f26c54f6393_1769876868822.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DJML Posts Strong Standalone Growth, But Consolidated Q3 Shows QoQ Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/DJML-Posts-Strong-Standalone-Growth-But-Consolidated-Q3-Shows-QoQ-Dip/697e2d255fc43f26c5508592</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/DJML-Posts-Strong-Standalone-Growth-But-Consolidated-Q3-Shows-QoQ-Dip/697e2d255fc43f26c5508592</guid><description>Mediaprint &amp; Logistics (DJML) reported robust 28.58% YoY standalone revenue growth for 9M FY26 to ₹6,994.93 Lakhs. However, consolidated Q3 FY26 revenue declined 14% QoQ to ₹2,760.16 Lakhs. The company reiterated long-term value creation strategy but offered no specific future financial guidance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:27:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e2d255fc43f26c5508591_1769876867585.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Stocks Slide on Fed Nominee Jitters, Inflation Fears, and Earnings Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Stocks-Slide-on-Fed-Nominee-Jitters-Inflation-Fears-and-Earnings-Woes/697d7a145fc43f26c54f69ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Stocks-Slide-on-Fed-Nominee-Jitters-Inflation-Fears-and-Earnings-Woes/697d7a145fc43f26c54f69ad</guid><description>U.S. equity benchmarks finished lower Friday, as investors digested President Donald Trump's nomination of Kevin Warsh for the Federal Reserve, widely seen as hawkish. Mixed corporate earnings reports and a higher-than-expected producer price inflation reading further pressured markets. The Dow, S&amp;P 500, and Nasdaq Composite all closed in the red, with materials and precious metals sectors leading declines.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d7a145fc43f26c54f69ac_1769876637725.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Tax Hikes Signal Global Tobacco Downturn</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Tax-Hikes-Signal-Global-Tobacco-Downturn/697d79275fc43f26c54f6906</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Tax-Hikes-Signal-Global-Tobacco-Downturn/697d79275fc43f26c54f6906</guid><description>Effective February 1, 2026, India has implemented a significant hike in Goods and Services Tax (GST) on tobacco products to 40%, alongside new excise duties. This move, designed to curb consumption and offset health costs in Southeast Asia, a region battling 3.2 million annual tobacco-related deaths, is expected to impact sales volumes and profitability for major players like ITC Ltd., Philip Morris International, and British American Tobacco. The regulatory pressure is mounting globally, with emerging nicotine products facing increased scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d79275fc43f26c54f6905_1769876676717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Pivots India's Oil Away from Russia, Eyes Venezuelan Resurgence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Pivots-Indias-Oil-Away-from-Russia-Eyes-Venezuelan-Resurgence/697d7ed15fc43f26c54f6ba6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Pivots-Indias-Oil-Away-from-Russia-Eyes-Venezuelan-Resurgence/697d7ed15fc43f26c54f6ba6</guid><description>The United States is actively encouraging India to resume oil purchases from Venezuela, a strategic move aimed at reducing India's dependence on Russian crude and diverting global energy flows. This push coincides with Venezuela's recent legislative reforms to open its oil sector to private investment and follows a US military operation that led to the capture of Nicolás Maduro. India, facing US trade tariffs and rising costs, is already diversifying its crude supply, with Russian imports declining significantly. This geopolitical recalibration could reshape energy trade routes and impact global oil market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d7ed15fc43f26c54f6ba5_1769876172443.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Freebies: Rs 1.7 Lakh Crore Fiscal Drain Warning</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Freebies-Rs-17-Lakh-Crore-Fiscal-Drain-Warning/697d7a185fc43f26c54f69d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Freebies-Rs-17-Lakh-Crore-Fiscal-Drain-Warning/697d7a185fc43f26c54f69d0</guid><description>India's Economic Survey 2025-26 flags escalating unconditional cash transfers (UCTs) as a significant fiscal risk, with spending projected to reach ₹1.7 lakh crore by FY26. This rapid expansion, driven by electoral incentives, is widening state revenue deficits and diverting funds from essential capital expenditure. While providing immediate consumption relief, the Survey argues UCTs fail to deliver durable gains in human capital and may even reduce female labor force participation, advocating a pivot to conditional, outcome-linked welfare programs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d7a185fc43f26c54f69cf_1769876268304.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Precious Metals Plunge: Options Frenzy Meets Fed Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Plunge-Options-Frenzy-Meets-Fed-Jitters/697d864f5fc43f26c54f73bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Plunge-Options-Frenzy-Meets-Fed-Jitters/697d864f5fc43f26c54f73bd</guid><description>Gold and silver markets faced significant volatility on Friday, January 30, 2026, with bullion plunging over 9% and silver experiencing its steepest intraday decline on record, exceeding 30%. This sharp correction followed a prolonged rally, exacerbated by intense options trading activity, including a potential gamma squeeze. The nomination of Kevin Warsh as Federal Reserve chair served as a trigger, bolstering the U.S. dollar and prompting investors to reassess market expectations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d864f5fc43f26c54f73bc_1769876124090.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Metals Eye Budget 2026 for Cost Relief, Reforms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Metals-Eye-Budget-2026-for-Cost-Relief-Reforms/697d82125fc43f26c54f6d75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Metals-Eye-Budget-2026-for-Cost-Relief-Reforms/697d82125fc43f26c54f6d75</guid><description>As India's Budget 2026 approaches, the domestic metals industry faces a dichotomy of robust demand, driven by infrastructure and energy transition initiatives, contrasted with significant cost pressures stemming from import reliance and inefficient resource utilization. Stakeholders are urging the government for fiscal relief, including duty rationalization on critical minerals, enhanced private participation in mining, and stable policy frameworks to bolster competitiveness in a volatile global market. The sector's strategic importance is amplified by its role in achieving national renewable energy targets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d82125fc43f26c54f6d74_1769875984169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nestle India: Record Sales Mask Margin Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nestle-India-Record-Sales-Mask-Margin-Headwinds/697d864c5fc43f26c54f73aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nestle-India-Record-Sales-Mask-Margin-Headwinds/697d864c5fc43f26c54f73aa</guid><description>Nestle India reported a record Q3 FY26 with net profit jumping 45-46% to ₹998-1018 crore and revenue up 19% to ₹5,667 crore, driven by strong volume growth across categories and channels. However, gross margins compressed by 70 basis points due to elevated raw material costs, expected to persist. Dolat Capital acknowledged the earnings beat, raising EPS estimates, but maintained a 'Reduce' rating with a ₹1,363 target price, citing limited upside despite strong long-term growth prospects. The stock hit a 52-week high near ₹1,332.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:12:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d864c5fc43f26c54f73a9_1769875973382.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Slashes Demat Credit Time to 30 Days</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Slashes-Demat-Credit-Time-to-30-Days/697d88a15fc43f26c54f791f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Slashes-Demat-Credit-Time-to-30-Days/697d88a15fc43f26c54f791f</guid><description>The Indian securities market is set for a significant operational upgrade as the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) abolishes the Letter of Confirmation (LOC) requirement for crediting securities. This regulatory move slashes the transfer timeline from an average of 150 days down to just 30 days. The change aims to bolster investor convenience, reduce processing risks, and improve overall market efficiency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:09:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d88a15fc43f26c54f791e_1769875750170.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indo Rama Synthetics: Q3 Profit Dips, 9M PAT Turns Around Amid Board Changes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Indo-Rama-Synthetics-Q3-Profit-Dips-9M-PAT-Turns-Around-Amid-Board-Changes/697e27ff5fc43f26c5508253</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Indo-Rama-Synthetics-Q3-Profit-Dips-9M-PAT-Turns-Around-Amid-Board-Changes/697e27ff5fc43f26c5508253</guid><description>Indo Rama Synthetics posted a 2% revenue rise but a 7.8% EBITDA decline in Q3 FY26, with PAT falling to ₹8.78 Cr. However, nine-month results show a dramatic turnaround with PAT turning positive at ₹86.08 Cr from a loss, driven by margin expansion. The company also saw key director resignations and appointments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:09:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e27ff5fc43f26c5508252_1769875742086.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economic Race: Sinha Eyes US, China</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Race-Sinha-Eyes-US-China/697d8a015fc43f26c54f7a1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Race-Sinha-Eyes-US-China/697d8a015fc43f26c54f7a1f</guid><description>Jayant Sinha, former finance committee chair, posits India's primary economic competition lies with the United States and China. He stressed that closing this gap hinges on enhancing education, boosting productivity, and accelerating innovation. Sinha illustrated the economic disparity by comparing India's per capita output to that of the U.S., which generates significantly higher GDP per person through sustained investment in education and technology. He cited China's rapid AI development as a benchmark for innovation capability. Sinha urged the Union Budget 2026 to prioritize educational ecosystems and the provision of modern tools to drive productivity and global competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d8a015fc43f26c54f7a1e_1769875597837.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Courts Tax Sovereignty, Scrutinizes Foreign Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/India-Courts-Tax-Sovereignty-Scrutinizes-Foreign-Investments/697d8a095fc43f26c54f7a33</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/India-Courts-Tax-Sovereignty-Scrutinizes-Foreign-Investments/697d8a095fc43f26c54f7a33</guid><description>The Supreme Court's judgment in the Tiger Global case affirms India's paramount right to tax income generated within its borders, even when routed through international treaties. Additional Solicitor General N. Venkataraman highlighted that tax treaties are not shields for abusive practices, emphasizing that genuine economic substance is now paramount for claiming treaty benefits. This ruling signals a stricter approach to foreign investment structures, moving away from form-based compliance towards a substance-centric review, potentially impacting future capital inflows and investment strategies in India.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697d8a095fc43f26c54f7a32_1769875501904.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's UDAN Scheme Eyes Budget Boost for Regional Air Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-UDAN-Scheme-Eyes-Budget-Boost-for-Regional-Air-Growth/697e28015fc43f26c5508266</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-UDAN-Scheme-Eyes-Budget-Boost-for-Regional-Air-Growth/697e28015fc43f26c5508266</guid><description>As India's Union Budget 2026 approaches, a significant focus is expected on the Ude Desh ka Aam Nagrik (UDAN) regional air connectivity scheme. The government aims to bolster this initiative through increased financial allocations, accelerated approvals for its modified version, and a strengthened emphasis on route sustainability. This push is designed to connect 120 new regional destinations, serve an estimated 40 million passengers over the next decade, and enhance air travel, particularly in remote, hilly, and North-Eastern regions. Despite past challenges, including route discontinuations and non-operational airports, the scheme's progress has been noteworthy, connecting numerous airports and carrying millions of passengers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:05:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e28015fc43f26c5508265_1769875542834.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>