<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:17:36 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Energy Revolution: Natural Gas Surge &amp; Top Stock Pick Set to Ignite Market Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Revolution-Natural-Gas-Surge-and-Top-Stock-Pick-Set-to-Ignite-Market-Growth/695326464342f77179e4d347</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Revolution-Natural-Gas-Surge-and-Top-Stock-Pick-Set-to-Ignite-Market-Growth/695326464342f77179e4d347</guid><description>India's oil and gas sector is undergoing a major transition, with natural gas becoming a key energy source. Policy reforms, infrastructure expansion like city gas distribution, and rising CNG adoption are driving strong medium- to long-term growth. Motilal Oswal Financial Services highlights the sector's positive outlook, identifying Mahanagar Gas as a top investment with a target price of ₹1,700, predicting an 11% volume CAGR.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:02:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695326464342f77179e4d346_1767057061317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Fines on Banks Shrink Dramatically in 2025: More Cases, Smaller Penalties Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Fines-on-Banks-Shrink-Dramatically-in-2025-More-Cases-Smaller-Penalties-Revealed/695325e24342f77179e4d279</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Fines-on-Banks-Shrink-Dramatically-in-2025-More-Cases-Smaller-Penalties-Revealed/695325e24342f77179e4d279</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) imposed lower fines on banks in 2025, with the median penalty nearly halved compared to previous years. While the number of penalty instances increased to 38 from 26 in 2023 and 30 in 2024, the total fines collected were ₹25.5 crore, down from ₹29.5 crore in 2024 and ₹53.3 crore in 2023. Experts suggest a shift towards a more consultative approach by the RBI, alongside improved compliance by banks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:56:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695325e24342f77179e4d278_1767056930497.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apollo Tyres: Big Sponsorship Cost to Cap Profit Gains? Stock Outlook Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Apollo-Tyres-Big-Sponsorship-Cost-to-Cap-Profit-Gains-Stock-Outlook-Revealed/695325754342f77179e4d1a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Apollo-Tyres-Big-Sponsorship-Cost-to-Cap-Profit-Gains-Stock-Outlook-Revealed/695325754342f77179e4d1a0</guid><description>Apollo Tyres faces margin pressure despite healthy demand in India, as weak demand persists in Europe. A significant ₹580 crore sponsorship deal for the Indian cricket team, spread over two and a half years, is expected to constrain near-term margin expansion from Q3 onwards. While Q2 FY26 Ebitda margins rose to 14.9% partly due to softening raw material costs, these costs are now expected to remain stable due to INR depreciation and supply disruptions. The stock trades at 19x FY27 earnings, with challenges in balancing market share and profitability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:56:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695325754342f77179e4d19f_1767056857650.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MarketSmith India's Top Stock Picks: Unlocking Investment Opportunities in Karur Vysya Bank &amp; VST Tillers Tractors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/MarketSmith-Indias-Top-Stock-Picks-Unlocking-Investment-Opportunities-in-Karur-Vysya-Bank-and-VST-Tillers-Tractors/695325824342f77179e4d1f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/MarketSmith-Indias-Top-Stock-Picks-Unlocking-Investment-Opportunities-in-Karur-Vysya-Bank-and-VST-Tillers-Tractors/695325824342f77179e4d1f2</guid><description>MarketSmith India has identified two promising stock recommendations: Karur Vysya Bank, citing its strong South Indian franchise, improving asset quality, and digital initiatives, and V.S.T Tillers Tractors, noting its leadership in power tillers, debt-free status, and consistent demand. The Indian equity markets closed cautiously subdued on Monday, with Nifty 50 and Sensex experiencing declines amid broad-based selling.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:56:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695325824342f77179e4d1f1_1767056939787.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's E-commerce Takeover: Amazon, Flipkart, Meesho Race to Dominate Chatbot Shopping!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-E-commerce-Takeover-Amazon-Flipkart-Meesho-Race-to-Dominate-Chatbot-Shopping/695324fb4342f77179e4d0b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-E-commerce-Takeover-Amazon-Flipkart-Meesho-Race-to-Dominate-Chatbot-Shopping/695324fb4342f77179e4d0b3</guid><description>The e-commerce landscape is rapidly shifting from keyword searches to AI-powered chatbots like ChatGPT and Google Gemini guiding consumer purchases. Major online retailers including Amazon, Flipkart, and Meesho are racing to optimize their product listings for these 'shopping agents' as they become critical for visibility. Experts predict AI shopping agents could influence up to 25% of e-commerce sales by 2030, forcing companies to adapt or risk disappearing from search results.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:56:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695324fb4342f77179e4d0b2_1767056712347.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>5 Midcap Stocks That Skyrocketed in 2025: Are You Holding Them?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/5-Midcap-Stocks-That-Skyrocketed-in-2025-Are-You-Holding-Them/695324444342f77179e4d007</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/5-Midcap-Stocks-That-Skyrocketed-in-2025-Are-You-Holding-Them/695324444342f77179e4d007</guid><description>Despite valuation concerns, five midcap stocks, primarily from finance and e-commerce, emerged as top wealth creators in 2025, delivering returns up to 119%. L&amp;T Finance led the pack with a 119% surge, followed by Aditya Birla Capital (89.6%), Muthoot Finance (81%), AU Small Finance Bank (77.55%), and FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) (62.47%). These stocks defied market skepticism to offer significant gains for investors over the past twelve months.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:52:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695324444342f77179e4d006_1767056524055.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Raja Venkatraman's Top Picks: Can These 3 Stocks Beat the Bearish Market?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Raja-Venkatramans-Top-Picks-Can-These-3-Stocks-Beat-the-Bearish-Market/69531ee74342f77179e4c97a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Raja-Venkatramans-Top-Picks-Can-These-3-Stocks-Beat-the-Bearish-Market/69531ee74342f77179e4c97a</guid><description>Amidst ongoing bearish pressure in Indian markets and cautious sentiment ahead of monthly expiry, analyst Raja Venkatraman has identified three trading opportunities. He recommends buying Housing and Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO) above ₹230, Lloyds Metals and Energy Limited above ₹1395, and selling Cyient below ₹1080. The market saw broad-based selling on Monday, with the Nifty closing lower.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:29:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69531ee74342f77179e4c979_1767055145813.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai's Reign Ends? Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Set to Snatch India's Coveted No. 2 Auto Spot!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundais-Reign-Ends-Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Set-to-Snatch-Indias-Coveted-No-2-Auto-Spot/69531daa4342f77179e4c857</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundais-Reign-Ends-Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Set-to-Snatch-Indias-Coveted-No-2-Auto-Spot/69531daa4342f77179e4c857</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra is projected to overtake Hyundai Motor India for the second position in the Indian passenger vehicle market by the end of 2025. Hyundai is expected to fall to fourth place, behind M&amp;M and Tata Motors. This marks Hyundai's first loss of its long-held second rank since 2019, driven by M&amp;M's successful new model launches and facelifts, while Hyundai faces pressure from an intensifying market and a slower product cycle.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69531daa4342f77179e4c856_1767054833000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Shifts Gears: Electric Buses &amp; Trucks Take Center Stage for 2026, Leaving 2-Wheelers Behind!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Shifts-Gears-Electric-Buses-and-Trucks-Take-Center-Stage-for-2026-Leaving-2-Wheelers-Behind/695318e64342f77179e4c4ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Shifts-Gears-Electric-Buses-and-Trucks-Take-Center-Stage-for-2026-Leaving-2-Wheelers-Behind/695318e64342f77179e4c4ec</guid><description>India is prioritizing electric buses and trucks, along with charging infrastructure, for 2026 under the ₹10,900 crore PM E-Drive scheme. This strategic shift moves away from incentives for electric two- and three-wheelers, which are set to expire in March 2026. The focus is on mass transport to combat rising air pollution, despite challenges like high costs and supply chain dependencies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:02:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695318e64342f77179e4c4eb_1767053627097.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market 2026: Experts Reveal SHOCKING Outlook as Global Rivals SOAR – What Lies Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Market-2026-Experts-Reveal-SHOCKING-Outlook-as-Global-Rivals-SOAR-What-Lies-Ahead/6953186d4342f77179e4c3e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Market-2026-Experts-Reveal-SHOCKING-Outlook-as-Global-Rivals-SOAR-What-Lies-Ahead/6953186d4342f77179e4c3e0</guid><description>Indian stock markets, Nifty 50 and Sensex, are trailing global peers in 2025. Experts predict a range-bound market in the first half of 2026 due to global headwinds, with a potential rally in the second half driven by returning foreign investment and expected double-digit earnings growth. Investment focus is shifting towards domestic manufacturing and resilient financials, while risks include global volatility and potential corrections in small and mid-cap stocks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:02:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953186d4342f77179e4c3df_1767053577076.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indians Book Holiday Escapes Last Minute! Is Your Travel Stock Ready for This Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indians-Book-Holiday-Escapes-Last-Minute-Is-Your-Travel-Stock-Ready-for-This-Surge/695318584342f77179e4c3b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indians-Book-Holiday-Escapes-Last-Minute-Is-Your-Travel-Stock-Ready-for-This-Surge/695318584342f77179e4c3b5</guid><description>Indian travellers are embracing last-minute holiday bookings, with nearly half of all trips planned within 15 days of departure, a significant jump from last year. Popular international destinations include Thailand, Dubai, and Vietnam, while domestic favourites like Udaipur and Dehradun are also seeing increased interest. This trend highlights a shift towards impulse-driven, short-haul international travel and experience-focused domestic getaways.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:01:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695318584342f77179e4c3b4_1767053601540.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>