<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:03:54 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Databricks Hits $5.4B Revenue Run-Rate, CEO Warns AI Threatens SaaS</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Databricks-Hits-54B-Revenue-Run-Rate-CEO-Warns-AI-Threatens-SaaS/698a543b757d40c781844c11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Databricks-Hits-54B-Revenue-Run-Rate-CEO-Warns-AI-Threatens-SaaS/698a543b757d40c781844c11</guid><description>Databricks announced a $5.4 billion revenue run-rate, achieving 65% year-over-year growth, with over $1.4 billion from its AI products. The company also secured $5 billion in funding at a $134 billion valuation. CEO Ali Ghodsi stated that while AI boosts current SaaS usage, it will ultimately render traditional SaaS business models obsolete by replacing user interfaces with natural language.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:40:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a543b757d40c781844c10_1770673329726.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pharma Giant Eyes QSR: Ajanta Promoters Seek ₹2K Cr for Burger King India Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Pharma-Giant-Eyes-QSR-Ajanta-Promoters-Seek-2K-Cr-for-Burger-King-India-Stake/698a3ae8757d40c781844221</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Pharma-Giant-Eyes-QSR-Ajanta-Promoters-Seek-2K-Cr-for-Burger-King-India-Stake/698a3ae8757d40c781844221</guid><description>Ajanta Pharma's promoter group is seeking up to ₹2,000 crore via debt to acquire a controlling stake in Restaurant Brands Asia (RBA), the operator of Burger King in India and Indonesia. RBA, currently valued around ₹3,700 crore, has shown revenue growth but suffers from persistent losses, evidenced by its negative P/E ratio of approximately -17x. This strategic pivot introduces considerable financial leverage and operational risk for the promoters into the highly competitive quick-service restaurant (QSR) segment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:52:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a3ae8757d40c781844220_1770666881312.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Impresario Pursues Scale via Acquisitions Ahead of IPO</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Impresario-Pursues-Scale-via-Acquisitions-Ahead-of-IPO/698a365fb81b2b81dc045bad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Impresario-Pursues-Scale-via-Acquisitions-Ahead-of-IPO/698a365fb81b2b81dc045bad</guid><description>Impresario Entertainment &amp; Hospitality is in talks to acquire several mid-sized restaurant chains and cafes, a strategic move to expand its footprint and achieve critical scale ahead of a proposed public listing within the next few years. The company, backed by India Resurgence Fund, reported revenue of $95 million in FY25, swinging to a $2 million profit from a net loss. This consolidation push mirrors industry-wide trends, driven by rapid market growth and intense competition, with projections suggesting India's food services market could exceed $120 billion by 2030.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:32:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a365fb81b2b81dc045bac_1770666153708.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Piramal Pharma Faces Court Pressure Amidst Plant Closure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Piramal-Pharma-Faces-Court-Pressure-Amidst-Plant-Closure/698a363cb81b2b81dc045ade</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Piramal-Pharma-Faces-Court-Pressure-Amidst-Plant-Closure/698a363cb81b2b81dc045ade</guid><description>Piramal Pharma Limited is under intense regulatory scrutiny following a Supreme Court directive that mandates the Gujarat Pollution Control Board (GPCB) to decide within a week on the company's plea to reopen its Dahej manufacturing facility. The plant, crucial for producing intermediates for the inhalation anesthetic sevoflurane, was shut over alleged hazardous waste discharge. The apex court refused interim relief, directing Piramal to pursue remedies before statutory authorities and the National Green Tribunal (NGT). This closure poses significant operational and financial risks, particularly as the company navigates stricter environmental compliance in India's pharmaceutical sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:32:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a363cb81b2b81dc045add_1770666188183.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel Faces EU Carbon Costs Amid UK Struggles, Analyst Optimism Wanes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Faces-EU-Carbon-Costs-Amid-UK-Struggles-Analyst-Optimism-Wanes/698a35f9b81b2b81dc045948</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Faces-EU-Carbon-Costs-Amid-UK-Struggles-Analyst-Optimism-Wanes/698a35f9b81b2b81dc045948</guid><description>Steel prices in Europe are poised for a structural increase due to the EU's Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (CBAM) and quota-based tariffs, impacting imports. Tata Steel's Dutch operations show improved profitability, moving towards debt-free status. However, its UK division continues to be a financial drain, despite government support initiatives totaling £2.5 billion. Analysts maintain a consensus 'Buy' rating for Tata Steel, with an average price target around ₹200-₹209, yet the company's Price-to-Earnings (P/E) ratio of approximately 27-38 is notably higher than peers like ArcelorMittal (P/E ~14-18). The European steel market faces demand contraction in 2024 with a modest recovery expected in 2025-26, shadowed by regulatory complexities and geopolitical tensions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a35f9b81b2b81dc045947_1770665564008.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Tax Rules: Selective Easing Masks Data Grab</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Tax-Rules-Selective-Easing-Masks-Data-Grab/698a35e0b81b2b81dc04585f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Tax-Rules-Selective-Easing-Masks-Data-Grab/698a35e0b81b2b81dc04585f</guid><description>India's Central Board of Direct Taxes (CBDT) is set to implement draft Income Tax Rules 2026 by March, aligning with the new Income-Tax Act 2025 effective April 1. While certain Permanent Account Number (PAN) quoting thresholds are being raised for transactions like property purchases and vehicle buys, the move also introduces enhanced reporting for digital assets and consumer services. Officials expect these adjustments to widen the tax base, aiming for greater compliance and revenue collection amid ambitious fiscal targets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:30:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a35e0b81b2b81dc04585e_1770665586248.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Tax Reforms: Perquisite Valuations Revised, CBDC Integration Noted</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Tax-Reforms-Perquisite-Valuations-Revised-CBDC-Integration-Noted/698a35c0b81b2b81dc045745</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Tax-Reforms-Perquisite-Valuations-Revised-CBDC-Integration-Noted/698a35c0b81b2b81dc045745</guid><description>India's Central Board of Direct Taxes has proposed significant revisions to employee perquisite valuations under the draft Income Tax Rules, 2026, effective April 1, 2026. These changes substantially increase tax-free limits for meals (to ₹200 per meal) and gifts (to ₹15,000 annually), while also revising taxable values for employer-provided vehicles to reflect inflation. Additionally, the draft rules formally incorporate Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) as an acceptable payment method, aligning with broader digital economy objectives. The revisions, currently open for public feedback, aim to modernize tax compliance and support employee financial well-being amidst rising costs. However, increased valuations for certain vehicle perquisites may lead to higher tax liabilities for some employees.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:30:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a35c0b81b2b81dc045744_1770665583688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHPC Floats ₹5,129 Crore Tender for J&amp;K Hydroelectric Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NHPC-Floats-5129-Crore-Tender-for-JandK-Hydroelectric-Project/698a3549b81b2b81dc04557a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NHPC-Floats-5129-Crore-Tender-for-JandK-Hydroelectric-Project/698a3549b81b2b81dc04557a</guid><description>State-owned NHPC Ltd. has initiated a ₹5,129 crore tender for its 1,856 MW Sawalkot hydroelectric project in Jammu and Kashmir. The tender, covering major civil and hydro-mechanical works, marks a crucial step in developing one of India's large under-construction hydro assets. Bids are due March 20, 2026, with completion targeted in nine years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:28:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a3549b81b2b81dc045579_1770665444357.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Renewables Face PSA Crunch: 44 GW Stuck Amidst RPO Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Renewables-Face-PSA-Crunch-44-GW-Stuck-Amidst-RPO-Push/698a318db81b2b81dc0451a4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Renewables-Face-PSA-Crunch-44-GW-Stuck-Amidst-RPO-Push/698a318db81b2b81dc0451a4</guid><description>The Indian government is pressing states with lagging Renewable Purchase Obligations (RPOs) to finalize Power Sale Agreements (PSAs). Despite significant progress in non-fossil fuel capacity, approximately 43.9 GW of renewable energy projects hold Letters of Award but lack signed PSAs, hindering their implementation and creating a bottleneck for India's 500 GW by 2030 target. This situation highlights systemic issues in project execution and grid integration, driving a strategic shift towards energy storage solutions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:12:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a318db81b2b81dc0451a3_1770664452646.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Hotels Defy Headwinds, But Growth Poses New Questions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/India-Hotels-Defy-Headwinds-But-Growth-Poses-New-Questions/698a30a1b81b2b81dc045007</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/India-Hotels-Defy-Headwinds-But-Growth-Poses-New-Questions/698a30a1b81b2b81dc045007</guid><description>India's hospitality sector achieved robust growth in 2025, boosting occupancy by 1.1 percentage points to 64% and average daily rates by 8.6% to ₹8,624. Despite geopolitical tensions and a large supply addition of 15,500 net rooms, Revenue Per Available Room (RevPAR) climbed 10.8%. While domestic demand and GDP growth fuel optimism, performance varies between metro and emerging cities, and escalating valuations warrant scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:08:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a30a1b81b2b81dc045006_1770664187404.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSE Profit Soars 174% On Transaction Fees, Valuation Scrutiny Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/BSE-Profit-Soars-174percent-On-Transaction-Fees-Valuation-Scrutiny-Intensifies/698a2303b81b2b81dc043b0c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/BSE-Profit-Soars-174percent-On-Transaction-Fees-Valuation-Scrutiny-Intensifies/698a2303b81b2b81dc043b0c</guid><description>The Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) posted a significant 174% rise in quarterly profit to ₹602 crore, propelled by an 83% surge in transaction revenue from derivatives and equity trading. Despite this performance, the exchange's high valuation, trading at a P/E of approximately 68.4x, warrants close examination when contrasted with competitor National Stock Exchange (NSE). Rising operational costs, particularly employee expenses, add another layer to the analysis of BSE's financial trajectory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:10:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a2303b81b2b81dc043b0b_1770660798837.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Domestic Capital Dominates Nifty 50, FIIs Stay Cautious</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Domestic-Capital-Dominates-Nifty-50-FIIs-Stay-Cautious/698a228ab81b2b81dc043956</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Domestic-Capital-Dominates-Nifty-50-FIIs-Stay-Cautious/698a228ab81b2b81dc043956</guid><description>Domestic institutional investors (DIIs) have surpassed foreign institutional investors (FIIs) in ownership of Nifty 50 companies for the first time in the December 2025 quarter, holding 24.8% against FIIs' 24.3%. This shift, driven by substantial domestic inflows via SIPs and mutual funds totaling $90.1 billion in 2025, underscores a more resilient Indian market less reliant on foreign capital. Concurrently, FIIs reduced their exposure, shedding $18.8 billion amidst global macroeconomic uncertainties. This evolving ownership structure, coupled with declining promoter stakes, points to a fundamental rebalancing of market forces.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:08:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a228ab81b2b81dc043955_1770660580101.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Grid Hikes Capex to ₹32,000 Cr, Eyes Energy Transition Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Hikes-Capex-to-32000-Cr-Eyes-Energy-Transition-Growth/698a1fbcb81b2b81dc043670</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Hikes-Capex-to-32000-Cr-Eyes-Energy-Transition-Growth/698a1fbcb81b2b81dc043670</guid><description>Power Grid Corporation of India Limited posted robust Q3 FY2025-26 results, with standalone PAT up 7% YoY to ₹4,160 crores and consolidated PAT up 8% YoY to ₹4,185 crores. The company revised its FY26 CAPEX guidance upwards to ₹32,000 crores, signaling aggressive expansion. A significant project pipeline of ₹1.95 lakh crores and strategic ventures like Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) and international partnerships underscore a strong growth outlook driven by India's energy transition. Challenges like land acquisition and RoW were noted, with management optimistic about new government measures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:56:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a1fbcb81b2b81dc04366f_1770659886703.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: Public REITs Unlock Value, But Tax Complexity Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Budget-2026-Public-REITs-Unlock-Value-But-Tax-Complexity-Looms/698a1bfdb81b2b81dc042fa1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Budget-2026-Public-REITs-Unlock-Value-But-Tax-Complexity-Looms/698a1bfdb81b2b81dc042fa1</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 champions infrastructure-led growth and aims to unlock value from idle public sector real estate assets through dedicated REITs. This strategic move targets deeper institutional participation and capital recycling. However, significant tax reforms, particularly changes to Minimum Alternate Tax (MAT) credits and their interplay with the new tax regime, introduce complexities for REIT managers and investors, demanding careful financial evaluation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:40:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a1bfdb81b2b81dc042fa0_1770658940850.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Route Mobile Revenue Dips, Profit Surges Amidst Leadership Shake-up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Route-Mobile-Revenue-Dips-Profit-Surges-Amidst-Leadership-Shake-up/698a1b0db81b2b81dc042dd3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Route-Mobile-Revenue-Dips-Profit-Surges-Amidst-Leadership-Shake-up/698a1b0db81b2b81dc042dd3</guid><description>Route Mobile Limited reported a 6.48% year-on-year decline in Q3 FY26 revenue to Rs. 1,107.06 crore. However, profitability saw a strong rebound, with Profit Before Tax (PBT) surging 26.42% YoY to Rs. 135.21 crore and Profit After Tax (PAT) rising 19.99% YoY to Rs. 102.56 crore. This improvement was driven by enhanced gross margins due to new customer additions in higher-margin segments. The company also announced a leadership transition with Rajdipkumar Gupta moving to Managing Director and Tushar Agnihotri taking over as Chief Executive Officer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:36:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a1b0db81b2b81dc042dd2_1770658796129.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSE Q3 Profit Skyrockets, But Growth Sustainability Questioned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/BSE-Q3-Profit-Skyrockets-But-Growth-Sustainability-Questioned/698a1a1ab81b2b81dc042bd8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/BSE-Q3-Profit-Skyrockets-But-Growth-Sustainability-Questioned/698a1a1ab81b2b81dc042bd8</guid><description>Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) posted a stellar third quarter for FY26, with consolidated net profit leaping 174% year-on-year to ₹602 crore. Revenue from operations climbed 62% to ₹1,244 crore, largely fueled by a near doubling of transaction charges. This robust performance, however, prompts an examination of the sustainability of such rapid expansion and the exchange's premium valuation against market peers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:32:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a1a1ab81b2b81dc042bd7_1770658482933.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nature's Collapse: Businesses Risk Economic Ruin, IPBES Report Warns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Natures-Collapse-Businesses-Risk-Economic-Ruin-IPBES-Report-Warns/698a192db81b2b81dc04052e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Natures-Collapse-Businesses-Risk-Economic-Ruin-IPBES-Report-Warns/698a192db81b2b81dc04052e</guid><description>A February 2026 report by the Intergovernmental Science-Policy Platform on Biodiversity and Ecosystem Services (IPBES) warns that global businesses are actively undermining their own long-term viability by degrading natural systems. Despite their reliance on biodiversity, current economic structures and financial flows disproportionately reward harmful practices, creating systemic risks. With only a fraction of companies reporting biodiversity impacts, and significant funding gaps for conservation, the report urges transformative change to align business profitability with ecological health.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:28:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a192db81b2b81dc04052d_1770658315424.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Route Mobile Plunges on ₹18.83 Cr Q3 Net Loss Amidst Write-offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Route-Mobile-Plunges-on-1883-Cr-Q3-Net-Loss-Amidst-Write-offs/698a18c4b81b2b81dc04038c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Route-Mobile-Plunges-on-1883-Cr-Q3-Net-Loss-Amidst-Write-offs/698a18c4b81b2b81dc04038c</guid><description>Route Mobile Limited posted a consolidated net loss of ₹18.83 Cr in Q3 FY26, a sharp contrast to a ₹85.47 Cr profit last year. This downturn was largely driven by ₹135.87 Cr in exceptional write-offs, including an arbitration award and a vendor advance. Consolidated revenue fell 6.47% YoY to ₹1,107.06 Cr. While standalone net profit surged 81.54% to ₹30.39 Cr, the consolidated picture signals significant headwinds. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹3 per share.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a18c4b81b2b81dc04038b_1770658330489.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DGCA's Grip Tightens: 352 Notices Signal Airline Compliance Crunch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/DGCAs-Grip-Tightens-352-Notices-Signal-Airline-Compliance-Crunch/698a1808b81b2b81dc03d12f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/DGCAs-Grip-Tightens-352-Notices-Signal-Airline-Compliance-Crunch/698a1808b81b2b81dc03d12f</guid><description>The Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA) has issued 352 show cause notices to scheduled commercial airlines for violations between January 2024 and December 2025. IndiGo and Air India received the highest numbers, signaling a significant increase in regulatory scrutiny. While 139 notices resulted in penalties, 113 led to warnings, indicating a broad spectrum of compliance challenges. This intensified oversight occurs amidst fleet expansions, potentially increasing operational costs and complexity for carriers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:23:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a1808b81b2b81dc03d12e_1770658053976.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Soars as Indian Aviation Sector Bleeds Billions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Soars-as-Indian-Aviation-Sector-Bleeds-Billions/698a17e4b81b2b81dc03d020</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Soars-as-Indian-Aviation-Sector-Bleeds-Billions/698a17e4b81b2b81dc03d020</guid><description>The Indian aviation sector recorded a collective loss of ₹5,289.73 crore for the financial year 2024-25. The Air India Group was a significant contributor, accounting for ₹9,808.12 crore of this deficit. Amidst widespread losses, IndiGo emerged as a standout performer, netting a substantial profit of ₹7,253.30 crore. Other carriers like SpiceJet and Akasa Air also reported considerable financial shortfalls. Airfares remain deregulated, determined solely by market forces.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:22:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a17e4b81b2b81dc03d01f_1770657988751.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Tech Startups Split: Profitability vs. Growth at All Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indian-Tech-Startups-Split-Profitability-vs-Growth-at-All-Costs/698a179bb81b2b81dc03ceb1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indian-Tech-Startups-Split-Profitability-vs-Growth-at-All-Costs/698a179bb81b2b81dc03ceb1</guid><description>The December quarter revealed a bifurcated Indian tech startup sector. While nine of the twelve major companies reported improved profitability, signaling a shift towards sustainable models, others like Meesho and Swiggy doubled down on aggressive investment, widening losses. This divergence is reshaping market perception and future growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:21:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a179bb81b2b81dc03ceb0_1770657779773.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Route Mobile Posts Net Loss, Revenue Dips; Declares ₹3 Dividend Amid Vendor Issues</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Route-Mobile-Posts-Net-Loss-Revenue-Dips-Declares-3-Dividend-Amid-Vendor-Issues/698a177eb81b2b81dc03c697</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Route-Mobile-Posts-Net-Loss-Revenue-Dips-Declares-3-Dividend-Amid-Vendor-Issues/698a177eb81b2b81dc03c697</guid><description>Route Mobile reported a stark Q3 FY26 net loss of ₹18.83 Cr, a significant reversal from last year's profit, primarily due to ₹135.87 Cr in exceptional items, including vendor advance write-offs. Consolidated revenue for the quarter fell 6.5% YoY to ₹1,107.06 Cr, with nine-month PAT down 47.9%. The board declared a ₹3 interim dividend and appointed Tushar Agnihotri as CEO to drive growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:21:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a177eb81b2b81dc03c696_1770657907793.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Java Capital Fund III Targets Deeptech's Long Game</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Java-Capital-Fund-III-Targets-Deeptechs-Long-Game/698a174db81b2b81dc03aef9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Java-Capital-Fund-III-Targets-Deeptechs-Long-Game/698a174db81b2b81dc03aef9</guid><description>Bengaluru-based Java Capital has launched its third fund, targeting ₹400 crore with a ₹150 crore greenshoe option, to invest in early-stage deeptech startups. The firm, known for its "first-cheque" approach, will back science-led, IP-driven companies in sectors like semiconductors, AI, and advanced manufacturing. This move signals a strategic bet on India's growing deeptech talent pool and a growing recognition of the sector's long-term potential, aiming to bridge the critical gap in patient capital required for complex innovations. The fund plans to invest in 15-20 companies over three to four years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:20:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698a174db81b2b81dc03aef8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>InfiniMind Raises $5.8M Seed for AI Video Intelligence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/InfiniMind-Raises-58M-Seed-for-AI-Video-Intelligence/698a156bb81b2b81dc0382f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/InfiniMind-Raises-58M-Seed-for-AI-Video-Intelligence/698a156bb81b2b81dc0382f5</guid><description>InfiniMind, co-founded by ex-Google Japan leaders Aza Kai and Hiraku Yanagita, has raised $5.8 million in seed funding. The startup is developing AI infrastructure to transform petabytes of unviewed video and audio content into structured, actionable business data. This funding fuels their expansion and product development, aiming to unlock the value trapped in enterprise 'dark data' through advanced vision-language models.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:12:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a156bb81b2b81dc0382f4_1770657329197.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Route Mobile PAT Up 20% Despite 98% PBT Slump on Vendor Write-offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Route-Mobile-PAT-Up-20percent-Despite-98percent-PBT-Slump-on-Vendor-Write-offs/698a14f8b81b2b81dc025f71</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Route-Mobile-PAT-Up-20percent-Despite-98percent-PBT-Slump-on-Vendor-Write-offs/698a14f8b81b2b81dc025f71</guid><description>Route Mobile reported mixed Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated PAT rising 19.99% YoY to ₹102.56 Cr, driven by tax benefits, even as PBT crashed 98.13% to ₹2.00 Cr due to a ₹135.87 Cr exceptional item from vendor write-offs. Revenue dipped 6.48% YoY to ₹1,107.06 Cr. Standalone PAT also fell sharply. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹3 per share and saw management changes with the re-designation of Rajdipkumar Gupta to MD and appointment of Tushar Agnihotri as CEO. Auditors noted interim financials of subsidiaries were unreviewed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:10:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a14f8b81b2b81dc025f70_1770657099461.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gokaldas Exports Q3 EBITDA Drops 18% On Tariffs; Claims 17% Growth Adjusted</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Gokaldas-Exports-Q3-EBITDA-Drops-18percent-On-Tariffs-Claims-17percent-Growth-Adjusted/698a11acb81b2b81dc01df34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Gokaldas-Exports-Q3-EBITDA-Drops-18percent-On-Tariffs-Claims-17percent-Growth-Adjusted/698a11acb81b2b81dc01df34</guid><description>Gokaldas Exports reported flat total income of INR 998 crores in Q3 FY'26, with EBITDA declining 18% YoY to INR 96 crores. This impact stems from the company sharing a INR 40.2 crore US tariff burden with customers. Management claims an adjusted EBITDA growth of 17% YoY post-tariff impact. The company is focusing on operational efficiencies, European business growth, and Africa expansion to counter headwinds, anticipating an India-EU FTA benefit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:56:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698a11acb81b2b81dc01df33.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pakka Pauses US Focus for Project Jagriti; Turnaround in Sight</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pakka-Pauses-US-Focus-for-Project-Jagriti-Turnaround-in-Sight/698a0f54b81b2b81dc01ca8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pakka-Pauses-US-Focus-for-Project-Jagriti-Turnaround-in-Sight/698a0f54b81b2b81dc01ca8f</guid><description>Pakka Limited strategically pauses US and Guatemala operations to concentrate resources on Project Jagriti and stabilizing its Indian business. The company reported a year-on-year revenue gap and wider food services losses in Q3, yet sees potential for a profitability turnaround, driven by 80% YoY B2C segment growth and operational efficiencies. A ₹60 crore equity funding gap for Project Jagriti is slated for closure via internal accruals and promoter equity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:46:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a0f54b81b2b81dc01ca8e_1770655658874.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dhara Rail Projects Secures Orders, But Stock Declines Amidst Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhara-Rail-Projects-Secures-Orders-But-Stock-Declines-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/698a0e65b81b2b81dc01a087</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhara-Rail-Projects-Secures-Orders-But-Stock-Declines-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/698a0e65b81b2b81dc01a087</guid><description>Dhara Rail Projects Ltd has secured two new contracts from Indian Railways valued at Rs 58.74 lakh for component supply and Rs 6.03 crore for system maintenance, both spanning two years. Despite this influx of business, the company's stock has experienced a significant year-to-date decline of approximately 23.8%. This performance underscores a potential disconnect between operational contract wins and investor sentiment, possibly driven by valuation concerns and a reliance on larger, recurring revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:42:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a0e65b81b2b81dc01a086_1770655425963.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Pact: Fleeting Edge for Exporters Amidst Global Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-US-Trade-Pact-Fleeting-Edge-for-Exporters-Amidst-Global-Competition/698a0df5b81b2b81dc019f33</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-US-Trade-Pact-Fleeting-Edge-for-Exporters-Amidst-Global-Competition/698a0df5b81b2b81dc019f33</guid><description>An interim trade agreement between India and the United States has lowered US tariffs on Indian textiles and seafood, aiming to boost price competitiveness and exports. While this offers immediate relief and has spurred stock rallies in companies like Gokaldas Exports and Welspun Living, the tariff differentials are marginal against key rivals. The deal provides a much-needed respite after months of pressure from elevated duties, but persistent global competition and a softening demand outlook present ongoing challenges for these export-dependent sectors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:40:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a0df5b81b2b81dc019f32_1770655305124.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UBS Leases Pune Tower: Flex Space Dominates BFSI Real Estate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/UBS-Leases-Pune-Tower-Flex-Space-Dominates-BFSI-Real-Estate/698a0cfcb81b2b81dc019da2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/UBS-Leases-Pune-Tower-Flex-Space-Dominates-BFSI-Real-Estate/698a0cfcb81b2b81dc019da2</guid><description>UBS Business Solutions India has committed over ₹263 crore for a full commercial tower lease in Pune's Yerwada district, spanning 165,290 sq ft. This substantial deal for a managed office facility highlights the increasing preference among large financial institutions for flexible, plug-and-play solutions over traditional leases. The transaction underscores Pune's emergence as a critical hub for banking and financial services, driven by the broader trend of enterprise-level adoption of flexible workspaces.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:36:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a0cfcb81b2b81dc019da1_1770655071149.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Slashes Social Fund Entry Point: Retail Revolution or SSE Strain?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Slashes-Social-Fund-Entry-Point-Retail-Revolution-or-SSE-Strain/698a0941b81b2b81dc015c82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Slashes-Social-Fund-Entry-Point-Retail-Revolution-or-SSE-Strain/698a0941b81b2b81dc015c82</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has proposed a drastic reduction in the minimum investment for social impact funds on the Social Stock Exchange (SSE) to ₹1,000, a steep drop from ₹2 lakh. This initiative aims to democratize access for retail investors and simplify fundraising for not-for-profit organizations (NPOs). SEBI also plans to extend NPO registration periods and ease Zero Coupon Zero Principal Instrument (ZCZP) subscription rules. However, these reforms prompt critical examination of whether they will inject substantial capital or merely create superficial engagement, potentially straining the SSE's operational capacity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:20:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a0941b81b2b81dc015c81_1770654105187.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Happiest Minds: Revenue Surges 10.7%, PAT Dips 19.6% on Labour Code Charge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Happiest-Minds-Revenue-Surges-107percent-PAT-Dips-196percent-on-Labour-Code-Charge/698a0815b81b2b81dc0156d9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Happiest-Minds-Revenue-Surges-107percent-PAT-Dips-196percent-on-Labour-Code-Charge/698a0815b81b2b81dc0156d9</guid><description>Happiest Minds Technologies reported a robust 10.7% YoY revenue growth for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹587.56 Crores. However, Profit After Tax (PAT) declined 19.6% YoY to ₹4,030 Lakhs, primarily due to an exceptional charge of ₹2,203 Lakhs from new Labour Codes. Adjusted PAT, excluding this one-off, grew a healthy 13.0% YoY. The company is doubling down on AI/GenAI investments, planning a 1000-strong professional team by FY27, and highlighted client wins in AI applications. Financial health shows a Debt-Equity ratio of 0.80 and improved Current Ratio of 1.73, though ROE/ROCE have declined.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:15:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a0815b81b2b81dc0156d8_1770653916012.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dynamatic Technologies Q3 Profit Plunges Despite Revenue Surge; Dividend Declared</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dynamatic-Technologies-Q3-Profit-Plunges-Despite-Revenue-Surge-Dividend-Declared/698a07feb81b2b81dc014ee5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dynamatic-Technologies-Q3-Profit-Plunges-Despite-Revenue-Surge-Dividend-Declared/698a07feb81b2b81dc014ee5</guid><description>Dynamatic Technologies reported a significant 44.7% YoY revenue jump to ₹21,826 lakhs in Q3 FY26 on a standalone basis. However, reported profit after tax (PAT) plummeted 59.6% YoY to ₹412 lakhs, heavily impacted by exceptional items totalling ₹1,095 lakhs related to new Labour Codes and UK subsidiary restructuring costs. On a consolidated basis, revenue grew 34.7% to ₹42,487 lakhs, with PAT rising 63.5% to ₹577 lakhs, also before significant exceptional items. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹5 per share.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:14:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698a07feb81b2b81dc014ee4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CreditAccess Grameen: Promoter Explores Exit, Stock Faces Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CreditAccess-Grameen-Promoter-Explores-Exit-Stock-Faces-Uncertainty/698a07d5b81b2b81dc013bbe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CreditAccess-Grameen-Promoter-Explores-Exit-Stock-Faces-Uncertainty/698a07d5b81b2b81dc013bbe</guid><description>CreditAccess Grameen Limited announced that its promoter, CreditAccess India B.V., is exploring options to identify new investors for an exit opportunity for its long-term investors. This move, prompted by a news report, injects uncertainty into the company's future ownership structure and strategic direction, with no specific details on potential investors or valuation provided yet. The company assures further disclosures on material developments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:14:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a07d5b81b2b81dc013bbd_1770654546832.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Saatvik Green Energy Bets Rs 2,500 Cr on Vertical Integration Amidst US Market Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Saatvik-Green-Energy-Bets-Rs-2500-Cr-on-Vertical-Integration-Amidst-US-Market-Push/698a06f0b81b2b81dc01080e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Saatvik-Green-Energy-Bets-Rs-2500-Cr-on-Vertical-Integration-Amidst-US-Market-Push/698a06f0b81b2b81dc01080e</guid><description>Saatvik Green Energy is significantly scaling its investment, planning approximately Rs 2,500 crore in capital expenditure for fiscal year 2027. This aggressive push is geared towards enhancing its integrated solar manufacturing capabilities, from modules to cells, and to capitalize on robust domestic demand and improving export prospects, particularly in the United States. The strategy aims to strengthen cost control and margin stability in a volatile raw material market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:10:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a06f0b81b2b81dc01080d_1770653494098.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways: Structural Deficit Looms Despite Capex Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Structural-Deficit-Looms-Despite-Capex-Surge/698a0697b81b2b81dc010645</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Structural-Deficit-Looms-Despite-Capex-Surge/698a0697b81b2b81dc010645</guid><description>Indian Railways' finances remain precarious, burdened by persistent high operating costs and an over-reliance on bulk freight like coal. Despite substantial government capital injections and ambitious growth targets, a structural revenue-cost imbalance threatens long-term fiscal health. Diversification efforts and operational efficiencies are underway but may not offset the deep-seated challenges of staffing expenses and a narrow profit margin, necessitating a strategic overhaul beyond incremental adjustments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:08:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698a0697b81b2b81dc010644.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Domestic Capital Ascends: India's Market Self-Reliance Surges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Domestic-Capital-Ascends-Indias-Market-Self-Reliance-Surges/698a0674b81b2b81dc01059a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Domestic-Capital-Ascends-Indias-Market-Self-Reliance-Surges/698a0674b81b2b81dc01059a</guid><description>India's equity market ownership is undergoing a profound structural transformation, with domestic institutional investors (DIIs), propelled by record retail inflows, now surpassing foreign institutional investors (FIIs). This shift, evident in both overall holdings and the benchmark Nifty50, signifies a maturing market less susceptible to foreign capital volatility and heralds a new era of domestic capital strength and self-reliance. Mutual fund Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) are a primary driver, providing sustained liquidity and stability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:08:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a0674b81b2b81dc010599_1770653395917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kaveri Seed Q3 Profit Plunges 50% YoY Despite Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Kaveri-Seed-Q3-Profit-Plunges-50percent-YoY-Despite-Revenue-Surge/698a05f7b81b2b81dc010430</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Kaveri-Seed-Q3-Profit-Plunges-50percent-YoY-Despite-Revenue-Surge/698a05f7b81b2b81dc010430</guid><description>Kaveri Seed Company reported a 16-20% YoY revenue growth for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹210.21 Cr consolidated. However, standalone PAT plunged 50.44% YoY to ₹7.46 Cr due to higher production costs and illegal seed impacts. The nine-month period showed modest PAT growth. Outlook remains cautiously optimistic with strong export performance and expected growth in maize and mustard, but faces challenges from market prices and acreage in key crops.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:06:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a05f7b81b2b81dc01042f_1770653267105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra Lifespace Seals Bengaluru JV with Japan's Mitsui Fudosan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mahindra-Lifespace-Seals-Bengaluru-JV-with-Japans-Mitsui-Fudosan/698a0592b81b2b81dc010270</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mahindra-Lifespace-Seals-Bengaluru-JV-with-Japans-Mitsui-Fudosan/698a0592b81b2b81dc010270</guid><description>Mahindra Lifespace Developers has executed a Shareholders Agreement and Investment Agreement with Japan's Mitsui Fudosan for a joint venture to develop its 'Alembic Undertaking' residential project in Bengaluru. The project, housed in subsidiary MBLDL, will see a ₹2303 crore rights issue, with MAHLIFE retaining 51% and MFA holding 49%. This strategic partnership aims to boost operational flexibility and execution focus in the Bengaluru market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:04:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698a0592b81b2b81dc01026f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Rally on Dollar Dip; Silver Volatility Rises</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rally-on-Dollar-Dip-Silver-Volatility-Rises/698a057fb81b2b81dc01019a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rally-on-Dollar-Dip-Silver-Volatility-Rises/698a057fb81b2b81dc01019a</guid><description>Precious metals saw a significant Monday surge, led by silver's 6.66% climb to Rs 2.72 lakh/kg and gold's 0.83% rise to Rs 1.58 lakh/10g. This rally was anchored by a weaker US dollar and persistent global macro uncertainty. While gold retained its safe-haven appeal, silver exhibited heightened volatility, indicating robust speculative interest ahead of critical US employment and inflation reports later in the week.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:04:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a057fb81b2b81dc010199_1770653154822.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>