<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:46:29 +0000</pubDate><item><title>RedotPay Eyes $1B IPO Amid Crypto Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/RedotPay-Eyes-1B-IPO-Amid-Crypto-Volatility/699d70fb04a25a58c84ed4cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/RedotPay-Eyes-1B-IPO-Amid-Crypto-Volatility/699d70fb04a25a58c84ed4cc</guid><description>RedotPay, a Hong Kong-based stablecoin payments firm, is planning a significant U.S. IPO, seeking over $1 billion and a valuation potentially exceeding $4 billion. The company has engaged major investment banks like JPMorgan and Goldman Sachs for a listing as early as this year. RedotPay has amassed over 6 million users and raised $194 million in 2025, supported by prominent crypto VCs. This move highlights ongoing investor interest in digital asset infrastructure, though the success of such a venture will depend on navigating a volatile market and evolving regulatory frameworks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:35:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d70fb04a25a58c84ed4cb_1771926323493.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Actuarial Deficit Threatens Financial Modernization</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Actuarial-Deficit-Threatens-Financial-Modernization/699d70db04a25a58c84ed4b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Actuarial-Deficit-Threatens-Financial-Modernization/699d70db04a25a58c84ed4b0</guid><description>India confronts a severe actuarial talent deficit, with fewer than one actuary per million population, starkly contrasting with Western nations. This capacity gap critically impedes the nation's transition to risk-based capital (RBC) and International Financial Reporting Standards (IFRS). The shortage exacerbates existing sector pressures, including escalating climate and health risks, and a persistent low-penetration, high-cost model, potentially delaying financial modernization goals and heightening systemic vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:35:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d70db04a25a58c84ed4af_1771926199113.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Stocks Tumble on AI Fears; Pharma Climbs on Value Chain Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IT-Stocks-Tumble-on-AI-Fears-Pharma-Climbs-on-Value-Chain-Gains/699d70d204a25a58c84ed48f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IT-Stocks-Tumble-on-AI-Fears-Pharma-Climbs-on-Value-Chain-Gains/699d70d204a25a58c84ed48f</guid><description>Indian IT stocks resumed their downward trend amid fears of AI-driven disruption, prompting broker downgrades. Conversely, the Nifty Pharma index has shown resilience, gaining value over the past year. This divergence stems from Pharma's strategic shift towards higher-margin complex generics and specialty drugs, a move that enhances its value chain positioning against commoditization. IT firms, reliant on export markets, face an uncertain future as technological shifts loom large.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:35:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d70d204a25a58c84ed48e_1771925925895.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Equity's Inflation Edge: Time Trumps Timing for Real Returns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Equitys-Inflation-Edge-Time-Trumps-Timing-for-Real-Returns/699d70cc04a25a58c84ed478</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Equitys-Inflation-Edge-Time-Trumps-Timing-for-Real-Returns/699d70cc04a25a58c84ed478</guid><description>Inflation quietly erodes purchasing power, making nominal gains deceptive. While short-term equity markets fluctuate, historical data from 2000-2025 demonstrates that extended holding periods of 10+ years consistently deliver substantial real returns, outpacing inflation significantly. Patient investors leveraging compounding are better positioned to build wealth than those reacting to market timing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d70cc04a25a58c84ed477_1771925980891.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Noida Airport's Rs 4,458 Cr Push: Logistics Dominance Gambit Launched</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airports-Rs-4458-Cr-Push-Logistics-Dominance-Gambit-Launched/699d705204a25a58c84ed36e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airports-Rs-4458-Cr-Push-Logistics-Dominance-Gambit-Launched/699d705204a25a58c84ed36e</guid><description>Uttar Pradesh has secured a Rs 4,458 crore investment from AISATS for significant infrastructure development at Noida International Airport. The agreement focuses on establishing an advanced cargo campus and a world-class air catering unit. This initiative is poised to position the airport as a critical air freight and logistics hub for North India, enhancing regional trade and creating substantial employment opportunities. The investment signals a strategic push to bolster the state's economic landscape and aviation sector capabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d705204a25a58c84ed36d_1771926053932.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Unlocks Bank M&amp;A Finance: New Rules Shift Deal Landscape</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Unlocks-Bank-MandA-Finance-New-Rules-Shift-Deal-Landscape/699d6fda04a25a58c84ed241</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Unlocks-Bank-MandA-Finance-New-Rules-Shift-Deal-Landscape/699d6fda04a25a58c84ed241</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's (RBI) new framework allows Indian banks to finance corporate acquisitions, historically dominated by NBFCs, AIFs, and offshore lenders. This policy shift aims to democratize deal funding, potentially lowering costs for Indian corporates and boosting M&amp;A activity. However, it introduces significant operational and risk management challenges for banks, necessitating robust underwriting and compliance. While M&amp;A deal values surged in 2025, banks are expected to approach this new segment cautiously. The framework includes strict criteria on borrower eligibility, leverage, and collateral, while also highlighting potential risks and limitations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:31:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d6fda04a25a58c84ed240_1771925779627.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Monetizes Iconic Hotels: Challenges Loom for ITDC Redevelopment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Monetizes-Iconic-Hotels-Challenges-Loom-for-ITDC-Redevelopment/699d6fd704a25a58c84ed22a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Monetizes-Iconic-Hotels-Challenges-Loom-for-ITDC-Redevelopment/699d6fd704a25a58c84ed22a</guid><description>The Indian government has earmarked ₹820 crore for The Ashok and ₹380 crore for Hotel Samrat redevelopment under the National Monetisation Pipeline (NMP) 2.0, utilizing Public Private Partnerships (PPP). While ITDC reports improved financials, these iconic but aging assets face modernization hurdles, long timelines, security concerns for Samrat, and intense competition from aggressively expanding private hotel chains. Successful execution hinges on navigating these complexities within ambitious schedules.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:31:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d6fd704a25a58c84ed229_1771925754921.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Data Boom: Pledges vs. Reality Amidst Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-AI-Data-Boom-Pledges-vs-Reality-Amidst-Hurdles/699d6f6904a25a58c84ed134</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-AI-Data-Boom-Pledges-vs-Reality-Amidst-Hurdles/699d6f6904a25a58c84ed134</guid><description>India's AI summit saw over $277 billion pledged for data centers and infrastructure, yet immediate GDP contribution remains minimal. Nomura forecasts construction acceleration but flags land, power, and labor as key impediments. While capacity is set to double, significant investment and complex infrastructural challenges persist. India's strategic alignment with the US-led Pax Silica initiative aims to bolster its role in the global AI supply chain, though traditional IT services face AI-driven disruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:29:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d6f6904a25a58c84ed133_1771925508303.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GDP Surge Overshadowed by Data Overhaul Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Surge-Overshadowed-by-Data-Overhaul-Uncertainty/699d6f6404a25a58c84ed11d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Surge-Overshadowed-by-Data-Overhaul-Uncertainty/699d6f6404a25a58c84ed11d</guid><description>India's economy is projected to grow by 8.1% in Q3 FY26, according to SBI Research, driven by robust domestic demand. However, the impending overhaul of the GDP series, including a shift to a 2022-23 base year and revised methodologies, introduces significant uncertainty regarding historical data comparability and future economic assessments. This statistical recalibration may overshadow the current growth figures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Centum Electronics Wins ₹590 Cr HAL Order for Advanced Radar Systems</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Centum-Electronics-Wins-590-Cr-HAL-Order-for-Advanced-Radar-Systems/699d6e7504a25a58c84ecf7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Centum-Electronics-Wins-590-Cr-HAL-Order-for-Advanced-Radar-Systems/699d6e7504a25a58c84ecf7f</guid><description>Centum Electronics has won a significant multi-phase order from Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL) for Active Electronically Scanned Array (AESA) Radar Systems. The deal, which includes a design and development phase and an indicative serial production phase, totals approximately ₹590 crore. This order is a key milestone for indigenous defence electronics and strengthens Centum's ties with HAL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:25:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d6e7504a25a58c84ecf7e_1771925568698.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LT Foods GST Demand Confirmed ₹32.41 Cr by Appellate Order, Company Plans Appeal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LT-Foods-GST-Demand-Confirmed-3241-Cr-by-Appellate-Order-Company-Plans-Appeal/699d6e7104a25a58c84ecf66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LT-Foods-GST-Demand-Confirmed-3241-Cr-by-Appellate-Order-Company-Plans-Appeal/699d6e7104a25a58c84ecf66</guid><description>LT Foods has received an appellate order from the Commissioner of CGST (Appeals-II), Delhi, confirming a GST demand of ₹32.41 crore, along with interest and penalties. This order reverses a previous ruling that had dropped the demand, concerning alleged wrongful GST exemption on plain-packaged rice supplies. The company plans to file an appeal at the GST Appellate Tribunal and currently anticipates no material financial or operational impact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:25:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d6e7104a25a58c84ecf65_1771925210167.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Efficiency Threatens Demand: Citrini Warns of Economic Downturn</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AIs-Efficiency-Threatens-Demand-Citrini-Warns-of-Economic-Downturn/699d6cb104a25a58c84ecdae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AIs-Efficiency-Threatens-Demand-Citrini-Warns-of-Economic-Downturn/699d6cb104a25a58c84ecdae</guid><description>A forward-looking analysis from Citrini Research projects artificial intelligence fulfilling its efficiency promises to a dangerous degree, potentially causing a severe economic crisis by 2028. The scenario foresees advanced AI automating white-collar tasks, leading to soaring corporate profits alongside a surge in unemployment exceeding 10%. This efficiency gain, however, risks creating a 'Ghost GDP' and a negative feedback loop where reduced consumer spending from job losses triggers further automation, destabilizing credit markets and challenging the economic status quo.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:17:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d6cb104a25a58c84ecdad_1771925450782.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Avenue Supermarts Shareholders Approve Anshul Asawa as MD &amp; CEO for 3 Years</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Avenue-Supermarts-Shareholders-Approve-Anshul-Asawa-as-MD-and-CEO-for-3-Years/699d6c1a04a25a58c84eccab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Avenue-Supermarts-Shareholders-Approve-Anshul-Asawa-as-MD-and-CEO-for-3-Years/699d6c1a04a25a58c84eccab</guid><description>Avenue Supermarts Limited shareholders overwhelmingly approved the appointment of Anshul Asawa as Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer for a three-year term starting April 1, 2026. The resolution passed with 99.67% of votes in favour, marking a significant leadership transition for the popular DMart retail chain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:15:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d6c1a04a25a58c84eccaa_1771925155809.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India IT Sector: $315B Revenue Goal Amid Global Slowdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-IT-Sector-315B-Revenue-Goal-Amid-Global-Slowdown/699d6a7404a25a58c84ecaf2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-IT-Sector-315B-Revenue-Goal-Amid-Global-Slowdown/699d6a7404a25a58c84ecaf2</guid><description>India's technology sector is forecast to reach $315 billion in revenue for fiscal year 2026, marking a 6.1% increase, according to Nasscom. This growth is underpinned by strong domestic demand and a significant contribution from new-age technologies like AI, estimated at $10-12 billion. However, global economic slowdowns and evolving client spending patterns introduce a layer of complexity, with some analysts anticipating muted growth for larger IT firms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d6a7404a25a58c84ecaf1_1771924549324.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alembic Pharma Receives USFDA Nod For Efinaconazole Solution; $500M Market Potential</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alembic-Pharma-Receives-USFDA-Nod-For-Efinaconazole-Solution-500M-Market-Potential/699d6a5b04a25a58c84eca77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alembic-Pharma-Receives-USFDA-Nod-For-Efinaconazole-Solution-500M-Market-Potential/699d6a5b04a25a58c84eca77</guid><description>Alembic Pharmaceuticals has secured final USFDA approval for its Efinaconazole Topical Solution, 10%. The drug targets toenail fungus, entering a US market estimated at $500 million. This approval, achieved with a Paragraph IV certification, positions Alembic to compete with the innovator product Jublia and signifies a key step in its US generics strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:07:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d6a5b04a25a58c84eca76_1771924163676.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBFCs: Growth Signal Mixed With Margin Durability Doubts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFCs-Growth-Signal-Mixed-With-Margin-Durability-Doubts/699d69e904a25a58c84ec922</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFCs-Growth-Signal-Mixed-With-Margin-Durability-Doubts/699d69e904a25a58c84ec922</guid><description>Kotak Institutional Equities highlights a strong growth phase for non-banking financial companies (NBFCs), driven by accelerated disbursements and expanding net interest margins in Q3FY26. However, the firm cautions that margin expansion might not endure through FY27 due to intense competition and evolving interest rate dynamics. This outlook suggests continued loan growth for favored entities like Bajaj Finance and Bajaj Finserv, though profitability pressures are anticipated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:05:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d69e904a25a58c84ec921_1771924704473.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nutraplus India FY25: ₹5 Lakh Net Loss; Auditor Flags Going Concern Doubt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Nutraplus-India-FY25-5-Lakh-Net-Loss-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Doubt/699d69db04a25a58c84ec8ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Nutraplus-India-FY25-5-Lakh-Net-Loss-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Doubt/699d69db04a25a58c84ec8ea</guid><description>Nutraplus India Limited reported a net loss of ₹5.01 lakh for FY25, a slight improvement from the previous year's ₹6.16 lakh loss. However, the company faces severe financial distress, including eroded net worth, negative working capital, and a loan default of ₹76.24 crore. Auditors have issued a qualified opinion, raising substantial doubt about its ability to continue as a going concern due to numerous financial and governance issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:05:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d69db04a25a58c84ec8e9_1771924051897.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Costly Evolution: Indian IT Faces Margin Squeeze, Infrastructure Surges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Costly-Evolution-Indian-IT-Faces-Margin-Squeeze-Infrastructure-Surges/699d69d904a25a58c84ec8d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Costly-Evolution-Indian-IT-Faces-Margin-Squeeze-Infrastructure-Surges/699d69d904a25a58c84ec8d4</guid><description>Mihir Vora of Trust Mutual Fund identifies AI as a profound disruptor, necessitating costly reinvention for Indian IT firms, which may pressure near-term margins. While the IT sector faces adaptation challenges, companies investing in R&amp;D can emerge as winners. Concurrently, demand for data centers and robust power infrastructure is surging, positioning transformer manufacturers, grid operators, and generator suppliers for significant growth, insulated from direct IT sector volatility.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:05:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d69d904a25a58c84ec8d3_1771924061509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kotak Mfg Fund: 4 Years, High Returns, Future Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Kotak-Mfg-Fund-4-Years-High-Returns-Future-Hurdles/699d69b704a25a58c84ec867</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Kotak-Mfg-Fund-4-Years-High-Returns-Future-Hurdles/699d69b704a25a58c84ec867</guid><description>The Kotak Manufacturing Fund concludes four years with ₹2,409 crore in assets, yielding a 21% CAGR for lump-sum investors and ₹72,152 from a ₹1,000 monthly SIP. Targeting key industrial themes, the fund maintains a diversified portfolio. Despite past success, inherent sector volatility and evolving competitive dynamics pose risks to sustained alpha generation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:04:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d69b704a25a58c84ec866_1771924013890.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Livspace Shakes Up Leadership, Cuts 1,000 Jobs Amid AI Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Livspace-Shakes-Up-Leadership-Cuts-1000-Jobs-Amid-AI-Push/699d693904a25a58c84ec771</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Livspace-Shakes-Up-Leadership-Cuts-1000-Jobs-Amid-AI-Push/699d693904a25a58c84ec771</guid><description>Livspace has confirmed the exit of Chief Business Officer Lalit Mittal and the dismissal of approximately 1,000 employees. The company describes these moves as a strategic reallocation of resources to foster an AI-native operational model. This restructuring follows shortly after news of India CEO Saurabh Jain's departure and occurs alongside the company's reported revenue growth of 23% to Rs 1,460 crore and a significant reduction in losses for fiscal year 2025. The company aims to enhance efficiency and productivity through advanced AI integration across its core functions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:02:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d693904a25a58c84ec770_1771924105005.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sanctions Bifurcate Asia: India Shifts from Russia as China Boosts Imports</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Sanctions-Bifurcate-Asia-India-Shifts-from-Russia-as-China-Boosts-Imports/699d68d604a25a58c84ec6f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Sanctions-Bifurcate-Asia-India-Shifts-from-Russia-as-China-Boosts-Imports/699d68d604a25a58c84ec6f6</guid><description>India's January 2026 Russian energy imports fell to €2.2 billion, marked by Reliance Industries' pause in sourcing from Russian suppliers due to international sanctions. This pivot contrasts sharply with China's record increase in Russian oil imports for the same month. The shift signals a divergence in Asian energy strategies, driven by regulatory compliance for India and demand expansion for China, with potential cost implications for New Delhi.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:01:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d68d604a25a58c84ec6f5_1771924623547.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC Bank Fraud: ₹556Cr Recovered, Governance Scrutiny Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-Bank-Fraud-556Cr-Recovered-Governance-Scrutiny-Intensifies/699d680a04a25a58c84ec533</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-Bank-Fraud-556Cr-Recovered-Governance-Scrutiny-Intensifies/699d680a04a25a58c84ec533</guid><description>IDFC First Bank is under intense scrutiny following a ₹590 crore fraud at its Chandigarh branch, involving government accounts. While Haryana has recovered ₹556 crore, including interest, within 24 hours, the incident has amplified questions about the bank's internal controls and governance. Analysts are divided, with some flagging earnings and control risks, while the bank asserts its capital strength and profitability remain intact pending a forensic audit. The stock experienced a significant decline following the disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:57:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d680a04a25a58c84ec532_1771923584505.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Man Infra Gets IOD for Pali Hill Project, Unlocking ₹500cr+ Sale Potential</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Man-Infra-Gets-IOD-for-Pali-Hill-Project-Unlocking-500cr-Sale-Potential/699d67e004a25a58c84ec502</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Man-Infra-Gets-IOD-for-Pali-Hill-Project-Unlocking-500cr-Sale-Potential/699d67e004a25a58c84ec502</guid><description>Man Infraconstruction Limited (MICL Group) has received the crucial Intimation of Disapproval (IOD) from municipal authorities for its ultra-luxurious Pali Hill project in Bandra West, Mumbai. This regulatory milestone permits the commencement of demolition and construction. The project, undertaken via associate Atmosphere Homes LLP (34% stake), has an estimated sale potential exceeding ₹500 crore and is slated for a formal launch next quarter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:57:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d67e004a25a58c84ec501_1771924012040.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank: Fraud Fallout vs. JP Morgan's Optimism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Fallout-vs-JP-Morgans-Optimism/699d677604a25a58c84ec44c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Fallout-vs-JP-Morgans-Optimism/699d677604a25a58c84ec44c</guid><description>IDFC First Bank's stock experienced a sharp decline following the disclosure of a ₹590 crore fraud at its Chandigarh branch, allegedly involving certain employees and Haryana government accounts. Despite this, global brokerage JP Morgan reiterated its 'Overweight' rating with a ₹91 target price, suggesting the market's reaction may be excessive. The bank has suspended employees, engaged KPMG for a forensic audit, and highlighted its strong capital adequacy to mitigate the impact, though near-term volatility is expected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:55:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d677604a25a58c84ec44b_1771923432458.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Disruption: Intermediaries Face Existential Threat, Tech Giants Reel</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Disruption-Intermediaries-Face-Existential-Threat-Tech-Giants-Reel/699d677004a25a58c84ec432</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Disruption-Intermediaries-Face-Existential-Threat-Tech-Giants-Reel/699d677004a25a58c84ec432</guid><description>Citrini Research's "2028 Global Intelligence Crisis" report has sent shockwaves through markets, predicting an AI-driven recession via "Agentic Commerce" and job displacement. This triggered sell-offs in payment and software sectors, with IBM shares plummeting 13%. While chipmakers and data centers are beneficiaries, traditional intermediaries face revenue erosion as AI bypasses transaction friction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:55:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d677004a25a58c84ec431_1771923513794.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IIFL Finance Eyes ₹1,000 Cr via NCDs; Eyes Growth Funding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Finance-Eyes-1000-Cr-via-NCDs-Eyes-Growth-Funding/699d64d404a25a58c84ec251</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Finance-Eyes-1000-Cr-via-NCDs-Eyes-Growth-Funding/699d64d404a25a58c84ec251</guid><description>IIFL Finance's Finance Committee has greenlit the issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) worth up to ₹1,000 crore. The senior, secured, listed debt instruments will be placed privately and listed on the NSE, aiming to bolster capital for growth or manage existing obligations. This move comes amidst ongoing efforts to strengthen its balance sheet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:44:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d64d404a25a58c84ec250_1771923111768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fear Overstated: Indian IT Poised for Modernization Opportunity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fear-Overstated-Indian-IT-Poised-for-Modernization-Opportunity/699d624b04a25a58c84ec059</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fear-Overstated-Indian-IT-Poised-for-Modernization-Opportunity/699d624b04a25a58c84ec059</guid><description>Market sentiment is excessively focused on AI disruption, a long-term possibility. While software faces rapid change, Indian IT services firms like TCS and Infosys are positioned to leverage AI for modernizing legacy systems, mitigating immediate structural risks. Recent volatility in global tech obscures this nuanced adaptation, with analysts largely maintaining positive outlooks on these resilient players.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:33:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d624b04a25a58c84ec058_1771922118095.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Regaal Resources Surges 15% on High Volume Amid Profit Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Regaal-Resources-Surges-15percent-on-High-Volume-Amid-Profit-Dip/699d624104a25a58c84ec03f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Regaal-Resources-Surges-15percent-on-High-Volume-Amid-Profit-Dip/699d624104a25a58c84ec03f</guid><description>Regaal Resources experienced a sharp 15% increase in its share price, accompanied by a 101-fold surge in trading volume, reaching an intraday high of ₹70.85. This rally occurred despite the company reporting a 6.9% year-on-year drop in Q3 FY26 profit after tax to ₹13.2 crore. A one-time ₹6.7 crore charge for a subsidy refund also impacted results, though total income grew by 25.7%. The move appears technically driven, contrasting with the stock's year-long downtrend and proximity to 52-week lows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:33:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d624104a25a58c84ec03e_1771922122226.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bombay HC Rules on Ambani Accounts: Fraud Classification Validated</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Bombay-HC-Rules-on-Ambani-Accounts-Fraud-Classification-Validated/699d624004a25a58c84ec028</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Bombay-HC-Rules-on-Ambani-Accounts-Fraud-Classification-Validated/699d624004a25a58c84ec028</guid><description>The Bombay High Court has authorized Indian Overseas Bank, IDBI Bank, and Bank of Baroda to classify Anil Ambani's and Reliance Communications Ltd.'s accounts as fraudulent. This decision overturns a previous stay, validating the Reserve Bank of India's Master Directions on fraud detection and borrower identification. The court affirmed the integrity of the forensic audit conducted by BDO India LLP, dismissing claims of its invalidity. This ruling bolsters confidence in the banking system's ability to combat financial misconduct and protect public funds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:33:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d624004a25a58c84ec027_1771922696545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DreamFolks ₹7.7 Cr GST Notice for FY23-24; Company Cites No Immediate Impact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DreamFolks-77-Cr-GST-Notice-for-FY23-24-Company-Cites-No-Immediate-Impact/699d61c704a25a58c84ebf4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DreamFolks-77-Cr-GST-Notice-for-FY23-24-Company-Cites-No-Immediate-Impact/699d61c704a25a58c84ebf4a</guid><description>DreamFolks Services Limited has received a GST show cause notice demanding ₹6.99 crore in GST and ₹0.70 crore as penalty, totalling ₹7.70 crore. The notice, issued by the Office of the Special Commissioner of Revenue (South Bengal) for FY 2023-24, alleges violations related to the 'place of supply' under the IGST Act. The company stated it does not envisage any immediate material impact and plans to file a response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d61c704a25a58c84ebf49_1771921971406.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eris Lifesciences Bets on Generic Semaglutide Disruption</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Eris-Lifesciences-Bets-on-Generic-Semaglutide-Disruption/699d615304a25a58c84ebe80</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Eris-Lifesciences-Bets-on-Generic-Semaglutide-Disruption/699d615304a25a58c84ebe80</guid><description>Eris Lifesciences is leveraging Natco Pharma's CDSCO approval for generic semaglutide to enter India's burgeoning diabetes and metabolic market. The strategic alliance, timed with Novo Nordisk's patent expiry in March 2026, anticipates significant price reductions, potentially lowering monthly treatment costs by up to 70-75%. This move capitalizes on India's high diabetes prevalence and Eris's established physician network, positioning it against a crowded field of domestic generic competitors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:29:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d615304a25a58c84ebe7f_1771921897817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC Rules: Developers Solely Liable for Real Estate Delays</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/SC-Rules-Developers-Solely-Liable-for-Real-Estate-Delays/699d60d904a25a58c84ebdd5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/SC-Rules-Developers-Solely-Liable-for-Real-Estate-Delays/699d60d904a25a58c84ebdd5</guid><description>The Supreme Court of India has definitively ruled that landowners are not liable for construction delays caused by developers in Joint Development Agreements (JDAs). In a significant victory for landowners, the apex court affirmed that contractual terms assigning construction and delivery obligations solely to the developer absolve landowners of delay compensation claims. Homebuyers must now pursue recourse exclusively against the errant developers, though landowners and developers remain jointly responsible for ensuring title transfer and executing sale deeds. This landmark judgment reshapes risk allocation in real estate partnerships, placing greater financial and legal onus on developers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:27:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d60d904a25a58c84ebdd4_1771921746172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indri Malt Disrupts Global Spirits; India Surges Past Scotch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indri-Malt-Disrupts-Global-Spirits-India-Surges-Past-Scotch/699d607604a25a58c84ebd5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indri-Malt-Disrupts-Global-Spirits-India-Surges-Past-Scotch/699d607604a25a58c84ebd5b</guid><description>Haryana-based Indri, produced by Piccadilly Agro Industries Limited, has rapidly ascended to become India's top-selling single malt and the world's fastest-growing Indian single malt for the second consecutive year. The brand has successfully challenged and, by many metrics, surpassed Scotch whisky's long-standing dominance within the Indian market, a phenomenon validated by international awards and substantial volume growth. This shift signifies a broader trend of premiumization and localization in India's burgeoning spirits sector, forcing global players to adapt.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:25:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d607604a25a58c84ebd5a_1771921648035.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Revamps GDP Data: Precision Boost Aims for Global Standard</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Revamps-GDP-Data-Precision-Boost-Aims-for-Global-Standard/699d5efc04a25a58c84ebc28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Revamps-GDP-Data-Precision-Boost-Aims-for-Global-Standard/699d5efc04a25a58c84ebc28</guid><description>India's national accounts are undergoing a significant overhaul with a new GDP data series releasing February 27, 2026. Shifting the base year from 2011-12 to 2022-23, the revised framework adopts double deflation and expands the item basket for price deflation to 500-600 from 180. This methodology upgrade aims to enhance data precision, particularly in the manufacturing sector, and address long-standing criticisms from economists and the International Monetary Fund (IMF).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:19:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d5efc04a25a58c84ebc27_1771921337591.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Himadri Speciality Chemical's Mahistikry Plant Becomes World's Largest Speciality Carbon Black Site</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Himadri-Speciality-Chemicals-Mahistikry-Plant-Becomes-Worlds-Largest-Speciality-Carbon-Black-Site/699d5c9f04a25a58c84eb8bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Himadri-Speciality-Chemicals-Mahistikry-Plant-Becomes-Worlds-Largest-Speciality-Carbon-Black-Site/699d5c9f04a25a58c84eb8bf</guid><description>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd has successfully commenced commercial operations for its expanded 70,000 MTPA Speciality Carbon Black manufacturing line at its Mahistikry facility in West Bengal, effective February 24, 2026. This significant capacity addition makes the Mahistikry plant the largest single-location Speciality Carbon Black manufacturing site globally, with total carbon black capacity reaching 2,50,000 MTPA.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:09:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d5c9f04a25a58c84eb8be_1771921370728.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Scrutinizes AI ROI; India's IT Faces AI Divide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-Scrutinizes-AI-ROI-Indias-IT-Faces-AI-Divide/699d5b4104a25a58c84eb6c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-Scrutinizes-AI-ROI-Indias-IT-Faces-AI-Divide/699d5b4104a25a58c84eb6c3</guid><description>US markets are now scrutinizing the massive return on investment from AI capital expenditure as hyperscalers shift to asset-heavy models, spending an estimated $620 billion in 2026. This scrutiny is leading to capital reallocation away from markets like India, which is perceived as a "reverse AI trade." Meanwhile, Indian IT firms face concerns over AI's disruption potential, though some analysts believe their resilience and role in developing smaller language models (SLMs) could offer a path forward. Foreign institutional investors have significantly reduced their exposure to Indian IT stocks, contributing to a sharp decline in the sector's market capitalization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:03:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d5b4104a25a58c84eb6c2_1771920499425.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KEC International Secures ₹1002 Cr Orders; Boosts T&amp;D and Cables Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Secures-1002-Cr-Orders-Boosts-TandD-and-Cables-Business/699d5ac604a25a58c84eb5e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Secures-1002-Cr-Orders-Boosts-TandD-and-Cables-Business/699d5ac604a25a58c84eb5e1</guid><description>KEC International has announced new orders totalling ₹1002 crore, strengthening its Transmission &amp; Distribution (T&amp;D) and Cables &amp; Conductors businesses. These wins include significant T&amp;D projects in India, an international transmission line, and tower supplies in the Americas, contributing to a year-to-date order intake of approximately ₹21,300 crore and enhancing customer diversification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:01:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d5ac604a25a58c84eb5e0_1771920198118.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Meta Internal Dissent on Encryption Fuels Safety vs. Privacy Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Meta-Internal-Dissent-on-Encryption-Fuels-Safety-vs-Privacy-Debate/699d5ac204a25a58c84eb5cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Meta-Internal-Dissent-on-Encryption-Fuels-Safety-vs-Privacy-Debate/699d5ac204a25a58c84eb5cb</guid><description>Internal documents reveal Meta executives pushed forward with encrypting Facebook and Instagram messaging services despite significant internal warnings that this move would cripple the company's ability to detect and report child exploitation cases. Senior policy and safety executives expressed grave concerns, with one describing the decision as "so irresponsible" and a "gross misstatement" of their safety capabilities. Projections indicated a substantial drop in reporting to child safety organizations, potentially leaving hundreds of exploitation cases undiscovered. Meta has since stated that new safety features were developed to work within encrypted chats, but the company continues to face multiple lawsuits globally over youth safety and mental health.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:01:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d5ac204a25a58c84eb5ca_1771920280427.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Meta Encryption Row Fuels Regulatory Storm, Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meta-Encryption-Row-Fuels-Regulatory-Storm-Valuation-Concerns/699d5ac104a25a58c84eb5b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meta-Encryption-Row-Fuels-Regulatory-Storm-Valuation-Concerns/699d5ac104a25a58c84eb5b4</guid><description>Meta faces intensifying legal and regulatory scrutiny over its encrypted messaging services, stemming from internal warnings about child exploitation risks. Court cases in New Mexico and by numerous attorneys general allege the company prioritized growth over user safety, potentially leading to significant financial and operational repercussions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:01:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d5ac104a25a58c84eb5b3_1771920225785.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Redevelopment: High-Risk, High-Reward Urban Real Estate Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Redevelopment-High-Risk-High-Reward-Urban-Real-Estate-Shift/699d5a7404a25a58c84eb4ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Redevelopment-High-Risk-High-Reward-Urban-Real-Estate-Shift/699d5a7404a25a58c84eb4ca</guid><description>India's urban real estate is increasingly driven by redevelopment, a shift from greenfield projects necessitated by land scarcity. This strategy unlocks value in established urban centers, attracting significant institutional capital, particularly in premium housing segments. However, the inherent complexity, rising construction costs, and aggressive demands from housing societies introduce substantial risks that require sophisticated investor oversight and developer expertise. Successful navigation demands patient capital and a focus on execution resilience rather than speculative price appreciation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 07:59:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d5a7404a25a58c84eb4c9_1771920324843.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>