<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:25:18 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Adani Electricity Mumbai's Credit Rating Upgraded to Crisil AAA</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Electricity-Mumbais-Credit-Rating-Upgraded-to-Crisil-AAA/69997797730b6847a517596d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Electricity-Mumbais-Credit-Rating-Upgraded-to-Crisil-AAA/69997797730b6847a517596d</guid><description>Adani Electricity Mumbai Limited (AEML), a unit of Adani Energy Solutions, received a credit rating upgrade to 'Crisil AAA' for its proposed NCDs, from 'Crisil AA+/Positive' with a Stable Outlook. This highest rating signifies improved financial standing and is expected to lower borrowing costs for future funding.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:15:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69997797730b6847a517596c_1771665420361.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Akme Fintrade OKs ₹85.75 Cr Warrant Issue; EGM on March 20</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-OKs-8575-Cr-Warrant-Issue-EGM-on-March-20/69997721730b6847a51758fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-OKs-8575-Cr-Warrant-Issue-EGM-on-March-20/69997721730b6847a51758fd</guid><description>Akme Fintrade's Board has approved a preferential issue of up to 12.25 crore warrants at ₹7 each, aiming to raise ₹85.75 crore. These warrants are convertible into equity shares within 18 months. Shareholder approval is slated for an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on March 20, 2026. This capital infusion is crucial for the NBFC's expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:13:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69997721730b6847a51758fc_1771665292292.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel: EU Carbon Tax Boost or Costly Burden?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-EU-Carbon-Tax-Boost-or-Costly-Burden/6999764a730b6847a5175840</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-EU-Carbon-Tax-Boost-or-Costly-Burden/6999764a730b6847a5175840</guid><description>Tata Steel Ltd. anticipates the European Union's Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (CBAM) will benefit its operations, positioning it as an 'equalisation tax' rather than a detriment. Managing Director TV Narendran highlighted that the company's significant European production footprint shields it from import tariffs. However, the global steel sector faces considerable disruption, with ongoing discussions and potential retaliatory measures from trading partners. Tata Steel's long-term decarbonization strategy in Europe, including phasing out blast furnaces by 2035, aligns with the EU's climate goals, yet the substantial investment required and evolving policy landscape present critical future considerations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:09:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999764a730b6847a517583f_1771665071149.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UVS Hospitality Acquires Calcio Restaurants for ₹350 Cr; Plans ₹47 Cr Fundraise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/UVS-Hospitality-Acquires-Calcio-Restaurants-for-350-Cr-Plans-47-Cr-Fundraise/699975ba730b6847a517579e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/UVS-Hospitality-Acquires-Calcio-Restaurants-for-350-Cr-Plans-47-Cr-Fundraise/699975ba730b6847a517579e</guid><description>UVS Hospitality and Services Limited is set to acquire up to 51% of Calcio Restaurants Private Limited in a substantial ₹350.27 crore share swap deal. The company also plans to raise ₹47.48 crore via a preferential issue and warrants. This strategic move aims to consolidate operations and bolster its presence in the hospitality and restaurant sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:07:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699975ba730b6847a517579d_1771664928267.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani's NMIA Rolls Out DigiYatra Amidst Sector Growth Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adanis-NMIA-Rolls-Out-DigiYatra-Amidst-Sector-Growth-Concerns/6999710a730b6847a5175601</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adanis-NMIA-Rolls-Out-DigiYatra-Amidst-Sector-Growth-Concerns/6999710a730b6847a5175601</guid><description>Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA), operated by Adani Airport Holdings Ltd. (AAHL), has launched its DigiYatra biometric system. This integration utilizes facial recognition for contactless, paperless passenger processing, aiming to reduce wait times and improve efficiency. NMIA is a key component of AAHL's expanding network and its significant expansion plans for India's growing aviation market. The rollout occurs as the broader Indian aviation sector navigates challenges including slowing growth and operational disruptions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:47:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999710a730b6847a5175600_1771663770053.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dr. Reddy's Secures First Abatacept Biosimilar Approval</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Secures-First-Abatacept-Biosimilar-Approval/69996a03730b6847a51753f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Secures-First-Abatacept-Biosimilar-Approval/69996a03730b6847a51753f3</guid><description>Dr. Reddy's Laboratories has achieved a significant regulatory milestone with the U.S. FDA accepting its Biologics License Application (BLA) for DRL-AB, a proposed biosimilar to Orencia® (abatacept). This marks the first such submission for an abatacept biosimilar, positioning Dr. Reddy's as a first-mover in the United States. The approval, expected to bring a cost-effective alternative for rheumatoid arthritis and other autoimmune conditions, underscores the company's growing capabilities in complex biologics and intensifies the competitive landscape for originator biologics.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:17:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69996a03730b6847a51753f2.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Rocked by US Tariff Ruling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Rocked-by-US-Tariff-Ruling/69996990730b6847a5175387</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Rocked-by-US-Tariff-Ruling/69996990730b6847a5175387</guid><description>The nascent India-US interim trade agreement faces significant headwinds following the US Supreme Court's invalidation of executive tariff authority. Indian opposition parties are demanding a renegotiation, citing risks to farmers and political motivations. While the US administration signals intent to reintroduce tariffs via alternative statutes, the ruling exposes the trade pact's structural fragility, amplifying concerns about its durability and India's strategic trade policy adjustments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:15:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69996990730b6847a5175386.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Stays Put: Liquidity Focus Signals New Policy Era</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Stays-Put-Liquidity-Focus-Signals-New-Policy-Era/69996849730b6847a517529f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Stays-Put-Liquidity-Focus-Signals-New-Policy-Era/69996849730b6847a517529f</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is expected to hold its benchmark repo rate steady at 5.25% through FY2026-27, signaling a prolonged pause. This strategy emphasizes proactive liquidity management and effective policy transmission over further rate adjustments. Bolstered by robust domestic demand and favorable trade agreements, India's growth outlook remains strong, projected to exceed 6.8% in FY27. While inflation is expected to rise from historic lows, it is anticipated to stay within the RBI's target band, suggesting minimal immediate pressure for rate hikes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:09:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69996849730b6847a517529e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Loan Restructuring: A Double-Edged Financial Tool</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Loan-Restructuring-A-Double-Edged-Financial-Tool/69996282730b6847a51750b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Loan-Restructuring-A-Double-Edged-Financial-Tool/69996282730b6847a51750b5</guid><description>Loan restructuring modifies loan terms, typically extending tenure to lower Equated Monthly Installments (EMIs) for borrowers facing temporary financial stress. While providing immediate relief, it inevitably increases total interest paid over the loan's life and flags credit records. Experts caution that it is ineffective for permanent income shortfalls, potentially only delaying inevitable defaults. Banks strategically employ restructuring to avoid Non-Performing Assets (NPAs), but borrowers must critically assess long-term affordability and recovery timelines.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:45:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69996282730b6847a51750b4_1771660346489.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bengaluru-Goa Vande Bharat Route Slowed by Terrain, Premium Speed Questioned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Bengaluru-Goa-Vande-Bharat-Route-Slowed-by-Terrain-Premium-Speed-Questioned/6999622b730b6847a5175046</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Bengaluru-Goa-Vande-Bharat-Route-Slowed-by-Terrain-Premium-Speed-Questioned/6999622b730b6847a5175046</guid><description>The planned Bengaluru-Goa Vande Bharat Express route is encountering significant speed restrictions due to the challenging Western Ghats terrain, potentially slowing the premium train to as low as 30 kmph on certain sections. This raises questions about its ability to deliver a truly high-speed experience and justify its premium pricing compared to existing slower services. While the proposal aims for a 13-hour journey, the operational speeds may fall short of passenger expectations and the train's design capabilities.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:43:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999622b730b6847a5175045_1771659951666.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Small Caps: Valuations Risk Amid Mixed 2026 Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Small-Caps-Valuations-Risk-Amid-Mixed-2026-Outlook/6999611c730b6847a5174f6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Small-Caps-Valuations-Risk-Amid-Mixed-2026-Outlook/6999611c730b6847a5174f6b</guid><description>Indian small-cap mutual funds navigate a pivotal 2026. While macroeconomic conditions, including supportive interest rates and strong GDP growth, provide a favorable backdrop, elevated valuations and a higher earnings miss rate among smaller companies introduce significant risk. Investors face a diverging landscape where historical performance contrasts with current market realities, necessitating a selective, quality-focused approach rather than broad category enthusiasm. Active management may offer an edge in discerning resilient opportunities within this volatile segment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:39:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999611c730b6847a5174f6a_1771659673308.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apollo Tyres FY25 ESG Rating 74.9; SES Assigns Voluntary Score</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apollo-Tyres-FY25-ESG-Rating-749-SES-Assigns-Voluntary-Score/6999609f730b6847a5174eec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apollo-Tyres-FY25-ESG-Rating-749-SES-Assigns-Voluntary-Score/6999609f730b6847a5174eec</guid><description>Apollo Tyres Ltd has announced its Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) rating of 74.9 for the financial year 2025. The rating was voluntarily assigned by SES ESG Research Private Limited, a SEBI-registered ESG Rating Provider. This disclosure underscores the company's increasing focus on sustainability and transparent reporting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:37:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999609f730b6847a5174eeb_1771659543542.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Senior Health Insurance: Standalone Plans Gain Traction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Senior-Health-Insurance-Standalone-Plans-Gain-Traction/69995b02730b6847a5174d5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Senior-Health-Insurance-Standalone-Plans-Gain-Traction/69995b02730b6847a5174d5f</guid><description>The Indian health insurance market is experiencing a significant shift towards standalone senior citizen policies, driven by persistent medical inflation and supportive regulatory reforms. While family floaters once offered a perceived solution, they are increasingly proving inadequate against escalating healthcare costs and specific elderly needs. Dedicated senior plans now offer better protection and tailored benefits, with children increasingly funding these policies for their parents, also leveraging tax benefits under Section 80D.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:13:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69995b02730b6847a5174d5e_1771658107748.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Autoline Industries: IndiaNivesh Fund Slashes Stake by 8.95% via In-Specie Distribution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Autoline-Industries-IndiaNivesh-Fund-Slashes-Stake-by-895percent-via-In-Specie-Distribution/69995830730b6847a5174c02</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Autoline-Industries-IndiaNivesh-Fund-Slashes-Stake-by-895percent-via-In-Specie-Distribution/69995830730b6847a5174c02</guid><description>IndiaNivesh Renaissance Fund has drastically reduced its shareholding in auto component maker Autoline Industries Ltd. from 10.57% to 1.62%, involving over 40 lakh shares. The transaction was executed through an 'In-Specie Distribution', a mechanism under SEBI regulations for Alternative Investment Funds. This significant stake reduction by a key fund investor comes amid recent legal challenges faced by Autoline Industries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:01:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69995830730b6847a5174c01_1771657384670.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coronation Fund Managers Crosses 5% Stake in ixigo (Le Travenues Technology)</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coronation-Fund-Managers-Crosses-5percent-Stake-in-ixigo-Le-Travenues-Technology/699955db730b6847a5174ac3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coronation-Fund-Managers-Crosses-5percent-Stake-in-ixigo-Le-Travenues-Technology/699955db730b6847a5174ac3</guid><description>Coronation Fund Managers Ltd., a South Africa-based asset manager, has acquired an additional 183,322 shares, or 0.04%, in Le Travenues Technology Limited (ixigo). This acquisition pushes its total shareholding in the Indian travel tech company to 5.03% of the equity share capital, crossing a key disclosure threshold. The move signifies continued institutional interest in ixigo's growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:51:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699955db730b6847a5174ac2_1771656771812.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Varvee Global's Stock Split: Turnaround Story or High-Stakes Gamble?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Varvee-Globals-Stock-Split-Turnaround-Story-or-High-Stakes-Gamble/699955d9730b6847a5174aad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Varvee-Globals-Stock-Split-Turnaround-Story-or-High-Stakes-Gamble/699955d9730b6847a5174aad</guid><description>Varvee Global Limited is executing a 1:2 stock split and a significant manufacturing expansion. While the company reports a dramatic financial turnaround under new management, with revenue surging nearly 80% and a swing to profitability, persistent concerns regarding long-term fundamentals and contrasting analyst ratings suggest a speculative growth narrative.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699955d9730b6847a5174aac_1771656797386.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Surges on Fear, But Fed &amp; Dollar Threaten Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-on-Fear-But-Fed-and-Dollar-Threaten-Rally/69995407730b6847a5174942</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-on-Fear-But-Fed-and-Dollar-Threaten-Rally/69995407730b6847a5174942</guid><description>Silver prices surged nearly 9% on February 21, driven by geopolitical tensions and a temporary dollar retreat. However, conflicting Federal Reserve signals and the dollar's potential resurgence introduce significant volatility, with analysts forecasting a wide trading range and tactical strategies advised. The metal's dual role as a safe-haven and industrial commodity creates complex price dynamics.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:43:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69995407730b6847a5174941_1771656310866.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VST Tillers Q3 FY26 Profit Surges 45%; Revenue Up 32%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VST-Tillers-Q3-FY26-Profit-Surges-45percent-Revenue-Up-32percent/69995406730b6847a517492b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VST-Tillers-Q3-FY26-Profit-Surges-45percent-Revenue-Up-32percent/69995406730b6847a517492b</guid><description>VST Tillers Tractors Ltd. has posted strong financial results for the nine months ended December 31, 2025 (9MFY26). The company reported a 31.6% increase in revenue to Rs 912 Crs and a significant 44.9% jump in net profit to Rs 100.7 Crs. Operational EBITDA margins also expanded notably. The company highlighted its strategic focus on expanding its tiller business, leadership in compact tractors, and global expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:43:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69995406730b6847a517492a_1771656317739.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RCI Industries gets BSE listing nod for 1.05 Cr shares post-NCLT revival</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RCI-Industries-gets-BSE-listing-nod-for-105-Cr-shares-post-NCLT-revival/699953f7730b6847a5174913</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RCI-Industries-gets-BSE-listing-nod-for-105-Cr-shares-post-NCLT-revival/699953f7730b6847a5174913</guid><description>RCI Industries &amp; Technologies Limited has received BSE's approval to list 1,05,26,315 equity shares of Rs. 10 face value. This crucial step follows the National Company Law Tribunal's (NCLT) sanctioning of JTL Industries' resolution plan, marking a significant stride towards the company's operational revival after its Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP). The company will now proceed to apply for trading approval.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:43:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699953f7730b6847a5174912_1771656305722.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gagan Infraenergy Subsidiary Buys 4.87% Stake in Jindal Steel</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Gagan-Infraenergy-Subsidiary-Buys-487percent-Stake-in-Jindal-Steel/69995383730b6847a5174881</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Gagan-Infraenergy-Subsidiary-Buys-487percent-Stake-in-Jindal-Steel/69995383730b6847a5174881</guid><description>Gagan Infraenergy Limited's wholly-owned subsidiary, Skyhigh Sustainable Limited, has acquired 4,97,09,952 equity shares, representing 4.87% of Jindal Steel Limited. The off-market transaction on February 20, 2026, was made under SEBI takeover regulations exemptions for promoter group entities, reinforcing existing affiliations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:41:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69995383730b6847a5174880_1771656175870.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Netweb Technologies India Secures 69 ESG Score for FY25</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Netweb-Technologies-India-Secures-69-ESG-Score-for-FY25/6999521c730b6847a5174794</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Netweb-Technologies-India-Secures-69-ESG-Score-for-FY25/6999521c730b6847a5174794</guid><description>Netweb Technologies India Limited has been awarded an ESG score of 69 for the financial year 2024-25 by NSE Sustainability Ratings and Analytics Limited. This rating, assigned by a SEBI-registered ESG Rating Provider, reflects the company's performance across environmental, social, and governance factors and is a key disclosure for investors focused on sustainable practices.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999521c730b6847a5174793_1771655813200.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Finsec Promoters Un-Pledge 49.3 Lakh Shares, Easing Promoter Overhang</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Finsec-Promoters-Un-Pledge-493-Lakh-Shares-Easing-Promoter-Overhang/69994f4b730b6847a5174663</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Finsec-Promoters-Un-Pledge-493-Lakh-Shares-Easing-Promoter-Overhang/69994f4b730b6847a5174663</guid><description>India Finsec Limited's promoters, Gopal Bansal HUF and Gopal Bansal LLP, have officially reported the release of a substantial 49,32,050 equity shares on February 20, 2026. This action represents 16.89% of the company's total share capital, significantly reducing the pledged promoter holdings and potentially easing overhang concerns for the stock. The total promoter shareholding remains at 55.98%.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:23:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994f4b730b6847a5174662_1771655128951.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCL Industries Promoters Boost Holdings via Open Market Buys</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCL-Industries-Promoters-Boost-Holdings-via-Open-Market-Buys/69994f47730b6847a517464d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCL-Industries-Promoters-Boost-Holdings-via-Open-Market-Buys/69994f47730b6847a517464d</guid><description>NCL Industries announced that key promoter group entities, Kalidindi Ravi and Kakatiya Industries Private Ltd, have acquired shares through open market transactions on February 19, 2026. While the acquisitions are marginal, they represent an increase in their respective shareholdings, signaling continued confidence from the promoter group in the company's future prospects.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:23:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994f47730b6847a517464c_1771655098286.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Treadmill: Big Tech's Spending Spree Risks Bubble</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Treadmill-Big-Techs-Spending-Spree-Risks-Bubble/69994c93730b6847a51744fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Treadmill-Big-Techs-Spending-Spree-Risks-Bubble/69994c93730b6847a51744fb</guid><description>The global push for Artificial Intelligence has companies locked onto an expensive 'treadmill,' compelling massive, non-negotiable capital expenditures for fear of obsolescence. While projections show AI driving significant economic growth and massive industry spending reaching trillions by 2026, a growing concern is the sustainability of these valuations and the concentration of power. The technology sector, particularly US mega-caps, showcases elevated P/E ratios, albeit with increasing investor selectivity. Meanwhile, sectors like India's IT services are already facing steep corrections due to AI's disruptive potential on traditional revenue streams. The accelerating pace and immense cost of AI development present significant systemic, geopolitical, and labor market risks, hinting at potential market corrections if tangible, profitable outcomes do not materialize at pace.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:11:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994c93730b6847a51744fa_1771654468029.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Central Bank of India Partners SBI Funds Management; ₹12.41 Lakh Crore AUM Access for Customers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Central-Bank-of-India-Partners-SBI-Funds-Management-1241-Lakh-Crore-AUM-Access-for-Customers/69994c04730b6847a5174478</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Central-Bank-of-India-Partners-SBI-Funds-Management-1241-Lakh-Crore-AUM-Access-for-Customers/69994c04730b6847a5174478</guid><description>Central Bank of India (CBI) has partnered with SBI Funds Management Limited (SBIFML) to offer its extensive range of mutual fund products to CBI's customer base. This strategic alliance will provide CBI customers access to SBIFML's substantial ₹12.41 lakh crore AUM and aims to diversify revenue streams for the public sector bank.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:09:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994c04730b6847a5174477_1771654252632.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBL Bank Appoints Jaideep Iyer as Executive Director, Rajeev Ahuja Retires</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBL-Bank-Appoints-Jaideep-Iyer-as-Executive-Director-Rajeev-Ahuja-Retires/699948bc730b6847a517431d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBL-Bank-Appoints-Jaideep-Iyer-as-Executive-Director-Rajeev-Ahuja-Retires/699948bc730b6847a517431d</guid><description>RBL Bank has announced a significant change in its Key Managerial Personnel (KMP). Rajeev Ahuja retired as Executive Director on February 20, 2026, after a decade with the bank. Jaideep Iyer has been appointed as the new Whole-time Director, designated as Executive Director, for a three-year term beginning February 21, 2026. The bank also updated its fair disclosure code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:55:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699948bc730b6847a517431c_1771653437889.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pashupati Cotspin Board Meets Feb 26 For Stock Split Proposal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Pashupati-Cotspin-Board-Meets-Feb-26-For-Stock-Split-Proposal/699947c7730b6847a5174283</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Pashupati-Cotspin-Board-Meets-Feb-26-For-Stock-Split-Proposal/699947c7730b6847a5174283</guid><description>Pashupati Cotspin Limited has announced a Board Meeting scheduled for February 26, 2026, to discuss and approve a proposed sub-division of its equity shares. This move, which requires shareholder and regulatory approvals, aims to increase share liquidity and affordability. An amendment to the company's Memorandum of Association is also on the agenda.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:51:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699947c7730b6847a5174282_1771653181024.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RPP Infra Secures Mega Orders, But Profit Margins Falter</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RPP-Infra-Secures-Mega-Orders-But-Profit-Margins-Falter/699946e1730b6847a51741de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RPP-Infra-Secures-Mega-Orders-But-Profit-Margins-Falter/699946e1730b6847a51741de</guid><description>RPP Infra Projects Limited announced substantial new work orders, boosting its total order book to ₹3,964 crore. The company secured a ₹205.89 crore contract for Chennai's Global Sports City and a ₹52.17 crore flood mitigation project. Despite this influx, recent Q3 FY26 results revealed a dramatic 95.15% year-on-year profit decline and an eight-quarter low operating margin of 1.00%, signaling execution and cost management challenges within a cautious infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:47:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699946e1730b6847a51741dd_1771652952892.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hi-Tech Gears: NCLAT Hearing Postponed, CIRP Stay Extended to April 20</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Gears-NCLAT-Hearing-Postponed-CIRP-Stay-Extended-to-April-20/69994660730b6847a517416d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Gears-NCLAT-Hearing-Postponed-CIRP-Stay-Extended-to-April-20/69994660730b6847a517416d</guid><description>Hi-Tech Gears Ltd has received a temporary reprieve as the National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) postponed its hearing scheduled for February 18, 2026. The tribunal has extended the interim stay on the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) until the next hearing, now slated for April 20, 2026. This continuation of the legal proceedings means the status quo is maintained, offering the company a further period of operational continuity amidst its insolvency resolution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994660730b6847a517416c_1771652814208.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Surges Amid Geopolitics, But Dollar &amp; Fed Cloud Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-Amid-Geopolitics-But-Dollar-and-Fed-Cloud-Outlook/69994507730b6847a5174071</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-Amid-Geopolitics-But-Dollar-and-Fed-Cloud-Outlook/69994507730b6847a5174071</guid><description>Silver prices jumped nearly 9% on February 21, driven by escalating geopolitical tensions and a retreat in the US dollar. However, underlying macroeconomic pressures, including a strong dollar and a divided Federal Reserve outlook, introduce substantial volatility. Analysts forecast a wide trading range, emphasizing tactical trading strategies amid conflicting market signals. Gold also shows strength, nearing $5,100 per ounce, indicating broader precious metal appeal.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:39:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994507730b6847a5174070_1771652473950.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emversity Secures $30M Series A for Skilling Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Emversity-Secures-30M-Series-A-for-Skilling-Expansion/699944fa730b6847a5174057</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Emversity-Secures-30M-Series-A-for-Skilling-Expansion/699944fa730b6847a5174057</guid><description>Emversity, an employability-focused EdTech platform, has secured $30 million in Series A funding led by Premji Invest, with participation from Lightspeed and Z47. This capital injection is earmarked for aggressive expansion across over 200 campuses and the introduction of new upskilling courses. The funding underscores investor confidence in Emversity's model of bridging the gap between higher education and industry demands, aiming to deliver job-ready graduates in a rapidly evolving skill-centric job market.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:39:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699944fa730b6847a5174056_1771652476283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Embraer's India Ambition: 200-Jet Orders Key to FAL</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Embraers-India-Ambition-200-Jet-Orders-Key-to-FAL/69993d2c730b6847a5173dbc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Embraers-India-Ambition-200-Jet-Orders-Key-to-FAL/69993d2c730b6847a5173dbc</guid><description>Embraer aims to establish a Final Assembly Line (FAL) in India, contingent on firm orders exceeding 200 regional jets. President and CEO Francisco Gomes Neto has indicated this threshold is critical for the venture's viability, with a potential 2028 rollout if orders materialize soon. In parallel, the company plans a 'completion centre' as an initial step if the primary target isn't met immediately. This strategic push leverages India's burgeoning aviation sector, projected to need at least 500 regional jets, positioning Embraer to serve both domestic and potentially regional markets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:05:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993d2c730b6847a5173dbb_1771650433280.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Microsoft Gaming Pivots to AI Under New CEO Asha Sharma</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microsoft-Gaming-Pivots-to-AI-Under-New-CEO-Asha-Sharma/69993d24730b6847a5173da3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microsoft-Gaming-Pivots-to-AI-Under-New-CEO-Asha-Sharma/69993d24730b6847a5173da3</guid><description>Microsoft Gaming has appointed Asha Sharma, formerly head of CoreAI, as its new CEO, replacing veteran Phil Spencer. This transition signals a strategic pivot towards leveraging artificial intelligence for operational efficiency and platform innovation, departing from Spencer's legacy focused on studio acquisitions and content expansion. Sharma aims to balance AI integration with creative integrity, emphasizing games as 'art crafted by humans' while navigating an increasingly competitive and saturated gaming market. Microsoft Gaming reported over 500 million monthly active users, but faces headwinds including revenue declines in its gaming division.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:05:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993d24730b6847a5173da2_1771650444747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IPO Surge Meets Market Caution: 2026 IPO Wave Faces Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Surge-Meets-Market-Caution-2026-IPO-Wave-Faces-Headwinds/69993c99730b6847a5173cf5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Surge-Meets-Market-Caution-2026-IPO-Wave-Faces-Headwinds/69993c99730b6847a5173cf5</guid><description>India's primary market is set for a robust IPO week, with eight new issues launching between February 23-27. However, this surge occurs against a backdrop of a cooling IPO market in early 2026, marked by lower listing gains and heightened investor selectivity due to volatile secondary markets and global economic uncertainties. Companies must now navigate stricter SEBI regulations and focus on realistic valuations to attract capital.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:03:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993c99730b6847a5173cf4_1771650331956.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BMW Eyes India EV Assembly: Cost Cuts vs. Luxury Rivals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/BMW-Eyes-India-EV-Assembly-Cost-Cuts-vs-Luxury-Rivals/69993c12730b6847a5173c5e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/BMW-Eyes-India-EV-Assembly-Cost-Cuts-vs-Luxury-Rivals/69993c12730b6847a5173c5e</guid><description>BMW Group is contemplating full local assembly for its Battery Electric Vehicles (BEVs) in India. This strategic pivot aims to leverage cost efficiencies and tariff advantages, accelerating electrification in a key growth market. The move follows the successful initial localization of the iX1 and seeks to enhance competitiveness against Mercedes-Benz and Audi, while navigating the rapidly evolving Indian luxury EV segment. Success will depend on scaling operations and managing component sourcing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:01:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993c12730b6847a5173c5d_1771650197258.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPI's Invisible Security Upgrade: Trust Boost for Digital Payments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/UPIs-Invisible-Security-Upgrade-Trust-Boost-for-Digital-Payments/69993712730b6847a5173b05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/UPIs-Invisible-Security-Upgrade-Trust-Boost-for-Digital-Payments/69993712730b6847a5173b05</guid><description>India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) is set for a significant security overhaul, aiming to make user sign-ups largely invisible by phasing out SMS-based verification. This strategic shift towards tokenized, back-end processes by the National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI) prioritizes enhanced fraud prevention and a smoother onboarding experience. The move is poised to further cement UPI's dominance in India's rapidly expanding digital payments market, projected to reach $10 trillion by 2026.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:39:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993712730b6847a5173b04_1771648876024.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Trade Pivot: Bilateral Gains vs. Global South Voice</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Indias-Digital-Trade-Pivot-Bilateral-Gains-vs-Global-South-Voice/69993473730b6847a5173a1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Indias-Digital-Trade-Pivot-Bilateral-Gains-vs-Global-South-Voice/69993473730b6847a5173a1a</guid><description>India faces a critical juncture in digital trade negotiations ahead of the WTO's MC14. Emerging details from interim FTAs with the US and EU suggest a potential departure from its long-held opposition to customs duties on e-transmissions and participation in WTO's Electronic Commerce Joint Statement Initiative (JSI). This strategic pivot aims to secure bilateral advantages but raises questions about its influence and commitment to developing nations' interests on the global stage.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:28:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993473730b6847a5173a19_1771648225143.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Brazil Pact: Securing Critical Minerals Beyond China</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Brazil-Pact-Securing-Critical-Minerals-Beyond-China/6999332c730b6847a5173923</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Brazil-Pact-Securing-Critical-Minerals-Beyond-China/6999332c730b6847a5173923</guid><description>Prime Minister Modi and President Lula finalized a memorandum of understanding on critical minerals, aiming to bolster India's supply chain diversification away from China. The agreement seeks to strengthen resource cooperation and advance strategic partnerships, targeting a significant increase in bilateral trade. This move is crucial for India's energy transition and manufacturing ambitions, leveraging Brazil's substantial mineral wealth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:23:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999332c730b6847a5173922_1771647922704.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Trade Tensions Persist Post-Court Ruling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Trade-Tensions-Persist-Post-Court-Ruling/699932ef730b6847a51738f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Trade-Tensions-Persist-Post-Court-Ruling/699932ef730b6847a51738f5</guid><description>Following a significant Supreme Court decision invalidating certain import tariffs, the US administration has swiftly implemented a new 10% global tariff under Section 122 of the Trade Act of 1974. This move maintains trade friction with partners like India, which is expected to bear the new levy, despite existing bilateral agreements and ongoing market volatility. The administration also confirmed that existing national security and unfair trade practice tariffs remain in effect, contributing to a complex and uncertain global trade environment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:22:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699932ef730b6847a51738f4_1771647914968.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rent vs. Buy Debate: Wealth Shift Amidst Rising Prices</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Rent-vs-Buy-Debate-Wealth-Shift-Amidst-Rising-Prices/69992e21730b6847a51737ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Rent-vs-Buy-Debate-Wealth-Shift-Amidst-Rising-Prices/69992e21730b6847a51737ad</guid><description>In India's 2026 property market, soaring home prices are increasingly outpacing salary growth, intensifying the rent versus buy dilemma. Changes in tax laws and robust returns from alternative investments are compelling a pragmatic re-evaluation, positioning renting not just as a lifestyle choice but a financially astute strategy for many. While property values climb, compressed rental yields and affordability concerns are reshaping wealth-building narratives beyond traditional homeownership.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:01:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69992e21730b6847a51737ac_1771646598000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>