<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:57:15 +0000</pubDate><item><title>RBI Approves ICICI Group Stake in Bandhan Bank Up to 9.95%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Approves-ICICI-Group-Stake-in-Bandhan-Bank-Up-to-995percent/698ca3fcfa94ce7dec49adcc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Approves-ICICI-Group-Stake-in-Bandhan-Bank-Up-to-995percent/698ca3fcfa94ce7dec49adcc</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has greenlit ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company, along with ICICI Bank group entities, to acquire a combined stake of up to 9.95% in Bandhan Bank. This approval, valid for one year, is contingent on strict adherence to regulatory norms including the Banking Regulation Act and SEBI guidelines. The move signals a significant potential shift in Bandhan Bank's shareholding structure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca3fcfa94ce7dec49adcb_1770824989304.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Neogen Chemicals Q3 PAT Crashes 63%, Auditor Flags NCD Covenant Breach</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Neogen-Chemicals-Q3-PAT-Crashes-63percent-Auditor-Flags-NCD-Covenant-Breach/698ca373fa94ce7dec499e56</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Neogen-Chemicals-Q3-PAT-Crashes-63percent-Auditor-Flags-NCD-Covenant-Breach/698ca373fa94ce7dec499e56</guid><description>Neogen Chemicals reported a dismal Q3 FY26, with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) plunging 63% YoY to ₹3.69 crore, despite a 9.2% revenue increase to ₹220.02 crore. Standalone PAT dropped 39%. A significant red flag emerged from the auditor's report highlighting non-compliance with debenture covenants and failure to maintain security cover for listed NCDs, raising serious concerns about financial health and risk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:42:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca373fa94ce7dec499e55_1770824823253.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dollar Industries Q3 Profit Dips 8% Despite Revenue Growth, Eyes Margin Stability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dollar-Industries-Q3-Profit-Dips-8percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-Margin-Stability/698ca2f0fa94ce7dec499b1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dollar-Industries-Q3-Profit-Dips-8percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-Margin-Stability/698ca2f0fa94ce7dec499b1a</guid><description>Dollar Industries Limited reported a challenging Q3 FY26, with operating revenue up 2.0% YoY to ₹3,884 million, but Profit After Tax (PAT) declined 8.1% YoY to ₹184 million. This marks a strategic shift, with management prioritizing profitability and operating leverage over aggressive topline growth amidst current industry dynamics. For the nine-month period (9M) FY26, however, the company showcased robust growth with PAT surging 21.1% YoY to ₹749 million on an 8.4% revenue increase. Key initiatives include a brand overhaul, new product launches, and a proposed merger of nine promoter group companies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca2f0fa94ce7dec499b19_1770824762961.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Star Housing Finance Profit Jumps, But Auditors Warn of Liquidity Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Star-Housing-Finance-Profit-Jumps-But-Auditors-Warn-of-Liquidity-Crisis/698ca2d1fa94ce7dec499a72</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Star-Housing-Finance-Profit-Jumps-But-Auditors-Warn-of-Liquidity-Crisis/698ca2d1fa94ce7dec499a72</guid><description>Star Housing Finance declared a Q4 FY25 net profit of ₹3.67 Cr. However, a limited review by statutory auditors raised serious concerns, including significant liquidity pressures, delays in salary payments, a vacant CFO position exceeding the statutory limit, and increased credit loss provisions. These findings cast a shadow over the reported financial performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:40:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca2d1fa94ce7dec499a71_1770824707773.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India's Export Push Faces Policy Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-Indias-Export-Push-Faces-Policy-Risk/698ca2b4fa94ce7dec4999a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-Indias-Export-Push-Faces-Policy-Risk/698ca2b4fa94ce7dec4999a7</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India MD &amp; CEO Tarun Garg has called for accelerated localization and enhanced global ambition for the domestic auto industry. While welcoming government policies and trade agreements, the strategy hinges on external factors and faces intensifying competition, potentially creating long-term sustainability challenges beyond current policy support.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:39:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca2b4fa94ce7dec4999a6_1770824583477.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Carraro India Surges on Strong Q3 Profit Growth, Capacity Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carraro-India-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-Growth-Capacity-Expansion/698ca2aefa94ce7dec49999f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carraro-India-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-Growth-Capacity-Expansion/698ca2aefa94ce7dec49999f</guid><description>Carraro India posted stellar Q3 FY26 results, with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 91% year-on-year to ₹281 million. Total income grew 27% YoY to ₹5,696 million, driven by robust domestic and export demand, particularly for agricultural and TBH axles. The company announced significant capacity expansion and is confident in exceeding its long-term revenue targets, underscoring a positive outlook fueled by growth in key Indian sectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:39:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca2aefa94ce7dec49999e_1770824645880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RRP Semiconductor Faces Auditor Scrutiny Over ₹12 Cr Dispute, Listing Appeal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/RRP-Semiconductor-Faces-Auditor-Scrutiny-Over-12-Cr-Dispute-Listing-Appeal/698ca232fa94ce7dec4996c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/RRP-Semiconductor-Faces-Auditor-Scrutiny-Over-12-Cr-Dispute-Listing-Appeal/698ca232fa94ce7dec4996c7</guid><description>RRP Semiconductor Limited's limited review report for Q3 FY26 flags significant concerns, including a ₹12 crore dispute with a subcontractor and ongoing recoverability issues with old balances. Auditors PAMS &amp; Associates drew particular attention to these matters, alongside the company's market share price disconnect from financial performance. A critical development is the ongoing appeal before the Securities Appellate Tribunal (SAT) concerning the revocation of listing approval for shares issued via preferential allotment, adding substantial regulatory and listing uncertainty for investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:37:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca232fa94ce7dec4996c6_1770824504352.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FY27 Budget: Fiscal Push for Long-Term Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-Budget-Fiscal-Push-for-Long-Term-Growth/698ca22afa94ce7dec4996bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-Budget-Fiscal-Push-for-Long-Term-Growth/698ca22afa94ce7dec4996bc</guid><description>Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman unveiled the FY27 budget, positioning it as the "first Budget of the second quarter of the 21st century." Key initiatives include a significant push in infrastructure, particularly waterways, to cut logistics costs. The budget also expands MSME definitions and introduces measures to foster export champions. Skilling is to be integrated into formal education, alongside the development of entrepreneurship hubs and regional medical centers. Fiscal projections estimate ₹44.04 lakh crore in gross tax receipts and a capital expenditure of ₹12.22 lakh crore (3.1% of GDP).</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:37:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca22afa94ce7dec4996bb_1770824499393.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Auto Sector's Record Output Masks EV Battery Execution Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Sectors-Record-Output-Masks-EV-Battery-Execution-Gap/698ca1cefa94ce7dec499578</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Sectors-Record-Output-Masks-EV-Battery-Execution-Gap/698ca1cefa94ce7dec499578</guid><description>India's automotive industry is celebrating record annual output approaching 31 million units in FY25, with exports also surging over 5.3 million units, driven by significant government Production Linked Incentive (PLI) schemes totaling nearly ₹44,000 crore for auto components and batteries. However, the ambitious push towards advanced manufacturing and electric mobility is shadowed by significant execution challenges, particularly in the nascent battery manufacturing sector, where only a fraction of targeted capacity has materialized, raising concerns about India's ability to integrate deeply into global value chains despite volume gains.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:35:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca1cefa94ce7dec499577_1770824405391.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Spotify Stock Surge Faces Scrutiny Amidst Growth Worries</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Spotify-Stock-Surge-Faces-Scrutiny-Amidst-Growth-Worries/698ca16bfa94ce7dec499557</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Spotify-Stock-Surge-Faces-Scrutiny-Amidst-Growth-Worries/698ca16bfa94ce7dec499557</guid><description>Spotify's stock surged nearly 15% following robust fourth-quarter earnings, driven by record user additions and tripled profits. However, a stark deceleration in projected premium subscriber growth for Q1 2026, coupled with persistent issues like high royalty payments to labels, underperforming ad revenue, and intense competition from YouTube, raises concerns about the sustainability of its valuation and long-term profitability. Recent price hikes may further test consumer price elasticity, creating a complex outlook for the audio streaming giant.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:34:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca16bfa94ce7dec499556_1770824398281.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI's Digital Push Aims to Revive SME Investor Trust</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/SEBIs-Digital-Push-Aims-to-Revive-SME-Investor-Trust/698ca11efa94ce7dec4993d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/SEBIs-Digital-Push-Aims-to-Revive-SME-Investor-Trust/698ca11efa94ce7dec4993d2</guid><description>SEBI is overhauling SME listing and disclosure rules, introducing a dedicated digital portal to simplify capital market access for small and medium enterprises. This initiative aims to boost investor confidence, which has been dented by past misuse of norms and persistent market hurdles. While SME platforms have shown growth, with over 1,400 listed firms and significant fundraising, recent performance has been mixed, prompting tighter regulations. SEBI seeks to balance growth facilitation with enhanced transparency and investor protection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:32:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca11efa94ce7dec4993d1_1770824324396.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Consumer Boom: PE Surge Amidst Broader Market Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Consumer-Boom-PE-Surge-Amidst-Broader-Market-Caution/698ca115fa94ce7dec49934e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Consumer-Boom-PE-Surge-Amidst-Broader-Market-Caution/698ca115fa94ce7dec49934e</guid><description>India's consumer sector experienced a four-year peak in private equity and venture capital investments during CY2025, reaching ₹35,800 crore across 309 deals, according to Equirus Capital. This surge is fueled by robust domestic consumption, a growing middle class, and attractive returns in segments like food, beauty, and D2C brands. However, broader PE/VC activity in India saw a slowdown in 2025 due to global uncertainties, and high valuations within the consumer sector are drawing increased investor caution. Despite these factors, India is poised to become the world's third-largest consumer market by 2026, supported by favorable macroeconomics, including low inflation and supportive interest rates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:32:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca115fa94ce7dec49934d_1770824435035.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>B. L. Kashyap &amp; Sons Reports Massive Profit Turnaround, Debt Slashed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/B-L-Kashyap-and-Sons-Reports-Massive-Profit-Turnaround-Debt-Slashed/698ca019fa94ce7dec498e04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/B-L-Kashyap-and-Sons-Reports-Massive-Profit-Turnaround-Debt-Slashed/698ca019fa94ce7dec498e04</guid><description>B. L. Kashyap &amp; Sons announced a significant financial turnaround for Q3 FY26. Revenue climbed 33.89% YoY to ₹323.87 Cr. Profitability surged with EBITDA up 364.15% to ₹28.87 Cr and PAT skyrocketing 955.36% to ₹11.83 Cr. The company also substantially reduced its fund-based debt from ₹700 Cr to ₹270 Cr and bolstered its order book to ₹5,293 Cr.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:28:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca019fa94ce7dec498e03_1770824035537.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zim Labs Q3 Rebounds; 9M FY26 Profits Plummet Amidst ₹35 Cr Fundraising</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zim-Labs-Q3-Rebounds-9M-FY26-Profits-Plummet-Amidst-35-Cr-Fundraising/698ca017fa94ce7dec498df6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zim-Labs-Q3-Rebounds-9M-FY26-Profits-Plummet-Amidst-35-Cr-Fundraising/698ca017fa94ce7dec498df6</guid><description>Zim Laboratories reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue up 12.8% YoY and PAT turning positive. However, the nine-month period (9MFY26) shows a significant decline in revenue, EBITDA, and PAT. The company is raising ₹35 crore via a preferential issue to Florintree Trinex LLP to fund expansion and registrations, while also progressing on CAPA remediation for EU-GMP compliance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:28:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ca017fa94ce7dec498df5_1770824006530.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apptronik Secures $935M, Valuation Soars to $5.3B Amid AI Robot Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apptronik-Secures-935M-Valuation-Soars-to-53B-Amid-AI-Robot-Race/698c9fa1fa94ce7dec498cbe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apptronik-Secures-935M-Valuation-Soars-to-53B-Amid-AI-Robot-Race/698c9fa1fa94ce7dec498cbe</guid><description>University of Texas spinout Apptronik has secured $935 million, pushing its valuation to $5.3 billion in a re-opened Series A. The funding round underscores intense investor interest in embodied AI and humanoid robotics. Apptronik's Apollo robot is designed for industrial tasks, leveraging partnerships with Google DeepMind and Mercedes-Benz to navigate a rapidly advancing and competitive market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:26:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9fa1fa94ce7dec498cbd_1770823889575.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eldeco Housing Secures ₹110 Cr Loan from Piramal Finance; Strict Covenants Apply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Eldeco-Housing-Secures-110-Cr-Loan-from-Piramal-Finance-Strict-Covenants-Apply/698c9f9ffa94ce7dec498cb6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Eldeco-Housing-Secures-110-Cr-Loan-from-Piramal-Finance-Strict-Covenants-Apply/698c9f9ffa94ce7dec498cb6</guid><description>Eldeco Housing &amp; Industries Limited has executed a Rs. 110 crore term loan facility agreement with Piramal Finance Limited. The loan, availed by the company and five subsidiaries, is earmarked for land acquisition and project expenses. Executed on February 11, 2026, the agreement features stringent security provisions, notably granting Piramal Finance the discretion to appoint a nominee director in case of payment default.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:26:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9f9ffa94ce7dec498cb5_1770823961398.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TPL Plastech Surges 22% Revenue, Boosts Margins on Efficiency Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TPL-Plastech-Surges-22percent-Revenue-Boosts-Margins-on-Efficiency-Gains/698c9f90fa94ce7dec498c19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TPL-Plastech-Surges-22percent-Revenue-Boosts-Margins-on-Efficiency-Gains/698c9f90fa94ce7dec498c19</guid><description>TPL Plastech reported a strong Q3 FY26 with revenue soaring 22.16% YoY to ₹1,112 Mn, driven by 25% volume growth. EBITDA and PAT climbed over 23% and 25% respectively, with margins expanding QoQ. The company is investing ₹15 Cr in automation and ₹5 Cr in solar power to enhance productivity and cut costs, aiming for ~20% CAGR growth over the next three years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:26:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9f90fa94ce7dec498c18_1770823894948.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GE Power India Surges on Massive Margin Expansion, PAT Turns Around</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GE-Power-India-Surges-on-Massive-Margin-Expansion-PAT-Turns-Around/698c9f4ffa94ce7dec498b74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GE-Power-India-Surges-on-Massive-Margin-Expansion-PAT-Turns-Around/698c9f4ffa94ce7dec498b74</guid><description>GE Power India posted a dramatic Q3 FY26 turnaround, with PAT shifting from a loss to a ₹716.8 million profit. Revenue grew 21.7% YoY to ₹3,856.2 million. Continuing operations saw EBITDA margins surge to 35.0% from 9.0% YoY, driven by operational excellence. However, the order book for continuing operations fell 38.3% YoY to ₹16,706 million due to contract terminations. The company is focused on core services and upgrades amidst ongoing business restructuring.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:25:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9f4ffa94ce7dec498b73_1770824031204.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AMD Industries Plunges into Deeper Loss as Revenue Drops 15%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AMD-Industries-Plunges-into-Deeper-Loss-as-Revenue-Drops-15percent/698c9f4dfa94ce7dec498b6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AMD-Industries-Plunges-into-Deeper-Loss-as-Revenue-Drops-15percent/698c9f4dfa94ce7dec498b6d</guid><description>AMD Industries Limited reported a grim financial update for Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue dropping 15.4% year-on-year to ₹3,798.40 Lakhs. The company's net loss widened significantly to ₹416.61 Lakhs from ₹169.15 Lakhs in the prior year, leading to a sharp decline in basic EPS to ₹(2.17). For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, revenue fell 5.5% and the company swung from a profit to a substantial net loss of ₹559.94 Lakhs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:25:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9f4dfa94ce7dec498b6c_1770823744185.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Carraro India Sees Profit Surge 91% on Strong Sales, Expands Capacity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carraro-India-Sees-Profit-Surge-91percent-on-Strong-Sales-Expands-Capacity/698c9ec7fa94ce7dec498866</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carraro-India-Sees-Profit-Surge-91percent-on-Strong-Sales-Expands-Capacity/698c9ec7fa94ce7dec498866</guid><description>Carraro India posted a stellar Q3 FY26 with PAT surging 91% YoY to INR 281 Mn, fueled by a 27% revenue jump to INR 5,768 Mn. EBITDA margins expanded significantly to 10.8%. For the nine months ended December 2025, PAT rose 38% to INR 889 Mn on a 21% income growth. The company announced a INR 623 Mn capex for axle capacity expansion, signalling confidence in sustained demand.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:22:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9ec7fa94ce7dec498865_1770823629490.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Draft Rules Target Bank Mis-selling, Dark Patterns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Draft-Rules-Target-Bank-Mis-selling-Dark-Patterns/698c9e3efa94ce7dec498604</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Draft-Rules-Target-Bank-Mis-selling-Dark-Patterns/698c9e3efa94ce7dec498604</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has unveiled draft "Responsible Business Conduct Amendment Directions, 2026," set to take effect July 1, 2026. These regulations target banks' advertising, marketing, and sales of financial products, introducing strict norms against mis-selling and deceptive practices like "dark patterns." Key provisions include mandatory comprehensive sales policies, clear definitions for direct selling agents, explicit customer consent for each product, and requirements for banks to refund and compensate customers in cases of established mis-selling. These directives aim to fundamentally reshape customer interactions and accountability within the Indian banking sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:20:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9e3efa94ce7dec498603_1770823505932.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Jobs Report: January Strength Masks Significant Growth Revisions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Jobs-Report-January-Strength-Masks-Significant-Growth-Revisions/698c9e3afa94ce7dec4985da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Jobs-Report-January-Strength-Masks-Significant-Growth-Revisions/698c9e3afa94ce7dec4985da</guid><description>The U.S. labor market added 130,000 jobs in January, surpassing expectations and lowering unemployment to 4.3%. However, a crucial annual benchmarking revision by the Bureau of Labor Statistics revealed job growth in the 12 months through March 2025 was nearly 900,000 lower than initially reported, signaling a substantial deceleration in underlying economic momentum. This divergence between a strong monthly headline and weaker historical data warrants careful investor scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:20:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9e3afa94ce7dec4985d9_1770823556170.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amara Raja Energy &amp; Mobility Charts US Expansion with $5M Subsidiary</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amara-Raja-Energy-and-Mobility-Charts-US-Expansion-with-5M-Subsidiary/698c9de7fa94ce7dec49851f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amara-Raja-Energy-and-Mobility-Charts-US-Expansion-with-5M-Subsidiary/698c9de7fa94ce7dec49851f</guid><description>Amara Raja Energy &amp; Mobility Limited announced the incorporation of a wholly-owned subsidiary in the United States, "ARE&amp;M US Inc." The company plans to invest up to USD 5 million to enhance customer service, establish a local presence for efficient delivery, and explore future localization, including manufacturing. This strategic move signals a significant push for global business expansion in the energy and mobility sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:19:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9de7fa94ce7dec49851e_1770823380572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Happiest Minds Posts 10.7% Revenue Growth Amidst AI Push, Margins See Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Happiest-Minds-Posts-107percent-Revenue-Growth-Amidst-AI-Push-Margins-See-Pressure/698c9dcffa94ce7dec4984e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Happiest-Minds-Posts-107percent-Revenue-Growth-Amidst-AI-Push-Margins-See-Pressure/698c9dcffa94ce7dec4984e9</guid><description>Happiest Minds Technologies reported a 10.7% YoY revenue increase to ₹587.6 crore for Q3 FY26, fueled by its AI First strategy. While adjusted profit rose 13.0% to ₹69.9 crore, reported PAT dipped 19.6% due to a ₹22.03 crore provision for the new wage code. EBITDA margins saw slight pressure, declining to 20.4% from 21.1% YoY. The company reiterated double-digit revenue growth guidance and plans to invest heavily in AI/GenAI, targeting a 1,000+ team by FY27. Operational utilization hit a recent high of 82%, but Days Sales Outstanding (DSO) increased to 92 days, with management prioritizing collections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:18:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9dcffa94ce7dec4984e8_1770823444880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Protean eGov: Growth Metrics Clash with Bearish Trends Amid CEO Exit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Protean-eGov-Growth-Metrics-Clash-with-Bearish-Trends-Amid-CEO-Exit/698c9dccfa94ce7dec4984da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Protean-eGov-Growth-Metrics-Clash-with-Bearish-Trends-Amid-CEO-Exit/698c9dccfa94ce7dec4984da</guid><description>Protean eGov Technologies posted a 13.1% revenue increase to ₹228.9 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by tax services and new ventures. EBITDA rose 31% to ₹46 crore, boosting margins to 19%. However, net profit saw a marginal 2.2% decline to ₹22.5 crore. The company maintains a strong balance sheet with zero debt and ₹800 crore in cash. The market reacted with a slight price dip, compounded by the recent resignation of MD &amp; CEO Suresh Sethi.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:18:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9dccfa94ce7dec4984d9_1770823465136.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mobavenue AI Tech Surges 107% on Q3 Profit, ₹100 Cr Fundraising</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mobavenue-AI-Tech-Surges-107percent-on-Q3-Profit-100-Cr-Fundraising/698c9d5cfa94ce7dec49839b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mobavenue-AI-Tech-Surges-107percent-on-Q3-Profit-100-Cr-Fundraising/698c9d5cfa94ce7dec49839b</guid><description>Mobavenue AI Tech Limited (formerly Lucent Industries) posted a stellar Q3 FY26 with consolidated PAT jumping 107.48% YoY to ₹760.83 lakhs on 67.17% revenue growth. The company completed a ₹50 Cr preferential allotment, declared a ₹0.50 dividend, and approved a further ₹100 Cr fundraising. This surge follows a strategic pivot to digital media and AI, with financial restatements impacting comparability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:16:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9d5cfa94ce7dec49839a_1770823267862.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Steel Q3 Profit Plunges 57% Amid Cotton Ginning Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bajaj-Steel-Q3-Profit-Plunges-57percent-Amid-Cotton-Ginning-Woes/698c9ccefa94ce7dec498128</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bajaj-Steel-Q3-Profit-Plunges-57percent-Amid-Cotton-Ginning-Woes/698c9ccefa94ce7dec498128</guid><description>Bajaj Steel Industries reported a challenging Q3 FY26, with revenue down 9.3% and PAT plummeting 56.9% YoY, largely due to its Cotton Ginning Machinery segment. However, diversified verticals like Infrastructure and Electrical Panels showed growth, bolstering the outlook. The company expects improvements in its core segment as clearances progress.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:14:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9ccefa94ce7dec498127_1770823175119.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Patanjali Foods Hits Record Revenue, FMCG Fuels Growth Ahead of FY26 Close.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Patanjali-Foods-Hits-Record-Revenue-FMCG-Fuels-Growth-Ahead-of-FY26-Close/698c9c6dfa94ce7dec497fe2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Patanjali-Foods-Hits-Record-Revenue-FMCG-Fuels-Growth-Ahead-of-FY26-Close/698c9c6dfa94ce7dec497fe2</guid><description>Patanjali Foods reported its highest-ever revenue in Q3FY26 at ₹10,483.71 crore, up 16.53% YoY, propelled by a 38.93% surge in its FMCG segment. The FMCG division now contributes significantly to EBITDA, while the Edible Oil segment, despite revenue growth, faces margin pressure. The company anticipates a strong FY26 close, leveraging favourable macro trends and its recent HPC acquisition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:12:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9c6dfa94ce7dec497fe1_1770823049968.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crompton Greaves Surges on 7% Revenue Growth, Enters Rs. 37,000 Cr Wires Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Crompton-Greaves-Surges-on-7percent-Revenue-Growth-Enters-Rs-37000-Cr-Wires-Market/698c9c6bfa94ce7dec497fdb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Crompton-Greaves-Surges-on-7percent-Revenue-Growth-Enters-Rs-37000-Cr-Wires-Market/698c9c6bfa94ce7dec497fdb</guid><description>Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals posted a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 7% YoY, driven by ECD and lighting segments. The company achieved a strong sequential revenue of Rs. 1,898 crores and saw EBITDA climb 18.5% with margins expanding to 10.3%. A significant strategic move includes entering the Rs. 36,000-37,000 crore residential wires market, aiming to become an end-to-end home solution provider. The solar business also showed considerable traction, with its rooftop segment booking Rs. 18-19 crores in Q3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:12:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9c6bfa94ce7dec497fda_1770823045838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>V-Guard Bets on Innovation Hub for Future Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/V-Guard-Bets-on-Innovation-Hub-for-Future-Growth/698c9c24fa94ce7dec497df7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/V-Guard-Bets-on-Innovation-Hub-for-Future-Growth/698c9c24fa94ce7dec497df7</guid><description>V-Guard Industries is injecting ₹200 crore to expand its new Kochi facility, anchored by a recently inaugurated innovation campus. This move signals a strategic pivot towards advanced R&amp;D and technology integration, aiming to bolster its product portfolio and capture higher value within India's robust consumer durables sector. The initiative is expected to generate approximately 400 high-skill jobs, reinforcing Kerala's standing as an electronics manufacturing hub and aligning with national 'Make in India' objectives. This expansion aims to fortify V-Guard's competitive edge through technological advancement, moving beyond traditional manufacturing capabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:11:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9c24fa94ce7dec497df6_1770822912810.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dollar Industries Q3 Profit Dips 8%, Realigns Strategy to Profitability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dollar-Industries-Q3-Profit-Dips-8percent-Realigns-Strategy-to-Profitability/698c9adcfa94ce7dec497a75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dollar-Industries-Q3-Profit-Dips-8percent-Realigns-Strategy-to-Profitability/698c9adcfa94ce7dec497a75</guid><description>Dollar Industries reported a mixed Q3 FY26, with PAT declining 8.1% YoY to ₹1,836 lakhs and revenue up a marginal 1.8%. Quarter-on-quarter, income dropped 17.7% and PAT slumped 47.8%, attributed to market competition and pricing pressures. Management announced a strategic pivot, prioritizing profitability and earnings quality over aggressive revenue expansion. Despite Q3 headwinds, the nine-month performance shows robust growth, with PAT up 21.1% YoY. The company is banking on its premium 'Force NXT' brand and expanding distribution channels for future growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:06:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9adcfa94ce7dec497a74_1770822799803.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashapuri Gold Ornament Posts Profit Surge Amidst Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ashapuri-Gold-Ornament-Posts-Profit-Surge-Amidst-Market-Volatility/698c9adcfa94ce7dec497a6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ashapuri-Gold-Ornament-Posts-Profit-Surge-Amidst-Market-Volatility/698c9adcfa94ce7dec497a6e</guid><description>Ashapuri Gold Ornament announced a robust 53% net profit increase to ₹17 crore for the December quarter, driven by higher gold prices and demand for its design-led B2B offerings. Income rose 6% to ₹247 crore, with EBITDA climbing 60% to ₹24 crore. Despite headline growth, the company navigates a market where elevated gold prices are impacting sales volumes across the industry, a challenge echoed by major players like Titan. Ashapuri aims to sustain growth by expanding its domestic market presence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:06:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9adcfa94ce7dec497a6d_1770822789607.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Advait Energy Q3 Revenue Soars 114%, Order Book Hits ₹1048 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Advait-Energy-Q3-Revenue-Soars-114percent-Order-Book-Hits-1048-Cr/698c9a7dfa94ce7dec4979df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Advait-Energy-Q3-Revenue-Soars-114percent-Order-Book-Hits-1048-Cr/698c9a7dfa94ce7dec4979df</guid><description>Advait Energy Transitions surged in Q3FY26, posting a 114% YoY revenue jump to ₹211 Cr, backed by a robust ₹1,048 Cr order book, up 132% YoY. The company secured its largest EPC order worth ₹216 Cr and is expanding into green hydrogen and fuel cells. However, consolidated EBITDA margins compressed to 11% (vs 15% YoY), a key point for investors to monitor amid strong growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:04:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9a7dfa94ce7dec4979de_1770822574187.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mobavenue AI Tech Q3 Profit Soars 107%, Revenue Jumps 67%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Mobavenue-AI-Tech-Q3-Profit-Soars-107percent-Revenue-Jumps-67percent/698c9a7cfa94ce7dec4979d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Mobavenue-AI-Tech-Q3-Profit-Soars-107percent-Revenue-Jumps-67percent/698c9a7cfa94ce7dec4979d8</guid><description>Mobavenue AI Tech Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26, with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 107.48% year-on-year to ₹760.83 lakhs on a 67.17% revenue increase to ₹5,512.11 lakhs. The company achieved a standalone turnaround, posting positive PAT and revenue after discontinuing prior operations. Key corporate actions included a ₹50 Cr preferential allotment and an interim dividend declaration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:04:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9a7cfa94ce7dec4979d7_1770822630549.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Exits Allianz JV, Q3 Profit Jumps 32%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finserv-Exits-Allianz-JV-Q3-Profit-Jumps-32percent/698c9a79fa94ce7dec49796d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finserv-Exits-Allianz-JV-Q3-Profit-Jumps-32percent/698c9a79fa94ce7dec49796d</guid><description>Bajaj Finserv Q3 FY'26: Exited Allianz JV, increasing group ownership to 97%. Consolidated profit surged 32% YoY (before one-offs) to ₹2,936 crore, driven by strong AUM growth and improved margins in subsidiaries like Bajaj Finance, Bajaj Life Insurance, and Bajaj General Insurance. Key one-offs included ₹1,406cr ECL provision by Bajaj Finance and ₹380cr Labor Code impact.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:04:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9a79fa94ce7dec49796c_1770822567293.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LG India Profit Drop: Margins Squeezed, Eyes Export Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Profit-Drop-Margins-Squeezed-Eyes-Export-Growth/698c9983fa94ce7dec497856</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Profit-Drop-Margins-Squeezed-Eyes-Export-Growth/698c9983fa94ce7dec497856</guid><description>LG Electronics India reported a 6.4% YoY revenue drop to ₹41.14 billion in Q3 FY26. Profit After Tax (PAT) plunged to ₹0.90 billion from ₹2.33 billion YoY, with EBITDA margins shrinking to 4.8% from 7.7%. Management cited lower demand, rising input costs, and currency headwinds. The company plans to double exports, leveraging its 'Make in India' strategy and a new plant, while focusing on premium and essential product lines.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:00:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c9983fa94ce7dec497855_1770822349118.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alembic Pharma Q3 Revenue Jumps 11% Amid Margin Squeeze &amp; One-Off Hit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alembic-Pharma-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-11percent-Amid-Margin-Squeeze-and-One-Off-Hit/698c98b5fa94ce7dec4976bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alembic-Pharma-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-11percent-Amid-Margin-Squeeze-and-One-Off-Hit/698c98b5fa94ce7dec4976bf</guid><description>Alembic Pharmaceuticals Limited reported an 11% year-over-year revenue increase to INR 1,876 crores in Q3 FY'26, driven by broad-based volume growth and ex-U.S. market traction. However, gross margins dipped to 72% due to product mix and pricing pressures. EBITDA grew 20% YoY, but a one-time INR 42 crore provision for employee benefits impacted reported PAT, leading to a 4% decline. Management highlighted a strategic U.S. shift and outlined growth drivers for India and international markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:56:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c98b5fa94ce7dec4976be_1770822059631.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Greenlights ICICI Group Stake Buildup in RBL Bank</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Greenlights-ICICI-Group-Stake-Buildup-in-RBL-Bank/698c983efa94ce7dec49737e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Greenlights-ICICI-Group-Stake-Buildup-in-RBL-Bank/698c983efa94ce7dec49737e</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has approved ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company (I-Pru AMC) and ICICI Bank group entities to collectively acquire up to 9.95% of RBL Bank's paid-up share capital. This regulatory nod, valid for one year, signifies substantial institutional interest in RBL Bank from a major financial conglomerate. The approval is subject to strict compliance with banking regulations and foreign exchange laws. Currently, the combined holding stands at 1.14%.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:54:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c983efa94ce7dec49737d_1770821878265.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sanathan Textiles Revenue Soars 32% QoQ Amid Expansion; Debt Reduction Noted</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Sanathan-Textiles-Revenue-Soars-32percent-QoQ-Amid-Expansion-Debt-Reduction-Noted/698c983afa94ce7dec497356</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Sanathan-Textiles-Revenue-Soars-32percent-QoQ-Amid-Expansion-Debt-Reduction-Noted/698c983afa94ce7dec497356</guid><description>Sanathan Textiles posted a robust 31.9% quarter-on-quarter revenue growth to ₹1,078.7 crore in Q3 FY'26, fueled by the Punjab facility's ramp-up. The company reported consolidated normalized EBITDA of ₹59.9 crore with a 5.6% margin. Management outlined ambitious targets for FY'27, including ₹5,700 crore revenue and double-digit EBITDA, backed by significant capacity expansions in Silvassa and Punjab. Notably, the company has reduced its debt, and the Punjab facility achieved EBITDA-positive performance this quarter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:54:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c983afa94ce7dec497355_1770821869856.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Approves ICICI Group's 9.95% Stake in IDFC FIRST Bank</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Approves-ICICI-Groups-995percent-Stake-in-IDFC-FIRST-Bank/698c980ffa94ce7dec49720a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Approves-ICICI-Groups-995percent-Stake-in-IDFC-FIRST-Bank/698c980ffa94ce7dec49720a</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has approved ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company Limited and group entities of ICICI Bank Limited to acquire up to 9.95% of IDFC FIRST Bank's paid-up share capital or voting rights. This regulatory nod comes with strict conditions, including compliance with banking laws and completion of the acquisition within one year. The aggregate holding must not exceed the 9.95% limit at any time. This approval marks a significant development in the bank's shareholder structure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:54:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c980ffa94ce7dec497209_1770821817387.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>