<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:59:04 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Aksh Optifibre Faces AED 41M Bank Demand Over Subsidiary Defaults</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Aksh-Optifibre-Faces-AED-41M-Bank-Demand-Over-Subsidiary-Defaults/698c7a9cfa94ce7dec490757</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Aksh-Optifibre-Faces-AED-41M-Bank-Demand-Over-Subsidiary-Defaults/698c7a9cfa94ce7dec490757</guid><description>Aksh Optifibre Limited disclosed receiving a demand notice for AED 41.34 Million (approx. ₹93.8 Cr) from Bank of Baroda, Dubai. The notice stems from loan defaults by its wholly-owned subsidiaries, AOL FZE and AOL Technologies FZE, for which Aksh Optifibre provided a corporate guarantee. The company is reviewing the notice and assessing legal remedies, with the maximum potential financial impact equaling the demanded sum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:48:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7a9cfa94ce7dec490756_1770814424873.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pioneer Investcorp Q3: Revenue Plunges 90%, Profit Soars Amidst Data Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Pioneer-Investcorp-Q3-Revenue-Plunges-90percent-Profit-Soars-Amidst-Data-Gap/698c7a60fa94ce7dec49067d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Pioneer-Investcorp-Q3-Revenue-Plunges-90percent-Profit-Soars-Amidst-Data-Gap/698c7a60fa94ce7dec49067d</guid><description>Pioneer Investcorp's Q3 FY26 results reveal a stark 90% year-on-year revenue plunge in standalone operations, even as net profit saw marginal dips. Consolidated income dropped 75%, yet profit before tax rose. The nine-month standalone figures show an even steeper revenue decline alongside a massive profit surge. Investors face a significant data gap, with balance sheet and cash flow details absent, and no forward guidance offered.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:47:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7a60fa94ce7dec49067c_1770814356245.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wonderla Chennai Park Opens; Q3 Profit Dips 29% Amid Launch Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Wonderla-Chennai-Park-Opens-Q3-Profit-Dips-29percent-Amid-Launch-Costs/698c7a23fa94ce7dec4905d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Wonderla-Chennai-Park-Opens-Q3-Profit-Dips-29percent-Amid-Launch-Costs/698c7a23fa94ce7dec4905d6</guid><description>Wonderla Holidays has launched its largest amusement park in Chennai, a ₹611 crore project. In Q3 FY26, revenue climbed 12% YoY to ₹141.5 crore, driven by higher ARPU. However, reported EBITDA fell 13% YoY to ₹32.17 crore and PAT declined 29% YoY to ₹14.5 crore. This was due to ₹8 crore in exceptional costs from new labour codes, ₹6 crore increased depreciation, and ₹5.5 crore in one-time launch expenses for the Chennai park.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:46:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698c7a23fa94ce7dec4905d5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pidilite's Domestic Demand Fuels 11% Revenue Growth, Exports Struggle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pidilites-Domestic-Demand-Fuels-11percent-Revenue-Growth-Exports-Struggle/698c79abfa94ce7dec4904c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pidilites-Domestic-Demand-Fuels-11percent-Revenue-Growth-Exports-Struggle/698c79abfa94ce7dec4904c9</guid><description>Pidilite Industries reported an 11% year-on-year revenue jump to ₹3,425 crore for Q3 FY26, driven by robust domestic demand and 9% underlying volume growth (UVG). While margins improved due to benign input prices, a ₹47 crore one-time charge impacted profitability. Exports declined 13.5% amidst geopolitical issues, though management anticipates a turnaround. The company remains focused on brand building and market share gains in key segments like waterproofing and tile adhesives.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:44:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c79abfa94ce7dec4904c8_1770814165744.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RSWM Ltd Q3 Profit Plunges 68% Amid Revenue Fall; Acquires PET Firm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/RSWM-Ltd-Q3-Profit-Plunges-68percent-Amid-Revenue-Fall-Acquires-PET-Firm/698c7953fa94ce7dec490259</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/RSWM-Ltd-Q3-Profit-Plunges-68percent-Amid-Revenue-Fall-Acquires-PET-Firm/698c7953fa94ce7dec490259</guid><description>RSWM Limited reported a challenging Q3 FY26 with consolidated net profit plummeting 67.9% YoY to ₹2.38 crore on an 8.7% revenue drop to ₹1,090.81 crore. Standalone margins compressed to 0.38%. However, the nine-month period saw a turnaround to profitability. The company also acquired LNJ GreenPet for ₹20.01 crore, marking an entry into the recycled PET resin business.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kirloskar Oil Engines Posts Strong Q3 Growth, Declares Interim Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kirloskar-Oil-Engines-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Declares-Interim-Dividend/698c78a8fa94ce7dec49007b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kirloskar-Oil-Engines-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Declares-Interim-Dividend/698c78a8fa94ce7dec49007b</guid><description>Kirloskar Oil Engines Limited (KOEL) reported a robust third quarter for FY26, with standalone revenue soaring 34.78% YoY to ₹1,380.61 Cr and PAT rising 32.74% to ₹86.32 Cr. Consolidated revenue grew 29.21% YoY to ₹1,872.60 Cr, with PAT surging 60.75% to ₹109.13 Cr. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹2.50 per share. An exceptional charge related to new labour codes impacted net profits, while its B2C water management business was classified as discontinued operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:40:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c78a8fa94ce7dec49007a_1770813955637.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JMJ Fin: PAT Jumps 51% Amid Revenue Slump, Audit Flags Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/JMJ-Fin-PAT-Jumps-51percent-Amid-Revenue-Slump-Audit-Flags-Concerns/698c784bfa94ce7dec48ffbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/JMJ-Fin-PAT-Jumps-51percent-Amid-Revenue-Slump-Audit-Flags-Concerns/698c784bfa94ce7dec48ffbb</guid><description>JMJ Fintech Limited posted a robust 51.7% year-on-year rise in Net Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹173.63 Lacs for Q3 FY26, driven by a significant margin expansion to 33.40%. However, total income from operations (Net) contracted by 27.6% YoY to ₹519.80 Lacs. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, revenue declined 19.2% YoY and PAT fell 12.8%. The company also approved the launch of its 'M/Money bro' digital lending app. An internal audit report raised concerns over decreased collections and increased administrative expenses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:38:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c784bfa94ce7dec48ffba_1770813829255.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ansal Buildwell Plunges into Loss, Subsidiary Faces Insolvency</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ansal-Buildwell-Plunges-into-Loss-Subsidiary-Faces-Insolvency/698c7847fa94ce7dec48ffb4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ansal-Buildwell-Plunges-into-Loss-Subsidiary-Faces-Insolvency/698c7847fa94ce7dec48ffb4</guid><description>Ansal Buildwell Limited posted a grim Q3 FY26, with standalone revenue plummeting 80.6% YoY to ₹166.59 lakhs, resulting in a net loss of ₹354.97 lakhs. The company also faces severe challenges with its wholly-owned subsidiary, Ansal Crown Infrabuild Private Limited, against which the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) has initiated Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP). Nine-month performance also shows significant declines, signaling deep operational and financial headwinds for the real estate firm.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:38:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7847fa94ce7dec48ffb3_1770813826408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Parsvnath Developers Q3 Loss Surges 376%, Auditor Flags 'Going Concern' Doubt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Parsvnath-Developers-Q3-Loss-Surges-376percent-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Doubt/698c7844fa94ce7dec48ff75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Parsvnath-Developers-Q3-Loss-Surges-376percent-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Doubt/698c7844fa94ce7dec48ff75</guid><description>Parsvnath Developers Limited has reported a staggering 376.55% year-on-year surge in its consolidated net loss for the third quarter of FY26, reaching ₹14,948.65 lakhs. The company's statutory auditors have explicitly raised a 'material uncertainty related to going concern', citing sustained cash losses, tight liquidity, and payment defaults. This development underscores severe financial distress compounded by extensive legal disputes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:38:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7844fa94ce7dec48ff74_1770813822293.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cosmo First Revenue Soars 28%, But Profitability Skids Amid Margin Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Cosmo-First-Revenue-Soars-28percent-But-Profitability-Skids-Amid-Margin-Pressure/698c774bfa94ce7dec48fd88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Cosmo-First-Revenue-Soars-28percent-But-Profitability-Skids-Amid-Margin-Pressure/698c774bfa94ce7dec48fd88</guid><description>Cosmo First Limited reported robust consolidated revenue growth of 28.31% YoY to ₹898.98 Cr for Q3 FY26. However, profitability faced pressure, with Net Profit remaining flat at ₹29.50 Cr. EBITDA margins compressed to 11.50% from 12.27% YoY, while finance costs escalated by 52.58%, impacting the bottom line.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:34:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c774bfa94ce7dec48fd87_1770813546260.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Updater Services Flags ₹230M Provision, Halts Avon Unit Amid Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Updater-Services-Flags-230M-Provision-Halts-Avon-Unit-Amid-Margin-Squeeze/698c7711fa94ce7dec48fcdf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Updater-Services-Flags-230M-Provision-Halts-Avon-Unit-Amid-Margin-Squeeze/698c7711fa94ce7dec48fcdf</guid><description>Updater Services reported a significant INR 230 million provision for receivables from its subsidiary Avon's logistics arm, forcing operations to halt. While its core IFM segment posted record revenue and a 14% YoY jump, the Business Support Services segment faced margin pressures due to strategic shifts. Management aims for 9-10% FY'26 revenue growth, with INR 2,053 million cash available for acquisitions, stressing the Avon issue is isolated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:33:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698c7711fa94ce7dec48fcde.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KOEL Reports Strong Profit Surge, Declares ₹2.50 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KOEL-Reports-Strong-Profit-Surge-Declares-250-Dividend/698c7613fa94ce7dec48f7b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KOEL-Reports-Strong-Profit-Surge-Declares-250-Dividend/698c7613fa94ce7dec48f7b7</guid><description>Kirloskar Oil Engines Limited (KOEL) posted robust financial results for Q3 FY26, with standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 54% year-on-year to ₹87.37 crore. Revenue from operations grew 35% YoY to ₹1,380.61 crore. Consolidated PAT rose 64% to ₹109.13 crore. The Board declared an interim dividend of ₹2.50 per share.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:29:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7613fa94ce7dec48f7b6_1770813217017.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Panabyte Revenue Surges 393% YoY, But Profit Plummets 94% QoQ</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Panabyte-Revenue-Surges-393percent-YoY-But-Profit-Plummets-94percent-QoQ/698c7612fa94ce7dec48f7b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Panabyte-Revenue-Surges-393percent-YoY-But-Profit-Plummets-94percent-QoQ/698c7612fa94ce7dec48f7b0</guid><description>Panabyte Technologies reported a staggering 393.45% YoY revenue increase to ₹1769.85 Lakhs for Q3 FY26. However, profitability took a severe hit with Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeting 94.17% QoQ to ₹21.11 Lakhs and PBT margins compressing to 7.36% from 23.53% YoY. The company is also assessing the financial implications of the New Labour Code, effective November 21, 2025, with no impact yet recognized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:29:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7612fa94ce7dec48f7af_1770813253985.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Panic Hits US Finance; India Focuses on Augmentation, Not Annihilation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Panic-Hits-US-Finance-India-Focuses-on-Augmentation-Not-Annihilation/698c75e9fa94ce7dec48f5c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Panic-Hits-US-Finance-India-Focuses-on-Augmentation-Not-Annihilation/698c75e9fa94ce7dec48f5c9</guid><description>On February 10, 2026, an AI-powered tax tool launch triggered a sharp sell-off in U.S. brokerage and wealth management stocks, with Charles Schwab, Raymond James, and LPL Financial experiencing significant declines. Investors reacted with anxiety over AI's potential to automate advisory roles and erode fee-based income. In contrast, India's financial sector views AI as an enhancement, emphasizing trust, accuracy, and regulatory oversight, suggesting a more nuanced integration strategy driven by distinct market structures and investor behavior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:28:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c75e9fa94ce7dec48f5c8_1770813204651.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>South West Pinnacle Exploration Hits Record Profit, Revenue Surges 29%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/South-West-Pinnacle-Exploration-Hits-Record-Profit-Revenue-Surges-29percent/698c756ffa94ce7dec48f496</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/South-West-Pinnacle-Exploration-Hits-Record-Profit-Revenue-Surges-29percent/698c756ffa94ce7dec48f496</guid><description>South West Pinnacle Exploration Ltd. has reported its strongest-ever Q3 FY26 and nine-month performance, driven by a 29.3% YoY revenue increase to INR 627 Mn and a 119.0% PAT surge to INR 92 Mn. EBITDA jumped 101.1% to INR 177 Mn, with margins expanding significantly. The company boasts an all-time high order book of INR 4,448 Mn, fueling confidence for year-end and Q4. Key strategic moves include entering underground drilling, progressing in Oman, and developing a Jharkhand coal block.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:26:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c756ffa94ce7dec48f495_1770813101029.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Diligent Media Faces Going Concern Doubt Amidst Sharp Losses &amp; GST Bill</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Diligent-Media-Faces-Going-Concern-Doubt-Amidst-Sharp-Losses-and-GST-Bill/698c752afa94ce7dec48f3e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Diligent-Media-Faces-Going-Concern-Doubt-Amidst-Sharp-Losses-and-GST-Bill/698c752afa94ce7dec48f3e4</guid><description>Diligent Media Corporation Limited has plunged into a severe financial crisis, reporting substantial losses and a sharp revenue decline in Q3 FY26. The company's statutory auditors have issued a qualified opinion and flagged a 'material uncertainty' about its ability to continue as a going concern, citing eroded net worth. Adding to the woes, a significant Goods and Services Tax (GST) demand of approximately ₹33.9 Crores has been levied.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:25:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c752afa94ce7dec48f3e3_1770812950886.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KOEL Q3 Revenue Surges 35%, Profit Jumps 61% on Strong Performance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KOEL-Q3-Revenue-Surges-35percent-Profit-Jumps-61percent-on-Strong-Performance/698c751ffa94ce7dec48f374</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KOEL-Q3-Revenue-Surges-35percent-Profit-Jumps-61percent-on-Strong-Performance/698c751ffa94ce7dec48f374</guid><description>Kirloskar Oil Engines Limited (KOEL) announced strong Q3 FY26 financial results on February 11, 2026. Standalone revenue grew 35% year-on-year to ₹1,380.61 Cr, with net profit rising 32% to ₹86.32 Cr. Consolidated revenue increased 29% YoY to ₹1,872.60 Cr, and consolidated net profit surged 61% YoY to ₹109.13 Cr. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹2.50 per share.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:25:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c751ffa94ce7dec48f373_1770813037309.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prashant India Plunges into Deep Loss Amidst Zero Revenue and Skyrocketing Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Prashant-India-Plunges-into-Deep-Loss-Amidst-Zero-Revenue-and-Skyrocketing-Debt/698c751efa94ce7dec48f36d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Prashant-India-Plunges-into-Deep-Loss-Amidst-Zero-Revenue-and-Skyrocketing-Debt/698c751efa94ce7dec48f36d</guid><description>Prashant India Ltd. has reported a staggering net loss of ₹267.35 lakhs for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, a sharp reversal from a profit in the prior year. Operational revenue evaporated to ₹0.00 lakhs, while expenses, heavily burdened by finance costs of ₹259.82 lakhs, surged dramatically. The company's equity remains deeply negative at ₹(2592.24) lakhs, signalling severe financial distress. An independent director has resigned.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:25:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c751efa94ce7dec48f36c_1770813012033.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Smartworks Expands Mumbai Footprint Amidst Fierce Flex Space Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Smartworks-Expands-Mumbai-Footprint-Amidst-Fierce-Flex-Space-Competition/698c7493fa94ce7dec48efcb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Smartworks-Expands-Mumbai-Footprint-Amidst-Fierce-Flex-Space-Competition/698c7493fa94ce7dec48efcb</guid><description>Smartworks Coworking Spaces has expanded its Mumbai portfolio to over 2 million sq ft with a new 182,300 sq ft lease in Andheri East. This move signals robust enterprise demand in the financial capital, a key market for the company. However, this expansion occurs within a hyper-competitive landscape where major players like WeWork India, Awfis, and Table Space are also aggressively scaling, raising questions about sustained profitability and market saturation amidst significant investment and premium valuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:22:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7493fa94ce7dec48efca_1770812831115.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRCON International Declares ₹1.20 Dividend Amidst Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IRCON-International-Declares-120-Dividend-Amidst-Profit-Slump/698c7458fa94ce7dec48eee1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IRCON-International-Declares-120-Dividend-Amidst-Profit-Slump/698c7458fa94ce7dec48eee1</guid><description>IRCON International Limited announced its Q3 FY26 results, reporting standalone revenue growth of 6.15% YoY to ₹1,965.35 Cr. However, standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) plunged 35.17% YoY to ₹91.18 Cr, with EPS down to ₹0.97. Consolidated revenue declined 16.87% YoY to ₹2,053.52 Cr, and PAT fell 47.19% YoY to ₹93.37 Cr. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹1.20 per share.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:21:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7458fa94ce7dec48eee0_1770812699710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Talbros Auto Q3 Surge: ₹220 Cr Revenue, ₹1000 Cr Order Book Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Talbros-Auto-Q3-Surge-220-Cr-Revenue-1000-Cr-Order-Book-Boost/698c7447fa94ce7dec48eea9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Talbros-Auto-Q3-Surge-220-Cr-Revenue-1000-Cr-Order-Book-Boost/698c7447fa94ce7dec48eea9</guid><description>Talbros Automotive Components Limited (TACL) posted a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 8% YoY to ₹220.4 crore and EBITDA climbing 12% to ₹39.8 crore, driven by demand and GST reforms. PAT rose 14% to ₹27.2 crore with improved margins. The company also secured new orders worth approximately ₹1,000 crore over five years, including substantial export and EV component wins, signaling strong future growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:21:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7447fa94ce7dec48eea8_1770812765991.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GPIL Charts Aggressive Growth: Mining, BESS, and Rs 25,000 Cr Vision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GPIL-Charts-Aggressive-Growth-Mining-BESS-and-Rs-25000-Cr-Vision/698c73a1fa94ce7dec48eb4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GPIL-Charts-Aggressive-Growth-Mining-BESS-and-Rs-25000-Cr-Vision/698c73a1fa94ce7dec48eb4a</guid><description>Godawari Power &amp; Ispat (GPIL) reported a robust Q3 FY26 with EBITDA margins climbing to 20% YoY, driven by a 46% surge in iron ore mining production and 15% growth in value-added steel sales. The company outlined an aggressive growth strategy, targeting INR 12,000-15,000 crores turnover by FY'28 and INR 25,000 crores by 2030. Key initiatives include doubling iron ore capacity, expanding pellet production, boosting solar power, and a significant entry into Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) manufacturing. Substantial capital expenditure of INR 2,000-2,500 crores is planned for FY26, with INR 2,000 crores +/- 200 crores for FY'27, backed by existing cash reserves and secured debt.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:18:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c73a1fa94ce7dec48eb49_1770812659394.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pioneer Investcorp Financials Raise Red Flags: Margin Anomaly, Data Inconsistency</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Pioneer-Investcorp-Financials-Raise-Red-Flags-Margin-Anomaly-Data-Inconsistency/698c737afa94ce7dec48ea5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Pioneer-Investcorp-Financials-Raise-Red-Flags-Margin-Anomaly-Data-Inconsistency/698c737afa94ce7dec48ea5c</guid><description>Pioneer Investcorp's Q3 FY26 results reveal a sharp 3.6% YoY revenue decline to ₹707.50 Crore and a 2.1% PAT drop to ₹756.36 Crore. However, the reported profit margin of 10.70% is inconsistent with these figures, suggesting a data anomaly. For the nine months, revenue fell 27.4%, but PAT surged 59.2% driven by an exceptionally high 64.18% margin, raising further questions. A major red flag is the consolidated net profit being identical to standalone figures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:18:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c737afa94ce7dec48ea5b_1770812629011.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ginni Filaments Q3 Profit Turns Around on 128% EBITDA Surge, But QoQ Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ginni-Filaments-Q3-Profit-Turns-Around-on-128percent-EBITDA-Surge-But-QoQ-Dips/698c736ffa94ce7dec48e9fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ginni-Filaments-Q3-Profit-Turns-Around-on-128percent-EBITDA-Surge-But-QoQ-Dips/698c736ffa94ce7dec48e9fe</guid><description>Ginni Filaments Limited has reported a significant profit turnaround for Q3 FY26, posting a net profit of ₹904.35 Lacs against a loss in the prior year. Revenue from operations grew 9.1% year-on-year to ₹8,201.83 Lacs, propelled by a substantial 128.2% surge in EBITDA to ₹1,527.98 Lacs, which widened the EBITDA margin to 18.6%. The nine-month period also saw robust growth, with revenue up 32.7% and EBITDA surging 178.1%. However, sequential results revealed a decline in revenue, EBITDA, and net profit compared to Q2 FY26, alongside an exceptional loss of ₹545.79 Lacs from the disposal of the Garment Division.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:17:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c736ffa94ce7dec48e9fd_1770812547489.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metropolis Healthcare Posts Stellar Q3 Results, Announces 3:1 Bonus Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Metropolis-Healthcare-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-Announces-31-Bonus-Share/698c736efa94ce7dec48e9f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Metropolis-Healthcare-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-Announces-31-Bonus-Share/698c736efa94ce7dec48e9f7</guid><description>Metropolis Healthcare Limited delivered a robust Q3 FY26, with group revenue surging 26% year-on-year to ₹406 crore and organic revenue rising 15%. The company reported a 52% year-on-year jump in Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹48 crore, excluding exceptional items, while EBITDA margins expanded by 280 basis points to 25% on an organic basis. Strategic shifts include focusing on high-quality B2B partnerships and exiting margin-dilutive businesses. The company reiterated its FY26 guidance for 12-13% organic growth and announced a 3:1 bonus share issue, reflecting strong financial health and future confidence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:17:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c736efa94ce7dec48e9f6_1770812510790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Refex Industries: Fund Deviation, IT Search, SEBI Fine Cast Shadow</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Refex-Industries-Fund-Deviation-IT-Search-SEBI-Fine-Cast-Shadow/698c7346fa94ce7dec48e8d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Refex-Industries-Fund-Deviation-IT-Search-SEBI-Fine-Cast-Shadow/698c7346fa94ce7dec48e8d7</guid><description>Refex Industries' Q3 FY26 CARE Ratings report reveals ₹18.21 crore in fund utilization deviations for vehicle loans, salaries, and equipment. The company also underwent Income Tax searches and its CMD, Anil Jain, received a ₹10 lakh SEBI penalty for UPSI communication. Additionally, Refex discontinued its power trading and refrigerant gases businesses during the quarter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:17:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7346fa94ce7dec48e8d6_1770812515075.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE IPO Greenlit: Valuation Surge Amidst OFS Structure &amp; Rival Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-IPO-Greenlit-Valuation-Surge-Amidst-OFS-Structure-and-Rival-Gains/698c72a6fa94ce7dec48e5fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-IPO-Greenlit-Valuation-Surge-Amidst-OFS-Structure-and-Rival-Gains/698c72a6fa94ce7dec48e5fe</guid><description>National Stock Exchange (NSE) has secured board approval for its long-awaited Initial Public Offering (IPO), slated for an Offer for Sale (OFS) structure. Unlisted shares have surged, reflecting an implied market capitalization of approximately ₹5.13 lakh crore. However, this move comes against a backdrop of mixed Q3 FY26 financial results and increasing competitive pressure from rival Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) in key derivatives segments. The regulatory hurdles appear cleared following a significant settlement with SEBI, but the OFS model raises questions about capital deployment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:14:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c72a6fa94ce7dec48e5fd_1770812344223.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gayatri Projects Exits CIRP, Faces 'Going Concern' Audit Warning</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gayatri-Projects-Exits-CIRP-Faces-Going-Concern-Audit-Warning/698c7264fa94ce7dec48e4c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gayatri-Projects-Exits-CIRP-Faces-Going-Concern-Audit-Warning/698c7264fa94ce7dec48e4c6</guid><description>Gayatri Projects has exited CIRP after a ₹750 crore OTS, becoming largely debt-free with a ₹5,500 crore order book. However, FY25 saw a ₹68.80 crore net loss and an eroded ₹1,472.91 crore net worth. Crucially, auditors flagged a material uncertainty regarding the company's ability to continue as a going concern.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:13:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7264fa94ce7dec48e4c5_1770812334942.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India EV Sales Climb 28% YoY, But Sequential Growth Cools</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-EV-Sales-Climb-28percent-YoY-But-Sequential-Growth-Cools/698c722afa94ce7dec48e2cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-EV-Sales-Climb-28percent-YoY-But-Sequential-Growth-Cools/698c722afa94ce7dec48e2cc</guid><description>Total Indian electric vehicle retail sales in January 2026 reached 2,19,109 units, a 28% increase year-on-year. While passenger vehicles surged 54.75%, three-wheelers and two-wheelers showed strong YoY gains but decreased from December's levels. FADA noted the growth is increasingly demand-driven, focusing on product-market fit and economics over subsidies, indicating a maturing market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:12:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c722afa94ce7dec48e2cb_1770812279531.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-UAE AI Pact: Beyond Ethics to Economic Power Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-UAE-AI-Pact-Beyond-Ethics-to-Economic-Power-Play/698c71b5fa94ce7dec48e1c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-UAE-AI-Pact-Beyond-Ethics-to-Economic-Power-Play/698c71b5fa94ce7dec48e1c5</guid><description>India and the UAE are enhancing their artificial intelligence collaboration, shifting focus from commercial gains to a human-centric approach emphasizing social welfare and ethical governance. A new MoU targets joint AI data centers and supercomputing projects in India, accelerating research and applications. While aiming for responsible AI, the partnership navigates complex challenges in ethical diversity, talent acquisition, and data governance, positioning both nations in the global AI race.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:10:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c71b5fa94ce7dec48e1c4_1770812140710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godrej Industries Q3 Sales Rise, But Margins Shrink; Standalone Sees Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godrej-Industries-Q3-Sales-Rise-But-Margins-Shrink-Standalone-Sees-Loss/698c7151fa94ce7dec48e03d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godrej-Industries-Q3-Sales-Rise-But-Margins-Shrink-Standalone-Sees-Loss/698c7151fa94ce7dec48e03d</guid><description>Godrej Industries (GIL) posted an 11% YoY consolidated revenue jump to ₹5,698 Crore in Q3 FY26, but operating margins compressed to 10.77%. Standalone operations reported a loss of ₹21.05 Crore against a profit last year, significantly impacted by margin compression and an exceptional item. The company also undertook subsidiary restructuring, including divesting Godrej Capital.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:08:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7151fa94ce7dec48e03c_1770812028877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dharani Finance Faces Auditor Red Flag Over Going Concern, Losses Widen</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Dharani-Finance-Faces-Auditor-Red-Flag-Over-Going-Concern-Losses-Widen/698c714cfa94ce7dec48e00d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Dharani-Finance-Faces-Auditor-Red-Flag-Over-Going-Concern-Losses-Widen/698c714cfa94ce7dec48e00d</guid><description>Dharani Finance Limited reported a wider net loss of INR 30.40 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, up from INR 23.04 Lakhs YoY, despite marginal revenue growth. Crucially, auditors issued a modified opinion, highlighting concerns over un-accrued interest on a substantial INR 200 Lakhs ICD and its potential impact on the company's Net Owned Funds, raising doubts about its viability as an NBFC and ability to continue as a going concern. This poses a significant regulatory risk for the company.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:08:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c714cfa94ce7dec48e00c_1770812110282.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apex Frozen Foods Surges YoY Profit, QOQ Profit Slips Amidst Exceptional Item</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Apex-Frozen-Foods-Surges-YoY-Profit-QOQ-Profit-Slips-Amidst-Exceptional-Item/698c7148fa94ce7dec48dfe3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Apex-Frozen-Foods-Surges-YoY-Profit-QOQ-Profit-Slips-Amidst-Exceptional-Item/698c7148fa94ce7dec48dfe3</guid><description>Apex Frozen Foods Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue up 14.54% YoY to ₹264.29 Cr. Net profit surged 4636% YoY to ₹10.09 Cr, reversing a year-ago loss. However, QoQ profit declined 15% to ₹10.09 Cr, and EPS dipped sequentially. The company recorded an exceptional item of ₹2.53 Cr. Nine-month financials show strong YoY growth in revenue and profit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:08:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7148fa94ce7dec48dfe2_1770812044757.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shringar House of Mangalsutra Q4 Revenue Soars 68%, Profit Growth Mixed Amid Margin Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shringar-House-of-Mangalsutra-Q4-Revenue-Soars-68percent-Profit-Growth-Mixed-Amid-Margin-Shift/698c7141fa94ce7dec48dfda</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shringar-House-of-Mangalsutra-Q4-Revenue-Soars-68percent-Profit-Growth-Mixed-Amid-Margin-Shift/698c7141fa94ce7dec48dfda</guid><description>Shringar House of Mangalsutra reported a strong Q4 FY25 with revenue leaping 68.37% YoY to ₹658.86 crore and PBT surging 138.29%. PAT grew 77.61%. However, for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, while revenue rose 41% YoY to ₹1,520.26 crore, PAT growth was a more subdued 15.77%, with PAT margins contracting to 3.12%. A significant increase in 'Other Income' in Q4 FY25 warrants attention.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:08:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c7141fa94ce7dec48dfd9_1770812017920.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indus Fila Posts Catastrophic Zero Revenue, Skyrocketing Losses in Q3</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indus-Fila-Posts-Catastrophic-Zero-Revenue-Skyrocketing-Losses-in-Q3/698c70bafa94ce7dec48ddf9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indus-Fila-Posts-Catastrophic-Zero-Revenue-Skyrocketing-Losses-in-Q3/698c70bafa94ce7dec48ddf9</guid><description>Indus Fila Limited has reported a dire financial state for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company declared zero revenue from operations for both periods, with total income solely from 'Other Income' amounting to ₹0 lakh. This operational paralysis has led to a significant surge in net losses, with Q3 FY26 witnessing a loss of ₹89.74 lakh, a sharp increase from the previous year. Total expenses have also risen, exacerbating the financial strain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:06:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c70bafa94ce7dec48ddf8_1770811860519.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apex Frozen Foods Q3 Profit Soars YoY, But QoQ Dip Raises Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Apex-Frozen-Foods-Q3-Profit-Soars-YoY-But-QoQ-Dip-Raises-Concerns/698c705cfa94ce7dec48dd71</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Apex-Frozen-Foods-Q3-Profit-Soars-YoY-But-QoQ-Dip-Raises-Concerns/698c705cfa94ce7dec48dd71</guid><description>Apex Frozen Foods Ltd. reported a strong turnaround in Q3 FY26, swinging to a net profit of ₹10.09 Cr from a loss of ₹0.22 Cr in the previous year, driven by a 14.53% YoY revenue increase to ₹264.29 Cr. The nine-month period saw a remarkable 15163% surge in net profit to ₹310.61 Cr. However, sequential profit dipped 15.01% QoQ. Export benefits of ₹12.44 Cr were recognized in Q3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:04:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c705cfa94ce7dec48dd70_1770811749978.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>V. B. Industries Turns Profitable on Other Income, Operations Nil</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/V-B-Industries-Turns-Profitable-on-Other-Income-Operations-Nil/698c6fdbfa94ce7dec48db94</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/V-B-Industries-Turns-Profitable-on-Other-Income-Operations-Nil/698c6fdbfa94ce7dec48db94</guid><description>V. B. Industries Limited reported a turnaround to profitability in Q3 FY26, with a Net Profit of ₹36.24 Lakhs, up from a loss of ₹21.38 Lakhs in Q3 FY25. However, this profit was solely driven by 'Other Income' of ₹53 Lakhs, as Revenue from Operations remained nil for the third consecutive quarter and nine months. Total expenses were slashed by 96.35% YoY.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:02:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c6fdbfa94ce7dec48db93_1770811674665.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sahyadri Industries Q3 Profit Soars 554%, Eyes Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sahyadri-Industries-Q3-Profit-Soars-554percent-Eyes-Expansion/698c6f6ffa94ce7dec48d982</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sahyadri-Industries-Q3-Profit-Soars-554percent-Eyes-Expansion/698c6f6ffa94ce7dec48d982</guid><description>Sahyadri Industries reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with net profit surging 553.95% year-on-year to ₹4.97 crore on an 11.14% revenue increase to ₹144.16 crore. For the nine-month period, net profit rose 21.54% to ₹18.45 crore. The company is actively expanding with new manufacturing units planned in Odisha and Maharashtra.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:00:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c6f6ffa94ce7dec48d981_1770811647105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dharani Finance Posts Loss, Auditor Questions NBFC Survival</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Dharani-Finance-Posts-Loss-Auditor-Questions-NBFC-Survival/698c6ef6fa94ce7dec48d782</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Dharani-Finance-Posts-Loss-Auditor-Questions-NBFC-Survival/698c6ef6fa94ce7dec48d782</guid><description>Dharani Finance Limited reported a net loss of ₹30.40 Lakhs for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, a sharp reversal from the prior year's profit. Auditors Srivatsan &amp; Associates issued a modified opinion, highlighting a ₹2 Crore unrecovered Inter-Corporate Deposit (ICD) and its impact on Reserve Bank of India (RBI) norms. This raises substantial doubt on the company's ability to continue as a Non-Banking Financial Company (NBFC) and as a going concern, depending critically on future capital infusion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:58:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c6ef6fa94ce7dec48d781_1770811440963.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Elgi Equipments Q3 Profit Lags Revenue Growth, Exceptional Charge Hits Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Elgi-Equipments-Q3-Profit-Lags-Revenue-Growth-Exceptional-Charge-Hits-Margins/698c6e97fa94ce7dec48d750</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Elgi-Equipments-Q3-Profit-Lags-Revenue-Growth-Exceptional-Charge-Hits-Margins/698c6e97fa94ce7dec48d750</guid><description>Elgi Equipments posted robust Q3 FY26 revenue growth of 21.66% standalone and 18.38% consolidated. However, net profit growth was curtailed, rising 12% standalone and 18.11% consolidated, largely due to an exceptional charge of ₹128 Mn (standalone) and ₹150 Mn (consolidated) stemming from the implementation of new Labour Codes. Standalone Q3 PAT margins saw compression, falling to 14.81% from 16.09% year-on-year.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:57:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c6e97fa94ce7dec48d74f_1770811395353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>