<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:21:23 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's GIFT City Poaches Global Billions! Is it the Next Dubai?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-GIFT-City-Poaches-Global-Billions-Is-it-the-Next-Dubai/6954e9f14342f77179edff6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-GIFT-City-Poaches-Global-Billions-Is-it-the-Next-Dubai/6954e9f14342f77179edff6d</guid><description>India's GIFT City is rapidly becoming a major international financial hub, attracting global capital and Non-Resident Indians (NRIs) onshore. Offering competitive tax exemptions, regulatory certainty, and the ability to conduct transactions in US dollars, it aims to rival established centers like Singapore and Dubai. This initiative is fostering new financial services, creating high-value jobs, and positioning India as a significant player in global finance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:09:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954e9f14342f77179edff6c_1767172669930.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tamil Nadu Supercharges EV Future: 100% Tax Exemption Extended to 2027!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tamil-Nadu-Supercharges-EV-Future-100percent-Tax-Exemption-Extended-to-2027/6954ea274342f77179edfffd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tamil-Nadu-Supercharges-EV-Future-100percent-Tax-Exemption-Extended-to-2027/6954ea274342f77179edfffd</guid><description>Tamil Nadu has extended its 100% motor vehicle tax exemption for all battery-operated electric vehicles (EVs) until December 31, 2027. Announced by Industries Minister TRB Rajaa, this pro-industry move by Chief Minister M K Stalin aims to boost EV adoption, improve affordability for consumers, and provide long-term certainty for manufacturers, reinforcing the state's commitment to sustainability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 09:09:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954ea274342f77179edfffc_1767172727768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lemon Tree Hotels Set for Explosive Growth? Mirae Asset Sharekhan Sees 29% Upside!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Lemon-Tree-Hotels-Set-for-Explosive-Growth-Mirae-Asset-Sharekhan-Sees-29percent-Upside/6954e6354342f77179edf5b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Lemon-Tree-Hotels-Set-for-Explosive-Growth-Mirae-Asset-Sharekhan-Sees-29percent-Upside/6954e6354342f77179edf5b2</guid><description>Mirae Asset Sharekhan is bullish on Lemon Tree Hotels, projecting double-digit growth driven by aggressive room additions, favourable industry tailwinds, and an asset-light model. The company reported 13% revenue and 10% Ebitda growth in H1FY26. For Q3, mid-teens revenue growth and 12-15% RevPAR growth are expected. Long-term forecasts include 13% revenue and 29% PAT CAGR over FY25-28, with a 29% potential upside from current levels.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954e6354342f77179edf5b1_1767171825678.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Uttar Pradesh Bets on Hybrids, Metros Sprint Ahead in EVs: India's Green Mobility Divide Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Uttar-Pradesh-Bets-on-Hybrids-Metros-Sprint-Ahead-in-EVs-Indias-Green-Mobility-Divide-Revealed/6954e5834342f77179edf210</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Uttar-Pradesh-Bets-on-Hybrids-Metros-Sprint-Ahead-in-EVs-Indias-Green-Mobility-Divide-Revealed/6954e5834342f77179edf210</guid><description>India's green mobility journey shows a clear regional divide. While Delhi, Karnataka, and Chandigarh are leading the charge in electric vehicle (EV) adoption, Uttar Pradesh is emerging as the country's largest market for hybrid cars. This trend is driven by state-specific policies, like tax waivers in UP, and varying consumer preferences across different regions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:48:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954e5834342f77179edf20f_1767171609977.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unleashes Rs 4,531 Crore Export Blitz: New Mission to Conquer Global Markets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Unleashes-Rs-4531-Crore-Export-Blitz-New-Mission-to-Conquer-Global-Markets/6954e4f94342f77179edf0a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Unleashes-Rs-4531-Crore-Export-Blitz-New-Mission-to-Conquer-Global-Markets/6954e4f94342f77179edf0a5</guid><description>The Indian government has unveiled key guidelines for its Export Promotion Mission (EPM), backed by a significant Rs 4,531 crore allocation for Market Access Support (MAS) between 2025-26 and 2030-31. This initiative aims to boost the global competitiveness of Indian exporters by funding their participation in international trade fairs, exhibitions, and buyer-seller meets, with enhanced support for priority sectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:48:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954e4f94342f77179edf0a4_1767171391790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Omaxe MD Mohit Goel Unpacks 2025's Winning Strategy: Consolidation &amp; Explosive Growth Blueprint Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Omaxe-MD-Mohit-Goel-Unpacks-2025s-Winning-Strategy-Consolidation-and-Explosive-Growth-Blueprint-Revealed/6954e38e4342f77179edec82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Omaxe-MD-Mohit-Goel-Unpacks-2025s-Winning-Strategy-Consolidation-and-Explosive-Growth-Blueprint-Revealed/6954e38e4342f77179edec82</guid><description>Omaxe Ltd.'s MD, Mohit Goel, states 2025 was about consolidation and disciplined growth in India's real estate. Despite market challenges like rising costs and cautious financing, demand remained strong in mid and premium segments, driven by genuine users. Omaxe focused on integrated townships in Tier 2 cities and its BeTogether platform for infrastructure-led development, planning further expansion in Tier 1 and Tier 2/3 hubs. The company emphasizes community-focused, amenity-rich environments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:42:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954e38e4342f77179edec81_1767171060693.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Oil Stocks EXPLODE: Gas Index Surges 3%, HPCL &amp; BPCL Hit Record Highs! What's Fueling This Rally?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indian-Oil-Stocks-EXPLODE-Gas-Index-Surges-3percent-HPCL-and-BPCL-Hit-Record-Highs-Whats-Fueling-This-Rally/6954e06d4342f77179ede4b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indian-Oil-Stocks-EXPLODE-Gas-Index-Surges-3percent-HPCL-and-BPCL-Hit-Record-Highs-Whats-Fueling-This-Rally/6954e06d4342f77179ede4b8</guid><description>India's Oil &amp; Gas index soared nearly 3% today, driven by a healthy business outlook and improved refining margins. Hindustan Petroleum Corporation (HPCL) and Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) surged up to 6%, hitting fresh 52-week highs. Indian Oil Corporation (IOC) and Oil India also saw significant gains, boosted by strong domestic demand projections and falling crude oil prices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:21:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954e06d4342f77179ede4b7_1767170231491.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Blasts Past 26,150, Sensex Soars 600+ Points! What's Driving This Monumental Year-End Rally?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Blasts-Past-26150-Sensex-Soars-600-Points-Whats-Driving-This-Monumental-Year-End-Rally/6954e0bf4342f77179ede578</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Blasts-Past-26150-Sensex-Soars-600-Points-Whats-Driving-This-Monumental-Year-End-Rally/6954e0bf4342f77179ede578</guid><description>India's benchmark indices, Nifty and Sensex, closed calendar year 2025 at record highs, with Nifty touching 26,156 and Sensex reaching 85,313. The rally was fueled by strong performances in oil marketing companies and metal stocks, alongside broad-based buying across the market. This marks the tenth consecutive year of gains for both indices. Analysts maintain a positive outlook for 2026, anticipating earnings growth, favorable fiscal and monetary policies, and easing geopolitical risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:21:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954e0bf4342f77179ede577_1767170404562.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Data Centre Boom: $80 Billion Needed by 2030 as AI &amp; Cloud Demand Skyrockets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Data-Centre-Boom-80-Billion-Needed-by-2030-as-AI-and-Cloud-Demand-Skyrockets/6954df084342f77179ede044</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Data-Centre-Boom-80-Billion-Needed-by-2030-as-AI-and-Cloud-Demand-Skyrockets/6954df084342f77179ede044</guid><description>India's data center sector is poised for massive growth, requiring an estimated $70–80 billion in investment by 2030 to meet escalating demand for cloud computing and artificial intelligence (AI). Industry leaders predict current capacity will need to double, creating significant opportunities for companies like Anant Raj and Yotta Data Services across infrastructure, co-location, and cloud services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:21:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954df084342f77179ede043_1767170098873.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Prices SHOCKER: Record Rally REVERSED! Expert Advice for Investors Amidst Dramatic Crash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Prices-SHOCKER-Record-Rally-REVERSED-Expert-Advice-for-Investors-Amidst-Dramatic-Crash/6954df1e4342f77179ede0fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Prices-SHOCKER-Record-Rally-REVERSED-Expert-Advice-for-Investors-Amidst-Dramatic-Crash/6954df1e4342f77179ede0fd</guid><description>Silver prices have experienced a sharp and sudden crash globally and in India, following one of the strongest rallies in recent years. Experts attribute this steep pullback to factors like higher margin requirements, forced selling, year-end tax harvesting, and thin liquidity, rather than a fundamental shift. While short-term volatility is expected, the long-term outlook for silver remains constructive due to industrial demand and supply constraints, with advice leaning towards gradual accumulation on dips for patient investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:18:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954df1e4342f77179ede0fc_1767170059033.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Insurance Sector Snapshot: Health Dominates, Growth Cools in FY25!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Sector-Snapshot-Health-Dominates-Growth-Cools-in-FY25/6954df124342f77179ede0a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Sector-Snapshot-Health-Dominates-Growth-Cools-in-FY25/6954df124342f77179ede0a2</guid><description>Health insurance led India's non-life insurance sector in fiscal year 2024-25, capturing 41.42% of total premiums. Despite its leading position, the segment's growth rate slowed significantly to 9.19%, down from 19.50% in the previous year. Motor insurance followed as the second-largest segment, growing 7.97% to Rs 99,093 crore. The Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority of India's report indicates moderated overall growth despite rising medical costs and increased awareness.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:17:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954df124342f77179ede0a1_1767169999189.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Plastic Out, Glass In: India's Kitchenware Giants Chase Profit via Health Trend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Plastic-Out-Glass-In-Indias-Kitchenware-Giants-Chase-Profit-via-Health-Trend/6954de074342f77179eddd82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Plastic-Out-Glass-In-Indias-Kitchenware-Giants-Chase-Profit-via-Health-Trend/6954de074342f77179eddd82</guid><description>Indian kitchenware companies are pushing consumers to switch from plastic to glass, citing health and premium lifestyle trends. While glass offers higher profit margins, companies like Borosil Ltd and Cello World Ltd face manufacturing and adoption challenges. Despite revenue growth, profitability in the glass segment is a key focus, with recent stock performance showing declines across the sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 08:16:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954de074342f77179eddd81_1767169771596.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Share India Securities Raises ₹35 Cr Via NCDs; Unveils New Subsidiary Amidst Mixed Financials!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Share-India-Securities-Raises-35-Cr-Via-NCDs-Unveils-New-Subsidiary-Amidst-Mixed-Financials/6954dcdd4342f77179edd9e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Share-India-Securities-Raises-35-Cr-Via-NCDs-Unveils-New-Subsidiary-Amidst-Mixed-Financials/6954dcdd4342f77179edd9e4</guid><description>Share India Securities Limited has approved the allotment of Secured Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) worth ₹35 crore. The company also incorporated a new wholly-owned subsidiary, Share India Wealth Multiplier Solutions Private Limited. This comes as the company reported a year-on-year decline in H1FY26 revenue and profit after tax, though Q2FY26 showed sequential growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:52:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954dcdd4342f77179edd9e3_1767169358221.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quyosh Energia Buys Big in KPI Green Energy, Shares Skyrocket 8%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Quyosh-Energia-Buys-Big-in-KPI-Green-Energy-Shares-Skyrocket-8percent/6954dc014342f77179edd6af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Quyosh-Energia-Buys-Big-in-KPI-Green-Energy-Shares-Skyrocket-8percent/6954dc014342f77179edd6af</guid><description>Quyosh Energia has acquired over 11 lakh shares of KPI Green Energy in a significant bulk deal, purchasing them at ₹454.61 per share. This strategic investment triggered an immediate surge, pushing KPI Green Energy's stock up by approximately 8.1% to an intra-day high of ₹513.6 on the BSE. The company also recently secured a major ₹696.50 crore contract from SJVN to develop a 200 MW solar power project in Gujarat, reinforcing its strong position in the renewable energy sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:48:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954dc014342f77179edd6ae_1767169111288.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Stocks Poised for Big Comeback in 2026: Earnings Surge &amp; Lower Valuations Signal Bright Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Stocks-Poised-for-Big-Comeback-in-2026-Earnings-Surge-and-Lower-Valuations-Signal-Bright-Future/6954dc574342f77179edd7d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Stocks-Poised-for-Big-Comeback-in-2026-Earnings-Surge-and-Lower-Valuations-Signal-Bright-Future/6954dc574342f77179edd7d0</guid><description>Indian equities are expected to deliver stronger returns in 2026 after underperforming global peers in 2025. This optimistic outlook is driven by improving corporate earnings, steady economic growth, more attractive valuations, and supportive government policies. While large-cap stocks appear attractive, small-cap segments may face continued pressure due to high valuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:48:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954dc574342f77179edd7cf_1767169383270.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VA Tech Wabag Stock Rockets as Brokerage Issues Strong 'Buy' Rating, Cites Massive Order Book!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VA-Tech-Wabag-Stock-Rockets-as-Brokerage-Issues-Strong-Buy-Rating-Cites-Massive-Order-Book/6954dc274342f77179edd71c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VA-Tech-Wabag-Stock-Rockets-as-Brokerage-Issues-Strong-Buy-Rating-Cites-Massive-Order-Book/6954dc274342f77179edd71c</guid><description>Motilal Oswal has reiterated its 'Buy' rating on VA Tech Wabag, setting a target price of ₹1,900. The brokerage is bullish due to the company's substantial ₹16,000 crore order book, strong revenue visibility, improving profitability, and a healthy balance sheet, projecting 15-20% revenue growth over the next three to four years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:48:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954dc274342f77179edd71b_1767169412833.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tether Fuels Speed's $8M Funding Blast for Lightning-Fast Bitcoin &amp; Stablecoin Payments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tether-Fuels-Speeds-8M-Funding-Blast-for-Lightning-Fast-Bitcoin-and-Stablecoin-Payments/6954db954342f77179edd4ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tether-Fuels-Speeds-8M-Funding-Blast-for-Lightning-Fast-Bitcoin-and-Stablecoin-Payments/6954db954342f77179edd4ef</guid><description>Speed, an India-based global payments firm leveraging the Bitcoin Lightning Network, has secured $8 million in a funding round led by Tether and ego death capital. This investment aims to accelerate Speed's mission of enabling real-world, low-cost, instant Bitcoin and stablecoin transactions worldwide. The company has already processed over $2.5 billion in volume and supports 1.2 million users, signaling strong growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:48:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954db954342f77179edd4ee_1767169009762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Green Energy Ignites Gujarat: 307 MW Power Boost Signals Renewable Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Green-Energy-Ignites-Gujarat-307-MW-Power-Boost-Signals-Renewable-Surge/6954dbab4342f77179edd545</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Green-Energy-Ignites-Gujarat-307-MW-Power-Boost-Signals-Renewable-Surge/6954dbab4342f77179edd545</guid><description>Adani Green Energy Limited has successfully operationalized 307.4 MW of new power projects across six subsidiaries in Gujarat's Khavda region. This significant expansion, effective January 1, 2026, boosts AGEL's total operational renewable capacity to 17,237.2 MW, reinforcing its position in India's renewable energy sector. The announcement comes as the company reported a 28% profit increase in its Q2 FY26 results.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:48:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954dbab4342f77179edd544_1767169164558.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Securities Analyst Slams 'BUY' on Bajaj Finance! Rs 1180 Target Revealed - Is This the Next Big Move?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/ICICI-Securities-Analyst-Slams-BUY-on-Bajaj-Finance-Rs-1180-Target-Revealed-Is-This-the-Next-Big-Move/6954db654342f77179edd463</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/ICICI-Securities-Analyst-Slams-BUY-on-Bajaj-Finance-Rs-1180-Target-Revealed-Is-This-the-Next-Big-Move/6954db654342f77179edd463</guid><description>Pankaj Pandey, Head of Research at ICICI Securities, recommends buying Bajaj Finance shares with a target price of ₹1,180. He believes the stock offers a favorable risk-reward at current levels around ₹1,000. Pandey projects strong profitability growth of 18-20% and bottom-line growth of 22-24%, expecting Bajaj Finance to benefit from potential GST cuts boosting consumption and credit demand. The NBFC has significantly outperformed the market in 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:48:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954db654342f77179edd462_1767169087653.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>January Stock Market Mystery Solved: Top Sectors Beat Flat Indices - Your 2026 Investment Edge Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/January-Stock-Market-Mystery-Solved-Top-Sectors-Beat-Flat-Indices-Your-2026-Investment-Edge-Revealed/6954db384342f77179edd369</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/January-Stock-Market-Mystery-Solved-Top-Sectors-Beat-Flat-Indices-Your-2026-Investment-Edge-Revealed/6954db384342f77179edd369</guid><description>Historical data shows the Indian stock market, specifically the Nifty 50, often starts the year with modest gains (average 0.4%) and positive closes in only three of the last ten Januarys. Mid-cap and small-cap indices also show weak trends. However, specific sectors like Realty (+2.5% average) and IT (+2.0% average) consistently outperform, with Auto and IT showing positive returns in seven out of ten years. Investors should focus on sector-specific opportunities rather than broad index bets for the New Year.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:47:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954db384342f77179edd368_1767169652166.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks Mixed: JSW Steel, Tata Steel Climb as Market Ends Mixed on Dec 31 - See Top Gainers &amp; Losers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Stocks-Mixed-JSW-Steel-Tata-Steel-Climb-as-Market-Ends-Mixed-on-Dec-31-See-Top-Gainers-and-Losers/6954da5c4342f77179edd040</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Stocks-Mixed-JSW-Steel-Tata-Steel-Climb-as-Market-Ends-Mixed-on-Dec-31-See-Top-Gainers-and-Losers/6954da5c4342f77179edd040</guid><description>On December 31, 2025, Indian stock markets experienced a mixed trading session. JSW Steel Ltd and Tata Steel Ltd were among the day's top gainers, showing significant price increases. Conversely, Tata Consultancy Services Ltd and Bajaj Finance Ltd appeared on the list of top losers. The benchmark Sensex closed up 0.60% at 85180.75 points, while the Nifty 50 index rose by 0.68% to 26114.25 points, indicating a broader market uptrend despite specific stock declines.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:47:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954da5c4342f77179edd03f_1767168873442.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCX Skyrockets on Morgan Stanley Upgrade &amp; Stock Split News! Target SHOT UP!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/MCX-Skyrockets-on-Morgan-Stanley-Upgrade-and-Stock-Split-News-Target-SHOT-UP/6954da1d4342f77179edcf7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/MCX-Skyrockets-on-Morgan-Stanley-Upgrade-and-Stock-Split-News-Target-SHOT-UP/6954da1d4342f77179edcf7b</guid><description>Multi Commodity Exchange of India (MCX) shares surged following a significant upgrade by Morgan Stanley. The brokerage moved its rating to 'Equal-weight' from 'Underweight' and sharply raised the target price by Rs 4,425 to Rs 11,135, citing a surge in Average Daily Transaction Revenue (ADTR) driven by gold and silver trading. Additionally, MCX announced its first stock split since 2012, a 5:1 sub-division, with a record date set for January 2, 2026. This news has boosted investor confidence, driving the stock higher.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:47:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954da1d4342f77179edcf7a_1767168651681.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2025 Shockwaves: CEO Exodus, Layoff Storms, and Culture Crises Rock Corporate India!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-Shockwaves-CEO-Exodus-Layoff-Storms-and-Culture-Crises-Rock-Corporate-India/6954dadb4342f77179edd1ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-Shockwaves-CEO-Exodus-Layoff-Storms-and-Culture-Crises-Rock-Corporate-India/6954dadb4342f77179edd1ee</guid><description>2025 was a turbulent year for India's corporate world, marked by a surge in CEO departures, significant layoffs from giants like TCS and startups, and major scandals such as IndusInd Bank's accounting issues. Debates intensified over long work hours, toxic workplace cultures, and the rise of 'silent layoffs', impacting employee morale and corporate governance. These events signal a critical juncture for India Inc's workplace norms and leadership accountability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:47:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954dadb4342f77179edd1ed_1767168958620.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Report Shocker: Urban Co-operative Banks Surge with 6-Year Highs in Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Report-Shocker-Urban-Co-operative-Banks-Surge-with-6-Year-Highs-in-Growth/6954d99d4342f77179edcd9d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Report-Shocker-Urban-Co-operative-Banks-Surge-with-6-Year-Highs-in-Growth/6954d99d4342f77179edcd9d</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's report reveals urban co-operative banks (UCBs) are in robust recovery, achieving their strongest credit growth in six years during FY25 at 6.7%. Deposits grew 5.2%, and profitability jumped 14.2% after a 52% rise in FY24. Asset quality improved significantly, with gross NPAs dropping to 6.2% and net NPAs at 0.7%, while capital buffers remain strong. UCBs also met their priority sector lending targets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:47:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d99d4342f77179edcd9c_1767168621462.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Star Forecasts Strong AC Comeback: 15% Growth &amp; Margin Boost Expected by FY27!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Blue-Star-Forecasts-Strong-AC-Comeback-15percent-Growth-and-Margin-Boost-Expected-by-FY27/6954d8704342f77179edc959</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Blue-Star-Forecasts-Strong-AC-Comeback-15percent-Growth-and-Margin-Boost-Expected-by-FY27/6954d8704342f77179edc959</guid><description>Blue Star's Managing Director B Thiagarajan anticipates a significant recovery for the air conditioner industry in FY27. Following a challenging FY26 marked by a flat market, normal summer conditions in 2026 are expected to drive 15% growth in room air conditioners. The company aims to restore margins to 8-8.5% and sees potential improvement in B2B segments like projects, factories, and data centers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:47:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d8704342f77179edc958_1767168178421.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Insurance Sector on Fire: 100% FDI &amp; GST Cut Spark HUGE Growth! What It Means For Your Money...</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Sector-on-Fire-100percent-FDI-and-GST-Cut-Spark-HUGE-Growth-What-It-Means-For-Your-Money/6954d9274342f77179edcb6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Sector-on-Fire-100percent-FDI-and-GST-Cut-Spark-HUGE-Growth-What-It-Means-For-Your-Money/6954d9274342f77179edcb6b</guid><description>India's insurance industry is undergoing a major transformation in 2025, driven by landmark policy changes like 100% foreign direct investment (FDI) approval and GST exemption on life and health premiums. Digitalization through platforms like Bima Sugam is accelerating, enhancing customer experience and operational efficiency. These reforms are attracting global capital, boosting competition, and making insurance more accessible and affordable, positioning the sector for strong, sustainable growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:47:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d9274342f77179edcb6a_1767168807185.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Equities Facing Major Hurdle! Top Fund Manager Warns of 2026 Valuation Trap - What Investors MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Facing-Major-Hurdle-Top-Fund-Manager-Warns-of-2026-Valuation-Trap-What-Investors-MUST-Know/6954d9014342f77179edcac9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Facing-Major-Hurdle-Top-Fund-Manager-Warns-of-2026-Valuation-Trap-What-Investors-MUST-Know/6954d9014342f77179edcac9</guid><description>Vinit Sambre of DSP Mutual Fund identifies high valuations as the primary challenge for Indian equities entering 2026, resulting in a thin margin of safety. He believes market direction will depend on valuations becoming more reasonable or earnings significantly improving. Sambre favors non-banking financial companies (NBFCs), the power sector, agrochemicals, and auto ancillaries, while advising caution on the consumer sector. He also maintains a contrarian positive view on the IT sector and sees long-term potential in mid- and small-cap stocks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:47:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d9014342f77179edcac8_1767168508940.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashika Group's Major Leap: SEBI Gives Green Light to Enter India's Booming Mutual Fund Market!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Ashika-Groups-Major-Leap-SEBI-Gives-Green-Light-to-Enter-Indias-Booming-Mutual-Fund-Market/6954d7e44342f77179edc7e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Ashika-Groups-Major-Leap-SEBI-Gives-Green-Light-to-Enter-Indias-Booming-Mutual-Fund-Market/6954d7e44342f77179edc7e4</guid><description>Ashika Group has received in-principle approval from SEBI to launch its mutual fund business. This allows the group to form an Asset Management Company (AMC) and prepare for launching various investment schemes, marking a significant expansion into India's asset management sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:47:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d7e44342f77179edc7e3_1767168050791.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Bags Massive 1,500 MW Solar Order &amp; Enters F&amp;O – Stock Poised for What?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Waaree-Energies-Bags-Massive-1500-MW-Solar-Order-and-Enters-FandO-Stock-Poised-for-What/6954d76b4342f77179edc70a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Waaree-Energies-Bags-Massive-1500-MW-Solar-Order-and-Enters-FandO-Stock-Poised-for-What/6954d76b4342f77179edc70a</guid><description>Waaree Energies has secured a significant 1,500 MW solar module supply order, including 1,000 MW of DCR modules, for FY 2026-27. The company also launched in the Futures and Options segment today. Meanwhile, its current CEO Amit Paithankar will step down in May 2026, with Jignesh Rathod appointed as CEO designate. Shares were trading up 0.80% at ₹3,001.40.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:47:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d76b4342f77179edc709_1767167947418.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DSP Fund Manager Sounds Alarm: Is India's Market Too Pricey? Discover Selective 2026 Opportunities!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/DSP-Fund-Manager-Sounds-Alarm-Is-Indias-Market-Too-Pricey-Discover-Selective-2026-Opportunities/6954d75e4342f77179edc6c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/DSP-Fund-Manager-Sounds-Alarm-Is-Indias-Market-Too-Pricey-Discover-Selective-2026-Opportunities/6954d75e4342f77179edc6c9</guid><description>Vineet Sambre, Head of Equities at DSP Mutual Fund, warns investors about high market valuations for 2026, citing a lack of margin for safety after 2025's uncertainties and earnings slowdown. He suggests looking at interest-rate sensitive sectors like Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs) and cyclical plays in power and agrochemicals. Sambre also sees potential in the IT sector due to attractive valuations, believing it has already priced in global risks and AI threats. He favors large-caps for the near term but remains optimistic about small and mid-caps' long-term performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:43:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d75e4342f77179edc6c8_1767167971608.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>InMobi's $150M Pre-IPO Funding Talks Ignite: Is India Listing Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/InMobis-150M-Pre-IPO-Funding-Talks-Ignite-Is-India-Listing-Next/6954d6474342f77179edc421</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/InMobis-150M-Pre-IPO-Funding-Talks-Ignite-Is-India-Listing-Next/6954d6474342f77179edc421</guid><description>Mobile advertising firm InMobi is reportedly in talks to raise $100-$150 million in a pre-IPO funding round. This move aims to establish a valuation benchmark for its planned Initial Public Offering, expected around fiscal year 2027. The company is also in the process of shifting its domicile to India from Singapore, following a recent significant financing round that reshaped its shareholder structure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:42:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d6474342f77179edc420_1767167723975.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Portfolio Rebalancing SHOCKER: Avoid This Massive Investor Mistake! Gold vs. Equity Dilemma Solved</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/2026-Portfolio-Rebalancing-SHOCKER-Avoid-This-Massive-Investor-Mistake-Gold-vs-Equity-Dilemma-Solved/6954d33c4342f77179edbcae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/2026-Portfolio-Rebalancing-SHOCKER-Avoid-This-Massive-Investor-Mistake-Gold-vs-Equity-Dilemma-Solved/6954d33c4342f77179edbcae</guid><description>As 2026 approaches, investors face a dilemma following gold and silver's stellar 2025 performance while equities lagged. Experts like Harshvardhan Roongta strongly advise against changing asset allocation based solely on recent returns, calling it a recurring retail investor mistake. Instead, they advocate for a goal-based strategy, recommending specific allocations for precious metals, equity, debt, and REITs tailored to different investment horizons to prevent disappointment and ensure long-term financial objectives are met.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:29:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d33c4342f77179edbcad_1767166880605.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Banks EXPLODE: Outperforming Nifty for 5 Years Straight – Are You Missing Out?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-EXPLODE-Outperforming-Nifty-for-5-Years-Straight-Are-You-Missing-Out/6954d19b4342f77179edb684</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-EXPLODE-Outperforming-Nifty-for-5-Years-Straight-Are-You-Missing-Out/6954d19b4342f77179edb684</guid><description>The Nifty PSU Bank index has surged 31% in calendar year 2025, marking its fifth consecutive year of outperforming the Nifty 50. This strong rally is driven by expectations of accelerated credit growth and improved bank profitability, with several public sector banks hitting multi-year highs. The index is closing in on its all-time high, reflecting robust investor interest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:15:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d19b4342f77179edb683_1767166539925.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW Steel: Buy Signal Flashed! Brokerage Eyes 10% Surge with Rs 1,123 Target – What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/JSW-Steel-Buy-Signal-Flashed-Brokerage-Eyes-10percent-Surge-with-Rs-1123-Target-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6954d0624342f77179edb0f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/JSW-Steel-Buy-Signal-Flashed-Brokerage-Eyes-10percent-Surge-with-Rs-1123-Target-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6954d0624342f77179edb0f5</guid><description>Axis Securities has issued a 'Buy' recommendation for JSW Steel, setting a target price of ₹1,123 per share, implying a 10% upside. The bullish outlook is driven by the company's impending capacity expansion, a growing product portfolio, and attractive current valuations, with the stock already trading above the target price. Key growth drivers include significant capacity enhancements at the Angul facility and margin improvement projects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:15:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d0624342f77179edb0f4_1767166142165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VA Tech Wabag Stock Skyrockets? Analysts See Stunning 50% Jump – Is This Your Next Big Investment?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VA-Tech-Wabag-Stock-Skyrockets-Analysts-See-Stunning-50percent-Jump-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Investment/6954d05f4342f77179edb0be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VA-Tech-Wabag-Stock-Skyrockets-Analysts-See-Stunning-50percent-Jump-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Investment/6954d05f4342f77179edb0be</guid><description>Analysts at Motilal Oswal Financial Services have maintained a 'Buy' rating on VA Tech Wabag, setting a target price of ₹1,900, indicating a potential 50% gain. The brokerage highlights strong order inflows, a healthy order book providing revenue visibility, and an improving composition of orders towards higher-margin segments. MOSL forecasts significant growth in revenue, EBITDA, and net profit, driven by execution and diversification. The stock reacted positively, trading up 4% following the upgrade.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:15:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d05f4342f77179edb0bd_1767166125175.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NPS Makes Big Changes: Will Your Mutual Fund Investments Still Be The Top Choice? Expert Explains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NPS-Makes-Big-Changes-Will-Your-Mutual-Fund-Investments-Still-Be-The-Top-Choice-Expert-Explains/6954d01b4342f77179edb018</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NPS-Makes-Big-Changes-Will-Your-Mutual-Fund-Investments-Still-Be-The-Top-Choice-Expert-Explains/6954d01b4342f77179edb018</guid><description>National Pension System (NPS) has introduced significant flexibility with new withdrawal and exit norms, extending the investment age and allowing higher lump-sum withdrawals. However, financial educator Mrin Agarwal believes these changes are unlikely to pull substantial long-term investor flows away from mutual funds, citing mutual funds' superior liquidity and lack of lock-in periods.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:15:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954d01b4342f77179edb017_1767166171097.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mid &amp; Small Caps Outshine Benchmarks in Year-End Surge! Steel Rally Fueled by New Duty?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Mid-and-Small-Caps-Outshine-Benchmarks-in-Year-End-Surge-Steel-Rally-Fueled-by-New-Duty/6954cebe4342f77179edacde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Mid-and-Small-Caps-Outshine-Benchmarks-in-Year-End-Surge-Steel-Rally-Fueled-by-New-Duty/6954cebe4342f77179edacde</guid><description>Indian mid and small-cap indices outperformed benchmark Nifty and Sensex on Wednesday, the final trading session of calendar year 2025, with gains of up to 1 percent. This recovery snapped recent losing streaks for these segments. A key driver was Steel Authority of India, which jumped over 5 percent following the government's imposition of a three-year safeguard duty on certain steel imports, boosting expectations for domestic producers. The broader market also saw a rebound, with Sensex and Nifty posting gains.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:11:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954cebe4342f77179edacdd_1767166171421.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai-Ahmedabad Bullet Train: 55% Complete! New 2029 Target Revealed - Will it Transform Indian Travel?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbai-Ahmedabad-Bullet-Train-55percent-Complete-New-2029-Target-Revealed-Will-it-Transform-Indian-Travel/6954cdea4342f77179edaa19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbai-Ahmedabad-Bullet-Train-55percent-Complete-New-2029-Target-Revealed-Will-it-Transform-Indian-Travel/6954cdea4342f77179edaa19</guid><description>India's first high-speed rail corridor between Mumbai and Ahmedabad has achieved over 55% physical progress, with financial outlays nearing 70% usage of ₹85,801 crore. The project, utilizing Japan's Shinkansen technology, is now targeted for completion by 2029, aiming to reduce travel time to under three hours and boost regional economic activity. Delays, primarily due to land acquisition issues and the COVID-19 pandemic, pushed back the original 2023 completion date.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:05:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954cdea4342f77179edaa18_1767165649146.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Record Bond Play: Can India's Debt Market Defy 2026 Storms?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Record-Bond-Play-Can-Indias-Debt-Market-Defy-2026-Storms/6954cd894342f77179eda890</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Record-Bond-Play-Can-Indias-Debt-Market-Defy-2026-Storms/6954cd894342f77179eda890</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India injected a record ₹11.7 lakh crore into the banking system in 2025 to support Indian government bonds and manage yields. Despite this unprecedented intervention and 125 basis points of rate cuts, the bond market faces uncertainty heading into 2026. Key challenges include significant government debt supply, a weakening rupee, and shifts in institutional investor demand, which continue to exert selling pressure despite the RBI's efforts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:02:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954cd894342f77179eda88f_1767165449806.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Investment Forecast: Stocks, Gold, Crypto, &amp; RBI's Major Shake-Up Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-Investment-Forecast-Stocks-Gold-Crypto-and-RBIs-Major-Shake-Up-Revealed/6954cd1f4342f77179eda746</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-Investment-Forecast-Stocks-Gold-Crypto-and-RBIs-Major-Shake-Up-Revealed/6954cd1f4342f77179eda746</guid><description>Navigate 2026 with confidence. This guide details investment strategies for stocks, stable FDs, rising gold/silver, and growing crypto markets. Discover RBI's crucial cybersecurity, digital banking, and data privacy reforms, plus insurance sector changes including increased foreign investment. Prepare for evolving market dynamics and regulatory shifts to make smart money moves.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:59:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954cd1f4342f77179eda745_1767165443646.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>