<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:50:24 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Choice International Surges on Stellar Q3 Results, PAT Skyrockets 113%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Choice-International-Surges-on-Stellar-Q3-Results-PAT-Skyrockets-113percent/6981e6c7d9d43ad9e17404d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Choice-International-Surges-on-Stellar-Q3-Results-PAT-Skyrockets-113percent/6981e6c7d9d43ad9e17404d7</guid><description>Choice International reported robust Q3 FY26 results. Revenue jumped 45.92% YoY to ₹308.60 Cr. PAT surged 113.47% YoY to ₹65.62 Cr, with EBITDA margin expanding to 37.92%. Strategic wins include wealth business acquisitions and an IPPB contract.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:40:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e6c7d9d43ad9e17404d6_1770122315823.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brigade Hotel Ventures Eyes 1,700 Keys by FY30 on Strong Q3 Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Brigade-Hotel-Ventures-Eyes-1700-Keys-by-FY30-on-Strong-Q3-Growth/6981eb1dd9d43ad9e1741587</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Brigade-Hotel-Ventures-Eyes-1700-Keys-by-FY30-on-Strong-Q3-Growth/6981eb1dd9d43ad9e1741587</guid><description>Brigade Hotel Ventures reported a robust Q3 FY'26, with total income up 14% YoY to ₹143 Crores, driven by a 17% rise in ARR and RevPAR. EBITDA climbed 17% to ₹51 Crores, and PAT surged 126% to ₹22 Crores. The company outlined an ambitious plan to nearly double its portfolio by adding 1,700 keys over five years, reaching 3,300 keys by FY'30, backed by a ₹3,600 Crore investment. Management cited healthy demand visibility and favorable market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:37:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981eb1dd9d43ad9e1741586_1770122266443.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Posts Strong Core Growth; Unveils AI-Driven LRS 2026-30 Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finance-Posts-Strong-Core-Growth-Unveils-AI-Driven-LRS-2026-30-Strategy/6981eac2d9d43ad9e174143a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finance-Posts-Strong-Core-Growth-Unveils-AI-Driven-LRS-2026-30-Strategy/6981eac2d9d43ad9e174143a</guid><description>Bajaj Finance reported a robust 23% YoY growth in core profits for Q3 FY26, driven by a 22% AUM expansion. Despite exceptional charges impacting reported net profit by 6%, the underlying business demonstrated strength. The company unveiled its ambitious Long-Range Strategy (LRS) 2026-30, heavily leveraging AI for customer-centricity, technology leadership, and risk management, targeting significant customer and AUM growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981eac2d9d43ad9e1741439_1770122091915.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JK Lakshmi Cement PAT Drops 25% Amid Costs; Eyes ₹3k Cr Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/JK-Lakshmi-Cement-PAT-Drops-25percent-Amid-Costs-Eyes-3k-Cr-Expansion/6981ea5bd9d43ad9e17412af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/JK-Lakshmi-Cement-PAT-Drops-25percent-Amid-Costs-Eyes-3k-Cr-Expansion/6981ea5bd9d43ad9e17412af</guid><description>JK Lakshmi Cement reported a 25.7% YoY decline in Q3 FY26 standalone PAT to ₹58.12 Cr, despite a 5.45% rise in Net Sales to ₹1588.40 Cr and a 10.50% increase in EBITDA to ₹235.13 Cr. The company is undertaking a significant ₹3000 Crore capacity expansion and has substantially improved its financial leverage, with Net Debt to EBITDA falling to 1.29x from 2.41x. A long-term vision targets 30 MTPA capacity by 2030.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:34:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981ea5bd9d43ad9e17412ae_1770122044628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Niva Bupa Health Insurance Posts 74% PAT Surge; Digital Channels Drive 31% Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Niva-Bupa-Health-Insurance-Posts-74percent-PAT-Surge-Digital-Channels-Drive-31percent-Growth/6981e72bd9d43ad9e174079d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Niva-Bupa-Health-Insurance-Posts-74percent-PAT-Surge-Digital-Channels-Drive-31percent-Growth/6981e72bd9d43ad9e174079d</guid><description>Niva Bupa Health Insurance reported a robust Q3 FY'26, with nine-month PAT soaring 74% YoY to ₹208 crore. Overall growth hit 31%, powered by a remarkable 46% surge in new business and 70% expansion in the direct digital channel. The company also improved its combined and expense ratios, targeting high-teens ROE in two years.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:32:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e72bd9d43ad9e174079c_1770121807674.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dixon Technologies Q3 Revenue Up 2%; Eyes ₹1 Lakh Crore Milestone via Component Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Technologies-Q3-Revenue-Up-2percent-Eyes-1-Lakh-Crore-Milestone-via-Component-Push/6981e6e9d9d43ad9e17405cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Technologies-Q3-Revenue-Up-2percent-Eyes-1-Lakh-Crore-Milestone-via-Component-Push/6981e6e9d9d43ad9e17405cc</guid><description>Dixon Technologies reported Q3 FY26 revenues of ₹10,678 Cr, a 2% YoY increase, while EBITDA grew 5.8% to ₹421 Cr. PAT saw a marginal dip to ₹214 Cr. The company highlighted significant expansion into component manufacturing, new JV developments for smartphones and display modules, and reiterated its ambition to cross ₹1 lakh crore in revenue within 3-4 years, despite near-term commodity inflation headwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:32:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e6e9d9d43ad9e17405cb_1770121877454.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Firstsource Profit Falls 33%, But Revenue and Margins Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Firstsource-Profit-Falls-33percent-But-Revenue-and-Margins-Rise/6981e9ded9d43ad9e17410c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Firstsource-Profit-Falls-33percent-But-Revenue-and-Margins-Rise/6981e9ded9d43ad9e17410c4</guid><description>Firstsource Solutions posted a Q3 net profit of ₹120 crore, down 33% from the prior quarter, primarily due to a ₹91.35-crore expense from India's new labor codes. Despite this, revenue climbed 6.6% sequentially to ₹2,467 crore, and EBIT increased 17.3% with margins expanding to 12.8%. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹5.50 per share. The stock closed up 1.48% on February 3rd.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:31:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e9ded9d43ad9e17410c3_1770121916653.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Export Relief Masks Deeper Competitiveness Questions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Export-Relief-Masks-Deeper-Competitiveness-Questions/6981e92cd9d43ad9e1740ea3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Export-Relief-Masks-Deeper-Competitiveness-Questions/6981e92cd9d43ad9e1740ea3</guid><description>The recent India-US trade agreement significantly reduces US tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, aiming to boost GDP by up to 30 basis points and revitalize labor-intensive sectors. While this offers immediate relief and improves India's relative cost competitiveness against key Asian peers, the long-term sustainability of these gains hinges on addressing structural economic factors beyond tariff levels.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:28:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e92cd9d43ad9e1740ea2_1770121718453.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Capital: Strategic Deal Valuations Spark Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aditya-Birla-Capital-Strategic-Deal-Valuations-Spark-Growth/6981e8c9d9d43ad9e1740d69</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aditya-Birla-Capital-Strategic-Deal-Valuations-Spark-Growth/6981e8c9d9d43ad9e1740d69</guid><description>Aditya Birla Capital announced a robust third quarter for FY2025-26, posting a 33% year-on-year profit increase to ₹945 crore. This performance was complemented by a strategic capital infusion, with Advent International acquiring a 14.3% stake in its housing finance subsidiary for ₹2,750 crore, valuing the entity at ₹19,250 crore. The company also saw its lending portfolio grow 30% and Assets Under Management expand 19% year-on-year, reflecting broad operational strength across its financial services verticals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:27:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e8c9d9d43ad9e1740d68_1770121632166.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Diaspora Capital Flow Boosted</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Diaspora-Capital-Flow-Boosted/6981e87ad9d43ad9e1740c5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Diaspora-Capital-Flow-Boosted/6981e87ad9d43ad9e1740c5d</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 unveils strategic enhancements aimed at channeling Non-Resident Indian (NRI) capital into the domestic economy. Key reforms include doubling individual equity investment limits in listed firms to 10% and raising the aggregate cap to 24%. Compliance for property sales is streamlined by eliminating the Tax Deducted at Source (TDS) Account Number (TAN) requirement for resident buyers. Furthermore, Tax Collected at Source (TCS) on overseas education, medical remittances, and tour packages has been significantly reduced to 2%, easing financial burdens for expatriates. These initiatives are designed to simplify engagement and encourage deeper financial integration with India's growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:23:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e87ad9d43ad9e1740c5c_1770121410681.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance PAT Dips 6% on Provisions, AUM Surges 22% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finance-PAT-Dips-6percent-on-Provisions-AUM-Surges-22percent-YoY/6981e7bbd9d43ad9e1740a70</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finance-PAT-Dips-6percent-on-Provisions-AUM-Surges-22percent-YoY/6981e7bbd9d43ad9e1740a70</guid><description>Bajaj Finance reported a 6% year-on-year dip in consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹4,066 crore for Q3 FY26, primarily due to an accelerated ECL provision of ₹1,406 crore and new labor code charges. Despite this, underlying operational performance remained robust, with consolidated Assets Under Management (AUM) surging 22% YoY to ₹484,477 crore and Net Interest Income growing 21% YoY. Standalone PAT rose 24% YoY to ₹4,581 crore, aided by a one-time gain from the sale of its stake in Bajaj Housing Finance Ltd.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e7bbd9d43ad9e1740a6f_1770121309059.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance PAT Dips 6% on Provisions, Core AUM Surges 22%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finance-PAT-Dips-6percent-on-Provisions-Core-AUM-Surges-22percent/6981e78ad9d43ad9e1740962</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finance-PAT-Dips-6percent-on-Provisions-Core-AUM-Surges-22percent/6981e78ad9d43ad9e1740962</guid><description>Bajaj Finance reported Q3 FY26 consolidated PAT of ₹4,066 crore, down 6% YoY, impacted by ₹1,406 crore accelerated ECL provisioning and ₹265 crore for New Labour Codes. Excluding these, PAT grew 23% YoY to ₹5,317 crore. Consolidated AUM surged 22% YoY to ₹484,477 crore, with new loans up 15%. Standalone PAT rose 24% to ₹4,581 crore, boosted by a ₹1,416 crore gain from the BHFL share sale.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:20:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e78ad9d43ad9e1740961_1770121188791.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ajmera Realty Hits Record Sales; Wadala Project GDV Surges Fivefold</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ajmera-Realty-Hits-Record-Sales-Wadala-Project-GDV-Surges-Fivefold/6981e70cd9d43ad9e17406ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ajmera-Realty-Hits-Record-Sales-Wadala-Project-GDV-Surges-Fivefold/6981e70cd9d43ad9e17406ed</guid><description>Ajmera Realty reported its highest-ever 9M FY26 sales at ₹1,431 Cr, up 72% YoY, driven by strong project execution. Collections surged 70% YoY to ₹787 Cr. The company revised its Wadala Boutique Office project's GDV to ₹5,300 Cr from ₹1,800 Cr, significantly boosting revenue visibility. Management expects to easily surpass the ₹1,600 Cr full-year sales guidance amid a strengthening real estate market. New business development projects worth ₹2,000 Cr were secured.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:18:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e70cd9d43ad9e17406ec_1770121085646.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KEC International Lands ₹1,020 Cr Orders, Order Book Surges Past ₹41K Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Lands-1020-Cr-Orders-Order-Book-Surges-Past-41K-Cr/6981e691d9d43ad9e1740377</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Lands-1020-Cr-Orders-Order-Book-Surges-Past-41K-Cr/6981e691d9d43ad9e1740377</guid><description>KEC International, the RPG Group's infrastructure major, announced new orders totalling ₹1,020 crore across its civil, transportation, T&amp;D, and cables segments. This infusion significantly bolsters its already robust ₹41,000 crore order book, reinforcing its strong growth trajectory and execution capability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gland Pharma Q3 Results Shine: Revenue Up 22%, Cenexi Turns Profitable</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Gland-Pharma-Q3-Results-Shine-Revenue-Up-22percent-Cenexi-Turns-Profitable/6981e5dfd9d43ad9e17400e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Gland-Pharma-Q3-Results-Shine-Revenue-Up-22percent-Cenexi-Turns-Profitable/6981e5dfd9d43ad9e17400e1</guid><description>Gland Pharma posted a strong Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue climbing 22% year-on-year to INR 16,954 million and adjusted EBITDA surging 25% to INR 4,490 million, achieving a healthy 26% margin. A key highlight was the turnaround of its European subsidiary, Cenexi, which turned profitable with positive EBITDA. The company plans INR 2,000 crore capex over five years, targeting 15% CAGR growth in high-end CDMO and specialty injectables.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:14:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e5dfd9d43ad9e17400e0_1770120808225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Choice International Q3 PAT Soars 113%, Revenue Jumps 45%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Choice-International-Q3-PAT-Soars-113percent-Revenue-Jumps-45percent/6981e622d9d43ad9e17401fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Choice-International-Q3-PAT-Soars-113percent-Revenue-Jumps-45percent/6981e622d9d43ad9e17401fe</guid><description>Choice International reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with PAT surging 113.35% YoY to ₹65.62 Cr and revenue climbing 44.91% to ₹303.36 Cr. Nine-month figures also show robust growth. Key segments like Wealth Management (AUM +328%) and NBFC (NIM +137 bps) excelled. Strategic acquisitions and a new contract with India Post Payments Bank are set to fuel future expansion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NCLT Approves JK Paper's Mega-Restructuring, Consolidates Packaging Units</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCLT-Approves-JK-Papers-Mega-Restructuring-Consolidates-Packaging-Units/6981e52bd9d43ad9e173fc9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCLT-Approves-JK-Papers-Mega-Restructuring-Consolidates-Packaging-Units/6981e52bd9d43ad9e173fc9e</guid><description>The National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), Ahmedabad, has sanctioned JK Paper Limited's comprehensive corporate restructuring scheme. This multi-entity arrangement involves amalgamating wholly-owned packaging subsidiaries into JK Paper, demerging Enviro Tech Ventures into PSV Agro Products, and integrating residual businesses. The move aims to consolidate packaging operations, enhance capital asset utilization, streamline supply chains, and reduce compliance costs for stronger future growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:11:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e52bd9d43ad9e173fc9d_1770120712836.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBCC Secures ₹271 Cr Orders Amid Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NBCC-Secures-271-Cr-Orders-Amid-Valuation-Scrutiny/6981e5add9d43ad9e173ffdb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NBCC-Secures-271-Cr-Orders-Amid-Valuation-Scrutiny/6981e5add9d43ad9e173ffdb</guid><description>NBCC (India) Limited added approximately ₹271.32 crore to its order book through new work orders. Key among these is a substantial ₹232.13 crore project from the Department of Fisheries, Uttarakhand, for the Namami Ganga Aquarium-cum-Discovery Learning Centre. The company also formalized an agreement with Kendriya Vidyalaya Sangathan (KVS) to provide Project Management Consultancy services for school infrastructure nationwide. These developments come as the company's stock closed at ₹100.40 on February 3, 2026, marking a 3.55% gain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Firstsource Solutions Revenue Surges 16%, FY26 Outlook Raised Despite PAT Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Revenue-Surges-16percent-FY26-Outlook-Raised-Despite-PAT-Dip/6981e507d9d43ad9e173fb5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Revenue-Surges-16percent-FY26-Outlook-Raised-Despite-PAT-Dip/6981e507d9d43ad9e173fb5b</guid><description>Firstsource Solutions posted a strong Q3 FY2026 with revenue climbing 16.2% YoY to ₹24,431 million, and EBIT growing 24.9%. While Q3 PAT declined due to ₹1 billion in exceptional items from new Labour Codes and prior year impairments, the nine-month PAT saw an increase. The company completed its UK acquisition of Pastdue Credit Solutions and raised its full-year FY2026 outlook, now targeting 14.5%-15.5% revenue growth and 11.5%-12% EBIT margins, driven by strong client additions and AI solutions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e507d9d43ad9e173fb5a_1770120584298.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eternal's Valuation Paradox: Analyst Surge Meets CEO Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eternals-Valuation-Paradox-Analyst-Surge-Meets-CEO-Shift/6981e43fd9d43ad9e173f82b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eternals-Valuation-Paradox-Analyst-Surge-Meets-CEO-Shift/6981e43fd9d43ad9e173f82b</guid><description>Eternal shares briefly touched a 10% upper circuit following Jefferies' addition to its India model portfolio, citing the India-US trade deal and growth prospects. The company also saw a leadership change with Albinder Singh Dhindsa succeeding Deepinder Goyal as CEO. Despite this optimism, the stock trades at an exceptionally high P/E ratio, reflecting aggressive growth expectations amidst intense competition in its core quick commerce and food delivery segments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:07:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e43fd9d43ad9e173f82a_1770120459361.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indus Infra Trust Declares ₹3.40 Payout Amidst Consolidated Revenue Drop &amp; Impairment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indus-Infra-Trust-Declares-340-Payout-Amidst-Consolidated-Revenue-Drop-and-Impairment/6981e406d9d43ad9e173f6ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indus-Infra-Trust-Declares-340-Payout-Amidst-Consolidated-Revenue-Drop-and-Impairment/6981e406d9d43ad9e173f6ed</guid><description>Indus Infra Trust declared a distribution of ₹3.40 per unit for Q3 FY25, comprising interest and return of capital. While standalone revenue rose 4.7% YoY, consolidated revenue dipped 14.8%. The Trust also reported an investment impairment and a deviation in IPO proceeds utilization, reallocating funds to general purposes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:05:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e406d9d43ad9e173f6ec_1770120340554.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Strides Pharma Q3: Record Profit Surge Driven by Ex-US Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Strides-Pharma-Q3-Record-Profit-Surge-Driven-by-Ex-US-Markets/6981e3ced9d43ad9e173f5f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Strides-Pharma-Q3-Record-Profit-Surge-Driven-by-Ex-US-Markets/6981e3ced9d43ad9e173f5f4</guid><description>Strides Pharma Science posted record Q3 FY'26 EBITDA of ₹236 Cr (+12% YoY) and 39% operational PAT growth to ₹128 Cr, fueled by strong Ex-US market performance (20% YoY growth). While US sales remained flat due to seasonal delays and competition, management reaffirms FY'28 targets for the US market and focuses on profitability and balance sheet strength.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:03:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e3ced9d43ad9e173f5f3_1770120226019.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godrej Agrovet Revenue Up 11%, Profit Flat Amid Liquidity Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Godrej-Agrovet-Revenue-Up-11percent-Profit-Flat-Amid-Liquidity-Woes/6981e34ed9d43ad9e173f485</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Godrej-Agrovet-Revenue-Up-11percent-Profit-Flat-Amid-Liquidity-Woes/6981e34ed9d43ad9e173f485</guid><description>Godrej Agrovet posted an 11% YoY revenue growth to ₹2,718 crore in Q3 FY26, but Profit After Tax remained flat at ₹109.73 crore, affected by a ₹30.44 crore exceptional charge linked to new labour codes. The company fully acquired Creamline Dairy. Investors are watching weak liquidity, marked by a 0.79 current ratio and negative working capital, despite an improved operating margin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:01:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e34ed9d43ad9e173f484_1770120096169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SAMHI Hotels Q3 Revenue Jumps 16%, But GST Hits Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/SAMHI-Hotels-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-16percent-But-GST-Hits-Margins/6981e2f4d9d43ad9e173f1f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/SAMHI-Hotels-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-16percent-But-GST-Hits-Margins/6981e2f4d9d43ad9e173f1f2</guid><description>SAMHI Hotels reported a resilient Q3 FY26, with total income up 16.2% YoY to ₹342 Cr and RevPAR rising 13%. Underlying EBITDA grew 19.2%, but reported margins compressed ~200 basis points due to GST impact. Management reiterated FY30 revenue targets and expects sustained RevPAR growth, while maintaining debt levels. Expansion continues with 1,900 rooms under development.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e2f4d9d43ad9e173f1f1_1770120003661.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Firstsource Solutions Posts Revenue Growth, PAT Dips on One-Offs, Lifts Guidance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Posts-Revenue-Growth-PAT-Dips-on-One-Offs-Lifts-Guidance/6981e289d9d43ad9e173f08c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Posts-Revenue-Growth-PAT-Dips-on-One-Offs-Lifts-Guidance/6981e289d9d43ad9e173f08c</guid><description>Firstsource Solutions reported a 16.2% YoY revenue jump in Q3 FY26 to ₹24,431M. However, reported PAT fell 24.9% YoY due to ₹1,001M in exceptional expenses from new labour codes and investment impairment. Adjusted PAT was resilient at ₹2,022M. The company raised its full-year revenue growth guidance to 14.5%-15.5% and declared an interim dividend of ₹5.50 per share.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e289d9d43ad9e173f08b_1770119919399.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Menzies Aviation Secures 15-Year Ground Handling Deal at BLR Airport</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Menzies-Aviation-Secures-15-Year-Ground-Handling-Deal-at-BLR-Airport/6981e318d9d43ad9e173f318</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Menzies-Aviation-Secures-15-Year-Ground-Handling-Deal-at-BLR-Airport/6981e318d9d43ad9e173f318</guid><description>Menzies Aviation has secured a significant 15-year contract to provide comprehensive ground handling services at Kempegowda International Airport Bengaluru (BLR), effective April 1, 2026. The agreement, awarded by airport operator BIAL, expands Menzies' operations beyond its existing cargo services to include passenger, ramp, and baggage handling. The company plans a substantial investment of over USD 9.2 million to modernize its ground support equipment, with a focus on introducing electric vehicles as part of its sustainability initiatives. This expansion is expected to create approximately 1,000 new local jobs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Balkrishna Industries Posts Q3 Growth Amidst Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balkrishna-Industries-Posts-Q3-Growth-Amidst-Global-Headwinds/6981df96d9d43ad9e173e851</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balkrishna-Industries-Posts-Q3-Growth-Amidst-Global-Headwinds/6981df96d9d43ad9e173e851</guid><description>Balkrishna Industries reported Q3 FY26 revenue growth of 4% YoY to INR 2,682 crores, driven by strong sequential volume increases and robust demand in India, which now constitutes 60% of its industrial and 40% agri business. The company is also seeing regained sales momentum in the US market despite tariffs, partly by absorbing costs with partners. While 9-month EBITDA saw an 11% YoY de-growth to INR 1,760 crores, margins remained steady at 22.7%. The company declared an interim dividend of INR 4 per share and is progressing with its new carbon black line and CV/PV foray.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:57:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981df96d9d43ad9e173e850_1770119828984.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rubicon Research: Stellar 52% Revenue Jump, Profit Soars 91%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Rubicon-Research-Stellar-52percent-Revenue-Jump-Profit-Soars-91percent/6981e25ed9d43ad9e173ef88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Rubicon-Research-Stellar-52percent-Revenue-Jump-Profit-Soars-91percent/6981e25ed9d43ad9e173ef88</guid><description>Rubicon Research reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue climbing 51.7% YoY to ₹4,755 million, driven by strong USD-denominated sales. Profit After Tax soared 91.2% YoY to ₹728 million. While gross margins compressed due to reliance on outsourced manufacturing, operating EBITDA margins held steady at 22.7%. The company anticipates margin improvement post-mid-2026 with its Pithampur facility's ramp-up.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vivimed Labs Faces CBI Probe Amid SBI Complaint &amp; Debt Transfer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Vivimed-Labs-Faces-CBI-Probe-Amid-SBI-Complaint-and-Debt-Transfer/6981e1e8d9d43ad9e173ee51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Vivimed-Labs-Faces-CBI-Probe-Amid-SBI-Complaint-and-Debt-Transfer/6981e1e8d9d43ad9e173ee51</guid><description>Vivimed Labs has informed exchanges about receiving a notice from the CBI concerning alleged financial irregularities, following a complaint by the State Bank of India (SBI). Concurrently, the company's financial assets have been acquired by Rare Asset Reconstruction Ltd. (Rare ARC), intensifying existing financial concerns and raising significant questions about its operational continuity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:56:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e1e8d9d43ad9e173ee50_1770119735297.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Firstsource Solutions Q3 Revenue Surges 16%, Raises FY26 Guidance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Q3-Revenue-Surges-16percent-Raises-FY26-Guidance/6981e039d9d43ad9e173ea8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Q3-Revenue-Surges-16percent-Raises-FY26-Guidance/6981e039d9d43ad9e173ea8d</guid><description>Firstsource Solutions posted a strong third quarter for FY26, with consolidated revenue climbing 16.2% year-on-year to ₹24,431 million. EBIT surged 24.9% YoY to ₹2,915 million, reflecting an 11.9% margin. The company also raised its full-year revenue growth and EBIT margin outlook, expecting revenue growth of 14.5%-15.5% in constant currency and an EBIT margin of 11.5%-12%. Firstsource Solutions declared an interim dividend of ₹5.50 per share. Reported profit after tax (PAT) for the quarter decreased YoY to ₹1,203 million due to exceptional items, including labour code impacts and investment impairment, impacting reported EPS to ₹1.71. However, adjusted PAT and EPS showed robust performance, and free cash flow generation remained strong at 164% of adjusted PAT.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e039d9d43ad9e173ea8c_1770119464396.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Firstsource Solutions Surges on 16% Revenue Growth, Guidance Upbeat</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Surges-on-16percent-Revenue-Growth-Guidance-Upbeat/6981e009d9d43ad9e173e9a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Surges-on-16percent-Revenue-Growth-Guidance-Upbeat/6981e009d9d43ad9e173e9a5</guid><description>Firstsource Solutions reported a strong Q3 FY26 with revenue up 16.2% YoY to ₹24,431 Million and EBIT increasing 24.9% YoY to ₹2,915 Million. EBIT margins expanded 80 bps. While Profit After Tax (PAT) showed a QoQ rise, it declined YoY/QoQ due to a ₹1,001 Million exceptional item from new Labour Codes. The company reaffirmed its FY26 guidance for 14.5-15.5% constant currency revenue growth and 11.5-12.0% EBIT margin, driven by acquisitions and Generative AI services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e009d9d43ad9e173e9a4_1770119283215.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Bonds Under Pressure as MFs Exit Amid Borrowing Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Bonds-Under-Pressure-as-MFs-Exit-Amid-Borrowing-Surge/6981e082d9d43ad9e173ec2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Bonds-Under-Pressure-as-MFs-Exit-Amid-Borrowing-Surge/6981e082d9d43ad9e173ec2c</guid><description>Indian mutual funds recorded unprecedented net sales of ₹290 billion in government bonds during January 2026, driven by a significant supply overhang and projected record gross borrowings exceeding ₹30 trillion in the upcoming fiscal year. This trend signals a strategic pivot away from sovereign debt, with funds now prioritizing shorter-duration corporate bonds and state debt for accrual-based income strategies over mark-to-market gains. The benchmark 10-year bond yield has reacted, rising approximately 7 basis points post-budget, reflecting persistent demand-supply pressures that outweigh positive market sentiment from trade developments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:49:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981e082d9d43ad9e173ec2b_1770119366349.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Firstsource Solutions Q3 Revenue Surges 16%, Margins Expand Amidst 'UnBPO' Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Q3-Revenue-Surges-16percent-Margins-Expand-Amidst-UnBPO-Drive/6981df60d9d43ad9e173e722</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Q3-Revenue-Surges-16percent-Margins-Expand-Amidst-UnBPO-Drive/6981df60d9d43ad9e173e722</guid><description>Firstsource Solutions reported a strong Q3FY26 with revenue surging 16.2% year-on-year to ₹24,431 Million and EBIT margins expanding by 80 basis points to 11.9%. The company projects robust FY26 growth and margin improvement driven by its 'UnBPO' strategy and recent acquisitions. However, reported PAT was affected by exceptional items, a point for investor watch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:45:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981df60d9d43ad9e173e721_1770119109954.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Firstsource Solutions: Reported Profit Dips 25% On One-offs; Adjusted PAT Soars, FY26 Outlook Raised</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Reported-Profit-Dips-25percent-On-One-offs-Adjusted-PAT-Soars-FY26-Outlook-Raised/6981df24d9d43ad9e173e527</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Reported-Profit-Dips-25percent-On-One-offs-Adjusted-PAT-Soars-FY26-Outlook-Raised/6981df24d9d43ad9e173e527</guid><description>Firstsource Solutions reported a 25% year-on-year dip in Q3 FY2026 net profit to ₹1,203 million due to ₹1,001 million in exceptional expenses, including new Labour Code impacts. However, adjusted profit grew robustly, up 83% to ₹2,022 million on 16.2% revenue growth. The company acquired UK's Pastdue Credit Solutions and raised its FY26 revenue growth and EBIT margin guidance, while declaring an interim dividend of ₹5.50.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981df24d9d43ad9e173e526_1770119017408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Varroc Engineering Wins 6-Year EV Charger Deal Worth ₹4,391 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Varroc-Engineering-Wins-6-Year-EV-Charger-Deal-Worth-4391-Cr/6981df48d9d43ad9e173e615</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Varroc-Engineering-Wins-6-Year-EV-Charger-Deal-Worth-4391-Cr/6981df48d9d43ad9e173e615</guid><description>Varroc Engineering has landed a significant six-year contract to supply advanced AC bi-directional wall chargers to a leading global EV OEM. The deal, projected to generate ₹4,391 million annually at peak capacity, marks a substantial expansion for Varroc in the electric mobility ecosystem and validates its advanced automotive technology capabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Action Construction Equipment Revenue Dips, Profit Climbs on Margin Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Action-Construction-Equipment-Revenue-Dips-Profit-Climbs-on-Margin-Boost/6981de69d9d43ad9e173e37d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Action-Construction-Equipment-Revenue-Dips-Profit-Climbs-on-Margin-Boost/6981de69d9d43ad9e173e37d</guid><description>Action Construction Equipment (ACE) reported a 2.4% YoY decline in Q3 FY26 revenue to ₹852.81 crore, yet managed an 8.1% rise in PAT to ₹115.88 crore. This growth was fueled by improved operating and net margins, and a significant jump in 'Other Income'. For the nine months, revenue fell 4.9% but PAT grew 10.3%. The company maintains low leverage with a debt-equity ratio of 0.07. However, no forward-looking guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:42:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981de69d9d43ad9e173e37c_1770118918605.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LT Foods Hits Record Revenue, But Margin Pressures Loom Large</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LT-Foods-Hits-Record-Revenue-But-Margin-Pressures-Loom-Large/6981de37d9d43ad9e173e277</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LT-Foods-Hits-Record-Revenue-But-Margin-Pressures-Loom-Large/6981de37d9d43ad9e173e277</guid><description>LT Foods reported record Q3 and nine-month revenues, up 23-24% YoY, driven by strong basmati and international sales. However, EBITDA margins compressed 30 bps due to higher brand investments and digitalization. Management guides for double-digit growth next fiscal, but faces headwinds from US tariffs, rising paddy prices, and a significant investment phase in its RTH/RTC business. An acquisition in Hungary was blocked.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:40:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981de37d9d43ad9e173e276_1770118826833.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Sparks Rally, But Froth &amp; Sector Disparities Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Rally-But-Froth-and-Sector-Disparities-Emerge/6981ddafd9d43ad9e173e05f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Rally-But-Froth-and-Sector-Disparities-Emerge/6981ddafd9d43ad9e173e05f</guid><description>Indian markets experienced a broad surge on February 3, 2026, driven by a new India-US trade agreement that lowered tariffs and boosted key sectors. The BSE Sensex and NSE Nifty-50 indices posted significant gains, with all sectoral indices trading in the green. However, a notable increase in low-priced stocks hitting upper circuits, coupled with the previous market reaction to Budget 2026's STT hike, suggests underlying speculative activity and potential sectoral divergences, even as macro indicators offer a constructive medium-term outlook.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981ddafd9d43ad9e173e05e_1770118711634.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Firstsource Solutions Q3 Revenue Jumps 16%, FY26 Outlook Raised</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-16percent-FY26-Outlook-Raised/6981dd76d9d43ad9e173df75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Firstsource-Solutions-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-16percent-FY26-Outlook-Raised/6981dd76d9d43ad9e173df75</guid><description>Firstsource Solutions reported robust Q3 FY2026 results, with revenues climbing 16.2% YoY to ₹24,431 million. Despite a reported PAT dip due to one-off charges totaling ₹1,001.45 million, adjusted PAT reached ₹2,022 million. The company raised its FY26 revenue growth forecast to 14.5%-15.5% and maintained an EBIT margin outlook of 11.5%-12%. An interim dividend of ₹5.50 per share was declared.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:38:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981dd76d9d43ad9e173df74_1770118595208.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asian Hotels North Raises ₹340 Cr From Elana Holdings, New Majority Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Asian-Hotels-North-Raises-340-Cr-From-Elana-Holdings-New-Majority-Stake/6981dddad9d43ad9e173e148</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Asian-Hotels-North-Raises-340-Cr-From-Elana-Holdings-New-Majority-Stake/6981dddad9d43ad9e173e148</guid><description>Asian Hotels (North) Limited has successfully completed a preferential allotment, raising approximately ₹340 Crores from ELANA HOLDINGS PTE. LTD. at ₹330 per share. This issuance significantly increases the company's paid-up equity capital and establishes ELANA HOLDINGS as the new majority shareholder with a 54.37% stake. The capital infusion signals investor confidence and a strategic shift.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>