<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:58:50 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Shocking Shift: Private Banks Lead Small Business Lending as PSBs Lose Ground to NBFCs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shocking-Shift-Private-Banks-Lead-Small-Business-Lending-as-PSBs-Lose-Ground-to-NBFCs/694cb59be10c98d07888d1cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shocking-Shift-Private-Banks-Lead-Small-Business-Lending-as-PSBs-Lose-Ground-to-NBFCs/694cb59be10c98d07888d1cb</guid><description>A report by SIDBI and CRIF High Mark reveals private banks now lead small business lending in India. Public sector banks (PSBs) have lost market share over the last two years, dropping to 37.8% by September 2025, with non-banking financial companies (NBFCs) steadily gaining ground, especially among sole proprietors. Overall credit exposure to small businesses reached ₹46 lakh crore, growing 16.2% year-on-year, driven by MSME support policies. Working capital loans remain dominant, while unsecured lending also shows strong momentum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:47:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cb59be10c98d07888d1ca_1766634974412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Auto Giant's Secret European Conquest: Motherson Buys Luxury Car's Lifeline!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Auto-Giants-Secret-European-Conquest-Motherson-Buys-Luxury-Cars-Lifeline/694cb557e10c98d07888d165</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Auto-Giants-Secret-European-Conquest-Motherson-Buys-Luxury-Cars-Lifeline/694cb557e10c98d07888d165</guid><description>Samvardhana Motherson International is acquiring Nexans Autoelectric, a German wiring harness maker crucial for BMW, Mercedes-Benz, and Porsche. This strategic move provides direct access to the high-end European automotive market. Analysts from Nomura and Motilal Oswal have reiterated Buy ratings, predicting significant earnings growth and seamless integration of this €749 million sales business.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:46:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cb557e10c98d07888d164_1766634908006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Novo Nordisk Eyes India's Rare Disease Market: New Centers &amp; Govt. Ties Fuel Ambitious Expansion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisk-Eyes-Indias-Rare-Disease-Market-New-Centers-and-Govt-Ties-Fuel-Ambitious-Expansion/694cb533e10c98d07888d11f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisk-Eyes-Indias-Rare-Disease-Market-New-Centers-and-Govt-Ties-Fuel-Ambitious-Expansion/694cb533e10c98d07888d11f</guid><description>Danish pharmaceutical giant Novo Nordisk is significantly expanding its presence in India's rare diseases sector, focusing on inherited blood disorders like thalassemia and sickle cell disease. The company plans to open five new specialized treatment centers by 2026, in addition to one already established, and is collaborating closely with Central and State governments to support affected families and patients. This strategic move aligns with India's national goals to reduce these conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:46:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cb533e10c98d07888d11e_1766634881210.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty 50 SHOCKER: These 5 Stocks MORE THAN DOUBLED Investor Wealth in 2025! Are You In?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-50-SHOCKER-These-5-Stocks-MORE-THAN-DOUBLED-Investor-Wealth-in-2025-Are-You-In/694ca4bfe10c98d07888c2e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-50-SHOCKER-These-5-Stocks-MORE-THAN-DOUBLED-Investor-Wealth-in-2025-Are-You-In/694ca4bfe10c98d07888c2e4</guid><description>In a volatile 2025, five Nifty 50 giants defied the market, delivering over 40% year-to-date returns. From automotive recovery to financial expansion, these stocks have rewarded shareholders significantly, showcasing pockets of strong growth amidst market uncertainties. Key drivers include robust revenue increases and profit surges, making them standouts for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 02:36:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ca4bfe10c98d07888c2e3_1766630659487.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Stock Market EXPLODES in 2025! Sensex, Nifty &amp; More Smash All-Time Highs – What You NEED to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Stock-Market-EXPLODES-in-2025-Sensex-Nifty-and-More-Smash-All-Time-Highs-What-You-NEED-to-Know/694c9a61e10c98d07888a155</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Stock-Market-EXPLODES-in-2025-Sensex-Nifty-and-More-Smash-All-Time-Highs-What-You-NEED-to-Know/694c9a61e10c98d07888a155</guid><description>In 2025, India's stock market witnessed historic milestones as key indices like the BSE Sensex and Nifty 50 surged to unprecedented all-time highs. The Sensex closed at a record 86,159.02, while the Nifty 50 reached 26,325.80. The Bank Nifty also broke the 60,000 mark, with midcap and broader indices like Nifty Midcap 100 and Nifty 500 joining the rally, signaling a robust year for Indian equities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:49:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9a61e10c98d07888a154_1766628003138.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Uncover India's Next Multibaggers: 3 Hidden Cable Stocks Set for Explosive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Uncover-Indias-Next-Multibaggers-3-Hidden-Cable-Stocks-Set-for-Explosive-Growth/694c9b33e10c98d07888a263</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Uncover-Indias-Next-Multibaggers-3-Hidden-Cable-Stocks-Set-for-Explosive-Growth/694c9b33e10c98d07888a263</guid><description>As India's infrastructure boom accelerates, demand for cables and wires surges across sectors like power, railways, and green energy. While large players like Polycab India Limited and KEI Industries Limited are well-known, this analysis highlights three small-cap cable manufacturers – Dynamic Cables Limited, Universal Cables Limited, and Paramount Communications Limited – that offer greater multibagger potential. The article explains how operating leverage, increasing capacity utilization, and absorption of fixed costs can drive significant earnings growth for these less-recognized companies, offering investors opportunities beyond the market leaders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:49:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9b33e10c98d07888a262_1766628313684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FIIs &amp; DIIs Pour Billions Into THIS AC Stock As Sector Tanks! Find Out Why!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FIIs-and-DIIs-Pour-Billions-Into-THIS-AC-Stock-As-Sector-Tanks-Find-Out-Why/694c9a45e10c98d07888a113</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FIIs-and-DIIs-Pour-Billions-Into-THIS-AC-Stock-As-Sector-Tanks-Find-Out-Why/694c9a45e10c98d07888a113</guid><description>Despite a 10.5% annual drop in the Nifty Consumer Durable index and significant FII selling worth ₹11,130 crore in Q2FY26, institutional investors are heavily backing Amber Enterprise India Limited. Both FIIs and DIIs increased their stakes, signaling confidence in the company's diversification into electronics manufacturing services, railway components, and solar/EV sectors, even as the company reported a Q2 loss. Amber Enterprise is a key AC component manufacturer and is expanding aggressively, particularly in PCB manufacturing facilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:49:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9a45e10c98d07888a112_1766628108519.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unseen Hero: The 'Tyre Skeleton' Stock Making Every 2nd Car Run Safely - Discover Rajratan's Hidden Empire!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Unseen-Hero-The-Tyre-Skeleton-Stock-Making-Every-2nd-Car-Run-Safely-Discover-Rajratans-Hidden-Empire/694c9a1be10c98d07888a0c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Unseen-Hero-The-Tyre-Skeleton-Stock-Making-Every-2nd-Car-Run-Safely-Discover-Rajratans-Hidden-Empire/694c9a1be10c98d07888a0c3</guid><description>Rajratan Global Wire Ltd is the dominant leader in India's essential bead wire market, the critical 'tyre skeleton' that ensures tyre safety. With over 50% domestic market share and a strategic international presence, particularly in Thailand, the company supplies major global tyre manufacturers, underpinning its vital role in the automotive sector. Its specialized product and long OEM approval cycles create a strong competitive moat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:49:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9a1be10c98d07888a0c2_1766627932891.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jaipur's Spice IPO Shatters Records: 918x Oversubscribed, Pulls in ₹25,300 Crore Bids!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Jaipurs-Spice-IPO-Shatters-Records-918x-Oversubscribed-Pulls-in-25300-Crore-Bids/694c991ae10c98d078889f5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Jaipurs-Spice-IPO-Shatters-Records-918x-Oversubscribed-Pulls-in-25300-Crore-Bids/694c991ae10c98d078889f5a</guid><description>Jaipur-based Shyam Dhani Industries' initial public offering (IPO) for its masala products was massively oversubscribed, hitting 918 times its target. The ₹38.5 crore IPO received bids worth approximately ₹25,300 crore, making it the fifth most subscribed SME IPO in India's history and the top performer for 2025. Funds will support working capital, loan repayment, marketing, and expansion, including a solar plant.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:43:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c991ae10c98d078889f59_1766627690511.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tired of Surprise Subscription Bills? NPCI's New Portal Makes Managing Autopay Effortless!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tired-of-Surprise-Subscription-Bills-NPCIs-New-Portal-Makes-Managing-Autopay-Effortless/694c9972e10c98d078889fe1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tired-of-Surprise-Subscription-Bills-NPCIs-New-Portal-Makes-Managing-Autopay-Effortless/694c9972e10c98d078889fe1</guid><description>The National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI) has launched a new central portal, upihelp.npci.org.in, simplifying the management of UPI autopay standing instructions. This initiative aims to enhance transparency and consumer control over recurring charges and subscriptions, curbing opaque billing practices. By December 31, 2025, all UPI network members must implement these changes, allowing users to view, manage, and even port mandates across different UPI apps with enhanced security features.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:43:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9972e10c98d078889fe0_1766627853673.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tired of Surprise Subscription Bills? NPCI's New Portal Makes Managing Autopay Effortless!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tired-of-Surprise-Subscription-Bills-NPCIs-New-Portal-Makes-Managing-Autopay-Effortless/694c9931e10c98d078889f85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tired-of-Surprise-Subscription-Bills-NPCIs-New-Portal-Makes-Managing-Autopay-Effortless/694c9931e10c98d078889f85</guid><description>The National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI) has launched a new central portal, upihelp.npci.org.in, simplifying the management of UPI autopay standing instructions. This initiative aims to enhance transparency and consumer control over recurring charges and subscriptions, curbing opaque billing practices. By December 31, 2025, all UPI network members must implement these changes, allowing users to view, manage, and even port mandates across different UPI apps with enhanced security features.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:43:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9931e10c98d078889f84_1766627724393.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Engineer Built Buffett's $174 Billion Cash Machine: The Secret to Berkshire's Success Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Engineer-Built-Buffetts-174-Billion-Cash-Machine-The-Secret-to-Berkshires-Success-Revealed/694c927de10c98d078889b20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Engineer-Built-Buffetts-174-Billion-Cash-Machine-The-Secret-to-Berkshires-Success-Revealed/694c927de10c98d078889b20</guid><description>Ajit Jain, an Indian engineer with no finance background, transformed Berkshire Hathaway's struggling reinsurance business under Warren Buffett. He masterfully managed the company's 'float' – premiums collected but not yet paid out – growing it to $174 billion. This capital pool, generating billions annually, fuels Buffett's investments and highlights Jain's pivotal role in Berkshire's vast empire.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:16:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c927de10c98d078889b1f_1766625997375.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Buffett Era Ends! Greg Abel Takes Over Berkshire's $1.1 Trillion Empire – 5 Key Changes Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Buffett-Era-Ends-Greg-Abel-Takes-Over-Berkshires-11-Trillion-Empire-5-Key-Changes-Ahead/694c9248e10c98d078889ad3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Buffett-Era-Ends-Greg-Abel-Takes-Over-Berkshires-11-Trillion-Empire-5-Key-Changes-Ahead/694c9248e10c98d078889ad3</guid><description>Greg Abel is set to succeed Warren Buffett as CEO of Berkshire Hathaway by the end of 2026. Abel, known for his strong financial background and success scaling Berkshire Hathaway Energy, is expected to bring a more active management style and tackle the challenge of deploying Berkshire's substantial $334 billion cash reserves. Investors anticipate a focus on operational rigor and potentially new sectors like technology and renewable energy, marking a significant shift from Buffett's era.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:16:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c9248e10c98d078889ad2_1766626140114.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Doubles Duplicate Securities Limit to ₹10 Lakh: Faster Process for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Doubles-Duplicate-Securities-Limit-to-10-Lakh-Faster-Process-for-Investors/694c920de10c98d078889a7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Doubles-Duplicate-Securities-Limit-to-10-Lakh-Faster-Process-for-Investors/694c920de10c98d078889a7f</guid><description>SEBI has significantly eased the process for issuing duplicate securities by doubling the monetary threshold for simplified documentation to ₹10 lakh. Investors holding securities valued up to ₹10,000 can now submit a simple undertaking on plain paper, while those above ₹10 lakh will need additional documents like an FIR or police complaint. Notarization is waived for lower-value holdings. These measures aim to make the process faster, more efficient, and promote dematerialization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:15:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c920de10c98d078889a7e_1766625876676.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Supercharges Auto Sector! Govt Nearly Doubles EV Funds – Big Wins or Missed Opportunities Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Supercharges-Auto-Sector-Govt-Nearly-Doubles-EV-Funds-Big-Wins-or-Missed-Opportunities-Ahead/694c8d80e10c98d078889839</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Supercharges-Auto-Sector-Govt-Nearly-Doubles-EV-Funds-Big-Wins-or-Missed-Opportunities-Ahead/694c8d80e10c98d078889839</guid><description>India's government plans to nearly double funding for its auto and auto component Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme to ₹5,500 crore in FY27, reinforcing its commitment to electric vehicle (EV) manufacturing and advanced automotive tech. Despite the increased allocation, new EV makers like Ather Energy are unlikely to get their application window reopened, as the scheme's eligibility criteria continue to favour established players. The move aims to boost domestic production, attract investment, and create jobs in the rapidly growing EV market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:53:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8d80e10c98d078889838_1766624845857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSNL STUNNER: 3G to VANISH! Is YOUR phone ready for the BIG 4G upgrade?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/BSNL-STUNNER-3G-to-VANISH-Is-YOUR-phone-ready-for-the-BIG-4G-upgrade/694c8c80e10c98d07888977a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/BSNL-STUNNER-3G-to-VANISH-Is-YOUR-phone-ready-for-the-BIG-4G-upgrade/694c8c80e10c98d07888977a</guid><description>State-owned telecom operator Bharat Sanchar Nigam Ltd (BSNL) is shutting down its 3G mobile services nationwide as part of a major cost-cutting and network upgrade initiative. The company will also terminate maintenance contracts with vendors like Nokia and ZTE for 3G sites. This move allows BSNL to reallocate crucial 2100 MHz spectrum entirely for its 4G network, aiming to boost capacity and performance. Users with 3G-only SIM cards or older handsets may need to upgrade to ensure continued service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:52:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8c80e10c98d078889779_1766624494274.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Giant in $500M US Patent War: Will Core Tech Ideas Be Blocked?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Giant-in-500M-US-Patent-War-Will-Core-Tech-Ideas-Be-Blocked/694c8ce8e10c98d0788897c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Giant-in-500M-US-Patent-War-Will-Core-Tech-Ideas-Be-Blocked/694c8ce8e10c98d0788897c2</guid><description>Hexaware Technologies has asked a US court to dismiss a $500 million patent infringement lawsuit filed by Natsoft. Hexaware argues the inventions, related to application modernization and GenAI, are abstract ideas not eligible for patents under US law. Natsoft claims Hexaware used software covered by nine of its patents, seeking damages that could significantly impact Hexaware's finances. The case highlights ongoing legal battles over software innovation patents.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:52:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8ce8e10c98d0788897c1_1766624736166.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Unlocks Simpler Investing: Major Demat Account Shake-up Coming!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Unlocks-Simpler-Investing-Major-Demat-Account-Shake-up-Coming/694c8b72e10c98d07888967c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Unlocks-Simpler-Investing-Major-Demat-Account-Shake-up-Coming/694c8b72e10c98d07888967c</guid><description>India's market regulator, SEBI, is simplifying Basic Services Demat Account (BSDA) rules effective March 31, 2026. Zero Coupon Zero Principal (ZCZP) bonds and delisted securities will no longer count towards the eligibility threshold for BSDA, making it easier for small investors. Depository Participants must now review accounts quarterly and convert eligible ones to BSDA by default unless investors actively opt out. This aims to reduce compliance burdens and enhance the BSDA facility.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:47:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8b72e10c98d07888967b_1766624345868.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Agri-Derivatives Market in Crisis: Why Key Futures Suspension Led to Sharp Decline!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Agri-Derivatives-Market-in-Crisis-Why-Key-Futures-Suspension-Led-to-Sharp-Decline/694c8afbe10c98d0788895f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Agri-Derivatives-Market-in-Crisis-Why-Key-Futures-Suspension-Led-to-Sharp-Decline/694c8afbe10c98d0788895f9</guid><description>India's agricultural derivatives market is facing a severe downturn, with turnover declining significantly since the suspension of seven liquid agri-futures in December 2021. SEBI and NCDEX data show a sharp drop in notional turnover and reduced participation from farmers and value chain partners. Experts are calling for a review of market microstructure and a potential revocation of suspensions to restore vitality and crucial risk management functions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:46:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8afbe10c98d0788895f8_1766624098816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Growth Secret: Tackle Air Pollution &amp; Boost Economy Together! EVs &amp; New Cities Key.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Secret-Tackle-Air-Pollution-and-Boost-Economy-Together-EVs-and-New-Cities-Key/694c8b72e10c98d0788896a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Secret-Tackle-Air-Pollution-and-Boost-Economy-Together-EVs-and-New-Cities-Key/694c8b72e10c98d0788896a7</guid><description>India faces a high Air Quality Index (AQI) problem, with policymakers fearing environmental action might hinder economic growth. However, an economist suggests this is an exaggerated fear. Solutions include subsidizing Electric Vehicles (EVs) and developing new urban centers to reduce pollution and congestion in big cities. These strategies can lower AQI without sacrificing GDP growth, while also improving public health and long-term economic potential.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:46:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8b72e10c98d0788896a6_1766624180925.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Paradox: IT Giants TCS, Accenture See Revenue Growth, But Is It New Money?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Paradox-IT-Giants-TCS-Accenture-See-Revenue-Growth-But-Is-It-New-Money/694c85fee10c98d078889418</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Paradox-IT-Giants-TCS-Accenture-See-Revenue-Growth-But-Is-It-New-Money/694c85fee10c98d078889418</guid><description>Major IT services companies like Tata Consultancy Services and Accenture are reporting impressive revenue growth from Artificial Intelligence. However, experts and company leaders suggest this growth may be cannibalizing existing revenue streams, improving efficiency rather than adding net new income. This trend raises questions about AI's true financial contribution beyond internal productivity gains.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:24:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c85fee10c98d078889417_1766622815357.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>