<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:55:43 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India REITs/InvITs: Debt Surge Fuels Growth Amidst Regulatory Tightening</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-REITsInvITs-Debt-Surge-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Regulatory-Tightening/699deddf04a25a58c8523243</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-REITsInvITs-Debt-Surge-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Regulatory-Tightening/699deddf04a25a58c8523243</guid><description>Specialized investment vehicles in India's real estate and infrastructure sectors are on track for record debt fundraising in FY26, raising ₹37,742 crore. The Reserve Bank of India's proposal to allow direct bank lending aims to lower borrowing costs. However, this surge in leverage is met with enhanced regulatory oversight and potential valuation concerns for high-performing trusts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kotak AMC Crosses ₹6 Trillion; IPO Market Shows Mixed Investor Signals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Kotak-AMC-Crosses-6-Trillion-IPO-Market-Shows-Mixed-Investor-Signals/699dedc004a25a58c8522c48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Kotak-AMC-Crosses-6-Trillion-IPO-Market-Shows-Mixed-Investor-Signals/699dedc004a25a58c8522c48</guid><description>Kotak Mahindra Asset Management Company (AMC) has surpassed ₹6 trillion in assets under management (AUM), driven significantly by its equity portfolio and consistent Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) inflows exceeding ₹1,500 crore monthly. Meanwhile, India's IPO market shows a bifurcated investor response: Gaudium IVF's IPO garnered strong demand at 7.27 times subscription, positioning it as a pioneer in the fertility sector's public market debut, while Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions' IPO secured 45% subscription on its second day, indicating cautious interest in the renewable energy space.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:28:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dedc004a25a58c8522c47_1771958478958.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Grid Narela Commissions 8.1 GW Rajasthan Solar Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Narela-Commissions-81-GW-Rajasthan-Solar-Project/699ded8f04a25a58c8521727</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Narela-Commissions-81-GW-Rajasthan-Solar-Project/699ded8f04a25a58c8521727</guid><description>POWERGRID Narela Transmission Limited, a subsidiary of Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd., has successfully commissioned its 8.1 GW transmission project in Rajasthan. The project is key to evacuating solar power and strengthens India's renewable energy infrastructure. This milestone aligns with national green energy targets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Exide Industries Invests ₹100 Cr in EV Battery Arm; Total Stake ₹4,352 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Exide-Industries-Invests-100-Cr-in-EV-Battery-Arm-Total-Stake-4352-Cr/699ded2004a25a58c851e05d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Exide-Industries-Invests-100-Cr-in-EV-Battery-Arm-Total-Stake-4352-Cr/699ded2004a25a58c851e05d</guid><description>Exide Industries Limited has infused an additional ₹100 crore into its wholly-owned subsidiary, Exide Energy Solutions Limited (EESL). This capital injection for EESL's greenfield lithium-ion battery project brings Exide's total investment in the subsidiary to ₹4,352.23 crore. Despite EESL reporting a net loss of ₹209.12 crore on a turnover of ₹116.89 crore in FY2024-25, Exide continues to back its strategic expansion into the burgeoning EV battery market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IOL Chemicals gets Europe nod for Cardiovascular API Clopidogrel Besilate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/IOL-Chemicals-gets-Europe-nod-for-Cardiovascular-API-Clopidogrel-Besilate/699ded1b04a25a58c851e031</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/IOL-Chemicals-gets-Europe-nod-for-Cardiovascular-API-Clopidogrel-Besilate/699ded1b04a25a58c851e031</guid><description>IOL Chemicals and Pharmaceuticals Limited announced it has received a Certificate of Suitability (CEP) from the European Directorate for the Quality of Medicines &amp; Health Care (EDQM) for its active pharmaceutical ingredient (API) 'Clopidogrel Besilate'. This pivotal certification, effective February 23, 2026, significantly enhances the company's market access for this key cardiovascular drug ingredient within Europe, complementing its existing CEP for 'Clopidogrel Bisulphate'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Infrastructure Fuels Crypto Miner Surge, Tech Adapts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Infrastructure-Fuels-Crypto-Miner-Surge-Tech-Adapts/699decd204a25a58c851cbd0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Infrastructure-Fuels-Crypto-Miner-Surge-Tech-Adapts/699decd204a25a58c851cbd0</guid><description>Bitcoin surpassed $64,000, mirroring a broader rebound in risk assets, largely propelled by advancements in artificial intelligence. Software companies demonstrated resilience by integrating AI through strategic partnerships, while select Bitcoin miners, directly benefiting from AI data center infrastructure demands, saw significant gains. This rally highlights a growing bifurcation, with AI infrastructure plays outperforming broader crypto sentiment and creating distinct opportunities and risks across the technology and digital asset sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sumuka Agro Sets March 9 Record Date for Gujjubhai Foods Merger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sumuka-Agro-Sets-March-9-Record-Date-for-Gujjubhai-Foods-Merger/699decce04a25a58c851cbae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sumuka-Agro-Sets-March-9-Record-Date-for-Gujjubhai-Foods-Merger/699decce04a25a58c851cbae</guid><description>Sumuka Agro Industries Limited has fixed March 9, 2026, as the record date to determine the eligibility of Gujjubhai Foods Private Limited shareholders for the merger. The approved share exchange ratio is 7 Sumuka Agro shares for every 4 Gujjubhai Foods shares. This corporate action follows the NCLT's sanction of the merger, paving the way for operational consolidation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>YES BANK FY25 ESG Score Hits 80.5; Governance Strong Amid Compliance Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/YES-BANK-FY25-ESG-Score-Hits-805-Governance-Strong-Amid-Compliance-Risks/699debfb04a25a58c851bcc6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/YES-BANK-FY25-ESG-Score-Hits-805-Governance-Strong-Amid-Compliance-Risks/699debfb04a25a58c851bcc6</guid><description>YES BANK has received an ESG score of 80.5 for FY 2024-25 from SES ESG Research, an improvement from the previous year. The bank highlights strong governance and environmental scores. However, the rating comes alongside disclosures of ongoing governance concerns, including board non-compliance, regulatory penalties, and a notable number of data privacy and sexual harassment complaints during the fiscal year.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sumuka Agro Industries: Gujjubhai Foods Merger Effective Feb 23, 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sumuka-Agro-Industries-Gujjubhai-Foods-Merger-Effective-Feb-23-2026/699debf504a25a58c851bc2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sumuka-Agro-Industries-Gujjubhai-Foods-Merger-Effective-Feb-23-2026/699debf504a25a58c851bc2a</guid><description>Sumuka Agro Industries Limited has announced the merger with Gujjubhai Foods Private Limited is now effective from February 23, 2026. This consolidation, following approval from the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) and completion of Ministry of Corporate Affairs filings, integrates Gujjubhai Foods into Sumuka Agro. The move is aimed at streamlining operations and strengthening the combined entity's market presence in the FMCG sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:20:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699debf504a25a58c851bc29_1771958121494.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Iykot Hitech Promoters Sell 34.58% Stake; Open Offer Triggered</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Iykot-Hitech-Promoters-Sell-3458percent-Stake-Open-Offer-Triggered/699debf004a25a58c851bc12</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Iykot-Hitech-Promoters-Sell-3458percent-Stake-Open-Offer-Triggered/699debf004a25a58c851bc12</guid><description>Iykot Hitech Toolroom is set for a change in control as its promoters execute a Share Purchase Agreement to sell 34.58% stake to Aspect Global Ventures Private Limited for ₹8 per share. This transaction mandates an open offer to public shareholders at ₹8.50 per share. Concurrently, the company approved the forfeiture of over 99 lakh partly paid-up equity shares due to unpaid call money, signalling recent financial pressure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:20:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699debf004a25a58c851bc11_1771959270913.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>T.T. Limited: Promoter Buys Shares, Stake Dilutes Sharply to 24.02%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/TT-Limited-Promoter-Buys-Shares-Stake-Dilutes-Sharply-to-2402percent/699deb8704a25a58c851b941</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/TT-Limited-Promoter-Buys-Shares-Stake-Dilutes-Sharply-to-2402percent/699deb8704a25a58c851b941</guid><description>T.T. Limited's promoter group, T T Brands Limited, acquired 43,138 shares for ₹4.16 lakh on February 24, 2026. However, the promoter's stake percentage sharply fell from 34.0308% to 24.02%. This substantial dilution, despite a purchase, points to a significant increase in the company's total outstanding shares, likely due to recent corporate actions like a rights issue and share split, impacting existing shareholders' proportional ownership.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindalco's Novelis Secures $200M Investment from AV Minerals, Bolstering IPO Prospects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindalcos-Novelis-Secures-200M-Investment-from-AV-Minerals-Bolstering-IPO-Prospects/699deaf504a25a58c851b597</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindalcos-Novelis-Secures-200M-Investment-from-AV-Minerals-Bolstering-IPO-Prospects/699deaf504a25a58c851b597</guid><description>Novelis Inc., a subsidiary of Hindalco Industries, has entered into a subscription agreement with AV Minerals (Netherlands) N.V. for the purchase of 13,33,333 common shares valued at approximately $200 million. This significant capital infusion comes as Novelis continues to navigate its path towards a potential initial public offering (IPO), signalling continued investor confidence in the global aluminum leader.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Schaeffler India FY25 Profit Jumps 22%; Declares ₹35 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Schaeffler-India-FY25-Profit-Jumps-22percent-Declares-35-Dividend/699dead704a25a58c851b48c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Schaeffler-India-FY25-Profit-Jumps-22percent-Declares-35-Dividend/699dead704a25a58c851b48c</guid><description>Schaeffler India reported robust FY25 results with a 22.4% rise in net profit to ₹11,962 crore and 16.3% revenue growth to ₹9,395 crore, driven by strong automotive sector demand. The company also declared a dividend of ₹35 per share, signalling financial health. A minor impact on Q4 PBT margin was noted due to the labour code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:15:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dead704a25a58c851b48b_1771957218129.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Akme Fintrade: Acquirer Group Lifts Stake to 6.78% via Open Market Buys</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-Acquirer-Group-Lifts-Stake-to-678percent-via-Open-Market-Buys/699deaad04a25a58c851b340</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-Acquirer-Group-Lifts-Stake-to-678percent-via-Open-Market-Buys/699deaad04a25a58c851b340</guid><description>AKME FINTRADE (INDIA) LTD. disclosed a significant shareholding increase under SEBI's SAST regulations. A group of acquirers, led by Subhash Phootarmal Rathod, collectively bought 1.253% of the company's voting capital via open market transactions between February 20-24, 2026. Their total holding now stands at 6.783%. This move signifies sustained interest from the acquirer group in the non-banking financial company.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:15:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699deaad04a25a58c851b33f_1771957093832.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Onix Solar Energy Clarifies Bank Guarantee Allegations; Operations Unaffected</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Onix-Solar-Energy-Clarifies-Bank-Guarantee-Allegations-Operations-Unaffected/699dea1204a25a58c851af2b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Onix-Solar-Energy-Clarifies-Bank-Guarantee-Allegations-Operations-Unaffected/699dea1204a25a58c851af2b</guid><description>Onix Solar Energy Limited has issued a clarification regarding media reports alleging fraudulent bank guarantee issues for its Maharashtra solar projects. The company stated it is not named as an accused in the FIR, that discrepancies in bank guarantees were rectified before the FIR filing, and confirmed its ongoing operations and financial position remain unaffected. The clarification comes amid reports of FIRs filed against associated entities for forged guarantees.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:12:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dea1204a25a58c851af2a_1771956987482.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Orient Electric: KYC Update Mandate for Physical Shareholders; Dividend Hold Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Orient-Electric-KYC-Update-Mandate-for-Physical-Shareholders-Dividend-Hold-Looms/699de86504a25a58c8515686</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Orient-Electric-KYC-Update-Mandate-for-Physical-Shareholders-Dividend-Hold-Looms/699de86504a25a58c8515686</guid><description>Orient Electric has issued a crucial update for shareholders holding physical securities, emphasizing mandatory KYC, PAN, and nomination details. Citing SEBI mandates, the company will withhold dividend payments for non-compliant shareholders from April 1, 2024. A special one-year window (Feb 5, 2026 - Feb 4, 2027) is also open for transferring physical securities sold before April 1, 2019.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:05:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de86504a25a58c8515685_1771958683826.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>WPIL Ltd: INR 1,300Cr+ Revenue; Global Push Targets 20% Product Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/WPIL-Ltd-INR-1300Cr-Revenue-Global-Push-Targets-20percent-Product-Growth/699de85b04a25a58c8514d66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/WPIL-Ltd-INR-1300Cr-Revenue-Global-Push-Targets-20percent-Product-Growth/699de85b04a25a58c8514d66</guid><description>WPIL Limited has reported over INR 1,300 crore in revenue for the first nine months of FY26, driven by its engineered flow solutions business. The company is aggressively expanding its global footprint through strategic acquisitions and joint ventures, targeting approximately 20% year-over-year growth in its product business over the next five years. While facing temporary moderation in its project business due to domestic funding, WPIL is focusing on high-margin international markets and exports to fuel future growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks Plunge on AI Disruption and Sovereign Risk Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Plunge-on-AI-Disruption-and-Sovereign-Risk-Fears/699de77104a25a58c850f5f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Plunge-on-AI-Disruption-and-Sovereign-Risk-Fears/699de77104a25a58c850f5f2</guid><description>The Indian IT sector is in distress following a Citrini Research report detailing AI-driven contract cancellations and risks to consumption-driven economies. The Nifty IT Index plummeted 4.74% to a 30-month low, entering bear-market territory with a 22% drop since February 4th. Benchmark indices also fell, wiping out ₹3.55 lakh crore in market capitalization. Concerns extend beyond job losses to potential sovereign economic vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Quintegra Solutions Seeks NCLT Nod for Capital Reduction to Write Off Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Quintegra-Solutions-Seeks-NCLT-Nod-for-Capital-Reduction-to-Write-Off-Losses/699de74304a25a58c850f563</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Quintegra-Solutions-Seeks-NCLT-Nod-for-Capital-Reduction-to-Write-Off-Losses/699de74304a25a58c850f563</guid><description>Quintegra Solutions Limited has applied to the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), Chennai, to reduce its share capital. The move, approved by shareholders, aims to write off accumulated losses of ₹178.12 crore by adjusting reserves, thereby improving the company's financial presentation and attracting investors. The face value of shares will be reduced from ₹10 to ₹1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>P&amp;G Hygiene's Legal Head Hegde to Oversee India, MEA Regional Operations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PandG-Hygienes-Legal-Head-Hegde-to-Oversee-India-MEA-Regional-Operations/699de74004a25a58c850f54d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PandG-Hygienes-Legal-Head-Hegde-to-Oversee-India-MEA-Regional-Operations/699de74004a25a58c850f54d</guid><description>Procter &amp; Gamble Hygiene &amp; Health Care Limited announced on February 24, 2026, that Mr. Ghanashyam Hegde, Legal Head, Executive Director, and Company Secretary, will assume a new regional role. Effective July 1, 2026, he will become Vice President &amp; Associate General Counsel – Market Operations, overseeing India, Middle East, Turkey, and Africa. This move signifies a broadening of responsibilities for key legal oversight within P&amp;G's expansive emerging markets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de74004a25a58c850f54c_1771956137566.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys Q3 FY26: AI Revenue Hits 5.5%; 90% Workforce AI-Enabled</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Q3-FY26-AI-Revenue-Hits-55percent-90percent-Workforce-AI-Enabled/699de6ff04a25a58c850f450</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Q3-FY26-AI-Revenue-Hits-55percent-90percent-Workforce-AI-Enabled/699de6ff04a25a58c850f450</guid><description>Infosys is aggressively integrating AI, with 5.5% of Q3 FY26 revenue now from AI and 90% of its workforce AI-enabled. Management forecasts a $300-$400 billion AI services market and reaffirms margin guidance, reinvesting AI-driven cost savings. Key challenges include the deployment gap and execution at scale.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:59:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de6ff04a25a58c850f44f_1771956107386.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SAMHI Subsidiary Gets Go-Ahead for 235-Room Hotel Expansion in Bangalore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SAMHI-Subsidiary-Gets-Go-Ahead-for-235-Room-Hotel-Expansion-in-Bangalore/699de6ca04a25a58c850f3cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SAMHI-Subsidiary-Gets-Go-Ahead-for-235-Room-Hotel-Expansion-in-Bangalore/699de6ca04a25a58c850f3cf</guid><description>SAMHI Hotels' subsidiary, ITHPL, has secured KIADB sanctioned layout plans for a second hotel development in Whitefield, Bangalore. This expansion will add approximately 235 rooms to its existing 142-room Westin-branded hotel, bringing the total inventory at the complex to around 377 rooms, reinforcing its presence in a key commercial hub.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:58:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de6ca04a25a58c850f3ce_1771956024089.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kome-On Communication Ltd AGM March 19; Delisting Proceedings Continue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kome-On-Communication-Ltd-AGM-March-19-Delisting-Proceedings-Continue/699de67504a25a58c850f30c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kome-On-Communication-Ltd-AGM-March-19-Delisting-Proceedings-Continue/699de67504a25a58c850f30c</guid><description>Kome-On Communication Limited has scheduled its 30th Annual General Meeting (AGM) for March 19, 2026, to adopt FY 2022-23 audited financials and appoint directors. The company appointed Mr. Shankar Kokane and Mrs. Renu Beniwal as Non-Executive Independent Directors. However, BSE Limited issued a delisting order on December 11, 2025, with ongoing proceedings until April 10, 2026, regarding the potential compulsory delisting of its equity shares, creating significant uncertainty for its trading status.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:57:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de67504a25a58c850f30b_1771955973092.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Subsidiary Wins 300 MW Gujarat Wind Project from SECI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Waaree-Energies-Subsidiary-Wins-300-MW-Gujarat-Wind-Project-from-SECI/699de66d04a25a58c850f2f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Waaree-Energies-Subsidiary-Wins-300-MW-Gujarat-Wind-Project-from-SECI/699de66d04a25a58c850f2f5</guid><description>Waaree Energies' subsidiary, Waaree Forever Energies, has been awarded a 300 MW wind power project in Dwarka, Gujarat, by the Solar Energy Corporation of India (SECI). This significant win includes a 25-year Power Purchase Agreement (PPA), providing long-term revenue visibility and reinforcing Waaree's expanding footprint in India's renewable energy sector, particularly in wind power development.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:57:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de66d04a25a58c850f2f4_1771956903092.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>H.G. Infra Wins ₹1,582 Cr NHAI Odisha Road Project as L-1 Bidder</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HG-Infra-Wins-1582-Cr-NHAI-Odisha-Road-Project-as-L-1-Bidder/699de5b304a25a58c850f0d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HG-Infra-Wins-1582-Cr-NHAI-Odisha-Road-Project-as-L-1-Bidder/699de5b304a25a58c850f0d1</guid><description>H.G. Infra Engineering Limited has been declared the Lowest (L-1) bidder by the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for a significant road project in Odisha. The bid is valued at ₹1,582.11 crore for the construction of a new six-lane access-controlled Capital Region Ring Road, Package-III. This marks a substantial addition to the company's order book, reinforcing its position in the infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:53:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de5b304a25a58c850f0d0_1771955749000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lux Industries Ratings Affirmed: AA Stable for ₹464Cr Debt by Acuite</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lux-Industries-Ratings-Affirmed-AA-Stable-for-464Cr-Debt-by-Acuite/699de4bb04a25a58c850ec80</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lux-Industries-Ratings-Affirmed-AA-Stable-for-464Cr-Debt-by-Acuite/699de4bb04a25a58c850ec80</guid><description>Lux Industries Limited's long-term bank facilities worth ₹464.18 crore have been reaffirmed at 'AA (Stable)' by Acuite Ratings &amp; Research Limited. Short-term facilities of ₹1.50 crore also retain an 'A1+ (Stable)' rating. This reaffirmation signals continued financial stability for the Kolkata-based apparel manufacturer, despite recent pressures on its profitability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:49:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de4bb04a25a58c850ec7f_1771955541476.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Birla Cotsyn Revival: NCLT Approves ₹52.43 Cr Scheme, Exits CIRP</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Birla-Cotsyn-Revival-NCLT-Approves-5243-Cr-Scheme-Exits-CIRP/699de46204a25a58c850ea7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Birla-Cotsyn-Revival-NCLT-Approves-5243-Cr-Scheme-Exits-CIRP/699de46204a25a58c850ea7b</guid><description>National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) has approved a Composite Scheme of Compromise and Arrangement for Birla Cotsyn (India) Limited, committing ₹52.43 Crore for its revival. This marks the company's exit from Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) and liquidation, paving the way for its continuation as a going concern under new acquirers. The approved scheme offers a significantly higher recovery for creditors compared to previous resolution attempts. This revival is expected to restore operations and generate economic value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:48:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de46204a25a58c850ea7a_1771955454275.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>3M India Seeks Shareholder Nod for Directors, ₹1200 Cr RPTs via Postal Ballot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/3M-India-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-Directors-1200-Cr-RPTs-via-Postal-Ballot/699de32b04a25a58c850e1e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/3M-India-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-Directors-1200-Cr-RPTs-via-Postal-Ballot/699de32b04a25a58c850e1e4</guid><description>3M India Limited has initiated a postal ballot process, seeking shareholder approval for crucial matters including the appointment of two new directors and significant related party transactions (RPTs) totaling ₹1,309 crore for FY 2026-27. The e-voting period runs from February 25 to March 26, 2026. Shareholder assent is vital for operational continuity and leadership transition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>StarlinePS Enterprises ₹3,300 Cr Fundraise Approved; Promoter Stake Dilutes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/StarlinePS-Enterprises-3300-Cr-Fundraise-Approved-Promoter-Stake-Dilutes/699de32604a25a58c850e1c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/StarlinePS-Enterprises-3300-Cr-Fundraise-Approved-Promoter-Stake-Dilutes/699de32604a25a58c850e1c5</guid><description>StarlinePS Enterprises Limited's shareholders have approved a massive ₹3,300 crore fundraising plan via a preferential issue of equity shares and convertible warrants. The move is set to significantly alter the company's shareholding structure, with promoter holding expected to dilute to 39.12% post-allotment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:43:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de32604a25a58c850e1c4_1771955287952.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>S H Kelkar FY25 Revenue ₹2,147 Cr; Projects ₹3,377 Cr Sales by FY29</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/S-H-Kelkar-FY25-Revenue-2147-Cr-Projects-3377-Cr-Sales-by-FY29/699de26b04a25a58c850a76c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/S-H-Kelkar-FY25-Revenue-2147-Cr-Projects-3377-Cr-Sales-by-FY29/699de26b04a25a58c850a76c</guid><description>S H Kelkar and Company Limited has submitted its investor presentation for the Kotak Annual Investor Conference, highlighting robust FY25 performance with total income at ₹2,147 crore and cash profit of ₹224 crore. The company detailed its growth strategy, including global expansion and capacity enhancements, projecting sales to reach ₹3,377 crore by FY29. It also outlined its focus on operational efficiency and ESG initiatives.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:39:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de26b04a25a58c850a76b_1771955442398.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Narayana Hrudayalaya Q3 Profit Surges 103%; Eyes India Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Narayana-Hrudayalaya-Q3-Profit-Surges-103percent-Eyes-India-Expansion/699de19904a25a58c85065d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Narayana-Hrudayalaya-Q3-Profit-Surges-103percent-Eyes-India-Expansion/699de19904a25a58c85065d2</guid><description>Narayana Hrudayalaya reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with consolidated profit after tax soaring 103% year-on-year to ₹372 crore on revenue growth of 16% to ₹1,218 crore. The company highlighted strong performance in its Indian operations, driven by specialized surgeries and margin improvements. Management reiterated a focus on maintaining leverage below 2.5x net debt to EBITDA and plans significant capex for domestic expansion, while navigating the integration of its UK acquisition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:36:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de19904a25a58c85065d1_1771955778820.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HealthCare Global Enterprises Approves ₹425 Cr Rights Issue At ₹512 Per Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HealthCare-Global-Enterprises-Approves-425-Cr-Rights-Issue-At-512-Per-Share/699de18b04a25a58c8506182</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HealthCare-Global-Enterprises-Approves-425-Cr-Rights-Issue-At-512-Per-Share/699de18b04a25a58c8506182</guid><description>HealthCare Global Enterprises (HCG) has received board approval for a ₹425 crore rights issue, priced at ₹512 per share, offering a 1:17 ratio to existing shareholders. The capital infusion aims to bolster its balance sheet and support growth initiatives, with a record date set for March 2, 2026. This move is expected to strengthen the company's financial flexibility as it continues its expansion trajectory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:36:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de18b04a25a58c8506181_1771954963715.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCG Rights Issue: ₹425 Cr to Fund Growth at ₹512/share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HCG-Rights-Issue-425-Cr-to-Fund-Growth-at-512share/699de15504a25a58c8504c2e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HCG-Rights-Issue-425-Cr-to-Fund-Growth-at-512share/699de15504a25a58c8504c2e</guid><description>HealthCare Global Enterprises (HCG) has approved terms for a rights issue to raise up to ₹425 crore at ₹512 per share. This capital infusion aims to bolster its financial position and support ongoing expansion in the competitive healthcare sector. The issue is structured with a 1:17 entitlement ratio for existing shareholders.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IndusInd Bank Plans London Investor Meets; Regulatory Overhang Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Plans-London-Investor-Meets-Regulatory-Overhang-Looms/699de0d304a25a58c8503236</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Plans-London-Investor-Meets-Regulatory-Overhang-Looms/699de0d304a25a58c8503236</guid><description>IndusInd Bank announced its upcoming analyst and institutional investor meetings to be held in London on March 2nd and 3rd, 2026. Organized by Jefferies India, these meetings aim to engage with the investment community. The bank, however, operates under the shadow of ongoing investigations by SEBI, SFIO, and NFRA concerning accounting irregularities and derivative portfolio issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:33:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699de0d304a25a58c8503235_1771954501231.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EU Proposes Permanent Russian Oil Ban, Targets Political Timing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/EU-Proposes-Permanent-Russian-Oil-Ban-Targets-Political-Timing/699ddf1304a25a58c84f7032</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/EU-Proposes-Permanent-Russian-Oil-Ban-Targets-Political-Timing/699ddf1304a25a58c84f7032</guid><description>The European Commission plans a legislative proposal for a permanent ban on Russian oil imports by April 15, deliberately scheduling it after Hungary's parliamentary elections. This move aims to solidify long-term energy policy, circumventing opposition from countries like Hungary and Slovakia. While the EU has drastically reduced Russian oil dependency since 2022, this permanent legislation signals a structural shift in energy security strategy, independent of geopolitical fluctuations. Market impact will depend on integrating these volumes with ongoing diversification efforts and global supply dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India-Israel FTA Talks: Strategic Tech &amp; Defense Synergy Takes Center Stage</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Israel-FTA-Talks-Strategic-Tech-and-Defense-Synergy-Takes-Center-Stage/699ddccf04a25a58c84f6df6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Israel-FTA-Talks-Strategic-Tech-and-Defense-Synergy-Takes-Center-Stage/699ddccf04a25a58c84f6df6</guid><description>Prime Minister Modi's visit coincides with the first formal round of India-Israel Free Trade Agreement negotiations, aimed at deepening economic ties. The focus extends beyond traditional goods to high-value sectors like technology, AI, cybersecurity, and defense, leveraging complementary strengths for future growth. While merchandise trade saw a dip in FY25 to $3.62 billion, the FTA is anticipated to catalyze growth in specialized industries and accelerate strategic collaboration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:15:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ddccf04a25a58c84f6df5_1771953718877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Renewable Surge: Capacity Growth Meets Grid and Supply Chain Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Renewable-Surge-Capacity-Growth-Meets-Grid-and-Supply-Chain-Hurdles/699ddc7104a25a58c84f6d81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Renewable-Surge-Capacity-Growth-Meets-Grid-and-Supply-Chain-Hurdles/699ddc7104a25a58c84f6d81</guid><description>India's renewable energy capacity is projected to surge from 475 GW in FY25 to 705 GW by FY30, driven by a 60.6% drop in solar and 20.4% wind costs. This rapid transition, which has already seen renewables contribute 5% to global capacity, signals grid decarbonization. However, challenges persist, including substantial investment needs for transmission infrastructure, reliance on imported critical minerals, and the financial health of distribution companies, posing risks to sustainable growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:14:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ddc7104a25a58c84f6d80_1771953399012.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Covasant Technologies Secures AI Governance Certification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Covasant-Technologies-Secures-AI-Governance-Certification/699ddbab04a25a58c84f6815</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Covasant-Technologies-Secures-AI-Governance-Certification/699ddbab04a25a58c84f6815</guid><description>Covasant Technologies has attained ISO/IEC 42001:2023 accreditation for its Artificial Intelligence Management System (AIMS). This certification places Covasant among global leaders like IBM and Microsoft, validating its AI governance practices for enterprise-grade deployment. The standard directly addresses key barriers to AI scaling, particularly for regulated sectors, by mitigating operational and regulatory risks associated with AI initiatives. This milestone complements Covasant's existing security and privacy certifications, creating a comprehensive governance ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ddbab04a25a58c84f6814_1771953454524.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haryana Probes Bank Fraud: Focus Shifts to Policy, Not Just Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Haryana-Probes-Bank-Fraud-Focus-Shifts-to-Policy-Not-Just-Recovery/699ddb9004a25a58c84f67c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Haryana-Probes-Bank-Fraud-Focus-Shifts-to-Policy-Not-Just-Recovery/699ddb9004a25a58c84f67c2</guid><description>Haryana has established a high-level committee to investigate unauthorized fund transfers and review its State Banking Policy following a substantial fraud involving IDFC First Bank and AU Small Finance Bank. While the state government claims full recovery of approximately Rs 556 crore plus Rs 22 crore interest within 24 hours, the committee's mandate extends to examining bank empanelment, deposit decisions, procedural lapses, and systemic failures to prevent recurrence. This probe signals a broader focus on regulatory oversight and institutional accountability within the financial sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:10:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ddb9004a25a58c84f67c1_1771953157901.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Infra Q1 FY26 Profit ₹1,102 Cr on Debt Gain; Core Revenue Nil</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Reliance-Infra-Q1-FY26-Profit-1102-Cr-on-Debt-Gain-Core-Revenue-Nil/699ddb6b04a25a58c84f6791</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Reliance-Infra-Q1-FY26-Profit-1102-Cr-on-Debt-Gain-Core-Revenue-Nil/699ddb6b04a25a58c84f6791</guid><description>Reliance Infrastructure posted a staggering consolidated profit of ₹1,102.56 crore for Q1 FY26, driven by a one-time ₹1,110.98 crore exceptional gain from a debt settlement related to its Sidhi Singrauli Road Project. However, this masks a dire operational reality: revenue from operations fell to nil, and the company faces severe liquidity crunch, a fully eroded net worth, and a qualified audit opinion, raising material uncertainty about its ability to continue as a going concern.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:10:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ddb6b04a25a58c84f6790_1771953658366.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>