<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:37:06 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Syrma SGS Tech Revenue Soars 43%, EBITDA Doubles Amid Strong Export Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Syrma-SGS-Tech-Revenue-Soars-43percent-EBITDA-Doubles-Amid-Strong-Export-Growth/6981be57d9d43ad9e1737346</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Syrma-SGS-Tech-Revenue-Soars-43percent-EBITDA-Doubles-Amid-Strong-Export-Growth/6981be57d9d43ad9e1737346</guid><description>Syrma SGS Technology Ltd. delivered a powerful Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue surging 43% year-on-year to INR 1,274 crores. Operating EBITDA more than doubled, growing 101% to INR 159 crores, boosting EBITDA margins to 12.6% from 8.2%. Profit After Tax (PAT) jumped 108% YoY to INR 110 crores. Growth was driven by strong performance across auto, med-tech, industrial, and IT/railways verticals, complemented by a 65% surge in exports. Management raised guidance and expressed confidence in FY27 targets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981be57d9d43ad9e1737345_1770110719361.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NMDC Q3 PAT Dips 10% Amidst ₹15,165 Cr Tax Cloud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NMDC-Q3-PAT-Dips-10percent-Amidst-15165-Cr-Tax-Cloud/6981bd8cd9d43ad9e1737005</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NMDC-Q3-PAT-Dips-10percent-Amidst-15165-Cr-Tax-Cloud/6981bd8cd9d43ad9e1737005</guid><description>NMDC reported mixed Q3 results. While revenue grew 14.6% standalone, PAT dropped 10.6% YoY due to increased costs. The company declared a ₹2.50 interim dividend and approved a critical minerals WOS. However, auditors flagged a massive ₹15,165 Cr contingent tax liability and significant dues from subsidiaries, raising concerns.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981bd8cd9d43ad9e1737004_1770110562098.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Freezes Transgene Biotek Accounts; Halts Operations Over Rs 38 Lac Penalty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Freezes-Transgene-Biotek-Accounts-Halts-Operations-Over-Rs-38-Lac-Penalty/6981be45d9d43ad9e1737284</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Freezes-Transgene-Biotek-Accounts-Halts-Operations-Over-Rs-38-Lac-Penalty/6981be45d9d43ad9e1737284</guid><description>SEBI has launched recovery proceedings against Transgene Biotek for a Rs 38 lac penalty, freezing all company bank accounts and prohibiting asset transfers. This drastic measure has brought all operations, including essential salary payments, to a complete standstill, severely impacting the firm's day-to-day functioning while an appeal remains pending at the Securities Appellate Tribunal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PCBL Surges 13% Despite 98% Profit Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/PCBL-Surges-13percent-Despite-98percent-Profit-Plunge/6981bdcfd9d43ad9e1737111</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/PCBL-Surges-13percent-Despite-98percent-Profit-Plunge/6981bdcfd9d43ad9e1737111</guid><description>PCBL reported a steep 98% year-on-year drop in net profit to ₹2 crore and an 8.2% revenue decline to ₹1,845 crore for the December quarter. Despite weak operational results, evidenced by falling EBITDA and compressed margins, the company's stock surged 13.64% on February 3, 2026. This market reaction suggests investor focus on broader sector trends, upcoming fiscal stimulus for the chemical industry, and positive analyst sentiment overriding immediate financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Narbada Gems Q3 Profit Soars 24% Amid Jewellery Amalgamation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Narbada-Gems-Q3-Profit-Soars-24percent-Amid-Jewellery-Amalgamation/6981bd57d9d43ad9e1736ee2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Narbada-Gems-Q3-Profit-Soars-24percent-Amid-Jewellery-Amalgamation/6981bd57d9d43ad9e1736ee2</guid><description>Narbada Gems &amp; Jewellery Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26 with a 24.03% YoY increase in net profit to ₹18.32 Cr, driven by strong 9-month performance (up 73.91% YoY to ₹71.39 Cr). The company also saw its net profit margin improve significantly YoY. However, performance sequentially declined QoQ, with revenue down 14.94% and profit down 38.83%. A major development is the NCLT's approval for amalgamation with Uday Jewellery Industries Limited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Saregama India Reports Strong Revenue Growth, PAT Dips on Charges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Saregama-India-Reports-Strong-Revenue-Growth-PAT-Dips-on-Charges/6981bbefd9d43ad9e1736b0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Saregama-India-Reports-Strong-Revenue-Growth-PAT-Dips-on-Charges/6981bbefd9d43ad9e1736b0a</guid><description>Saregama India announced mixed Q3 FY26 results. Revenue surged 16.5% YoY to Rs 2,382 Mn, with music licensing up 29%. Adjusted EBITDA jumped 43% to Rs 1,153 Mn, expanding margins to 48%. However, PAT fell 17.8% YoY to Rs 512 Mn due to a Rs 70 Mn non-cash labour code charge. The company made a strategic minority investment in Bhansali Productions for film music IP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:16:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981bbefd9d43ad9e1736b09_1770110170604.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Finance CFO Confident on FY26 Growth Targets as Profit Jumps 19%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Cholamandalam-Finance-CFO-Confident-on-FY26-Growth-Targets-as-Profit-Jumps-19percent/6981bc68d9d43ad9e1736d28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Cholamandalam-Finance-CFO-Confident-on-FY26-Growth-Targets-as-Profit-Jumps-19percent/6981bc68d9d43ad9e1736d28</guid><description>Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company Limited (CIFCL) is firmly on track to meet its FY26 Assets Under Management (AUM) growth targets, according to CFO D Arul Selvan. The non-banking lender reported a 19% year-on-year increase in net profit to ₹1,288 crore for Q3FY26, driven by strong disbursements across vehicle finance, loans against property, and home loans. Disbursements grew 16% overall, with the nascent gold loan business also scaling rapidly.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PCBL Chemical Profit Plunges 98% Amid Margin Squeeze, Expansion Continues</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/PCBL-Chemical-Profit-Plunges-98percent-Amid-Margin-Squeeze-Expansion-Continues/6981bc12d9d43ad9e1736c25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/PCBL-Chemical-Profit-Plunges-98percent-Amid-Margin-Squeeze-Expansion-Continues/6981bc12d9d43ad9e1736c25</guid><description>PCBL Chemical reported a challenging Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue down 8.2% YoY to ₹1,846 Crore and PAT plummeting 98% to ₹2 Crore. EBITDA margins compressed to 12% from 16% YoY. Despite the financial headwinds, the company progressed on operational expansions, including new Specialty Black lines and a US subsidiary for battery chemicals, alongside a ₹400 Crore net debt reduction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Phoenix Mills Reports 15% Revenue Growth on Robust Retail Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Phoenix-Mills-Reports-15percent-Revenue-Growth-on-Robust-Retail-Demand/6981bbaad9d43ad9e17369e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Phoenix-Mills-Reports-15percent-Revenue-Growth-on-Robust-Retail-Demand/6981bbaad9d43ad9e17369e2</guid><description>Phoenix Mills reported a 15% YoY consolidated revenue increase to Rs. 1,121 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by a strong 25% surge in retail consumption. Consolidated EBITDA grew 19% YoY to Rs. 656 crore. The company highlighted robust performance across its retail, office, hospitality, and residential segments, with future growth expected from ongoing developments and asset optimization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Saregama India Q3 Revenue Plummets 46%, Margins Surge on Music Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Saregama-India-Q3-Revenue-Plummets-46percent-Margins-Surge-on-Music-Growth/6981bb7ad9d43ad9e17368d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Saregama-India-Q3-Revenue-Plummets-46percent-Margins-Surge-on-Music-Growth/6981bb7ad9d43ad9e17368d7</guid><description>Saregama India reported a sharp 46.0% YoY consolidated revenue decline to ₹26,038 Lakhs in Q3 FY26, hit hard by the Events segment's 92% drop. PAT fell 17.5% YoY. However, operational efficiency improved, with EBITDA margins expanding to 35.4% from 20.7% YoY. Music and Artist Management segments showed robust growth, offsetting declines elsewhere. The company also announced two strategic acquisitions and an interim dividend of ₹4.5 per share. No forward-looking guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:11:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Magellanic Cloud Approves Merger, QIP, and Board Changes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Magellanic-Cloud-Approves-Merger-QIP-and-Board-Changes/6981bb04d9d43ad9e1736788</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Magellanic-Cloud-Approves-Merger-QIP-and-Board-Changes/6981bb04d9d43ad9e1736788</guid><description>Magellanic Cloud Limited shareholders approved a key merger with IVIS International via the fast-track route at an EOGM. The meeting also sanctioned a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) for capital infusion and approved new board appointments, including a new Chairman and Managing Director.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Interarch Building Solutions: Record Q3 Revenue Fuels Expansion Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Interarch-Building-Solutions-Record-Q3-Revenue-Fuels-Expansion-Ambitions/6981ba94d9d43ad9e1736625</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Interarch-Building-Solutions-Record-Q3-Revenue-Fuels-Expansion-Ambitions/6981ba94d9d43ad9e1736625</guid><description>Interarch Building Solutions achieved a landmark Q3 FY26 with Rs 523 crore in revenue, marking 43.7% year-on-year growth. EBITDA and Profit After Tax also saw robust increases. The company's Rs 1,685 crore order book and strategic manufacturing expansion signal a positive outlook, despite a premium valuation. Analysts maintain a 'Strong Buy' rating with a significant price target.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:06:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DEE Development Surges 76% Revenue, But Auditor Flags Subsidiary Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/DEE-Development-Surges-76percent-Revenue-But-Auditor-Flags-Subsidiary-Concerns/6981b56dd9d43ad9e1735ae3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/DEE-Development-Surges-76percent-Revenue-But-Auditor-Flags-Subsidiary-Concerns/6981b56dd9d43ad9e1735ae3</guid><description>DEE Development Engineers reported a strong Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 76.58% YoY to ₹28,606.77 Lacs, turning PAT positive at ₹1,855.42 Lacs. Standalone figures also surged. However, the auditor's report raised significant concerns regarding the impairment of subsidiary Malwa Power Private Limited and an ongoing civil writ petition impacting tariff rates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:06:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b56dd9d43ad9e1735ae2_1770109582105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Finolex Industries: Monsoon Woes &amp; Strategic Pivot to 50:50 Mix</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Finolex-Industries-Monsoon-Woes-and-Strategic-Pivot-to-5050-Mix/6981b8acd9d43ad9e17362ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Finolex-Industries-Monsoon-Woes-and-Strategic-Pivot-to-5050-Mix/6981b8acd9d43ad9e17362ee</guid><description>Prabhudas Lilladher downgraded Finolex Industries' FY26 pipes segment volume growth to flattish from mid-single digits, citing prolonged monsoon impact on P&amp;F volumes which fell ~6.0% YoY in 9MFY26. The report noted EBITDA margins tracking ~12%. Despite this, management aims for a 50:50 agri/non-agri mix, a shift from the current 62:38. The brokerage maintains an 'Accumulate' rating with a revised TP of Rs 199, projecting FY25-28E revenue/EBITDA/PAT CAGR of 6.3%/11.6%/17.0%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:04:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b8acd9d43ad9e17362ed_1770109482342.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LIC Housing Finance Faces Margin Squeeze Amid Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/LIC-Housing-Finance-Faces-Margin-Squeeze-Amid-Fierce-Competition/6981b920d9d43ad9e1736438</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/LIC-Housing-Finance-Faces-Margin-Squeeze-Amid-Fierce-Competition/6981b920d9d43ad9e1736438</guid><description>LIC Housing Finance's third-quarter disbursements grew a modest 4% year-on-year, pressured by aggressive bank competition. This has capped loan book expansion expectations to 6-7% for FY26-27 and is projected to moderate net interest margins (NIMs) to 2.4% by FY28. Despite an improving asset quality, Prabhudas Lilladher downgraded the stock to 'Accumulate' with a price target of Rs 525, cutting FY26/27 earnings estimates due to these headwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:02:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b920d9d43ad9e1736437_1770109352231.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor Stock Near Highs Amid Record Quarter, Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Stock-Near-Highs-Amid-Record-Quarter-Valuation-Scrutiny/6981b82cd9d43ad9e1736187</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Stock-Near-Highs-Amid-Record-Quarter-Valuation-Scrutiny/6981b82cd9d43ad9e1736187</guid><description>TVS Motor Company achieved its highest-ever quarterly revenue and EBITDA, exceeding estimates due to PLI recognition, improved demand, and cost efficiencies. Analysts maintain positive outlooks, with Prabhudas Lilladher retaining 'ACCUMULATE' and a ₹4,200 target. However, TVS Motor's trailing twelve-month P/E ratio of approximately 65x significantly outpaces peers Bajaj Auto (31x) and Hero MotoCorp (21x), raising valuation concerns despite strong growth projections and a share price nearing its 52-week high of ₹3,909.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b82cd9d43ad9e1736186_1770109211054.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alkyl Amines Q3 Profit Falls 3.4% YoY, Revenue Dips; No Guidance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Alkyl-Amines-Q3-Profit-Falls-34percent-YoY-Revenue-Dips-No-Guidance/6981b5dbd9d43ad9e1735d92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Alkyl-Amines-Q3-Profit-Falls-34percent-YoY-Revenue-Dips-No-Guidance/6981b5dbd9d43ad9e1735d92</guid><description>Alkyl Amines Chemicals Limited reported a decline in Q3 FY26 performance, with revenue down 4.63% YoY to ₹354 Cr and PAT down 3.43% YoY to ₹42.26 Cr. Sequentially, revenue and PAT also saw a dip. The company provided no management guidance or future outlook, leaving investors with limited visibility.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b5dbd9d43ad9e1735d91_1770108782377.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dixon Tech Bets on Integration Beyond PLI for Margin Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Tech-Bets-on-Integration-Beyond-PLI-for-Margin-Expansion/6981b658d9d43ad9e1735ef4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Tech-Bets-on-Integration-Beyond-PLI-for-Margin-Expansion/6981b658d9d43ad9e1735ef4</guid><description>Dixon Technologies' CFO, Saurabh Gupta, detailed a robust strategy to mitigate potential reductions in Production-Linked Incentive (PLI) schemes. The company is aggressively pursuing backward integration, especially in displays and camera modules, aiming for margin expansion by FY28 irrespective of future PLI allocations. This focus on operational control aims to ensure long-term growth and resilience within India's expanding electronics manufacturing sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:50:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b658d9d43ad9e1735ef3_1770108643661.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor Posts Record Q3 Results; Revenue Surges 37%, Profit Jumps 53%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Posts-Record-Q3-Results-Revenue-Surges-37percent-Profit-Jumps-53percent/6981b5a4d9d43ad9e1735bfb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Posts-Record-Q3-Results-Revenue-Surges-37percent-Profit-Jumps-53percent/6981b5a4d9d43ad9e1735bfb</guid><description>TVS Motor Company reported a record-breaking Q3 FY26, with sales volume up 27% YoY. Operating revenue soared 37% to INR 12,476 Cr, EBITDA climbed 51% to INR 1,634 Cr, and PAT surged 53% to INR 940 Cr, improving margins by 120 bps. Electric two-wheeler and three-wheeler sales saw significant growth, and the company raised FY26 capex guidance to INR 1,700 Cr for future expansion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b5a4d9d43ad9e1735bfa_1770108517691.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rossell Techsys Revenue Soars 71% But Profit Dives 64% On One-Off Charge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rossell-Techsys-Revenue-Soars-71percent-But-Profit-Dives-64percent-On-One-Off-Charge/6981b4e4d9d43ad9e17359ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rossell-Techsys-Revenue-Soars-71percent-But-Profit-Dives-64percent-On-One-Off-Charge/6981b4e4d9d43ad9e17359ac</guid><description>Rossell Techsys reported a robust 71% YoY revenue surge to ₹129.93 Cr for Q3 FY26. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) plunged 64% to ₹7.33 Cr, impacted by an exceptional charge of ₹1.02 Cr related to employee benefit liabilities under new Labour Codes. Standalone revenues also grew, but PAT saw a similar 64% decline. The company holds ₹339.60 Cr in working capital loans and provided no future guidance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DEE Engineers Posts Strong Turnaround, But Auditor Flags Major Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DEE-Engineers-Posts-Strong-Turnaround-But-Auditor-Flags-Major-Risks/6981b4b5d9d43ad9e17358a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DEE-Engineers-Posts-Strong-Turnaround-But-Auditor-Flags-Major-Risks/6981b4b5d9d43ad9e17358a5</guid><description>DEE Development Engineers has reported a significant turnaround in Q3 FY26, posting a consolidated profit of ₹1,855.42 lacs against a loss last year, on a 76.6% revenue jump to ₹28,606.77 lacs. A 70% acquisition of Molsieve Designs also boosts prospects. However, auditors flagged uncertainties regarding the impairment of subsidiary Malwa Power's assets and a sub-judice tariff dispute with PSPCL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:45:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b4b5d9d43ad9e17358a4_1770108320580.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Partners Leonardo for India Helicopter Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Adani-Partners-Leonardo-for-India-Helicopter-Hub/6981b471d9d43ad9e173577f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Adani-Partners-Leonardo-for-India-Helicopter-Hub/6981b471d9d43ad9e173577f</guid><description>Adani Defence &amp; Aerospace and Italian major Leonardo have signed a Memorandum of Understanding to build a comprehensive helicopter manufacturing ecosystem in India. This collaboration aims to bolster the 'Make in India' initiative, enhance national self-reliance in defense production, and cater to the growing demand for military and civilian helicopters. The partnership will encompass manufacturing, assembly, robust maintenance, repair, and overhaul (MRO) capabilities, alongside pilot training programs, addressing India's significant helicopter deficit.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:44:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b471d9d43ad9e173577e_1770108149364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Ports Surges 22% Revenue, Lifts FY26 Guidance on Strong Cargo Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Ports-Surges-22percent-Revenue-Lifts-FY26-Guidance-on-Strong-Cargo-Growth/6981b3ccd9d43ad9e17355e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Ports-Surges-22percent-Revenue-Lifts-FY26-Guidance-on-Strong-Cargo-Growth/6981b3ccd9d43ad9e17355e0</guid><description>Adani Ports reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue up 22% YoY to ₹9,705 Cr and PAT rising 21% to ₹3,043 Cr. The company raised its full-year FY26 revenue and EBITDA guidance, driven by strong cargo volumes and strategic acquisitions like NQXT Australia. Growth was broad-based across logistics, marine, and international/domestic ports, signalling strong execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b3ccd9d43ad9e17355df_1770108008119.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JioBlackRock Launches Digital Advisory, Shaking Up Indian Wealthtech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/JioBlackRock-Launches-Digital-Advisory-Shaking-Up-Indian-Wealthtech/6981b382d9d43ad9e17353da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/JioBlackRock-Launches-Digital-Advisory-Shaking-Up-Indian-Wealthtech/6981b382d9d43ad9e17353da</guid><description>Jio Financial Services Limited (JFSL) and BlackRock Inc. have launched JioBlackRock Personalised Investment Advice, a digital platform offering tailored investment guidance. Aimed at democratizing access for Indian retail investors, the service combines BlackRock's Aladdin® technology with JFSL's digital reach. With a low entry point of ₹10,000 and competitive pricing, the platform aims to disrupt the existing wealthtech landscape by providing institutional-grade tools at an affordable cost, fueling a new phase of competition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:38:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b382d9d43ad9e17353d9_1770107895640.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aether Industries Q3 Revenue Jumps 44%, PAT Up 49% on CEM Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aether-Industries-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-44percent-PAT-Up-49percent-on-CEM-Growth/6981b3b6d9d43ad9e17354f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aether-Industries-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-44percent-PAT-Up-49percent-on-CEM-Growth/6981b3b6d9d43ad9e17354f4</guid><description>Aether Industries reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue surging 44% YoY to ₹3,171 Million and PAT climbing 49% YoY to ₹645 Million. The growth was propelled by increasing Contract Manufacturing (CEM) and Large Scale Manufacturing (LSM) demand, leading to a significant improvement in EBITDA margins to 34.15%. The company also added 15 new customers and is on track with capacity expansions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GK Energy Expands Retail Solar Push for Stronger Cash Flow</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GK-Energy-Expands-Retail-Solar-Push-for-Stronger-Cash-Flow/6981b128d9d43ad9e1734e6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GK-Energy-Expands-Retail-Solar-Push-for-Stronger-Cash-Flow/6981b128d9d43ad9e1734e6d</guid><description>GK Energy is strategically expanding into the Retail Solar Rooftop System (RTS) EPC segment, moving beyond its solar pump business. This move targets improved cash flow, enhanced working capital efficiency, and a stable recurring revenue pipeline, positioning GK Energy as an integrated solar infrastructure leader aligned with favourable policy momentum.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:35:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b128d9d43ad9e1734e6c_1770107754071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Canara Robeco Hybrid Fund: SIP Success vs. Recent Performance Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Canara-Robeco-Hybrid-Fund-SIP-Success-vs-Recent-Performance-Gap/6981b312d9d43ad9e17352ab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Canara-Robeco-Hybrid-Fund-SIP-Success-vs-Recent-Performance-Gap/6981b312d9d43ad9e17352ab</guid><description>Despite a legacy of robust wealth creation through systematic investment plans, Canara Robeco Equity Hybrid Fund shows a widening performance gap against leading aggressive hybrid peers and its benchmark index over 1- and 5-year periods. While the broader category attracts significant investor capital, and the recent Union Budget 2026 signals a macro environment favorable to long-term investment strategies, the fund's returns suggest a challenge in maintaining competitive edge. The fund's Regular Plan expense ratio is notably higher than its Direct Plan and category averages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Aether Industries Posts 44% Revenue Surge; Fire Incident Impact Under Review</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aether-Industries-Posts-44percent-Revenue-Surge-Fire-Incident-Impact-Under-Review/6981b1c5d9d43ad9e1735046</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aether-Industries-Posts-44percent-Revenue-Surge-Fire-Incident-Impact-Under-Review/6981b1c5d9d43ad9e1735046</guid><description>Aether Industries reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue soaring 44.7% year-on-year to ₹3,171.21 million and profit leaping 48.6% to ₹644.79 million. Standalone performance also saw strong growth. However, auditor reports noted an ongoing assessment of financial impact from a Q3 FY24 fire incident, with no adjustments yet for fixed asset loss.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:33:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b1c5d9d43ad9e1735045_1770107588378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Construction Finance: Sector Faces Funding Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Construction-Finance-Sector-Faces-Funding-Hurdles/6981b1a4d9d43ad9e1734fc7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Construction-Finance-Sector-Faces-Funding-Hurdles/6981b1a4d9d43ad9e1734fc7</guid><description>Financing self-constructed homes reveals intricate mechanisms distinct from ready-unit purchases. Staged loan disbursals, tied to construction milestones, necessitate upfront borrower capital and diligent oversight. The pre-EMI period, where only interest is paid on disbursed amounts, highlights potential cash flow pressures for developers managing extended timelines. Tax benefits, contingent on completion certificates, further emphasize project finalization risks. This dynamic points to significant operational and capital management challenges for construction firms and lenders, despite robust underlying housing demand. The sector must balance evolving regulatory demands with project execution efficiency to maintain financial stability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:30:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981b1a4d9d43ad9e1734fc6_1770107454800.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NATCO Pharma Bags Tentative US FDA Approval for Generic Cancer Drug</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/NATCO-Pharma-Bags-Tentative-US-FDA-Approval-for-Generic-Cancer-Drug/6981b055d9d43ad9e1734cb5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/NATCO-Pharma-Bags-Tentative-US-FDA-Approval-for-Generic-Cancer-Drug/6981b055d9d43ad9e1734cb5</guid><description>NATCO Pharma has secured tentative approval from the US FDA for its generic Erdafitinib tablets, a significant stride into the US oncology market. The drug targets advanced urothelial carcinoma and mirrors the branded version that saw approximately USD 60 million in US sales. This development could unlock a new, substantial revenue stream for the Hyderabad-based pharmaceutical firm.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Jio Buys Sikhya Entertainment for Global Content Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Reliance-Jio-Buys-Sikhya-Entertainment-for-Global-Content-Play/6981b039d9d43ad9e1734bbe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Reliance-Jio-Buys-Sikhya-Entertainment-for-Global-Content-Play/6981b039d9d43ad9e1734bbe</guid><description>Reliance Industries, via Jio Studios, has acquired a 50.1% stake in Sikhya Entertainment for ₹150 crore. The deal, finalized on February 2, 2026, integrates the Oscar-winning production house into Jio Studios' media arm. This strategic move aims to leverage Sikhya's acclaimed storytelling and creative talent to enhance Jio Studios' intellectual property and content pipeline for both Indian and international markets, signaling a deep commitment to premium, creator-led content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:22:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Zydus Wellness Revenue Surges 109%, But Q3 Profit Turns Negative</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zydus-Wellness-Revenue-Surges-109percent-But-Q3-Profit-Turns-Negative/6981abaed9d43ad9e173437c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zydus-Wellness-Revenue-Surges-109percent-But-Q3-Profit-Turns-Negative/6981abaed9d43ad9e173437c</guid><description>Zydus Wellness reported a staggering 108.9% YoY revenue surge in Q3 FY26 to ₹9,649 million, fueled by the Comfort Click acquisition. Gross margins expanded robustly by 15.6 pp. However, adjusted net profit turned negative at ₹(333) million, heavily impacted by acquisition costs, financing, and amortization expenses. YTD PAT declined 79.9%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981abaed9d43ad9e173437b_1770106871011.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPL Profit Plunges 96% YoY; Asian Energy Discovers Oil</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/UPL-Profit-Plunges-96percent-YoY-Asian-Energy-Discovers-Oil/6981ac01d9d43ad9e1734527</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/UPL-Profit-Plunges-96percent-YoY-Asian-Energy-Discovers-Oil/6981ac01d9d43ad9e1734527</guid><description>UPL Limited's Q3 FY25 net profit plunged 96.34% YoY to ₹32 crore, severely impacting profitability despite marginal revenue growth. Year-to-date revenue also declined. Meanwhile, Asian Energy Services reported a significant oil discovery in Gujarat, with initial production of 100 bopd. Global brokerage Morgan Stanley offered a constructive outlook on Indian equities, maintaining an Overweight stance on Financials, Consumer Discretionary, and Industrials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981ac01d9d43ad9e1734526_1770106580220.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Cut to 18% Boosts India Exports Amid Trade Reset</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Cut-to-18percent-Boosts-India-Exports-Amid-Trade-Reset/6981ad6ad9d43ad9e17348f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Cut-to-18percent-Boosts-India-Exports-Amid-Trade-Reset/6981ad6ad9d43ad9e17348f1</guid><description>The United States has significantly lowered import duties on Indian goods to 18%, a substantial decrease from previous high rates that had strained bilateral trade. This strategic trade reset is expected to inject new life into India's export sector, particularly in textiles, apparel, leather, and gems, by enhancing price competitiveness against Asian rivals and potentially accelerating order flows. The move signifies a de-escalation following a period of heightened trade tensions, paving the way for renewed economic engagement and deeper integration into U.S. supply chains.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981ad6ad9d43ad9e17348f0_1770106408543.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Wellness Sales Surge 113% on Acquisition Boost, But Guidance Lacking</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zydus-Wellness-Sales-Surge-113percent-on-Acquisition-Boost-But-Guidance-Lacking/6981ac11d9d43ad9e1734602</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zydus-Wellness-Sales-Surge-113percent-on-Acquisition-Boost-But-Guidance-Lacking/6981ac11d9d43ad9e1734602</guid><description>Zydus Wellness Ltd. reported a stunning 113.7% YoY surge in Q3 FY26 net sales to Rs 9,633 million, fueled by recent acquisitions. EBITDA jumped 312.2% to Rs 610 million. Key brands like Sugar Free and Everyuth maintained market leadership, with new product launches and geographical expansion underway. However, the company provided no specific forward-looking guidance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:11:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981ac11d9d43ad9e1734601_1770106277825.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>B2B Software Soars, Moschip/Vishnu Profits Dive; Banks Signal Credit Stress</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/B2B-Software-Soars-MoschipVishnu-Profits-Dive-Banks-Signal-Credit-Stress/6981ac7cd9d43ad9e17347a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/B2B-Software-Soars-MoschipVishnu-Profits-Dive-Banks-Signal-Credit-Stress/6981ac7cd9d43ad9e17347a9</guid><description>B2B Software Technologies posted an 85% YoY jump in Q3 PAT on robust revenue growth, while its consolidated performance was even stronger. In contrast, Moschip Technologies saw its Q3 profit slump 65% despite revenue gains, and Vishnu Chemicals reported declining profitability. Meanwhile, numerous bank notices for loan recovery signal potential credit market stress.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:09:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981ac7cd9d43ad9e17347a8_1770106141359.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ather Energy Surges on Strong Q3 as Diversification Powers Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ather-Energy-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-as-Diversification-Powers-Growth/6981ab91d9d43ad9e17342c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ather-Energy-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-as-Diversification-Powers-Growth/6981ab91d9d43ad9e17342c1</guid><description>Ather Energy shares surged nearly 13% after reporting a substantially narrowed net loss of ₹85 crore in Q3 FY26, down from ₹198 crore a year prior. Record sales volumes of 67,851 units fueled a 50% revenue jump to ₹996 crore. The company highlighted increasing non-vehicle revenue, now 14% of total income, as a key driver for improved unit economics and profitability, signaling a robust operational turnaround.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981ab91d9d43ad9e17342c0_1770105981038.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dodla Dairy Wins Tax Dispute, Secures INR 33 Cr Refund</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Dodla-Dairy-Wins-Tax-Dispute-Secures-INR-33-Cr-Refund/6981aae4d9d43ad9e1733c64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Dodla-Dairy-Wins-Tax-Dispute-Secures-INR-33-Cr-Refund/6981aae4d9d43ad9e1733c64</guid><description>Dodla Dairy Limited has secured a significant victory as the Income Tax Appellate Tribunal (ITAT) dismissed Revenue's appeals on Section 80-IB deductions for multiple Assessment Years. The company is set to receive an confirmed refund of INR 26.2 crores, including interest, and estimates an additional INR 6.7 crores through rectification applications, totaling approximately INR 33 crores. This development significantly bolsters the company's liquidity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981aae4d9d43ad9e1733c63_1770105805296.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Signed; Rally Hinges on Earnings Revival</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Signed-Rally-Hinges-on-Earnings-Revival/6981ab7dd9d43ad9e17341f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Signed-Rally-Hinges-on-Earnings-Revival/6981ab7dd9d43ad9e17341f3</guid><description>Indian equity markets surged following the announcement of a new India-US trade agreement that slashed tariffs. While the deal offers a sentiment boost, market watchers stress that the rally's longevity hinges on a significant corporate earnings recovery, with recent Q3FY26 results showing minimal growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Valiant Communications Surges 165% Revenue, Turns Profitable on Strong Q3</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valiant-Communications-Surges-165percent-Revenue-Turns-Profitable-on-Strong-Q3/6981a4f6d9d43ad9e1732650</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valiant-Communications-Surges-165percent-Revenue-Turns-Profitable-on-Strong-Q3/6981a4f6d9d43ad9e1732650</guid><description>Valiant Communications Ltd. reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue soaring 165% YoY to ₹22.14 Cr and a significant turnaround to a ₹6.05 Cr PAT from a loss last year. YTD PAT surged 197% to ₹16.04 Cr. The company also initiated a preferential issuance of warrants for potential ₹46 Cr capital. However, no future guidance was provided, and other income includes fair market value gains.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981a4f6d9d43ad9e173264f_1770105602539.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>