<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:34:29 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Elpro International Buys Fintech Firm Mynd Solutions for ₹11.37 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Elpro-International-Buys-Fintech-Firm-Mynd-Solutions-for-1137-Cr/69a1b408fa7d0695d1abf1f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Elpro-International-Buys-Fintech-Firm-Mynd-Solutions-for-1137-Cr/69a1b408fa7d0695d1abf1f9</guid><description>Elpro International Ltd. announced on February 27, 2026, its acquisition of equity shares in Mynd Solutions Private Limited for ₹11.37 Crores. Mynd Solutions, an RBI-licensed fintech entity operating the "Mlxchange" platform, reported a total turnover of ₹104.70 Crores in FY25. This strategic move aims to bolster Elpro International's footprint in the rapidly growing financial technology sector, aligning with its diversification strategy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:11:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b408fa7d0695d1abf1f8_1772205379218.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Credit Boom Diverges: Gold Loans Surge Amid Export Slowdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Credit-Boom-Diverges-Gold-Loans-Surge-Amid-Export-Slowdown/69a1b2c4fa7d0695d1abf08e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Credit-Boom-Diverges-Gold-Loans-Surge-Amid-Export-Slowdown/69a1b2c4fa7d0695d1abf08e</guid><description>Indian credit markets show a pronounced split in January 2026. Gold-backed lending exploded by 128% year-on-year, indicating elevated household demand for liquidity. Concurrently, overall non-food credit accelerated to 14%, with retail loans up 15% and corporate borrowing improving. Conversely, export credit plummeted 17.2%, a direct consequence of global trade uncertainties and past US tariff adjustments. The renewable energy sector also saw substantial 62% growth, largely driven by regulatory mandates. This dual trend underscores a robust domestic economy grappling with external trade pressures and highlights a growing reliance on gold as an accessible credit source.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:05:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b2c4fa7d0695d1abf08d_1772205075448.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Nears $4T GDP Amid Data Overhaul and Growth Revisions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Nears-4T-GDP-Amid-Data-Overhaul-and-Growth-Revisions/69a1b22efa7d0695d1abefe7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Nears-4T-GDP-Amid-Data-Overhaul-and-Growth-Revisions/69a1b22efa7d0695d1abefe7</guid><description>India is projected to surpass the $4 trillion GDP mark by fiscal year 2026-27, supported by a revised series of National Accounts Estimates. The new methodology enhances data accuracy, especially for manufacturing, while a recalibrated GDP base leads to an increased fiscal deficit ratio. This data overhaul aims to address previous concerns regarding statistical reliability, positioning India's economic narrative on a more robust foundation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:03:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b22efa7d0695d1abefe6_1772204721933.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OpenAI Lands $110B War Chest for AI Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAI-Lands-110B-War-Chest-for-AI-Dominance/69a1b0d6fa7d0695d1abee3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAI-Lands-110B-War-Chest-for-AI-Dominance/69a1b0d6fa7d0695d1abee3a</guid><description>OpenAI has finalized a colossal $110 billion funding round, bringing its pre-money valuation to $730 billion. Major investors Amazon, Nvidia, and SoftBank injected $50 billion, $30 billion, and $30 billion, respectively. This infusion fuels OpenAI's ambitious expansion, highlighted by a new strategic partnership with Amazon Web Services (AWS) focused on enterprise AI agent deployment through the 'OpenAI Frontier' platform. Despite this deepening relationship with AWS, OpenAI reaffirmed its exclusive stateless API commitment with Microsoft Azure, underscoring a complex multi-cloud strategy amidst escalating global AI competition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:57:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b0d6fa7d0695d1abee39_1772204388236.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goyal's $54M Temple Raise: Deep Tech Gamble in Crowded Wearables</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Goyals-54M-Temple-Raise-Deep-Tech-Gamble-in-Crowded-Wearables/69a1b0d1fa7d0695d1abee22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Goyals-54M-Temple-Raise-Deep-Tech-Gamble-in-Crowded-Wearables/69a1b0d1fa7d0695d1abee22</guid><description>Deepinder Goyal, fresh from leading Zomato, has injected $54 million into his new venture, Temple, at a $190 million valuation. This early-stage funding, primarily from Zomato's early backers and employees, signals strong conviction in Goyal's vision for a high-performance wearable tracking cerebral blood flow for elite athletes. Temple enters a saturated market against giants like Whoop and Oura, but Goyal's track record in ambitious, long-term projects, including longevity research and aerospace, underpins this bold pivot into deep-tech hardware.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:57:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b0d1fa7d0695d1abee21_1772204355761.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Elitecon Int. ED Resigns; Sunbridge Agro Deal Reversal Under Review</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Elitecon-Int-ED-Resigns-Sunbridge-Agro-Deal-Reversal-Under-Review/69a1b046fa7d0695d1abed7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Elitecon-Int-ED-Resigns-Sunbridge-Agro-Deal-Reversal-Under-Review/69a1b046fa7d0695d1abed7d</guid><description>Elitecon International accepted Executive Director Dayanand Ray's resignation. The company is also reviewing the reversal of its Sunbridge Agro Private Limited acquisition due to significant funding issues and unreleased pledged shares, appointing legal advisors to explore a resolution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:55:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1b046fa7d0695d1abed7c_1772204212720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CBDC Pilot: India Rewrites Welfare Distribution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/CBDC-Pilot-India-Rewrites-Welfare-Distribution/69a1ac12fa7d0695d1abeaf2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/CBDC-Pilot-India-Rewrites-Welfare-Distribution/69a1ac12fa7d0695d1abeaf2</guid><description>India has initiated a Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) pilot in Puducherry, enabling the digital rupee (e₹) for food subsidy transfers under the Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Anna Yojana. Beneficiaries now receive programmable e₹ tokens directly into CBDC wallets, enhancing transparency, efficiency, and ensuring targeted utilization of funds. This initiative builds upon previous digital governance reforms and aims to address operational challenges, with potential for national expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:37:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1ac12fa7d0695d1abeaf1_1772203406364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki Bets on Existing Network for EVs, Skips Dedicated Channels</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Bets-on-Existing-Network-for-EVs-Skips-Dedicated-Channels/69a1aba1fa7d0695d1abea61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Bets-on-Existing-Network-for-EVs-Skips-Dedicated-Channels/69a1aba1fa7d0695d1abea61</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki India Limited (MSIL) will not create a dedicated retail network for electric vehicles (EVs), opting instead to integrate them within its existing multi-powertrain portfolio and leverage its premium Nexa network. The company's first EV, the e Vitara, is priced from ₹17.49 lakh, with a Battery-as-a-Service option available. Production will be measured, initially below 2,000 units monthly, with a new dedicated EV production line planned for July 2026. This contrasts with Tata Motors' dedicated EV strategy, as MSIL prioritizes customer experience across all powertrains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:35:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1aba1fa7d0695d1abea60_1772203033372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Shatters SaaS Playbook, Valuations Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Shatters-SaaS-Playbook-Valuations-Plunge/69a1ab9ffa7d0695d1abea4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Shatters-SaaS-Playbook-Valuations-Plunge/69a1ab9ffa7d0695d1abea4a</guid><description>The traditional SaaS model, built on per-seat pricing and feature expansion, is collapsing under the weight of AI-driven automation. AI agents are abstracting human workflows, shifting value from 'systems of record' to 'systems of agency.' This seismic shift has triggered a market correction, with software valuations plummeting. Companies must now pivot to outcome-based pricing, redefine competitive moats, and redesign go-to-market strategies to survive and thrive.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:35:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1ab9ffa7d0695d1abea49_1772203040614.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai Court Seals EOW Closure, Weakens ED Probe in MSCB Case</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Mumbai-Court-Seals-EOW-Closure-Weakens-ED-Probe-in-MSCB-Case/69a1a704fa7d0695d1abe727</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Mumbai-Court-Seals-EOW-Closure-Weakens-ED-Probe-in-MSCB-Case/69a1a704fa7d0695d1abe727</guid><description>A Mumbai special court has accepted the Economic Offences Wing (EOW) closure report in the ₹25,000-crore Maharashtra State Cooperative Bank (MSCB) case, effectively clearing Maharashtra Deputy Chief Minister Sunetra Pawar, the late Ajit Pawar, and over 70 others. The decision signifies a legal reprieve, significantly complicating the Enforcement Directorate's (ED) parallel money-laundering probe which hinges on the EOW's findings. The EOW concluded no criminal offense was committed, highlighting substantial loan recoveries and no financial loss to the bank.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:15:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a704fa7d0695d1abe726_1772201964330.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Legacy Auto Giants Overtake EV Startups in India's Two-Wheeler Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Legacy-Auto-Giants-Overtake-EV-Startups-in-Indias-Two-Wheeler-Race/69a1a67bfa7d0695d1abe61a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Legacy-Auto-Giants-Overtake-EV-Startups-in-Indias-Two-Wheeler-Race/69a1a67bfa7d0695d1abe61a</guid><description>TVS Motor solidified its leadership in India's electric two-wheeler market for February 2026, capturing 28.9% share, while Ola Electric plummeted to seventh place with just 3.7%. Established manufacturers like Bajaj Auto and Ather Energy secured second and third positions, respectively. This shift highlights the growing dominance of legacy players leveraging manufacturing scale and brand trust, increasingly challenging newer entrants. Ola Electric's sharp decline underscores the intense competitive pressures and evolving market dynamics in the rapidly maturing EV segment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:13:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a67bfa7d0695d1abe619_1772201813778.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India GCCs Leapfrog Cost Role, Embrace AI &amp; Geopolitics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-GCCs-Leapfrog-Cost-Role-Embrace-AI-and-Geopolitics/69a1a675fa7d0695d1abe603</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-GCCs-Leapfrog-Cost-Role-Embrace-AI-and-Geopolitics/69a1a675fa7d0695d1abe603</guid><description>India is solidifying its position as a premier Global Capability Center (GCC) destination, with approximately 2,000 centers currently operating and projections indicating rapid expansion. Artificial intelligence is fundamentally reshaping these GCCs, elevating them from cost-arbitrage entities to strategic global functions where significant R&amp;D and front-office activities are now concentrated. Geopolitical trade tensions and global protectionism, paradoxically, have become tailwinds, accelerating foreign investment and GCC establishment in India. This surge is significantly impacting the commercial real estate sector, accounting for a substantial portion of office space absorption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a675fa7d0695d1abe602_1772201973108.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>K&amp;R Rail Q3 FY26 Loss Widens to ₹0.86 Cr on 92% Revenue Drop</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KandR-Rail-Q3-FY26-Loss-Widens-to-086-Cr-on-92percent-Revenue-Drop/69a1a670fa7d0695d1abe5ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KandR-Rail-Q3-FY26-Loss-Widens-to-086-Cr-on-92percent-Revenue-Drop/69a1a670fa7d0695d1abe5ec</guid><description>K &amp; R Rail Engineering reported a steep 92% YoY revenue decline in Q3 FY26, swinging to a consolidated net loss of ₹0.86 Cr from a profit last year. The sharp fall was attributed to project completion asset sales and the cancellation of a subsidiary's license, signalling significant operational challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:13:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a670fa7d0695d1abe5eb_1772201693069.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Finance Raises ₹831 Cr via Secured NCDs at 8.6% Coupon</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Cholamandalam-Finance-Raises-831-Cr-via-Secured-NCDs-at-86percent-Coupon/69a1a491fa7d0695d1abe435</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Cholamandalam-Finance-Raises-831-Cr-via-Secured-NCDs-at-86percent-Coupon/69a1a491fa7d0695d1abe435</guid><description>Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company Limited (CIFL) has successfully allotted ₹831 crore of Secured Non-Convertible Securities through private placement on the NSE's WDM segment. This capital infusion, part of a larger ₹1500 crore issue, carries an 8.60% coupon rate and matures in March 2029. The fundraising bolsters the NBFC's capital base for its expanding loan book.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 14:05:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a491fa7d0695d1abe434_1772201417883.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Techknowgreen Solutions Earns TRL 9 Certification for Wetland Technology</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Techknowgreen-Solutions-Earns-TRL-9-Certification-for-Wetland-Technology/69a1a333fa7d0695d1abe236</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Techknowgreen-Solutions-Earns-TRL-9-Certification-for-Wetland-Technology/69a1a333fa7d0695d1abe236</guid><description>Techknowgreen Solutions Limited has secured a Technology Readiness Level (TRL) 9 certification for its Circular Economic Wetland Technology, issued by the National Establishment for Technology Readiness Assessment (NETRA). This milestone validates the technology as proven and ready for operational deployment, marking a significant achievement for the company's environmental solutions.

This certification underscores Techknowgreen's commitment to innovation in wastewater treatment and positions its technology for broader commercial application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:59:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a333fa7d0695d1abe235_1772200875566.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motherson Completes JV With Taiwan's Macauto For Auto Parts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Motherson-Completes-JV-With-Taiwans-Macauto-For-Auto-Parts/69a1a32dfa7d0695d1abe220</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Motherson-Completes-JV-With-Taiwans-Macauto-For-Auto-Parts/69a1a32dfa7d0695d1abe220</guid><description>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited has finalized its joint venture, Motherson Macauto Solutions Limited (MMASL), with Taiwan's Macauto Industrial Co., Ltd. Effective February 27, 2026, the JV will focus on designing, developing, manufacturing, and servicing automotive parts like door, window, and roof sunshade systems. This strategic move enhances Motherson's product capabilities and market reach in the automotive sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:59:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a32dfa7d0695d1abe21f_1772200887020.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anirit Ventures Acquires Agritech Firm for ₹12.87 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Anirit-Ventures-Acquires-Agritech-Firm-for-1287-Cr/69a1a328fa7d0695d1abe20a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Anirit-Ventures-Acquires-Agritech-Firm-for-1287-Cr/69a1a328fa7d0695d1abe20a</guid><description>Anirit Ventures Limited announced the successful acquisition of 100% equity in Anirit Agritech Private Limited for ₹12.87 crore. Funded by its rights issue proceeds, the move is set to bolster Anirit Ventures' footprint in the burgeoning Agritech sector, with a focus on controlled weather farming. This strategic expansion signals a push into a new growth area for the company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:59:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a328fa7d0695d1abe209_1772201059684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABB India posts record CY2025 orders, revenue; declares dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-India-posts-record-CY2025-orders-revenue-declares-dividend/69a1a1d8fa7d0695d1abe075</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-India-posts-record-CY2025-orders-revenue-declares-dividend/69a1a1d8fa7d0695d1abe075</guid><description>ABB India announced its best-ever CY2025 performance with record orders of ₹14,115 crore and revenue of ₹13,203 crore, both growing 8%. The company declared a final dividend of ₹29.59 per share, underpinned by strong demand across segments and a robust order backlog. However, margin pressures persist due to higher material and labor costs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:53:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a1d8fa7d0695d1abe074_1772200699867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Stock Surges Amidst Strong Orders, But Valuation Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Stock-Surges-Amidst-Strong-Orders-But-Valuation-Looms/69a1a15ffa7d0695d1abdfba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Stock-Surges-Amidst-Strong-Orders-But-Valuation-Looms/69a1a15ffa7d0695d1abdfba</guid><description>Hitachi Energy India (HEIL) has seen its stock price surge by 54% in the past month, driven by strong fourth-quarter financial results and an expanding order backlog. Revenue grew 29% year-over-year, while operating profit and adjusted net profit saw significant increases of 107% and 241%, respectively. The company's operating profit margin improved to 16.6%. Despite positive operational momentum and a substantial order book exceeding ₹29,900 crore, the stock's valuation, trading at a P/E of approximately 292x trailing twelve months earnings, presents a key area for investor scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:51:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a15ffa7d0695d1abdfb9_1772200426071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Investor Boom Matures: AMCs Face Valuation Tests</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Investor-Boom-Matures-AMCs-Face-Valuation-Tests/69a1a107fa7d0695d1abdee0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Investor-Boom-Matures-AMCs-Face-Valuation-Tests/69a1a107fa7d0695d1abdee0</guid><description>India's financial markets are witnessing a profound shift, with over 12 crore unique investors now active, primarily through mutual funds and ETFs. This surge, fueled by post-pandemic financial literacy and a move away from traditional savings like gold and property, highlights a maturing investor base. Leading asset management companies (AMCs) like HDFC AMC and ICICI Prudential AMC, while managing record Assets Under Management (AUM), face scrutiny as their valuations appear stretched against industry averages. The trend indicates not just growth, but a growing demand for diversified, sophisticated investment products.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:49:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a107fa7d0695d1abdedf_1772200490387.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Niva Bupa Faces IRDAI's Spotlight Amid Regulatory Crackdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Niva-Bupa-Faces-IRDAIs-Spotlight-Amid-Regulatory-Crackdown/69a1a0d1fa7d0695d1abdec7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Niva-Bupa-Faces-IRDAIs-Spotlight-Amid-Regulatory-Crackdown/69a1a0d1fa7d0695d1abdec7</guid><description>Niva Bupa Health Insurance is under increased regulatory scrutiny following a Show Cause Notice (SCN) and Letter of Advice from the IRDAI, issued on February 26, 2026. These actions stem from an inspection in February 2025, citing violations of master circulars concerning business operations, policyholder protection, and corporate governance. While the company asserts no immediate financial impact, the development occurs within a broader context of IRDAI intensifying oversight across the health insurance sector, with peer companies also facing penalties for compliance lapses. The stock closed down 2.3% on the NSE, reflecting investor caution over potential long-term implications for governance and operational integrity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a0d1fa7d0695d1abdec6_1772200369541.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brahmaputra Waterways Inaugurated: Northeast Trade Gateway Unlocked</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Brahmaputra-Waterways-Inaugurated-Northeast-Trade-Gateway-Unlocked/69a1a021fa7d0695d1abdd9f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Brahmaputra-Waterways-Inaugurated-Northeast-Trade-Gateway-Unlocked/69a1a021fa7d0695d1abdd9f</guid><description>Union Minister Sarbananda Sonowal inaugurated three key inland waterway projects on National Waterway-2 (Brahmaputra River), enhancing customs, immigration, and administrative functions. These developments aim to revive the river as a major economic corridor, reducing logistics costs and strengthening cross-border trade with Bangladesh and beyond, aligning with India's 'Vikas and Virasat' vision.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:46:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1a021fa7d0695d1abdd9e_1772200125816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eros Bets on 'Sovereign Identity' in Cultural AI Launch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eros-Bets-on-Sovereign-Identity-in-Cultural-AI-Launch/69a19ffffa7d0695d1abdd23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eros-Bets-on-Sovereign-Identity-in-Cultural-AI-Launch/69a19ffffa7d0695d1abdd23</guid><description>Eros Innovation has launched Large Cultural Voice Models (LCVM) and PERSONA AI infrastructure in Tamil Nadu, focusing on preserving cultural nuances, emotion, and identity in AI. This move into "sovereign AI" and "identity as a digital asset" positions the company to capture a unique market niche within India's rapidly expanding artificial intelligence sector. The initiative aims to create over 1,000 high-skill jobs and fosters collaboration with IIT Madras, aligning with national efforts to build indigenous, culturally grounded AI solutions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19ffffa7d0695d1abdd22_1772200215260.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Autonomous Leap: Oaktree Memo Flags Systemic Economic Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Autonomous-Leap-Oaktree-Memo-Flags-Systemic-Economic-Shift/69a19f9dfa7d0695d1abdbd2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Autonomous-Leap-Oaktree-Memo-Flags-Systemic-Economic-Shift/69a19f9dfa7d0695d1abdbd2</guid><description>Oaktree Capital Management's Howard Marks asserts AI has evolved from a productivity tool to autonomous agents, a transition poised to redefine industries and labor. Released February 26, 2026, the memo "AI Hurtles Ahead" highlights AI's unprecedented adoption speed and self-improvement capabilities, while cautioning investors about current valuations and the potential for significant economic and societal upheaval. This marks a fundamental shift, potentially separating a $50 billion market from one measured in trillions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:43:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19f9dfa7d0695d1abdbd1_1772199944692.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Real Estate: Trust Deficit Deters Buyers Amidst Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Real-Estate-Trust-Deficit-Deters-Buyers-Amidst-Growth/69a19f8bfa7d0695d1abdbbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Real-Estate-Trust-Deficit-Deters-Buyers-Amidst-Growth/69a19f8bfa7d0695d1abdbbb</guid><description>Despite strong demand and market expansion, home buying in India is hampered by a pervasive trust deficit. Buyers are apprehensive due to fears of project delays, undisclosed fees, and unfulfilled promises, a concern amplified by the increasing scale and complexity of developments. While regulatory reforms aim to bolster transparency, confidence remains the critical constraint on sustainable market growth. Addressing this requires a collective commitment to accountability, realistic timelines, and upfront communication across the entire real estate ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:43:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19f8bfa7d0695d1abdbba_1772199920913.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Director Liability Drives Demand for Governance Audits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Director-Liability-Drives-Demand-for-Governance-Audits/69a19f3dfa7d0695d1abdb2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Director-Liability-Drives-Demand-for-Governance-Audits/69a19f3dfa7d0695d1abdb2c</guid><description>The IndiGo governance breakdown revealed the inadequacy of current corporate oversight ratings. Beyond external scores, directors face escalating personal legal, reputational, and ethical exposure. This necessitates a shift towards 'director assurance audits'—independent, director-focused examinations of real risk and preparedness, rather than superficial compliance metrics. Such audits aim to equip board members with a clear understanding of liabilities, a crucial step given the stringent legal framework and insurance limitations in India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:42:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19f3dfa7d0695d1abdb2b_1772199881759.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Carraro India Invests ₹300 Cr Amid Tractor Tech Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carraro-India-Invests-300-Cr-Amid-Tractor-Tech-Shift/69a19e7bfa7d0695d1abd9f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carraro-India-Invests-300-Cr-Amid-Tractor-Tech-Shift/69a19e7bfa7d0695d1abd9f5</guid><description>Carraro India is set to invest approximately ₹300 crore over three years, starting FY27, to expand manufacturing capacity for driveline components. This strategic move capitalizes on India's agricultural sector's shift towards higher-horsepower, four-wheel-drive (4WD) and electric tractors, alongside robust demand in the construction equipment market driven by infrastructure development. The company anticipates significant revenue growth, projecting over ₹3,500 crore annually by FY30, bolstered by strong order visibility and increasing localization. However, this ambitious expansion faces hurdles including the slow adoption of electric tractors and intense market competition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:39:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19e7bfa7d0695d1abd9f4_1772199870824.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gravita Acquires Copper Maker, Eyes EV Battery Recycling Amidst Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Gravita-Acquires-Copper-Maker-Eyes-EV-Battery-Recycling-Amidst-Risks/69a19e7bfa7d0695d1abd9de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Gravita-Acquires-Copper-Maker-Eyes-EV-Battery-Recycling-Amidst-Risks/69a19e7bfa7d0695d1abd9de</guid><description>Gravita India has acquired Rashtriya Metals Industries Limited (RMIL) for ₹565 crore, significantly expanding its copper recycling capacity. The company also launched a lithium-ion battery recycling plant in Mundra. While regulatory tailwinds and growing EV demand support these ventures, Gravita faces high valuation multiples compared to industry peers and risks tied to commodity price volatility and the nascent EV battery recycling sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:39:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19e7bfa7d0695d1abd9dd_1772199718294.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GAIL bets Rs 1,736 Cr on Wind Power Amid Profit Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/GAIL-bets-Rs-1736-Cr-on-Wind-Power-Amid-Profit-Dip/69a19d8afa7d0695d1abd8cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/GAIL-bets-Rs-1736-Cr-on-Wind-Power-Amid-Profit-Dip/69a19d8afa7d0695d1abd8cc</guid><description>GAIL India announced a significant Rs 1,736.25 crore investment for a new 178.2 MW greenfield wind power project in Maharashtra, signaling a strategic pivot towards renewable energy. This initiative comes as the company reported a sequential decline in its third-quarter net profit to Rs 1,602.57 crore, with revenue also seeing a slight decrease. The wind project, targeted for completion within 24 months, will be financed through a mix of debt and equity, bolstering GAIL's long-term business growth and energy transition alignment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:35:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19d8afa7d0695d1abd8cb_1772199632012.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kabra Extrusiontechnik Bags ₹133 Cr Energy Storage Contract</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kabra-Extrusiontechnik-Bags-133-Cr-Energy-Storage-Contract/69a19c25fa7d0695d1abd792</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kabra-Extrusiontechnik-Bags-133-Cr-Energy-Storage-Contract/69a19c25fa7d0695d1abd792</guid><description>Kabra Extrusiontechnik Limited has secured a significant ₹133 crore contract for energy storage contract manufacturing from an undisclosed domestic client. The order is slated for execution between FY 2026-27, marking a notable development in the company's diversification into the energy sector. This new business underscores potential growth in its manufacturing capabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:29:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19c25fa7d0695d1abd791_1772199263004.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IIFL Home Finance Secures $300M ECB Amidst India's Housing Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Home-Finance-Secures-300M-ECB-Amidst-Indias-Housing-Crisis/69a19ad1fa7d0695d1abd62c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Home-Finance-Secures-300M-ECB-Amidst-Indias-Housing-Crisis/69a19ad1fa7d0695d1abd62c</guid><description>IIFL Home Finance has secured its inaugural $300 million syndicated external commercial borrowing (ECB) facility, led by the Asian Development Bank (ADB) with participation from MUFG, Emirates Bank, Sampath Bank, and Hatton National Bank. This funding is earmarked to bolster affordable housing finance for low-income borrowers, with a focus on women, and includes a significant allocation for green-certified homes. The deal positions IIFL Home Finance as a pioneer in accessing international syndicated debt for this segment, even as India grapples with a severe and widening affordable housing shortage where supply has plummeted relative to demand.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:23:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19ad1fa7d0695d1abd62b_1772199085971.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jagran Prakashan: NCLT Defers EGM on Director Removal Till March 19</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Jagran-Prakashan-NCLT-Defers-EGM-on-Director-Removal-Till-March-19/69a19acbfa7d0695d1abd615</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Jagran-Prakashan-NCLT-Defers-EGM-on-Director-Removal-Till-March-19/69a19acbfa7d0695d1abd615</guid><description>The National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) has deferred an Extra-ordinary General Meeting (EGM) of Jagran Prakashan Limited, initially called by its holding company Jagran Media Network Investment Private Limited (JMNIPL). The EGM was intended to vote on the removal of seven independent directors and one whole-time director. The NCLT's intervention provides a temporary reprieve from this boardroom battle, postponing further decisions until March 19, 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:23:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19acbfa7d0695d1abd614_1772198935427.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India IT Navigates AI Shift: Disruption Fuels Transformation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-IT-Navigates-AI-Shift-Disruption-Fuels-Transformation/69a19a16fa7d0695d1abd478</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-IT-Navigates-AI-Shift-Disruption-Fuels-Transformation/69a19a16fa7d0695d1abd478</guid><description>India's robust IT sector, projected to exceed $300 billion in revenue by fiscal year 2026, confronts significant disruption from Artificial Intelligence. While fears of widespread job losses are considered overblown, the industry faces a "painful transition." Experts emphasize rapid reskilling and leveraging India's inherent cost efficiencies and vast talent pool to pivot from traditional labor arbitrage towards innovation and higher-value services, mitigating near-term pressures on established revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:20:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19a16fa7d0695d1abd477_1772198561877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Temple Raises $54M in Founder-Focused Round</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Temple-Raises-54M-in-Founder-Focused-Round/69a19a10fa7d0695d1abd45d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Temple-Raises-54M-in-Founder-Focused-Round/69a19a10fa7d0695d1abd45d</guid><description>Temple, the health tech venture founded by Deepinder Goyal, has secured $54 million in funding at a $190 million valuation. This capital infusion is primarily driven by investors who previously backed Goyal's food delivery giant, Zomato, alongside significant participation from Temple's early employees. The funds are designated for further product development of Temple's experimental brain flow monitoring device, aiming to sustain operations until its public launch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:20:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19a10fa7d0695d1abd45c_1772198558400.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Africa Green Summit: Ambition High, Execution Faces Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Africa-Green-Summit-Ambition-High-Execution-Faces-Hurdles/69a199f2fa7d0695d1abd3fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Africa-Green-Summit-Ambition-High-Execution-Faces-Hurdles/69a199f2fa7d0695d1abd3fd</guid><description>Africa's Green Economy Summit 2026 convenes in Cape Town, emphasizing a critical shift from ambition to action for green and blue economy development. While projections estimate trillions in economic value and millions of jobs, deep-seated challenges in policy execution, infrastructure development, skills gaps, and financing accessibility remain significant obstacles to realizing this potential. The summit aims to bridge the gap between vision and viable investment, but persistent systemic issues and sectoral hurdles cast a shadow over optimistic forecasts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:19:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a199f2fa7d0695d1abd3fc_1772198559868.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Legal Tech Faces Trust Deficit Amidst Judicial Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/AI-Legal-Tech-Faces-Trust-Deficit-Amidst-Judicial-Scrutiny/69a1998afa7d0695d1abd356</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/AI-Legal-Tech-Faces-Trust-Deficit-Amidst-Judicial-Scrutiny/69a1998afa7d0695d1abd356</guid><description>India's Supreme Court is sounding alarms over AI-generated legal falsehoods, including non-existent case citations. This judicial rebuke, occurring alongside global AI governance talks, exposes a critical trust deficit and governance gap for AI legal technology. The trend risks increasing operational costs for law firms through verification burdens and necessitates stringent regulatory oversight, potentially slowing market expansion for AI legal tools that lack robust accuracy controls. The legal profession confronts a pivotal moment demanding verifiable AI solutions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:18:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1998afa7d0695d1abd355_1772198662583.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's SIM Binding Rules Spark Regulatory Overreach Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-SIM-Binding-Rules-Spark-Regulatory-Overreach-Fears/69a19980fa7d0695d1abd2fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-SIM-Binding-Rules-Spark-Regulatory-Overreach-Fears/69a19980fa7d0695d1abd2fc</guid><description>The Broadband India Forum (BIF) has formally challenged the Department of Telecommunications' (DoT) new SIM binding directives and cybersecurity rules. BIF contends these regulations, set to take effect soon, contain significant legal flaws and exceed the mandate of the Telecommunications Act, 2023. The framework broadly defines 'Telecommunication Identifier User Entities' (TIUEs), encompassing entities like Paytm and WhatsApp, and imposes obligations beyond traditional telecom services, risking regulatory conflict and stifling digital innovation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:17:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a19980fa7d0695d1abd2fb_1772198360902.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alps Industries Shareholders OK New Directors, Boost Capital to ₹3450 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Alps-Industries-Shareholders-OK-New-Directors-Boost-Capital-to-3450-Cr/69a198d7fa7d0695d1abd1a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Alps-Industries-Shareholders-OK-New-Directors-Boost-Capital-to-3450-Cr/69a198d7fa7d0695d1abd1a5</guid><description>Alps Industries Limited shareholders have overwhelmingly approved key resolutions, including the appointment of four new directors for multi-year terms and an amendment to the authorized share capital, now standing at ₹3,450 crore. The company's registered office will also relocate from Ghaziabad to Noida. These approvals, with over 99.9% shareholder backing, are significant steps in the company's ongoing revival plan following its Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP).</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:15:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a198d7fa7d0695d1abd1a4_1772198247936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Green Energy Relief: GIB Delays Ease, But Sector Faces Deeper Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Energy-Relief-GIB-Delays-Ease-But-Sector-Faces-Deeper-Hurdles/69a1987ffa7d0695d1abd0e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Energy-Relief-GIB-Delays-Ease-But-Sector-Faces-Deeper-Hurdles/69a1987ffa7d0695d1abd0e8</guid><description>The Ministry of New and Renewable Energy (MNRE) has provided a force majeure-like status to commissioning delays caused by Supreme Court proceedings over Great Indian Bustard (GIB) habitats. This move offers crucial relief to approximately 8.6 GW of renewable capacity, shielding developers from penalties. However, the decision underscores the ongoing tension between stringent environmental protection mandates and India's rapid energy infrastructure expansion, a conflict that continues to present structural challenges and potential risks for the sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:13:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1987ffa7d0695d1abd0e7_1772198147654.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharat Electronics Declares ₹1.95 Interim Dividend for FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Bharat-Electronics-Declares-195-Interim-Dividend-for-FY26/69a197ebfa7d0695d1abd061</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Bharat-Electronics-Declares-195-Interim-Dividend-for-FY26/69a197ebfa7d0695d1abd061</guid><description>Bharat Electronics' Board has approved an interim dividend of ₹1.95 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. This payout, representing 195% of the face value, highlights the company's strong financial performance and commitment to shareholder returns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 13:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a197ebfa7d0695d1abd060_1772198177817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>