<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:59:02 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Happy Forgings Boosts PAT 15% on Strong Q3, Plans Ludhiana Land Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Happy-Forgings-Boosts-PAT-15percent-on-Strong-Q3-Plans-Ludhiana-Land-Acquisition/6989ad5cb81b2b81dcff25fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Happy-Forgings-Boosts-PAT-15percent-on-Strong-Q3-Plans-Ludhiana-Land-Acquisition/6989ad5cb81b2b81dcff25fe</guid><description>Happy Forgings Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue climbing 12.74% YoY to ₹399.47 Crores and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 15.20% YoY to ₹83.93 Crores. The company also announced a proposal to acquire 10.5 acres of land in Ludhiana for ₹32 Crores, signaling future expansion plans. Nine-month PAT grew an impressive 26.28%.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Abans Financial Standalone Tanks; Consolidated Surges Amid Merger Talks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Abans-Financial-Standalone-Tanks-Consolidated-Surges-Amid-Merger-Talks/6989ac84b81b2b81dcff23cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Abans-Financial-Standalone-Tanks-Consolidated-Surges-Amid-Merger-Talks/6989ac84b81b2b81dcff23cb</guid><description>Abans Financial Services Limited reported a sharp divergence in Q3 FY26 results. Standalone operations saw revenue plummet 58.13% YoY to ₹876.52 Lakhs and PAT drop 57.94% to ₹592.33 Lakhs. Conversely, consolidated revenue surged 407.37% to ₹6,49,461.44 Lakhs, with PAT growing 27.47% to ₹3,431.03 Lakhs. The company also proposed a merger of its subsidiaries.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:44:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989ac84b81b2b81dcff23ca_1770631057912.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JioHotstar Bolsters Tech Leadership for AI-Driven Streaming</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/JioHotstar-Bolsters-Tech-Leadership-for-AI-Driven-Streaming/6989ac71b81b2b81dcff2323</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/JioHotstar-Bolsters-Tech-Leadership-for-AI-Driven-Streaming/6989ac71b81b2b81dcff2323</guid><description>JioHotstar is aggressively staffing its technology and product divisions with seasoned professionals from global tech firms. This strategic move aims to leverage artificial intelligence for delivering hyper-personalized streaming experiences, enhance viewer engagement, and optimize marketing intelligence. The influx of expertise signals a significant push by Reliance Industries to deepen its competitive edge in India's dynamic digital entertainment sector, focusing on technological innovation to drive future growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:44:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989ac71b81b2b81dcff2322.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fintech Surge: GFTN-SPF Pact Fuels Global Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Fintech-Surge-GFTN-SPF-Pact-Fuels-Global-Ambitions/6989ab81b81b2b81dcff20f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Fintech-Surge-GFTN-SPF-Pact-Fuels-Global-Ambitions/6989ab81b81b2b81dcff20f7</guid><description>The Global Finance &amp; Technology Network (GFTN) and the Startup Policy Forum (SPF) have formalized a strategic partnership to propel India's fintech and startup sectors onto the global stage. Announced at the Black Swan Summit India 2026, the collaboration aims to enhance policy engagement, foster international collaboration, and support Indian startups in their overseas expansion. Key focus areas include digital finance infrastructure, responsible AI, digital assets, and cross-border payments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PNG Jewellers Posts Stellar Q3 Profit Surge, Revenue Jumps 35%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PNG-Jewellers-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Profit-Surge-Revenue-Jumps-35percent/6989aaabb81b2b81dcff1ea5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PNG-Jewellers-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Profit-Surge-Revenue-Jumps-35percent/6989aaabb81b2b81dcff1ea5</guid><description>P N Gadgil Jewellers Limited reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with standalone revenue up 35.17% YoY to ₹32,533.43M and PAT soaring 95.10% to ₹1,662.74M. Consolidated PAT surged 98.64% YoY to ₹1,709.11M. The company confirmed full utilization of IPO funds for store expansion and debt repayment. An exceptional item related to employee benefits provision was noted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Electricals Posts Consolidated Loss, Standalone Profit Boosted by One-offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bajaj-Electricals-Posts-Consolidated-Loss-Standalone-Profit-Boosted-by-One-offs/6989aa89b81b2b81dcff1dbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bajaj-Electricals-Posts-Consolidated-Loss-Standalone-Profit-Boosted-by-One-offs/6989aa89b81b2b81dcff1dbb</guid><description>Bajaj Electricals Limited reported a consolidated net loss of ₹4,114 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, a stark reversal from last year's profit. The standalone net profit surged to ₹12,921 Lakhs, primarily due to a substantial net gain of ₹12,889 Lakhs from exceptional items and a ₹1,996 Lakhs tax credit. However, underlying operating performance weakened, with standalone profit before exceptional items turning into a loss of ₹2,028 Lakhs from a profit in the prior year. Consolidated revenue from operations fell 18.5% year-on-year to ₹10,509 Lakhs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:36:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989aa89b81b2b81dcff1dba.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Enviro Infra Fraud Shocks Investors: Profit Plummets 96% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Enviro-Infra-Fraud-Shocks-Investors-Profit-Plummets-96percent-YoY/6989aa14b81b2b81dcff1c49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Enviro-Infra-Fraud-Shocks-Investors-Profit-Plummets-96percent-YoY/6989aa14b81b2b81dcff1c49</guid><description>Enviro Infra Engineers Limited reported dismal Q3 FY26 results, with standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeting 96.1% year-on-year to ₹61.74 Lakhs. The consolidated PAT declined 33.7% to ₹486.06 Lakhs. Significant exceptional charges of ₹1,259.11 Lakhs and ₹4,525.76 Lakhs were recorded on standalone and consolidated nine-month periods, respectively, linked to a disclosed fraud incident. Standalone revenue fell 21.3% YoY in Q3, while consolidated revenue saw a modest 7.9% rise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:34:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989aa14b81b2b81dcff1c48_1770630381444.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Electricals: ₹30Cr Q3 Loss, Revenue Dips; Standalone Profit Surges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bajaj-Electricals-30Cr-Q3-Loss-Revenue-Dips-Standalone-Profit-Surges/6989a99db81b2b81dcff1a95</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bajaj-Electricals-30Cr-Q3-Loss-Revenue-Dips-Standalone-Profit-Surges/6989a99db81b2b81dcff1a95</guid><description>Bajaj Electricals unveiled mixed Q3 FY26 results, reporting a consolidated net loss of ₹3,085 lakhs, a stark reversal from last year's profit, heavily impacted by ₹-2,889 lakhs in exceptional items primarily due to new labour codes. Consolidated revenue slipped 18.5% YoY to ₹104,830 lakhs. Conversely, standalone net profit surged by 287% to ₹12,921 lakhs, though basic EPS declined to ₹2.89. The company also approved selling office premises for ₹26.53 crore to related entities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:32:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989a99db81b2b81dcff1a94.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Launches India's Longest Range Electric 3-Wheeler</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Bajaj-Auto-Launches-Indias-Longest-Range-Electric-3-Wheeler/6989a955b81b2b81dcff193a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Bajaj-Auto-Launches-Indias-Longest-Range-Electric-3-Wheeler/6989a955b81b2b81dcff193a</guid><description>Bajaj Auto has launched the WEGO P9018, its new electric three-wheeler, marking a significant entry into the EV commercial vehicle segment. This model boasts India's longest certified range of 296 km, powered by a 17.7 kWh battery. Positioned as the largest electric three-wheeler, it aims to enhance operator earnings by facilitating high-volume mobility over medium to long distances. Priced at ₹4,41,247 ex-showroom, it targets diverse markets across India.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:31:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a955b81b2b81dcff1939_1770630232035.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Holdings Posts 27% PAT Surge; Insurance Arm Shows Mixed Performance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cholamandalam-Holdings-Posts-27percent-PAT-Surge-Insurance-Arm-Shows-Mixed-Performance/6989a940b81b2b81dcff1829</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cholamandalam-Holdings-Posts-27percent-PAT-Surge-Insurance-Arm-Shows-Mixed-Performance/6989a940b81b2b81dcff1829</guid><description>Cholamandalam Financial Holdings (CFHL) announced robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated PAT jumping 27% YoY to ₹1,386 Cr, driven by strong performance at Cholamandalam Investment &amp; Finance (CIFCL). CIFCL saw disbursements up 17% and AUM grow 20%. However, its insurance subsidiary, Cholamandalam MS General Insurance (CMSGICL), reported a mixed quarter, with PAT boosted by MTM gains but nine-month PAT declining 30% due to higher claims. Increased employee costs from new labour codes were also noted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:30:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a940b81b2b81dcff1828_1770630045317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ceigall India Revenue Soars 19%; Declining Profit, High Debt Raise Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ceigall-India-Revenue-Soars-19percent-Declining-Profit-High-Debt-Raise-Concern/6989a923b81b2b81dcff1759</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ceigall-India-Revenue-Soars-19percent-Declining-Profit-High-Debt-Raise-Concern/6989a923b81b2b81dcff1759</guid><description>Ceigall India posted robust Q3 FY26 consolidated revenue growth of 19.3% YoY to ₹9,911 million, fueled by infrastructure demand. However, Profit After Tax (PAT) saw only a marginal 2.3% YoY rise to ₹724 million, with 9M FY26 PAT down 16.0%. The company is banking on a substantial order book, including L1 bids for major metro and corridor projects, and strategic asset monetization to fund growth and reduce leverage. International expansion is also underway, but declining profitability metrics raise questions for investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:30:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a923b81b2b81dcff1758_1770629899084.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Holdings Profit Surges 27% Driven by Financing Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Cholamandalam-Holdings-Profit-Surges-27percent-Driven-by-Financing-Growth/6989a84eb81b2b81dcff1544</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Cholamandalam-Holdings-Profit-Surges-27percent-Driven-by-Financing-Growth/6989a84eb81b2b81dcff1544</guid><description>Cholamandalam Financial Holdings (CFHL) reported robust Q3 FY26 consolidated results, with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 27% year-on-year to ₹1,386 Cr on a 17% revenue increase. Assets Under Management in its financing segment grew 20.4% to ₹2.27 lakh crore. While the insurance segment's GWP rose, its nine-month PAT declined 29.5% due to higher claims, though Q3 PAT benefited from MTM gains. Standalone PAT also showed strong growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:26:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a84eb81b2b81dcff1543_1770629765310.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Venky's Q3 Profit Doubles: Margin Surge Meets High Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Venkys-Q3-Profit-Doubles-Margin-Surge-Meets-High-Valuation/6989a831b81b2b81dcff144f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Venkys-Q3-Profit-Doubles-Margin-Surge-Meets-High-Valuation/6989a831b81b2b81dcff144f</guid><description>Venky's (India) Ltd. announced a robust third quarter with net profit more than doubling to ₹48.6 crore, fueled by enhanced realisations in its core poultry segment. Revenue increased by 9% year-on-year to ₹960 crore, while EBITDA margins expanded sharply to 7.3% from 3.3% a year ago. Despite the strong performance, the company's shares trade at a high valuation, prompting a closer look at the sustainability of these gains amidst industry cycles.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:26:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a831b81b2b81dcff144e_1770629634889.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rashi Peripherals Q3 Revenue Surges 43%, PAT Jumps 132% on PC Market Rebound</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Rashi-Peripherals-Q3-Revenue-Surges-43percent-PAT-Jumps-132percent-on-PC-Market-Rebound/6989a778b81b2b81dcff1256</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Rashi-Peripherals-Q3-Revenue-Surges-43percent-PAT-Jumps-132percent-on-PC-Market-Rebound/6989a778b81b2b81dcff1256</guid><description>Rashi Peripherals reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 43% YoY to INR 4,030 cr, and PAT soaring 132% YoY to INR 75 cr, margins at 1.85%. The company attributes this surge to a recovering PC market, strategic pricing, and an anticipated technology upgrade cycle. Management expresses optimism for multi-year growth, focusing on demand creation and geographic expansion, despite the phasing out of Micron's 'Crucial' consumer brand business. Working capital remains disciplined at 60 days, with a debt-to-equity ratio of 0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:23:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989a778b81b2b81dcff1255.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Virtuoso Opto Surges: Q3 Sales Nearly Double, Diversification Drives Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Virtuoso-Opto-Surges-Q3-Sales-Nearly-Double-Diversification-Drives-Margins/6989a759b81b2b81dcff115a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Virtuoso-Opto-Surges-Q3-Sales-Nearly-Double-Diversification-Drives-Margins/6989a759b81b2b81dcff115a</guid><description>Virtuoso Optoelectronics Ltd reported a robust Q3 FY26, with net sales nearly doubling QoQ to INR 205 cr (up 36% YoY). EBITDA margins exceeded 11% due to successful diversification into refrigeration and other segments. The company reaffirms FY26 revenue guidance of INR 800-900 cr and plans significant capacity expansions, particularly in compressors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:22:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989a759b81b2b81dcff1159.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fraud Alleged as Enviro Infra Engineers' Profits Plunge 65.7%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Fraud-Alleged-as-Enviro-Infra-Engineers-Profits-Plunge-657percent/6989a746b81b2b81dcff10a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Fraud-Alleged-as-Enviro-Infra-Engineers-Profits-Plunge-657percent/6989a746b81b2b81dcff10a8</guid><description>Enviro Infra Engineers Limited (EIEL) disclosed alarming unaudited results, revealing a 65.7% year-on-year profit after tax (PAT) decline for Q3 FY26 to ₹1,657.55 Lakhs on a consolidated basis. Revenue also fell 28.7% YoY. Significantly, the company's independent auditor flagged the identification of fraud within the company during the nine-month period, though their review conclusion was not modified. No management guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:22:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a746b81b2b81dcff10a7_1770629315116.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal's Sector Bets: 5 Stocks Eyeing Major Upside</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Motilal-Oswals-Sector-Bets-5-Stocks-Eyeing-Major-Upside/6989a6cdb81b2b81dcff0f22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Motilal-Oswals-Sector-Bets-5-Stocks-Eyeing-Major-Upside/6989a6cdb81b2b81dcff0f22</guid><description>Brokerage firm Motilal Oswal has initiated 'Buy' ratings on five stocks across jewellery, finance, consumer durables, water infrastructure, and electronics manufacturing sectors. These recommendations, projecting potential gains of up to 58%, are based on anticipated earnings growth and balance sheet improvements. However, a comprehensive market analysis indicates significant divergences in risk profiles, valuation concerns, and competitive positioning among these selected entities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:20:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a6cdb81b2b81dcff0f21_1770629169557.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coromandel International Revenue Jumps 26%, Profit Dips Amidst Raw Material Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Coromandel-International-Revenue-Jumps-26percent-Profit-Dips-Amidst-Raw-Material-Surge/6989a655b81b2b81dcff0d79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Coromandel-International-Revenue-Jumps-26percent-Profit-Dips-Amidst-Raw-Material-Surge/6989a655b81b2b81dcff0d79</guid><description>Coromandel International reported a strong 26% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹8,863 Cr for Q3 FY26. However, Net Profit After Tax (PAT) saw a 4% decline to ₹488 Cr, attributed partly to significant raw material price increases and subsidy collection challenges. The company highlighted robust performance in Crop Protection and Specialty Nutrients segments, with capacity expansions and new product launches driving growth. Management reaffirmed fertilizer EBITDA targets post-commissioning of backward integration projects, while assessing CDMO opportunities and global Nano DAP expansion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:18:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a655b81b2b81dcff0d78_1770629128336.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CCL Products Posts Stellar Q3; Revenue Surges 38%, Debt Falls Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/CCL-Products-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Revenue-Surges-38percent-Debt-Falls-Sharply/6989a61cb81b2b81dcff0c0f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/CCL-Products-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Revenue-Surges-38percent-Debt-Falls-Sharply/6989a61cb81b2b81dcff0c0f</guid><description>CCL Products India delivered robust Q3 FY26 results with 38% YoY revenue growth to INR 1,053 Cr and a 59% Net Profit jump to INR 100.26 Cr. The company significantly reduced gross debt to INR 1,448 Cr and net debt to INR 1,248 Cr, ahead of schedule. Strong volume growth and domestic brand expansion fuel the positive outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:17:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a61cb81b2b81dcff0c0e_1770628973815.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vishnu Chemicals Eyes 20% EBITDA Margins by FY28 Amid Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Vishnu-Chemicals-Eyes-20percent-EBITDA-Margins-by-FY28-Amid-Expansion/6989a5fcb81b2b81dcff0ae6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Vishnu-Chemicals-Eyes-20percent-EBITDA-Margins-by-FY28-Amid-Expansion/6989a5fcb81b2b81dcff0ae6</guid><description>Vishnu Chemicals reported resilient Q3 FY26 results, with revenue up 2.5% QoQ to ₹411.3 cr and EBITDA up 6% to ₹61.7 cr, margins improving to 15%. The company is executing strategic backward integration via a South African mine acquisition and commercializing Strontium Carbonate. Management targets 20% EBITDA margins by FY28, fueled by new capacities and favourable trade policies, with significant CAPEX planned.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:16:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a5fcb81b2b81dcff0ae5_1770628809029.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lloyds Enterprises: Q3 Loss, 9M Profit Fueled by 'Other Income', Sells Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Enterprises-Q3-Loss-9M-Profit-Fueled-by-Other-Income-Sells-Stake/6989a5e5b81b2b81dcff0a38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Enterprises-Q3-Loss-9M-Profit-Fueled-by-Other-Income-Sells-Stake/6989a5e5b81b2b81dcff0a38</guid><description>Lloyds Enterprises reported a mixed Q3 FY26. Standalone revenue surged 108% YoY to ₹48.76 Cr, but the company posted a ₹4.68 Cr net loss. Consolidated revenue grew marginally to ₹299.18 Cr, with net profit falling 33.4% to ₹27.50 Cr. For nine months, standalone net profit jumped to ₹246.64 Cr, heavily boosted by ₹301.94 Cr 'Other Income'. The company also approved a ₹500 Cr NCD issuance and sold its stake in subsidiary LEWL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:16:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a5e5b81b2b81dcff0a37_1770628714255.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lloyds Enterprises Posts Mixed Q3; Eyes ₹500 Cr NCD for Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Enterprises-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Eyes-500-Cr-NCD-for-Growth/6989a413b81b2b81dcff0745</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Enterprises-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Eyes-500-Cr-NCD-for-Growth/6989a413b81b2b81dcff0745</guid><description>Lloyds Enterprises Limited unveiled mixed financial results for Q3 FY26, reporting a standalone net loss of ₹4.68 crore despite a 108% YoY revenue jump to ₹48.76 crore. However, the nine-month period saw a monumental 1589% YoY surge in standalone Net Profit to ₹246.64 crore, driven primarily by a significant boost in 'Other Income'. On a consolidated basis, Q3 Net Profit dipped 33% YoY to ₹27.50 crore, while 9M Net Profit soared 217% to ₹314.22 crore, also propelled by substantial 'Other Income'. The company also approved a ₹500 crore Non-Convertible Debenture issuance and divested its stake in subsidiary Lloyds Engineering Works.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:08:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a413b81b2b81dcff0744_1770628260019.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ceigall India Appoints New CEO, Sells Highway Arm for ₹177 Cr Amid Fraud Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ceigall-India-Appoints-New-CEO-Sells-Highway-Arm-for-177-Cr-Amid-Fraud-Probe/6989a402b81b2b81dcff06c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ceigall-India-Appoints-New-CEO-Sells-Highway-Arm-for-177-Cr-Amid-Fraud-Probe/6989a402b81b2b81dcff06c6</guid><description>Ceigall India Limited has appointed Mr. A. Saravanan as its new CEO, effective February 10, 2026. The company also approved the sale of its step-down subsidiary, Ceigall Malout Abohar Sadhuwali Highways Private Limited, for ₹177 Crores, expected to complete by June 30, 2026. This divestment comes as the company reported strong Q3 FY26 financial results with standalone revenue up 23.25% and consolidated revenue up 22.89% YoY. However, Ceigall India lodged an FIR for alleged fraudulent purchases totaling ₹89.65 Million in the quarter, though it stated no P&amp;L impact due to accounting adjustments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:08:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a402b81b2b81dcff06c5_1770628188781.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>eMudhra Rejects 3i Infotech Fraud Claims, Prepares Legal Onslaught</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/eMudhra-Rejects-3i-Infotech-Fraud-Claims-Prepares-Legal-Onslaught/6989a30db81b2b81dcff053b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/eMudhra-Rejects-3i-Infotech-Fraud-Claims-Prepares-Legal-Onslaught/6989a30db81b2b81dcff053b</guid><description>eMudhra Limited has strongly refuted serious allegations of fraud, conflict of interest, and undervaluation by 3i Infotech Limited. During an investor conference call, Executive Chairman Venkatraman Srinivasan detailed historical transactions, including the 2010 divestment and preference share redemptions, asserting full transparency and compliance. eMudhra denied any wrongdoing and declared its readiness to legally contest the claims, expressing confidence in prevailing in court.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a30db81b2b81dcff053a_1770627965582.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TAJGVK Hotels Posts Record 9M Profit Amid Expansion, Q3 Dip Due to One-Offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/TAJGVK-Hotels-Posts-Record-9M-Profit-Amid-Expansion-Q3-Dip-Due-to-One-Offs/6989a21bb81b2b81dcff039f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/TAJGVK-Hotels-Posts-Record-9M-Profit-Amid-Expansion-Q3-Dip-Due-to-One-Offs/6989a21bb81b2b81dcff039f</guid><description>TAJGVK Hotels &amp; Resorts reported a record Profit After Tax (PAT) of ₹89 Crore for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, a 35% YoY surge driven by 13.6% revenue growth and a 35.6% EBITDA margin. However, Q3 FY26 saw an 8% revenue rise to ₹138 Crore, but PAT declined 14.7% to ₹29 Crore due to ₹6.18 Crore in one-time expenses, including gratuity provisions and license fee hikes. The company is set to open its new Taj Yelahanka hotel and acquire a majority stake in Taj Santacruz, Mumbai, bolstering future growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:00:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a21bb81b2b81dcff039e_1770627678092.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Keystone Realtors Posts 23% Presales Jump, Expands Commercial Footprint</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Keystone-Realtors-Posts-23percent-Presales-Jump-Expands-Commercial-Footprint/6989a1a6b81b2b81dcff024b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Keystone-Realtors-Posts-23percent-Presales-Jump-Expands-Commercial-Footprint/6989a1a6b81b2b81dcff024b</guid><description>Keystone Realtors reported a strong Q3 FY26 with INR 837 crores in presales, driving YTD growth to 23% YoY. The company achieved INR 2,676 crores YTD, bolstered by significant business development wins that exceeded guidance by 1.44x. Gross margins improved to 35% YTD, while maintaining a net cash positive position with INR 625 crores gross debt and INR 717 crores free cash. Strategic expansion into commercial real estate and focus on redevelopment signal robust future prospects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:58:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a1a6b81b2b81dcff024a_1770627576004.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TAJGVK Hotels Buys Majority Control of Taj Santacruz for ₹16 Crore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/TAJGVK-Hotels-Buys-Majority-Control-of-Taj-Santacruz-for-16-Crore/6989a0cbb81b2b81dcff004f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/TAJGVK-Hotels-Buys-Majority-Control-of-Taj-Santacruz-for-16-Crore/6989a0cbb81b2b81dcff004f</guid><description>TAJGVK Hotels &amp; Resorts will acquire an additional 2.01% stake in Green Woods Palaces and Resorts, operator of Taj Santacruz, for ₹16.09 crore. This move increases TAJGVK's shareholding to 51%, making Green Woods a subsidiary and consolidating control over the prime Mumbai luxury hotel asset. The company reported strong consolidated FY24-25 results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:54:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a0cbb81b2b81dcff004e_1770627432192.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Beats Q3 Estimates, Valuation Offers Relative Appeal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Zydus-Lifesciences-Beats-Q3-Estimates-Valuation-Offers-Relative-Appeal/6989a0b1b81b2b81dcfeff98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Zydus-Lifesciences-Beats-Q3-Estimates-Valuation-Offers-Relative-Appeal/6989a0b1b81b2b81dcfeff98</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences reported third-quarter earnings that surpassed analyst forecasts, driving a significant stock price increase. The company's net profit and revenue showed robust year-on-year growth, with margins also expanding. This performance positions Zydus favorably with a P/E ratio that appears attractive when benchmarked against major competitors in the Indian pharmaceutical sector, even as industry-wide challenges persist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:54:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a0b1b81b2b81dcfeff97_1770627323006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Graphite India Rebounds to Profitability, but Long-Term Concerns Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Graphite-India-Rebounds-to-Profitability-but-Long-Term-Concerns-Linger/6989a03bb81b2b81dcfefe76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Graphite-India-Rebounds-to-Profitability-but-Long-Term-Concerns-Linger/6989a03bb81b2b81dcfefe76</guid><description>Graphite India Limited returned to profitability in Q3 FY26, reporting a consolidated net profit of ₹68 crore on revenue of ₹642 crore, a significant improvement from the prior year's net loss. However, the company's nine-month profit has declined year-on-year, and it faces headwinds from softer electrode prices and a history of poor sales growth. Analysts maintain a mixed outlook with a 'Hold' rating and expensive valuation concerns.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:52:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989a03bb81b2b81dcfefe75_1770627274697.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Stocks Diverge: SBI Soars, REC Dips Amidst Merger Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Stocks-Diverge-SBI-Soars-REC-Dips-Amidst-Merger-Woes/69899eefb81b2b81dcfefc39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Stocks-Diverge-SBI-Soars-REC-Dips-Amidst-Merger-Woes/69899eefb81b2b81dcfefc39</guid><description>Indian equities showed strength, led by State Bank of India hitting record highs on robust December quarter results and broad PSU bank support. Shipping Corporation of India surged on profit growth, while Vodafone Idea gained on promoter buying despite structural challenges. Kalyan Jewellers also rallied strongly after excellent earnings. Conversely, Suzlon Energy saw profit-taking, and REC shares declined due to uncertainty surrounding its proposed merger with PFC. The market demonstrates a clear preference for validated earnings growth over speculative future prospects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:46:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69899eefb81b2b81dcfefc38_1770627027363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Suprajit Engineering Q3: Standalone Profit Jumps 17%, Consolidated Profit Plunges 62%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Suprajit-Engineering-Q3-Standalone-Profit-Jumps-17percent-Consolidated-Profit-Plunges-62percent/69899ed4b81b2b81dcfefb6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Suprajit-Engineering-Q3-Standalone-Profit-Jumps-17percent-Consolidated-Profit-Plunges-62percent/69899ed4b81b2b81dcfefb6b</guid><description>Suprajit Engineering reported a mixed Q3 FY26. Standalone revenue climbed 8.47% to ₹4,940.61 million, with PAT up 16.85% to ₹710.26 million and margins improving. However, consolidated revenue surged 17.72% to ₹9,789.57 million, PAT plummeted 62.52% to ₹125.27 million, and margins contracted significantly to 1.28%. This divergence was driven by an exceptional provision for new Labour Codes and higher tax expenses, impacting the consolidated figures. The company declared an interim dividend of Re. 1.50 per share.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:46:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69899ed4b81b2b81dcfefb6a_1770626885604.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks Rise on FII Inflows, Japan Capital Shift; IT Faces Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Stocks-Rise-on-FII-Inflows-Japan-Capital-Shift-IT-Faces-Headwinds/69899d85b81b2b81dcfef903</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Stocks-Rise-on-FII-Inflows-Japan-Capital-Shift-IT-Faces-Headwinds/69899d85b81b2b81dcfef903</guid><description>Indian stock markets opened higher, propelled by robust foreign institutional investor (FII) inflows and a strategic shift in global capital allocation influenced by Japan's economic security policies. While banking stocks are poised for gains due to strong credit growth, the IT sector faces uncertainty from 'Anthropic shock,' contrasting the broader market optimism. Asian markets provided a supportive backdrop for this advance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:40:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69899d85b81b2b81dcfef902_1770626662672.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Velocity Shipping Fuels Growth with Internal Capital, Faces Market Giants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Velocity-Shipping-Fuels-Growth-with-Internal-Capital-Faces-Market-Giants/69899d6db81b2b81dcfef834</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Velocity-Shipping-Fuels-Growth-with-Internal-Capital-Faces-Market-Giants/69899d6db81b2b81dcfef834</guid><description>Velocity is injecting ₹100 crore from its own revenue into Velocity Shipping, its AI-led logistics subsidiary, over two years. This move aims to enhance speed and reliability for digital-first brands, building on the subsidiary's rapid 70% month-on-month order growth and 40% revenue contribution. While demonstrating financial discipline, this internal funding strategy positions Velocity Shipping against well-capitalized competitors like Shiprocket and Xpressbees, demanding significant operational efficiency and technological advantage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:40:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69899d6db81b2b81dcfef833_1770626600816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Giants Surge to New Peaks on Robust Demand Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Giants-Surge-to-New-Peaks-on-Robust-Demand-Outlook/69899b18b81b2b81dcfef537</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Giants-Surge-to-New-Peaks-on-Robust-Demand-Outlook/69899b18b81b2b81dcfef537</guid><description>Leading Indian steelmakers, including Tata Steel, JSW Steel, and Jindal Steel, have surged to fresh record highs. Robust domestic demand, a shift to net export status, and supportive government trade policies are fueling the rally. Analysts forecast sustained growth for the sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:30:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69899b18b81b2b81dcfef536_1770626268073.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Life Insurance: GST Cut Fuels Growth Amidst Margin Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Life-Insurance-GST-Cut-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Margin-Pressure/69899abfb81b2b81dcfef3a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Life-Insurance-GST-Cut-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Margin-Pressure/69899abfb81b2b81dcfef3a8</guid><description>India's life insurance industry is experiencing a surge in demand following the Goods and Services Tax (GST) exemption on individual life insurance premiums, effective September 22, 2025. While this policy shift makes policies up to 18% cheaper and stimulates new business premiums, it also introduces margin compression for insurers due to the loss of input tax credits, potentially increasing operational expenses by 3-8%. Analysts are closely watching how companies manage this dual impact to sustain growth momentum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:28:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69899abfb81b2b81dcfef3a7_1770626127245.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Growth: Domestic Firepower Meets Earnings Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Domestic-Firepower-Meets-Earnings-Scrutiny/69899aa2b81b2b81dcfef2f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Domestic-Firepower-Meets-Earnings-Scrutiny/69899aa2b81b2b81dcfef2f3</guid><description>India's economic strength, driven by a potent domestic capital flywheel, offers insulation from global volatility. While private equity, M&amp;A, and retail investments exceed $100 billion each over 2024-2025, senior Axis Capital leadership notes that concrete evidence of corporate earnings recovery is now the paramount factor for attracting sustained foreign institutional investor capital amid global uncertainties. Geopolitical shifts provide psychological impetus, but profitability will dictate market performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:28:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69899aa2b81b2b81dcfef2f2_1770625934115.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>State Borrowing Surge Sends Indian Bonds Lower; RBI Unveils Credit Derivatives Draft</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/State-Borrowing-Surge-Sends-Indian-Bonds-Lower-RBI-Unveils-Credit-Derivatives-Draft/69899a22b81b2b81dcfef17b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/State-Borrowing-Surge-Sends-Indian-Bonds-Lower-RBI-Unveils-Credit-Derivatives-Draft/69899a22b81b2b81dcfef17b</guid><description>Indian bond markets opened lower as states announced a significant increase in borrowing plans for the week. Fourteen states will raise approximately ₹486 billion, a jump from the previous indication. Concurrently, the Reserve Bank of India released draft rules for credit derivatives, seeking feedback by February 27, aiming to enhance the corporate bond market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:26:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69899a22b81b2b81dcfef17a_1770625780010.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Best Agrolife Revenue Drops 26% Amid Rains, But Profitability Turns Around</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Best-Agrolife-Revenue-Drops-26percent-Amid-Rains-But-Profitability-Turns-Around/698999b4b81b2b81dcfef023</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Best-Agrolife-Revenue-Drops-26percent-Amid-Rains-But-Profitability-Turns-Around/698999b4b81b2b81dcfef023</guid><description>Best Agrolife Ltd. reported a challenging Q3 FY26 with revenue down 26% YoY to ₹202.9 crore, hit by adverse weather and market conditions. Despite the topline decline, the company achieved an EBITDA turnaround, reporting ₹3.8 crore profit versus a loss last year, and narrowed its PAT loss to ₹12.7 crore. Nine-month revenue fell 28.5% to ₹1101 crore. The company highlighted operational discipline, a strong branded portfolio, increased patented product contribution, and significant OPEX rationalization as key drivers. Management expressed confidence in future growth, supported by new patents and product launches.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:24:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698999b4b81b2b81dcfef022_1770625698655.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Graphite India Posts Strong Q3 Profit Recovery Amid Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Graphite-India-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Recovery-Amid-Revenue-Growth/698998bcb81b2b81dcfeee32</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Graphite-India-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Recovery-Amid-Revenue-Growth/698998bcb81b2b81dcfeee32</guid><description>Graphite India Limited reported a significant turnaround in Q3 FY2026, with standalone net profit soaring 3233% YoY to ₹100 Crores on a 34% revenue jump to ₹643 Crores. Consolidated net profit also swung to a profit of ₹67 Crores from a loss. This quarterly strength contrasts with a 13.59% decline in standalone net profit for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. Inventory write-downs and pending tax appeals remain key considerations for investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:20:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698998bcb81b2b81dcfeee31_1770625464905.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEML Q3 Dip Masks 9M Surge; Energy-Minerals Integration Powers Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEML-Q3-Dip-Masks-9M-Surge-Energy-Minerals-Integration-Powers-Growth/698997ccb81b2b81dcfeec59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEML-Q3-Dip-Masks-9M-Surge-Energy-Minerals-Integration-Powers-Growth/698997ccb81b2b81dcfeec59</guid><description>Sarda Energy &amp; Minerals Ltd (SEML) reported a Q3 FY26 revenue dip of 3% YoY to ₹1,276 Cr due to planned turbine maintenance, with PAT falling 5%. However, 9M FY26 showed robust growth: revenue up 30% to ₹4,437 Cr and EBITDA surged 53% to ₹1,672 Cr, margins expanding to 35.8%. The company is advancing its integrated energy-plus-minerals strategy, scaling SKS Power, commissioning hydro and solar projects, and executing mining licenses, eyeing a decade-long opportunity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:16:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698997ccb81b2b81dcfeec58_1770625304770.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>