<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:26:47 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Hits Record High! Silver Prices Soar, Stock Surges 36% in 30 Days - What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Zinc-Hits-Record-High-Silver-Prices-Soar-Stock-Surges-36percent-in-30-Days-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694e2a59e10c98d0788e03a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Zinc-Hits-Record-High-Silver-Prices-Soar-Stock-Surges-36percent-in-30-Days-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694e2a59e10c98d0788e03a3</guid><description>Hindustan Zinc shares touched a fresh 52-week high of ₹646.50 on Friday, driven by a record run in silver prices and geopolitical tensions. The stock has surged an impressive 35.87% in the past 30 days, reflecting strong investor interest amid rising metal values and expectations of global economic shifts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Massive €1.4 Billion Lawsuit Hits Tata Steel Netherlands Over Hazardous Emissions: Is Your Investment Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-14-Billion-Lawsuit-Hits-Tata-Steel-Netherlands-Over-Hazardous-Emissions-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/694e29a3e10c98d0788e01f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-14-Billion-Lawsuit-Hits-Tata-Steel-Netherlands-Over-Hazardous-Emissions-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/694e29a3e10c98d0788e01f1</guid><description>Tata Steel's Dutch subsidiaries are facing legal action demanding €1.4 billion ($1.5 billion) in compensation for alleged damages from hazardous emissions. Residents near the Velsen-Noord plants claim health issues and reduced property values, while the company strongly refutes the unsubstantiated, speculative claims and is prepared to defend itself.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:13:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e29a3e10c98d0788e01f0_1766730259919.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Sparks Credit Revolution: Your Score Updates Twice As Fast From 2025! Get Ready for 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Sparks-Credit-Revolution-Your-Score-Updates-Twice-As-Fast-From-2025-Get-Ready-for-2026/694e29a4e10c98d0788e021d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Sparks-Credit-Revolution-Your-Score-Updates-Twice-As-Fast-From-2025-Get-Ready-for-2026/694e29a4e10c98d0788e021d</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is set to transform credit reporting starting January 1, 2025. Banks and NBFCs must now update borrower credit information bi-weekly, slashing the update lag from 30-45 days to just 15 days. Proposed changes from July 2026 aim for weekly updates, boosting transparency and enabling faster loan approvals and risk assessment for lenders, while empowering borrowers with quicker recognition of positive credit behaviour.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:13:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e29a4e10c98d0788e021c_1766730319903.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiaMART vs. OpenAI: Court Rules "Strong Case" As AI Giant Faces Lawsuit Over ChatGPT Search Exclusion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IndiaMART-vs-OpenAI-Court-Rules-Strong-Case-As-AI-Giant-Faces-Lawsuit-Over-ChatGPT-Search-Exclusion/694e2926e10c98d0788e00cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IndiaMART-vs-OpenAI-Court-Rules-Strong-Case-As-AI-Giant-Faces-Lawsuit-Over-ChatGPT-Search-Exclusion/694e2926e10c98d0788e00cc</guid><description>IndiaMART InterMESH Limited has filed a lawsuit at the Calcutta High Court against OpenAI Inc, alleging unlawful exclusion of its website from ChatGPT search results. The court observed a strong prima facie case, noting potential reputational and commercial damage to IndiaMART due to selective discrimination. While no interim relief was granted, fresh service was ordered on OpenAI for a future hearing. The case involves allegations of trade libel, trademark dilution, and unfair competition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:12:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e2926e10c98d0788e00cb_1766730229867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Steel Surge: Govt Eyes 300 MT Capacity by 2030 Amidst Green Push &amp; Global Hurdles!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Steel-Surge-Govt-Eyes-300-MT-Capacity-by-2030-Amidst-Green-Push-and-Global-Hurdles/694e28fde10c98d0788e0000</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Steel-Surge-Govt-Eyes-300-MT-Capacity-by-2030-Amidst-Green-Push-and-Global-Hurdles/694e28fde10c98d0788e0000</guid><description>The Indian government is prioritizing steel production and raw material security, aiming for 300 million tonnes of installed capacity by 2030. The focus includes expanding capacity, adopting low-carbon technologies, and developing green steel. Despite being the world's second-largest producer, the sector faces challenges like rising imports and volatile raw material prices. Initiatives like the Production Linked Incentive scheme and efforts to secure coking coal and iron ore are underway to meet targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:10:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e28fde10c98d0788dffff_1766730095751.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Defence Stocks Skyrocket: Will Year-End Defence Deals Ignite A Massive Rally?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Defence-Stocks-Skyrocket-Will-Year-End-Defence-Deals-Ignite-A-Massive-Rally/694e282ae10c98d0788dfea7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Defence-Stocks-Skyrocket-Will-Year-End-Defence-Deals-Ignite-A-Massive-Rally/694e282ae10c98d0788dfea7</guid><description>Indian defence stocks rallied sharply on Friday, defying market weakness. This surge is driven by high expectations for the Defence Acquisition Council (DAC) meeting, expected to fast-track key procurement proposals like missile systems for the Navy and Air Force. The positive sentiment highlights growing investor confidence in India's indigenous defence manufacturing capabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:08:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e282ae10c98d0788dfea6_1766729973252.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stock SURGES 30%! Dilip Buildcon Lands Massive ₹1,850 Crore Power Project – What This Means!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stock-SURGES-30percent-Dilip-Buildcon-Lands-Massive-1850-Crore-Power-Project-What-This-Means/694e23e5e10c98d0788df987</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stock-SURGES-30percent-Dilip-Buildcon-Lands-Massive-1850-Crore-Power-Project-What-This-Means/694e23e5e10c98d0788df987</guid><description>Dilip Buildcon Limited has been identified as the L-1 bidder for a significant Rs 1,850 crore power transmission project in Karnataka, awarded by REC Power Development and Consultancy Limited. The project involves developing a 400 kV sub-station and associated transmission lines under a 35-year Build, Own, Operate, and Transfer (BOOT) model. This substantial win strengthens Dilip Buildcon's infrastructure portfolio and long-term asset base. The company's stock has recently seen a notable 30% increase from its 52-week low.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:49:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e23e5e10c98d0788df986_1766728770006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lodha Developers Stock Set for 43% Surge? Brokerage Reveals Massive Growth Drivers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Lodha-Developers-Stock-Set-for-43percent-Surge-Brokerage-Reveals-Massive-Growth-Drivers/694e2300e10c98d0788df84f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Lodha-Developers-Stock-Set-for-43percent-Surge-Brokerage-Reveals-Massive-Growth-Drivers/694e2300e10c98d0788df84f</guid><description>Mirae Asset Sharekhan has issued a strong positive report on Lodha Developers, projecting a 43% upside potential for the stock. The brokerage highlights an aggressive launch pipeline, expanding geographic footprint, and rising annuity income as key growth drivers. Lodha's robust execution, infrastructure-led demand, and promising developments like the Palava township and a significant data centre platform are expected to fuel future growth and enhance cash flow visibility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:44:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e2300e10c98d0788df84e_1766728617364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹100 Crore Order Ignites Apollo Micro Systems: Stock Rockets 135% This Year!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/100-Crore-Order-Ignites-Apollo-Micro-Systems-Stock-Rockets-135percent-This-Year/694e2250e10c98d0788df6ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/100-Crore-Order-Ignites-Apollo-Micro-Systems-Stock-Rockets-135percent-This-Year/694e2250e10c98d0788df6ea</guid><description>Apollo Micro Systems Ltd. shares surged over 3% after securing ₹100.24 crore in orders for Unmanned Aerial Systems from a private company for the Ministry of Defence. These systems are slated for delivery within four months. The defence stock has already seen a remarkable 135% increase in value this year, significantly outperforming the benchmark Nifty 50. The company also recently received DRDO approvals for Directed Energy Weapons technology transfers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:44:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e2250e10c98d0788df6e9_1766728343163.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Surges Past $90,000: Is the Crypto Bull Run Back With a Bang?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Surges-Past-90000-Is-the-Crypto-Bull-Run-Back-With-a-Bang/694e21a7e10c98d0788df5b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Surges-Past-90000-Is-the-Crypto-Bull-Run-Back-With-a-Bang/694e21a7e10c98d0788df5b9</guid><description>Bitcoin has rebounded strongly, nearing the $90,000 mark, trading at $88,970.24 with a 1.41% daily increase. Analysts suggest the cryptocurrency is showing renewed strength, potentially signaling a delayed 'Santa Rally.' While volatility persists due to a large crypto options expiry today, the price action is being watched closely. Key support is seen at $87,000 and resistance at $89,700, with a sustained break above this level potentially leading to a rally towards $100,000. Broader market sentiment and liquidity are key drivers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:38:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e21a7e10c98d0788df5b8_1766728336561.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supreme Court Rescues Stalled Supertech Project: Homebuyers Get Hope as Court Orders Completion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Supreme-Court-Rescues-Stalled-Supertech-Project-Homebuyers-Get-Hope-as-Court-Orders-Completion/694e2101e10c98d0788df4b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Supreme-Court-Rescues-Stalled-Supertech-Project-Homebuyers-Get-Hope-as-Court-Orders-Completion/694e2101e10c98d0788df4b2</guid><description>The Supreme Court has used its extraordinary powers under Article 142 of the Constitution to revive Supertech's stalled Supernova project in Noida. A court-appointed committee will now oversee the project's completion, protecting homebuyers' interests and managing resolution proceedings against the developer, Supertech Realtors Pvt Ltd. This move bypasses standard insolvency procedures to ensure the project's delivery.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:38:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e2101e10c98d0788df4b1_1766728037031.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-UK Trade Deal SEALED! Landmark Agreement &amp; Vision 2035 Set to Skyrocket Bilateral Ties - What It Means For You!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-UK-Trade-Deal-SEALED-Landmark-Agreement-and-Vision-2035-Set-to-Skyrocket-Bilateral-Ties-What-It-Means-For-You/694e203ee10c98d0788df33b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-UK-Trade-Deal-SEALED-Landmark-Agreement-and-Vision-2035-Set-to-Skyrocket-Bilateral-Ties-What-It-Means-For-You/694e203ee10c98d0788df33b</guid><description>India and the United Kingdom have finalized a landmark Free Trade Agreement (FTA), culminating over four years of negotiations. Signed during Prime Minister Narendra Modi's July visit to the UK, the deal, alongside a 'Vision 2035' pact, aims to significantly boost bilateral ties beyond trade. The Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement (CETA) is projected to increase bilateral trade by over £25 billion, reaching approximately £69.1 billion annually upon ratification. The agreement also paves the way for increased collaboration in education and innovation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:31:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e203ee10c98d0788df33a_1766727809938.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cupid Stock EXPLODES 529% in 2025! What's Driving This Small-Cap Rocket?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cupid-Stock-EXPLODES-529percent-in-2025-Whats-Driving-This-Small-Cap-Rocket/694e1c50e10c98d0788deb3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cupid-Stock-EXPLODES-529percent-in-2025-Whats-Driving-This-Small-Cap-Rocket/694e1c50e10c98d0788deb3f</guid><description>Cupid, a leading manufacturer of condoms and personal care products, has seen its stock surge an astonishing 529% in 2025, including a 45% rally in December. This remarkable growth is driven by expanded FMCG offerings, a significant reduction in promoter-pledged shares, and stellar H1FY26 financial results showing a 114% profit jump and improved margins. The company forecasts a stronger second half of FY26 and continued expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:09:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e1c50e10c98d0788deb3e_1766726808449.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quality Power Shares Surge 4% After Major Acquisition Announcement – Strategic Move into High-Growth Sectors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quality-Power-Shares-Surge-4percent-After-Major-Acquisition-Announcement-Strategic-Move-into-High-Growth-Sectors/694e1b5fe10c98d0788de9a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quality-Power-Shares-Surge-4percent-After-Major-Acquisition-Announcement-Strategic-Move-into-High-Growth-Sectors/694e1b5fe10c98d0788de9a3</guid><description>Quality Power Electrical Equipments announced the acquisition of a 76% equity stake in Veeral Controls Private Limited for approximately ₹15.20 crore. This strategic move aims to expand Quality Power's technology base into high-current power conversion, strengthening its participation in green hydrogen, industrial, rail, and defense applications. The news boosted Quality Power's share price by 4% on Friday, outperforming the subdued market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:09:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e1b5fe10c98d0788de9a2_1766726581196.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Top Stock Picks Unveiled! Analysts Reveal Multi-Bagger Stocks with Targets – Don't Miss Out!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Top-Stock-Picks-Unveiled-Analysts-Reveal-Multi-Bagger-Stocks-with-Targets-Dont-Miss-Out/694e1b28e10c98d0788de8fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Top-Stock-Picks-Unveiled-Analysts-Reveal-Multi-Bagger-Stocks-with-Targets-Dont-Miss-Out/694e1b28e10c98d0788de8fe</guid><description>Analysts have revealed their top stock picks for December 26, including Hindustan Zinc, IRCTC, PNB Housing Finance, Ajanta Pharma, and Nuvama Wealth. These recommendations come with specific price targets and stop-loss levels, offering guidance for both intraday traders and long-term investors amidst a flat Nifty.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:09:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e1b28e10c98d0788de8fd_1766726667834.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Railway Stocks Surge! PSU Giants Like RVNL, IRFC Rally for 5th Day, Trimming Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Railway-Stocks-Surge-PSU-Giants-Like-RVNL-IRFC-Rally-for-5th-Day-Trimming-Losses/694e1aabe10c98d0788de7dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Railway-Stocks-Surge-PSU-Giants-Like-RVNL-IRFC-Rally-for-5th-Day-Trimming-Losses/694e1aabe10c98d0788de7dd</guid><description>Indian railway Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs), including Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd. (RVNL), RailTel Corporation of India Ltd., and IRFC Ltd., have surged for the fifth consecutive day. RVNL shares jumped up to 10% on Friday, marking their biggest single-day gain since May. This rally is significantly reducing their year-to-date losses, with RVNL now only down 11% for the year. Revised railway fares have also come into effect.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:08:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e1aabe10c98d0788de7dc_1766726486558.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MIDWEST LTD. EXPLODES 55% HIGHER? Motilal Oswal Issues Bold 'BUY' Call on Newly Listed Mining Stock!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MIDWEST-LTD-EXPLODES-55percent-HIGHER-Motilal-Oswal-Issues-Bold-BUY-Call-on-Newly-Listed-Mining-Stock/694e1ac3e10c98d0788de814</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MIDWEST-LTD-EXPLODES-55percent-HIGHER-Motilal-Oswal-Issues-Bold-BUY-Call-on-Newly-Listed-Mining-Stock/694e1ac3e10c98d0788de814</guid><description>Motilal Oswal has initiated coverage on Midwest Ltd., a newly listed mining firm, with a 'buy' rating and a price target of ₹2,000, suggesting a 23% upside. In a bull case, the target is raised to ₹2,500, implying a 54% potential gain. The brokerage highlights Midwest's strong fundamentals, diversification into quartz and Heavy Mineral Sands (HMS), and robust profitability, projecting significant revenue and earnings growth over the next few years.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:08:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e1ac3e10c98d0788de813_1766726523771.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2026 Policy Maze: Reforms, Risks, and Welfare Spending Set to Dominate!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Policy-Maze-Reforms-Risks-and-Welfare-Spending-Set-to-Dominate/694e19f4e10c98d0788de643</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Policy-Maze-Reforms-Risks-and-Welfare-Spending-Set-to-Dominate/694e19f4e10c98d0788de643</guid><description>India braces for an eventful 2026 with the Modi 3.0 administration focusing on reforms, managing economic risks, and redistribution policies. Welfare measures, particularly direct cash transfers, are expected to gain prominence due to their political appeal, especially with key state elections looming. This policy direction aims to build on previous gains amidst a complex socio-economic landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:08:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e19f4e10c98d0788de642_1766726203176.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2026 Investment Shift: Allspring Eyes AI &amp; Select Sectors, Warns on IT/Pharma!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-2026-Investment-Shift-Allspring-Eyes-AI-and-Select-Sectors-Warns-on-ITPharma/694e19e7e10c98d0788de614</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-2026-Investment-Shift-Allspring-Eyes-AI-and-Select-Sectors-Warns-on-ITPharma/694e19e7e10c98d0788de614</guid><description>Allspring Global Investments forecasts a selective emerging markets approach for 2026, prioritizing India, Korea, and AI themes. While easing valuations favor Indian financials and autos, the firm remains cautious on IT and pharma. Korea is overweight due to AI-driven memory chip demand, and potential US AI funding could spur market growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:08:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e19e7e10c98d0788de613_1766726231081.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Railway Stocks Soar on Budget Hopes! RVNL, IRCTC, IRFC Jump as Investors Bet on Infrastructure Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Railway-Stocks-Soar-on-Budget-Hopes-RVNL-IRCTC-IRFC-Jump-as-Investors-Bet-on-Infrastructure-Boom/694e19b4e10c98d0788de5bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Railway-Stocks-Soar-on-Budget-Hopes-RVNL-IRCTC-IRFC-Jump-as-Investors-Bet-on-Infrastructure-Boom/694e19b4e10c98d0788de5bd</guid><description>Railway stocks like Rail Vikas Nigam Limited, Indian Railway Finance Corporation, and Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation saw significant gains on Dalal Street. This rally is driven by anticipation of higher infrastructure spending in the upcoming Union Budget 2026, recent railway passenger fare rationalization, and a sector rotation into value plays after a period of underperformance. Investors are positioning for potential capital expenditure boosts, improving revenue visibility, and renewed focus on the railway sector's role in India's growth story.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:05:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e19b4e10c98d0788de5bc_1766726294558.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Box Office Roar: Regional Cinema Dominates, Bollywood's Existential Crisis Deepens!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Box-Office-Roar-Regional-Cinema-Dominates-Bollywoods-Existential-Crisis-Deepens/694e18dee10c98d0788de3c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-Box-Office-Roar-Regional-Cinema-Dominates-Bollywoods-Existential-Crisis-Deepens/694e18dee10c98d0788de3c9</guid><description>India's film industry is undergoing a major transformation. Regional cinema, especially from the South (Kannada, Telugu), is achieving massive box-office success, outperforming traditional Bollywood films. Exhibitors like PVR Inox Ltd. report significant revenue jumps from regional content, while Hindi film collections see only modest growth. This shift signifies a demand for fresh stories and diverse cinematic universes, pushing the established Bollywood industry into an existential crisis.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:01:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e18dee10c98d0788de3c8_1766725986760.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta Gets Andhra Govt Green Light: 20 New Oil &amp; Gas Wells Approved to Boost Production!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Vedanta-Gets-Andhra-Govt-Green-Light-20-New-Oil-and-Gas-Wells-Approved-to-Boost-Production/694e17e3e10c98d0788de15c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Vedanta-Gets-Andhra-Govt-Green-Light-20-New-Oil-and-Gas-Wells-Approved-to-Boost-Production/694e17e3e10c98d0788de15c</guid><description>Vedanta Limited's Cairn Oil &amp; Gas division has received a conditional No Objection Certificate (NOC) from the Andhra Pradesh government to drill 20 onshore oil and gas wells in the Krishna district. This approval facilitates development under the Discovered Small Field Policy, 2018, but prohibits water withdrawal from irrigation sources like the Bandar Canal. The move is expected to contribute to India's domestic energy production goals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:00:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e17e3e10c98d0788de15b_1766725671103.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta Gets Major Green Light: 20 New Oil &amp; Gas Wells Approved in Andhra Pradesh!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Vedanta-Gets-Major-Green-Light-20-New-Oil-and-Gas-Wells-Approved-in-Andhra-Pradesh/694e181be10c98d0788de1bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Vedanta-Gets-Major-Green-Light-20-New-Oil-and-Gas-Wells-Approved-in-Andhra-Pradesh/694e181be10c98d0788de1bf</guid><description>Vedanta Limited's Cairn Oil &amp; Gas Division has received a conditional No Objection Certificate (NOC) from the Andhra Pradesh government to drill 20 onshore oil and gas wells in the Krishna district. This development, under the Discovered Small Field (DSF) Policy 2018, aims to boost domestic energy production. The NOC is subject to specific terms, emphasizing no drawing of water from irrigation sources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:00:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e181be10c98d0788de1be_1766725759217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brigade Enterprises: Motilal Oswal's Shocking 52% Upside 'Buy' Call Stuns Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Brigade-Enterprises-Motilal-Oswals-Shocking-52percent-Upside-Buy-Call-Stuns-Investors/694e13a7e10c98d0788ddc61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Brigade-Enterprises-Motilal-Oswals-Shocking-52percent-Upside-Buy-Call-Stuns-Investors/694e13a7e10c98d0788ddc61</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services maintains a 'Buy' rating on Brigade Enterprises with a target price of ₹1,338, indicating a potential 52% increase. The firm highlights strong residential presales growth, projected to rise 19% CAGR from FY25-28. Brigade Enterprises is also planning strategic expansion into new geographic areas and asset classes, including significant growth in its hospitality segment, aiming to more than double its hotel keys by FY30.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:34:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e13a7e10c98d0788ddc60_1766724768256.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerages Reveal 3 Indian Stocks to BUY Now: Big Price Targets Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokerages-Reveal-3-Indian-Stocks-to-BUY-Now-Big-Price-Targets-Unveiled/694e1312e10c98d0788ddba5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokerages-Reveal-3-Indian-Stocks-to-BUY-Now-Big-Price-Targets-Unveiled/694e1312e10c98d0788ddba5</guid><description>Brokerages HDFC Securities and Motilal Oswal have highlighted Clean Science and Technology, Midwest, and Brigade Enterprises for investors. HDFC upgraded Clean Science to 'Add' with a ₹964 target, citing capacity expansion and attractive valuations after a correction. Motilal Oswal initiated Midwest with a 'Buy' and ₹2,000 target, focusing on its granite market leadership and diversification. They also maintained a 'Buy' on Brigade Enterprises with a ₹1,338 target, driven by strong presales and hospitality growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:34:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e1312e10c98d0788ddba4_1766725026988.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SIP Frequency Myth Busted: Daily, Monthly, or Quarterly - Does it REALLY Matter for Your Returns?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/SIP-Frequency-Myth-Busted-Daily-Monthly-or-Quarterly-Does-it-REALLY-Matter-for-Your-Returns/694e117ee10c98d0788dd9ab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/SIP-Frequency-Myth-Busted-Daily-Monthly-or-Quarterly-Does-it-REALLY-Matter-for-Your-Returns/694e117ee10c98d0788dd9ab</guid><description>An experiment comparing daily, monthly, and quarterly SIPs over 15 years on the Nifty 50 index reveals that the frequency of investment makes a negligible difference to long-term returns when the total amount invested remains the same. Monthly SIPs are recommended for practicality, aligning with salary cycles and ease of management, rather than for superior returns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:29:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e117ee10c98d0788dd9aa_1766724095027.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IPO Frenzy: Promoters Cash Out ₹79,000 Cr, PE Investors Bag ₹20,644 Cr - What It Means for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-IPO-Frenzy-Promoters-Cash-Out-79000-Cr-PE-Investors-Bag-20644-Cr-What-It-Means-for-Your-Investments/694e10b6e10c98d0788dd875</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-IPO-Frenzy-Promoters-Cash-Out-79000-Cr-PE-Investors-Bag-20644-Cr-What-It-Means-for-Your-Investments/694e10b6e10c98d0788dd875</guid><description>In 2025, Indian IPOs saw massive fundraising of around ₹1.76 lakh crore. Promoters aggressively offloaded stakes worth ₹79,000 crore, while private equity investors divested ₹20,644 crore through Offer-for-Sale components. However, listing performance turned subdued, with average IPO gains dropping significantly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:29:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e10b6e10c98d0788dd874_1766724070963.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KVP Tax Shock: Rs 5 Lakh Interest Bill Arrives! Are You Ready for This Maturity Trap?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/KVP-Tax-Shock-Rs-5-Lakh-Interest-Bill-Arrives-Are-You-Ready-for-This-Maturity-Trap/694e1109e10c98d0788dd902</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/KVP-Tax-Shock-Rs-5-Lakh-Interest-Bill-Arrives-Are-You-Ready-for-This-Maturity-Trap/694e1109e10c98d0788dd902</guid><description>Kisan Vikas Patra (KVP) investors are facing a tax dilemma at maturity. When the entire interest earned over several years is paid out in a single year, the postal department reports it as current year's income. This means taxpayers might have to pay tax on the full Rs 5 lakh interest in one go, even though it was earned over eight years and four months. Expert advice suggests opting for the accrual basis for taxation annually to avoid this lump sum tax burden.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:29:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e1109e10c98d0788dd901_1766723946217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Tread Water: Nifty50 Edges Below 26,100 as Experts Warn of Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Tread-Water-Nifty50-Edges-Below-26100-as-Experts-Warn-of-Consolidation/694e0e4be10c98d0788dd227</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Tread-Water-Nifty50-Edges-Below-26100-as-Experts-Warn-of-Consolidation/694e0e4be10c98d0788dd227</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks Nifty50 and BSE Sensex opened lower on Friday amid muted global and domestic sentiment. Nifty50 hovered just above 26,100, while Sensex dropped over 140 points. Experts anticipate market consolidation in the absence of major economic triggers, with foreign investors potentially increasing sales while domestic institutions offer support. Investors are advised to focus on high-quality large-cap stocks and value opportunities, cautioning against market exuberance seen in some IPOs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:17:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e0e4be10c98d0788dd226_1766723250325.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>8 Indian Giants Flashing Major Sell Signal! Adani Power, ONGC, ICICI Bank - Is This a Warning?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/8-Indian-Giants-Flashing-Major-Sell-Signal-Adani-Power-ONGC-ICICI-Bank-Is-This-a-Warning/694e0af7e10c98d0788dcec1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/8-Indian-Giants-Flashing-Major-Sell-Signal-Adani-Power-ONGC-ICICI-Bank-Is-This-a-Warning/694e0af7e10c98d0788dcec1</guid><description>Eight major Indian largecap stocks, including Adani Power, ONGC, and ICICI Bank, have shown a 'Bearish Engulfing Candlestick Pattern' on their charts as of Wednesday, December 24, 2025. This technical indicator, formed by comparing the current day's candle to the previous day's, signals a potential shift from an upward trend to a downward one. Investors are watching these formations closely for potential trading signals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:58:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e0af7e10c98d0788dcec0_1766722392601.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Luggage Stocks Set to Soar? Elara Capital Predicts Up to 37% Upside Amid Recovery Cycle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Luggage-Stocks-Set-to-Soar-Elara-Capital-Predicts-Up-to-37percent-Upside-Amid-Recovery-Cycle/694e0a41e10c98d0788dcd83</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Luggage-Stocks-Set-to-Soar-Elara-Capital-Predicts-Up-to-37percent-Upside-Amid-Recovery-Cycle/694e0a41e10c98d0788dcd83</guid><description>Elara Capital forecasts a sustained recovery for India's luggage sector, expecting 12% annual growth to reach ₹36,000 crore by 2028. The firm sees significant upside potential, citing improved product mix and cost controls. Safari Industries is projected for a 37% rise, while VIP Industries, undergoing ownership transition, offers a 9% potential upside amid repair and stabilization efforts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:58:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e0a41e10c98d0788dcd82_1766722227030.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coforge's $2 Billion Encora Deal on the Horizon? Board Meets Today Amidst Acquisition Buzz!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforges-2-Billion-Encora-Deal-on-the-Horizon-Board-Meets-Today-Amidst-Acquisition-Buzz/694e0a04e10c98d0788dcd0e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforges-2-Billion-Encora-Deal-on-the-Horizon-Board-Meets-Today-Amidst-Acquisition-Buzz/694e0a04e10c98d0788dcd0e</guid><description>Indian IT firm Coforge Ltd. is reportedly in advanced talks to acquire Encora, a software services provider specializing in AI, data, and cloud, for approximately $2 billion. This potential mega-deal comes just hours before Coforge's board convenes to discuss a crucial fundraising proposal. Encora, currently owned by private equity firm Advent International, adds significant capabilities in innovation software. Coforge, which recently acquired Cigniti Technologies for over ₹2,000 crore, possesses substantial cash reserves, potentially facilitating this strategic move.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:58:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e0a04e10c98d0788dcd0d_1766722166171.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Consumer Tech's Big Shift: Profitability is King Now, Not Just Growth! Are Investors Finding New Value?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-Consumer-Techs-Big-Shift-Profitability-is-King-Now-Not-Just-Growth-Are-Investors-Finding-New-Value/694e09e8e10c98d0788dccca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-Consumer-Techs-Big-Shift-Profitability-is-King-Now-Not-Just-Growth-Are-Investors-Finding-New-Value/694e09e8e10c98d0788dccca</guid><description>India's consumer tech sector is transitioning from prioritizing scale to focusing on profitability. Investors now look for improving unit economics, operating leverage, and disciplined capital allocation. While demand drivers like urbanization remain strong, competition is intensifying. Companies like Eternal, Swiggy, Meesho, Urban Company, and Lenskart are navigating this shift, with varying success in achieving bottom-line improvements and free cash flow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:53:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e09e8e10c98d0788dccc9_1766722091605.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold SHOCKS Market: Fed Rate Cut Hopes &amp; Global Chaos Fuel Record Surge! See Prices Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-SHOCKS-Market-Fed-Rate-Cut-Hopes-and-Global-Chaos-Fuel-Record-Surge-See-Prices-Now/694e098fe10c98d0788dcc12</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-SHOCKS-Market-Fed-Rate-Cut-Hopes-and-Global-Chaos-Fuel-Record-Surge-See-Prices-Now/694e098fe10c98d0788dcc12</guid><description>Gold prices are soaring, hitting new highs near $4,500 per ounce and ₹1,38,179 per 10 grams on MCX India. This uptrend is driven by expectations of future Federal Reserve interest rate cuts and escalating geopolitical tensions, including conflicts involving Israel, Iran, and the US. Analysts predict gold could reach $5,000 by late 2026 as investors seek safe havens amidst global uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:53:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e098fe10c98d0788dcc11_1766722074267.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Royal Orchid Hotels: This Week's Top Pick With 3X Growth Potential Unpacked!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Royal-Orchid-Hotels-This-Weeks-Top-Pick-With-3X-Growth-Potential-Unpacked/694e089ae10c98d0788dca57</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Royal-Orchid-Hotels-This-Weeks-Top-Pick-With-3X-Growth-Potential-Unpacked/694e089ae10c98d0788dca57</guid><description>Royal Orchid Hotels Limited (ROHL) is highlighted as a tactical stock pick, benefiting from the sustained hotel industry up-cycle and its aggressive expansion plans to nearly triple room inventory to 22,000 keys by 2030. The new Iconiqa hotel in Mumbai is expected to be a key contributor and break even in Q3FY26. Despite recent stock underperformance, ROHL's attractive valuation at 11.6x EV/EBIDTA (FY27 projections) presents a compelling entry point for investors anticipating strong double-digit growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:53:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e089ae10c98d0788dca56_1766721787880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Historic Bond Blitz: Rs 2 Trillion Buyback Promises Cheaper Loans!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Historic-Bond-Blitz-Rs-2-Trillion-Buyback-Promises-Cheaper-Loans/694e08dde10c98d0788dcaca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Historic-Bond-Blitz-Rs-2-Trillion-Buyback-Promises-Cheaper-Loans/694e08dde10c98d0788dcaca</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) announced a massive Rs 2 trillion bond purchase, marking the highest ever in a single fiscal year. This move aims to infuse liquidity into the system, counteracting drains from foreign exchange interventions. The objective is to keep government bond yields low, ensuring policy transmission and potentially leading to reduced borrowing costs across the economy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:52:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e08dde10c98d0788dcac9_1766721878714.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Delhi High Court Shakes Up Online World: Domain Registrars Lose Safe Harbour Amid Fraud Crackdown!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Delhi-High-Court-Shakes-Up-Online-World-Domain-Registrars-Lose-Safe-Harbour-Amid-Fraud-Crackdown/694e07efe10c98d0788dc921</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Delhi-High-Court-Shakes-Up-Online-World-Domain-Registrars-Lose-Safe-Harbour-Amid-Fraud-Crackdown/694e07efe10c98d0788dc921</guid><description>The Delhi High Court has ruled that Domain Name Registrars (DNRs) will lose their 'safe harbour' protection and can be held liable for trademark infringement and online fraud. This landmark decision, stemming from a Dabur India Limited complaint, requires DNRs to provide complete registrant details and prohibits them from masking information. The court also issued directives to government bodies and banks to enhance online fraud prevention measures and protect well-known trademarks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:52:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e07efe10c98d0788dc920_1766721648146.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Silent Killer: Air Pollution Crisis Rivals COVID, Doctors Issue Stark Warning!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Silent-Killer-Air-Pollution-Crisis-Rivals-COVID-Doctors-Issue-Stark-Warning/694e07e2e10c98d0788dc8dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Silent-Killer-Air-Pollution-Crisis-Rivals-COVID-Doctors-Issue-Stark-Warning/694e07e2e10c98d0788dc8dd</guid><description>Doctors warn India faces its biggest health crisis since COVID-19 due to severe air pollution, with a vast, undiagnosed airway disease burden building. The transport sector significantly pollutes Delhi, though the government acknowledges air pollution as a trigger for respiratory issues without conclusive mortality data. Urgent, sustained policies focusing on early detection and clean air are critical to address this looming health emergency.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e07e2e10c98d0788dc8dc_1766721714520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titan's Daring Leap: Secret Lab Diamond Brand 'beYon' Set to Dazzle Mumbai!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titans-Daring-Leap-Secret-Lab-Diamond-Brand-beYon-Set-to-Dazzle-Mumbai/694e07a0e10c98d0788dc85d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titans-Daring-Leap-Secret-Lab-Diamond-Brand-beYon-Set-to-Dazzle-Mumbai/694e07a0e10c98d0788dc85d</guid><description>Titan Company Limited is launching 'beYon', its new exclusive brand for lab-grown diamond jewellery, with the first store opening in Mumbai on December 29, 2025. This strategic move diversifies Titan's luxury offerings, tapping into India's growing demand for sustainable, lab-created gemstones. Future expansion is planned for Mumbai and Delhi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:49:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e07a0e10c98d0788dc85c_1766721511138.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ajanta Pharma's Bold Move: Biocon Deal Sparks Global Growth &amp; Big Profits!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ajanta-Pharmas-Bold-Move-Biocon-Deal-Sparks-Global-Growth-and-Big-Profits/694e0238e10c98d0788dc18b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ajanta-Pharmas-Bold-Move-Biocon-Deal-Sparks-Global-Growth-and-Big-Profits/694e0238e10c98d0788dc18b</guid><description>PL Capital rates Ajanta Pharma 'Buy' with a ₹3,200 target after its in-licensing deal with Biocon to market semaglutide across 26 emerging markets. Biocon will supply, Ajanta will commercialize. The brokerage forecasts strong Ebitda and PAT growth (17%/14% CAGR FY25-28) and expects ₹200 crore in FY28 sales from this venture, noting a strong strategic fit with Ajanta's existing global franchise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:25:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e0238e10c98d0788dc18a_1766720258773.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>