<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:56:26 +0000</pubDate><item><title>MIC Electronics: Orders Boost Sales, But Profitability Concerns Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/MIC-Electronics-Orders-Boost-Sales-But-Profitability-Concerns-Linger/698c25b80c9da38e2e768736</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/MIC-Electronics-Orders-Boost-Sales-But-Profitability-Concerns-Linger/698c25b80c9da38e2e768736</guid><description>MIC Electronics Limited has won new railway contracts totaling over Rs 59 crore, fueling a substantial Q3FY26 net sales increase of 668%. However, net profit for the nine-month period declined year-on-year, signaling potential margin pressures. The company's high P/E ratio of approximately 110x stands in contrast to peers like Siemens India (P/E ~48x-75x) and RVNL (P/E ~57x-69x), raising valuation questions amidst mixed analyst sentiment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:46:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c25b80c9da38e2e768735_1770792706674.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Akasa Air's Growth Falters as Co-Founder Exits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Akasa-Airs-Growth-Falters-as-Co-Founder-Exits/698c24d50c9da38e2e768451</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Akasa-Airs-Growth-Falters-as-Co-Founder-Exits/698c24d50c9da38e2e768451</guid><description>Akasa Air faces leadership instability as Chief Commercial Officer and co-founder Praveen Iyer resigns, the second high-level exit this year. This departure occurs as the airline attempts to accelerate expansion, hampered by persistent Boeing 737 MAX delivery delays. Despite securing $125 million in August 2025 funding, recurring executive turnover raises concerns about operational execution and the airline's ability to achieve its ambitious growth targets against a challenging Indian aviation market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:42:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c24d50c9da38e2e768450_1770792481572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Middle East Tensions Risk $108 Oil, Global Economic Crash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Middle-East-Tensions-Risk-108-Oil-Global-Economic-Crash/698c24ce0c9da38e2e768401</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Middle-East-Tensions-Risk-108-Oil-Global-Economic-Crash/698c24ce0c9da38e2e768401</guid><description>Heightened geopolitical instability in the Middle East presents a growing risk to global oil markets. While previous conflicts have had limited impact, an escalation targeting energy infrastructure or critical shipping lanes like the Strait of Hormuz could trigger a sustained oil price surge, potentially to $108 per barrel. Such a scenario would revive inflation risks, slow global growth, and force hawkish monetary policy responses, echoing the seismic economic shocks of the 1970s.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Motherson Hits 52-Week High on Q3 Beat; Debt &amp; Peers In Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Motherson-Hits-52-Week-High-on-Q3-Beat-Debt-and-Peers-In-Focus/698c246a0c9da38e2e768310</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Motherson-Hits-52-Week-High-on-Q3-Beat-Debt-and-Peers-In-Focus/698c246a0c9da38e2e768310</guid><description>Samvardhana Motherson International's stock climbed to a new 52-week high, propelled by robust Q3 FY26 earnings showing a 9% year-on-year profit increase. Analysts from Motilal Oswal and Nomura reiterated 'Buy' ratings, citing outperformance driven by premiumization, EV transition, and acquisition integration. However, a slight increase in net debt and a premium valuation relative to some peers present headwinds for sustained momentum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Energies: Broker Initiates 'Buy', But Risks Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Premier-Energies-Broker-Initiates-Buy-But-Risks-Linger/698c23f50c9da38e2e7681a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Premier-Energies-Broker-Initiates-Buy-But-Risks-Linger/698c23f50c9da38e2e7681a8</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services launched coverage on Premier Energies with a 'Buy' rating and a Rs 1,000 price target, citing significant capacity expansion and strong backward integration. The brokerage anticipates a 30% EBITDA CAGR from FY25-FY28. However, the company faces sector-wide risks including potential oversupply and increasing competition, alongside the execution demands of its ambitious diversification into transformers, inverters, and battery storage systems. The recent India-US trade deal provides a potential export catalyst, but margin sustainability remains a key monitorable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:38:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c23f50c9da38e2e7681a7_1770792258285.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kalyan Jewellers Stock Struggles Despite Strong Earnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kalyan-Jewellers-Stock-Struggles-Despite-Strong-Earnings/698c23f30c9da38e2e76817f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kalyan-Jewellers-Stock-Struggles-Despite-Strong-Earnings/698c23f30c9da38e2e76817f</guid><description>Kalyan Jewellers posted a strong 90% year-on-year net profit increase to Rs 4,163 million in Q3 FY26, driven by 42.1% revenue growth to Rs 103,434 million and 27% same-store-sales growth. Despite these impressive figures, the stock has declined nearly 20% over the past year. Market sentiment is currently weighed down by gold price volatility, intense competition, and a significant promoter pledge, overshadowing the company's operational successes and positive analyst outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Surges: India's Rally Faces Fed Signals, Currency Swings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-Indias-Rally-Faces-Fed-Signals-Currency-Swings/698c23690c9da38e2e767eb6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-Indias-Rally-Faces-Fed-Signals-Currency-Swings/698c23690c9da38e2e767eb6</guid><description>Gold prices in India climbed on February 11, 2026, propelled by a softer U.S. dollar, expectations of Federal Reserve rate cuts, and geopolitical unease. However, the rally's longevity faces scrutiny amid mixed Fed signals, currency volatility, and shifting import duty considerations. While sustained demand from central banks like China and institutional investors provides a floor, a wide spectrum of analyst price targets for 2026 highlights potential for both continued appreciation and significant pullbacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Midwest Gold Pivots to Rare Earths: Execution Risk Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Midwest-Gold-Pivots-to-Rare-Earths-Execution-Risk-Looms/698c22e80c9da38e2e767d6f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Midwest-Gold-Pivots-to-Rare-Earths-Execution-Risk-Looms/698c22e80c9da38e2e767d6f</guid><description>Midwest Gold is undergoing a strategic restructuring, merging with Midwest Energy via a reverse merger to pivot from granite manufacturing to rare-earth magnets. This move aims to consolidate private energy entities under public ownership, capitalizing on India's push for domestic critical material production. The company is investing heavily in a "mine-to-magnet" plant, targeting 5,000-tonne capacity, with promoters raising capital from institutional investors. Positioned to benefit from PLI schemes, Midwest targets automotive, solar, and MRI sectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:34:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c22e80c9da38e2e767d6e_1770791972154.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Q3 Profit Soars 38.5% on Automotive Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Q3-Profit-Soars-385percent-on-Automotive-Boom/698c22e30c9da38e2e767d4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Q3-Profit-Soars-385percent-on-Automotive-Boom/698c22e30c9da38e2e767d4a</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated profit after tax (PAT) surging 38.5% year-on-year to ₹5,021 crore, driven by a significant 24.4% rise in revenue from operations to ₹51,580 crore. The Automotive sector was a key growth driver, showing a 29.8% revenue increase. However, the Farm Equipment segment's profitability declined 21.9% despite revenue growth, and the company noted exceptional charges and an inability to estimate the impact of new ELV rules.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Classic Filaments Open Offer: Acquirers Bid Rs. 12 for 26% Stake; IDC Finds Price Fair</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Classic-Filaments-Open-Offer-Acquirers-Bid-Rs-12-for-26percent-Stake-IDC-Finds-Price-Fair/698c22860c9da38e2e767cd0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Classic-Filaments-Open-Offer-Acquirers-Bid-Rs-12-for-26percent-Stake-IDC-Finds-Price-Fair/698c22860c9da38e2e767cd0</guid><description>Acquirers Sumit Bansal and associates have launched an Open Offer for Classic Filaments Ltd. (CFL), aiming to acquire up to 26% of its equity at Rs. 12 per share. The Committee of Independent Directors has deemed the offer price fair and reasonable. This strategic move follows the acquirers' earlier purchase of a 68.51% stake at Rs. 10 per share. The tendering period is set from February 11 to February 25, 2026. Separately, TCI Express Limited reported a loss before tax for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Q3 PAT Jumps 54% on Auto, Farm, Services Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Q3-PAT-Jumps-54percent-on-Auto-Farm-Services-Strength/698c22000c9da38e2e767cac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Q3-PAT-Jumps-54percent-on-Auto-Farm-Services-Strength/698c22000c9da38e2e767cac</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 54% year-on-year to ₹4,675 crore on consolidated revenue growth of 26% to ₹52,100 crore. The diversified business model showed strength across Automotive, Farm Equipment, and Services segments, with subsidiaries like MMFSL and Mahindra Lifespaces delivering exceptional performances. Standalone performance also saw significant revenue and PAT increases.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Q3 PAT Surges 38.5% on Strong Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Q3-PAT-Surges-385percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/698c21740c9da38e2e767c37</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Q3-PAT-Surges-385percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/698c21740c9da38e2e767c37</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra's consolidated revenue surged 24.4% YoY to ₹51,580 Cr in Q3 FY26, while Profit After Tax (PAT) jumped an impressive 38.5% to ₹5,021 Cr. The automotive segment drove strong growth, though the farm equipment division reported a decline in segment results despite higher revenue. The company incurred significant exceptional losses totaling ₹861 Cr from retiral benefits and asset impairments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KMC Speciality Hospitals Posts Stellar Q3 Earnings With 82% PAT Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/KMC-Speciality-Hospitals-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Earnings-With-82percent-PAT-Surge/698c1f450c9da38e2e76790c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/KMC-Speciality-Hospitals-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Earnings-With-82percent-PAT-Surge/698c1f450c9da38e2e76790c</guid><description>KMC Speciality Hospitals India Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue climbing 33.74% YoY to ₹82.06 Cr and PAT soaring 82.74% to ₹13.73 Cr. PAT margins expanded significantly to 16.50% from 12.01% YoY. Nine-month performance also showed strong double-digit growth across revenue and profit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JioFinance Aggregator: JFSL's Play for Retail Savings Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/JioFinance-Aggregator-JFSLs-Play-for-Retail-Savings-Dominance/698c1eae0c9da38e2e767452</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/JioFinance-Aggregator-JFSLs-Play-for-Retail-Savings-Dominance/698c1eae0c9da38e2e767452</guid><description>JioFinance's new feature allows users to compare and invest in fixed deposits (FDs) from various banks and NBFCs on a single platform, offering rates up to 8.15%. This strategic move by Jio Financial Services Limited (JFSL) leverages its digital infrastructure to simplify the fragmented FD market, enhance customer engagement, and consolidate its position as a comprehensive financial services provider. The platform promises transparency and a fully digital booking process, aiming to attract a significant share of retail savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:16:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c1eae0c9da38e2e767451_1770790887356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ONGC &amp; MOL JV: Securing Ethane Supply Amidst Global Energy Flux</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-and-MOL-JV-Securing-Ethane-Supply-Amidst-Global-Energy-Flux/698c1e450c9da38e2e7672b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-and-MOL-JV-Securing-Ethane-Supply-Amidst-Global-Energy-Flux/698c1e450c9da38e2e7672b0</guid><description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) has established a joint venture with Japanese shipping major Mitsui O.S.K. Lines (MOL) through two GIFT City-incorporated entities. Each JV will operate a Very Large Ethane Carrier (VLEC) under the Indian flag, tasked with transporting US-sourced ethane to ONGC's subsidiary, OPaL. This strategic move aims to enhance ONGC's energy logistics capabilities and deepen its value chain integration, while leveraging MOL's extensive maritime expertise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:14:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c1e450c9da38e2e7672af_1770790780857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MTNL Defaults ₹9,115 Cr on Bank Loans, Signals Grave Financial Distress</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/MTNL-Defaults-9115-Cr-on-Bank-Loans-Signals-Grave-Financial-Distress/698c1e430c9da38e2e7672a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/MTNL-Defaults-9115-Cr-on-Bank-Loans-Signals-Grave-Financial-Distress/698c1e430c9da38e2e7672a8</guid><description>Mahanagar Telephone Nigam Limited (MTNL) has formally notified stock exchanges of its default in repaying principal and interest to multiple banks. As of January 31, 2026, the company owes ₹9,115.65 Cr—₹7,794.34 Cr in principal and ₹1,321.31 Cr in interest—to lenders including Union Bank of India and State Bank of India. This default signals critical financial distress for the state-owned telecom operator, raising severe concerns about its operational continuity and future viability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:14:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c1e430c9da38e2e7672a7_1770790779537.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airtel Deploys AI Security Against OTP Fraud, Eyes Trust Premium</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airtel-Deploys-AI-Security-Against-OTP-Fraud-Eyes-Trust-Premium/698c1db50c9da38e2e7671c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airtel-Deploys-AI-Security-Against-OTP-Fraud-Eyes-Trust-Premium/698c1db50c9da38e2e7671c8</guid><description>Bharti Airtel is bolstering its defenses against OTP-related bank fraud with a new AI-powered "Fraud Alert" tool. This system identifies risky incoming calls and warns users before they inadvertently share sensitive banking information. As digital fraud escalates in India, this initiative aims to build critical customer trust and differentiate Airtel in a competitive market. The rollout aims for nationwide coverage within two weeks. This move aligns with the broader industry trend of leveraging AI for enhanced security and signals Airtel's strategic investment in customer protection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KMC Speciality Hospitals Surges: Q3 PAT Jumps 83% on Strong Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/KMC-Speciality-Hospitals-Surges-Q3-PAT-Jumps-83percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/698c1cd30c9da38e2e76710a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/KMC-Speciality-Hospitals-Surges-Q3-PAT-Jumps-83percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/698c1cd30c9da38e2e76710a</guid><description>KMC Speciality Hospitals (India) Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26, with revenue from operations soaring 33.73% year-on-year to ₹82.06 Crore. Profit Before Tax (PBT) surged by 83.86% to ₹18.48 Crore, and Profit After Tax (PAT) jumped 82.71% to ₹13.73 Crore. Profit Before Tax margins improved substantially to 22.51% from 16.37% in the prior year's quarter. Sequentially, revenue grew 9.55% and PAT rose 26.63% QoQ, signalling sustained growth momentum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Krsnaa Diagnostics Recovers ₹130 Cr Govt Dues, Posts 4% Revenue Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Krsnaa-Diagnostics-Recovers-130-Cr-Govt-Dues-Posts-4percent-Revenue-Rise/698c1cd10c9da38e2e767103</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Krsnaa-Diagnostics-Recovers-130-Cr-Govt-Dues-Posts-4percent-Revenue-Rise/698c1cd10c9da38e2e767103</guid><description>Krsnaa Diagnostics reported Q3 FY'26 revenue of INR 1,812 million, up 4% YoY, significantly boosted by a INR 130 crore recovery of government dues. Normalized EBITDA reached INR 484 million (27% margin), and normalized PAT stood at INR 168 million (9% margin). Margins were temporarily impacted by expansion costs, which management termed a timing issue. The company highlights growth drivers from its Rajasthan project and a rapidly expanding B2C segment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KNR Constructions: Q3 Margins Slip, Debt Rises; ₹1543 Cr Divestment Awaits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-Q3-Margins-Slip-Debt-Rises-1543-Cr-Divestment-Awaits/698c1bde0c9da38e2e766fc9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-Q3-Margins-Slip-Debt-Rises-1543-Cr-Divestment-Awaits/698c1bde0c9da38e2e766fc9</guid><description>KNR Constructions reported mixed Q3 FY26 results with standalone revenue at ₹585 Cr and consolidated at ₹743 Cr. The company faced margin compression in Q3 FY26 due to project finalization costs, alongside an increase in consolidated debt to ₹2,443 Cr. However, a significant ₹1,543 Cr divestment from SPVs and a robust order book of ₹8,849 Cr provide a positive forward outlook, with management projecting FY28 revenue to reach ₹4,500 Cr and targeting margin recovery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:04:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Motherson Shares Surge on Strong Q3; Analysts Eye $108B Vision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Motherson-Shares-Surge-on-Strong-Q3-Analysts-Eye-108B-Vision/698c1a0e0c9da38e2e766c34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Motherson-Shares-Surge-on-Strong-Q3-Analysts-Eye-108B-Vision/698c1a0e0c9da38e2e766c34</guid><description>Samvardhana Motherson reported better-than-expected Q3 FY26 results, with revenue up 13.5% and EBITDA surging 80%. The company announced new greenfield investments and a strong leverage ratio, defying a subdued market and sparking a significant stock price rally. Analysts maintain positive ratings, citing ambitious long-term growth targets, but focus shifts to sustained margin expansion and competitive positioning amid aggressive expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Titan Hits Record High: Strong Q3 Fuels Rally, Valuation Scrutinized</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Hits-Record-High-Strong-Q3-Fuels-Rally-Valuation-Scrutinized/698c19a40c9da38e2e766abc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Hits-Record-High-Strong-Q3-Fuels-Rally-Valuation-Scrutinized/698c19a40c9da38e2e766abc</guid><description>Titan Company stock reached an all-time high on Wednesday, driven by stellar Q3 FY26 results that saw revenue climb 42% and net profit surge 61%. The company's market capitalization neared ₹4 trillion, surpassing UltraTech Cement. While festive demand bolstered jewellery sales, the company's premium valuation and the impact of elevated gold prices present a complex outlook for sustained growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fusion Finance's Profit Return Meets Sector Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fusion-Finances-Profit-Return-Meets-Sector-Headwinds/698c19900c9da38e2e7669c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fusion-Finances-Profit-Return-Meets-Sector-Headwinds/698c19900c9da38e2e7669c4</guid><description>Fusion Finance has returned to profitability, reporting a net profit of ₹14.05 crore for Q3 FY26, ending a six-quarter losing streak. This turnaround, driven by improved collections and cost management under new CEO Sanjay Garyali, has fueled an 18% stock rally in the past month, significantly outperforming broader indices. However, the microfinance sector faces persistent asset quality pressures and a cautious outlook, with industry experts anticipating normalization only in the latter half of FY26. Fusion's negative P/E ratio and weak ROE highlight investor skepticism regarding the sustainability of its recovery amid these broader industry challenges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:54:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c19900c9da38e2e7669c3_1770789600576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashiana Housing: Profit Surge Masks Declining Property Bookings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ashiana-Housing-Profit-Surge-Masks-Declining-Property-Bookings/698c19040c9da38e2e76691d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ashiana-Housing-Profit-Surge-Masks-Declining-Property-Bookings/698c19040c9da38e2e76691d</guid><description>Ashiana Housing reported a spectacular Q3 FY26 with net profit jumping 420% to ₹56.65 crore and revenue surging 167% to ₹373.35 crore, driving a 16.3% stock price rally. However, this impressive financial performance contrasts with a year-on-year decline in property bookings, with area booked falling to 5.46 lakh sq. ft. and sales value decreasing to ₹397.03 crore. The company also declared an interim dividend of ₹1 per share.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Power: Growth Metrics Shine, Market Dims Stock</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Growth-Metrics-Shine-Market-Dims-Stock/698c189c0c9da38e2e76686a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Growth-Metrics-Shine-Market-Dims-Stock/698c189c0c9da38e2e76686a</guid><description>Torrent Power's third quarter earnings showed significant improvement, with revenue up 4.3% to ₹6,777.8 crore and EBITDA soaring 26.2% to ₹1,403 crore, expanding margins to 20.7%. Despite these strong results and a projected doubling of operational capacity to 10.6 GWp, the company's shares fell over 5%. This divergence highlights investor scrutiny of growth strategies and sector-wide pressures overshadowing positive financial performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:50:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c189c0c9da38e2e766869_1770789369641.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brightcom Shares Soar on Share Cancellation; Governance Concerns Persist</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brightcom-Shares-Soar-on-Share-Cancellation-Governance-Concerns-Persist/698c18980c9da38e2e766862</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brightcom-Shares-Soar-on-Share-Cancellation-Governance-Concerns-Persist/698c18980c9da38e2e766862</guid><description>Brightcom Group shares have rallied nearly 46% since January 30th, driven by a board decision to cancel preference shares allotted to two investors and a recent regulatory settlement. Trading volumes have surged, with BGL being one of the most actively traded stocks. Despite the significant price jump, the stock remains well below its 52-week high. Persistent governance issues and a high valuation, compared to industry peers, cast a shadow over the sustainability of this speculative rally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Coforge Boosts CodeInsightAI with Agentic AI for Enterprise Modernization</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-Boosts-CodeInsightAI-with-Agentic-AI-for-Enterprise-Modernization/698c17aa0c9da38e2e766508</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-Boosts-CodeInsightAI-with-Agentic-AI-for-Enterprise-Modernization/698c17aa0c9da38e2e766508</guid><description>Coforge Limited has significantly upgraded its CodeInsightAI platform by integrating advanced Agentic AI capabilities. This enhancement aims to accelerate enterprise modernization by automating complex reverse and forward engineering processes for legacy systems. Leveraging multi-agent capabilities, LLMs, and a cloud-agnostic architecture, the platform promises accuracy and compliance at scale. Now available on AWS and Azure marketplaces, this move solidifies Coforge's strategic position in AI-led engineering and digital transformation services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Harsha Engineers Q3 Revenue Surges 17%, Subsidiary Losses &amp; Expansion Plans Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Harsha-Engineers-Q3-Revenue-Surges-17percent-Subsidiary-Losses-and-Expansion-Plans-Loom/698c17310c9da38e2e766466</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Harsha-Engineers-Q3-Revenue-Surges-17percent-Subsidiary-Losses-and-Expansion-Plans-Loom/698c17310c9da38e2e766466</guid><description>Harsha Engineers International reported a robust 17.4% year-on-year revenue growth in its India Engineering segment for Q3 FY26, alongside a consolidated adjusted EBITDA increase to INR 64.3 Cr. The company is pushing forward with a USD 9.94 million brownfield expansion in China and significant investment in its Advantek facility. However, net losses in subsidiaries and a one-time provision impacted profitability, while working capital remains high at 140 days. Management eyes double-digit growth in FY27.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:44:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c17310c9da38e2e766465_1770788977212.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Palm Oil Stocks Dip Amid Supply Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Palm-Oil-Stocks-Dip-Amid-Supply-Concerns/698c17080c9da38e2e766429</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Palm-Oil-Stocks-Dip-Amid-Supply-Concerns/698c17080c9da38e2e766429</guid><description>Palm oil purchases from major buyers India and China are projected to increase between January and April, signaling a drawdown in global stockpiles. This demand surge coincides with a broader global edible oil market deficit, where consumption growth of 7.1 million tons is expected to outpace production by 5.3 million tons in the 2025/2026 season. Despite stable production estimates from Indonesia and Malaysia, this widening gap suggests a tightening supply-demand balance, potentially supporting firmer price levels in the coming months.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd: Goyal Steps Down CEO, Director Pay Hike Amidst FY25 Profit Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eternal-Ltd-Goyal-Steps-Down-CEO-Director-Pay-Hike-Amidst-FY25-Profit-Surge/698c16ac0c9da38e2e766417</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eternal-Ltd-Goyal-Steps-Down-CEO-Director-Pay-Hike-Amidst-FY25-Profit-Surge/698c16ac0c9da38e2e766417</guid><description>Eternal Limited announced founder Deepinder Goyal's move from Group CEO to Vice Chairman to pursue new ventures, with Albinder Dhindsa taking over as CEO. Shareholders will vote on proposed INR 1 crore annual remuneration for four Independent Directors and Goyal's re-appointment. The company reported a robust FY25 consolidated PAT of ₹527 crore, up 50.1% YoY, and significant Q3FY26 margin improvements across food delivery, quick commerce, and B2B segments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Wakefit IPO Funds Untouched Post Q3FY26; Utilisation Plans Stall</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Wakefit-IPO-Funds-Untouched-Post-Q3FY26-Utilisation-Plans-Stall/698c14530c9da38e2e765cff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Wakefit-IPO-Funds-Untouched-Post-Q3FY26-Utilisation-Plans-Stall/698c14530c9da38e2e765cff</guid><description>Wakefit Innovations' Pre-IPO proceeds of ₹56 crore and IPO proceeds of ₹377.18 crore remain entirely unutilised as of December 31, 2025. Funds are parked in fixed deposits, with no deployment against stated objectives such as new store setups and marketing activities in Q3FY26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jubilant Foodworks Navigates Profit Growth Amid Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Jubilant-Foodworks-Navigates-Profit-Growth-Amid-Margin-Pressures/698c11a50c9da38e2e765584</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Jubilant-Foodworks-Navigates-Profit-Growth-Amid-Margin-Pressures/698c11a50c9da38e2e765584</guid><description>Jubilant Foodworks posted a significant 68.6% year-on-year rise in net profit to ₹72.9 crore for Q3 FY26, buoyed by a 13.3% revenue increase to ₹24,372 crore. Despite this headline growth, the company's EBITDA margin saw pressure, and Like-for-Like (LFL) growth in Domino's India moderated to 5%. The results arrive amidst intense competition from Devyani International, which widened its net loss, and Sapphire Foods, which also reported a net loss despite revenue gains. Analysts remain cautiously optimistic, with a focus on the sustainability of operational efficiencies and pricing power in a challenging consumer environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Eicher Motors Hits All-Time High Amid Mixed Analyst Views</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Hits-All-Time-High-Amid-Mixed-Analyst-Views/698c11960c9da38e2e7654b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Hits-All-Time-High-Amid-Mixed-Analyst-Views/698c11960c9da38e2e7654b5</guid><description>Eicher Motors shares surged to a new record high of ₹7,791, propelled by a 21.3% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹1,420.61 crore in Q3 FY26. The company also announced a significant ₹958 crore investment to expand Royal Enfield's manufacturing capacity. Despite the rally, persistent concerns over growth sustainability and valuation from analysts like Motilal Oswal contrast sharply with a generally positive market consensus, creating a bifurcated outlook for the stock.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:20:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c11960c9da38e2e7654b4_1770787548917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Insurance: AI Tries to Fix Trust Deficit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurance-AI-Tries-to-Fix-Trust-Deficit/698c11050c9da38e2e7653b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurance-AI-Tries-to-Fix-Trust-Deficit/698c11050c9da38e2e7653b7</guid><description>India's insurance sector is growing rapidly but plagued by mis-selling, evidenced by high grievance rates despite massive claim volumes. Insurers are deploying AI and digital tools to enhance transparency, reduce service costs by up to 30%, and improve claims handling. This strategic pivot aims to bridge consumer understanding gaps and rebuild trust, emphasizing informed decision-making over aggressive sales tactics to safeguard financial futures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c11050c9da38e2e7653b6_1770787305509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>S&amp;S Power Switchgear Surges 104% on Profit Turnaround, Q3 Revenue Doubles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SandS-Power-Switchgear-Surges-104percent-on-Profit-Turnaround-Q3-Revenue-Doubles/698c10930c9da38e2e765398</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SandS-Power-Switchgear-Surges-104percent-on-Profit-Turnaround-Q3-Revenue-Doubles/698c10930c9da38e2e765398</guid><description>S&amp;S Power Switchgear Limited reported a remarkable Q3 FY26, with revenue soaring 104.33% YoY to ₹80.30 Cr. The company returned to profitability, with EBIDA turning positive at ₹5.90 Cr (7.35% margin) against a loss in the prior year. EPS also flipped positive to ₹2.84. For the nine-month period, revenue grew 53.93% YoY to ₹201.80 Cr, and EBIDA improved significantly. Management expressed optimism about sustaining momentum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nava Ltd Surges 83.5% QoQ Profit; Zambia Projects Drive Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Nava-Ltd-Surges-835percent-QoQ-Profit-Zambia-Projects-Drive-Growth/698c0f2c0c9da38e2e765240</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Nava-Ltd-Surges-835percent-QoQ-Profit-Zambia-Projects-Drive-Growth/698c0f2c0c9da38e2e765240</guid><description>Nava Limited posted a stellar Q3 FY'26 with consolidated net profit soaring 83.5% quarter-on-quarter to ₹325.7 crore. Operational resilience in its energy business, particularly Maamba Energy Limited (MEL) operating at 97% PLF, and improved volumes and margins in mining fueled this surge. Diversification projects in Zambia, including thermal and solar power, are progressing steadily, signaling a robust future outlook despite a discussion on the sustainability of a significant jump in 'other income' driven by forex fluctuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Sparks Valuation Fear: Citi Strategist Eyes Long-Term Multiples</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Sparks-Valuation-Fear-Citi-Strategist-Eyes-Long-Term-Multiples/698c0bb60c9da38e2e764e98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Sparks-Valuation-Fear-Citi-Strategist-Eyes-Long-Term-Multiples/698c0bb60c9da38e2e764e98</guid><description>AI's growing influence is reshaping investor sentiment towards financial services and software stocks, prompting a re-evaluation of long-term valuations. Citi strategist Drew Pettit highlights that while current earnings remain robust, the market is reacting to potential future valuation multiples, a phenomenon dubbed the 'terminal multiple problem'. This shift mirrors past reactions in the software sector, where tech advancements led to adjusted future expectations. Citi advises balancing growth and cyclical stock exposure amid global diversification trends.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TVS Supply Chain Surges on Q3 Beat Amidst Lingering Valuation Pains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TVS-Supply-Chain-Surges-on-Q3-Beat-Amidst-Lingering-Valuation-Pains/698c0b6b0c9da38e2e764e84</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TVS-Supply-Chain-Surges-on-Q3-Beat-Amidst-Lingering-Valuation-Pains/698c0b6b0c9da38e2e764e84</guid><description>TVS Supply Chain Solutions Ltd. saw its shares climb 13% on February 11, 2026, following a robust third-quarter earnings report that reversed a year-ago net loss and expanded margins. Revenue grew 11% year-on-year to ₹2,715.8 crore, with EBITDA up 36.7%. However, the rally occurs against a backdrop of significant year-long stock declines, high valuation multiples compared to industry peers, weak capital efficiency, and ongoing regulatory disputes, suggesting a cautious outlook for sustained recovery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Som Distilleries Stock Tumbles on Profit Collapse, Defying Alcohol Sector Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Som-Distilleries-Stock-Tumbles-on-Profit-Collapse-Defying-Alcohol-Sector-Boom/698c0b060c9da38e2e764de1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Som-Distilleries-Stock-Tumbles-on-Profit-Collapse-Defying-Alcohol-Sector-Boom/698c0b060c9da38e2e764de1</guid><description>Som Distilleries and Breweries reported a severe decline in its third-quarter fiscal 2026 performance, with net profit plummeting 76% year-on-year to ₹4.6 crore and revenue falling 16.8% to ₹250.5 crore. This stark underperformance, marked by a significant compression in EBITDA margins to 7.9%, contrasts sharply with the robust growth and premiumisation trends sweeping the Indian alcoholic beverage sector. The market reacted negatively, sending shares down as much as 11.7% and nearing its 52-week low. The company's valuation now stands at a discount to peers, reflecting investor concerns over its operational execution amidst sector tailwinds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Maharashtra Power Plant Units Ordered Closed Over Pollution Violations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Maharashtra-Power-Plant-Units-Ordered-Closed-Over-Pollution-Violations/698c0a010c9da38e2e764bdc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Maharashtra-Power-Plant-Units-Ordered-Closed-Over-Pollution-Violations/698c0a010c9da38e2e764bdc</guid><description>The Central Pollution Control Board (CPCB) has directed the immediate cessation of operations for units 6 and 8 at the Parli Thermal Power Station (PTPS) in Maharashtra. This directive, issued on February 5, 2026, stems from a pattern of environmental non-compliance, including excessively high particulate matter emissions and expired operating consents, highlighting significant regulatory breaches by the state-owned facility. The Maharashtra Pollution Control Board (MPCB) is tasked with enforcing the closure, underscoring the seriousness of the environmental infractions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>