<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 21:22:09 +0000</pubDate><item><title>CleanMax Raises ₹1500Cr Pre-IPO Amidst India's Green Energy Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/CleanMax-Raises-1500Cr-Pre-IPO-Amidst-Indias-Green-Energy-Boom/6988f076b81b2b81dcfd9ece</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/CleanMax-Raises-1500Cr-Pre-IPO-Amidst-Indias-Green-Energy-Boom/6988f076b81b2b81dcfd9ece</guid><description>CleanMax Enviro Energy Solutions has successfully raised ₹1,500 crore in a pre-IPO funding round, with participation from global investors like Temasek Holdings and Bain Capital at ₹1,053 per share. This capital infusion precedes a planned ₹5,200 crore Initial Public Offering, for which the company has received SEBI approval. As a significant player in India's solar rooftop segment, CleanMax intends to utilize these funds primarily for debt reduction and general corporate purposes, capitalizing on robust growth and policy support within the nation's renewable energy sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:22:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988f076b81b2b81dcfd9ecd_1770582280418.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Radiance Secures $100M for India Green Energy Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Radiance-Secures-100M-for-India-Green-Energy-Expansion/6988e878b81b2b81dcfd9c07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Radiance-Secures-100M-for-India-Green-Energy-Expansion/6988e878b81b2b81dcfd9c07</guid><description>Renewable energy firm Radiance Renewables secured $100 million in equity funding from Impact Fund Denmark and FMO. The capital injection will fuel expansion into greenfield solar, hybrid wind-solar, and battery storage projects, targeting commercial and industrial clients. This move supports India's energy transition amid surging demand for cost-effective clean power.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:48:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988e878b81b2b81dcfd9c06_1770580256555.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Rooftops for Electric Air Taxi Vertiports</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Eyes-Rooftops-for-Electric-Air-Taxi-Vertiports/6988e78ab81b2b81dcfd9aa2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Eyes-Rooftops-for-Electric-Air-Taxi-Vertiports/6988e78ab81b2b81dcfd9aa2</guid><description>Rooftops of Indian buildings could soon transform into landing pads for electric air taxis, according to a Confederation of Indian Industry (CII) report. The industry body suggests this could generate new revenue streams while easing urban congestion. A pilot project proposing an eVTOL corridor in the National Capital Region (NCR) aims to slash travel times and foster a domestic "Make in India" aerospace ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:44:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988e78ab81b2b81dcfd9aa1_1770579991213.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CreditAccess India Eyes Promoter Exit Amidst Microfinance Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CreditAccess-India-Eyes-Promoter-Exit-Amidst-Microfinance-Boom/6988e716b81b2b81dcfd993e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CreditAccess-India-Eyes-Promoter-Exit-Amidst-Microfinance-Boom/6988e716b81b2b81dcfd993e</guid><description>CreditAccess India BV is initiating a search for new investors to facilitate an exit for its long-term shareholders, including Olympus Capital Asia and the Asian Development Bank. The move aims to unlock liquidity during a perceived up-cycle in the Indian microfinance sector. Despite strong financial health and growth projections for its subsidiary CreditAccess Grameen, the promoter is preparing for a strategic ownership shift. While Axis Bank was rumored to be interested, both entities denied such speculation, reinforcing the company's focus on a fair market-valued exit rather than a discounted sale.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:42:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988e716b81b2b81dcfd993d_1770579946378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bonfiglioli India IPO: Parent Eyes $250M Via OFS</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bonfiglioli-India-IPO-Parent-Eyes-250M-Via-OFS/6988e69cb81b2b81dcfd97f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bonfiglioli-India-IPO-Parent-Eyes-250M-Via-OFS/6988e69cb81b2b81dcfd97f2</guid><description>Bonfiglioli S.p.A. is set to list its Indian subsidiary, Bonfiglioli Transmissions, targeting approximately $250 million through an Offer for Sale (OFS). This move by the Italian parent company focuses on divesting existing shares rather than raising new capital for the subsidiary, which has operated profitably in India for over 25 years and reported substantial revenues in 2025. The listing aims to capitalize on the strong performance of Bonfiglioli Transmissions within India's growing industrial manufacturing sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:40:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988e69cb81b2b81dcfd97f1_1770579782493.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Exporters Gain Edge as US Tariffs Slash to 18%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Exporters-Gain-Edge-as-US-Tariffs-Slash-to-18percent/6988e530b81b2b81dcfd9627</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Exporters-Gain-Edge-as-US-Tariffs-Slash-to-18percent/6988e530b81b2b81dcfd9627</guid><description>Indian exporters are poised for a significant resurgence following a sharp reduction in US tariffs from an imposed 50% to a new 18%. Companies like Mrs. Bectors Food Specialities, Mokalbari Kanoi Tea Estate, and businesses in the textile and leather sectors expect renewed growth, increased exports, and restored price competitiveness in the North American market. This development reverses previous challenges caused by tariffs, safeguarding jobs and enabling companies to pursue expansion plans and higher sales volumes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:34:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988e530b81b2b81dcfd9626_1770579334013.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPFO Bets on Performance Incentives for Higher Returns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/EPFO-Bets-on-Performance-Incentives-for-Higher-Returns/6988e4c2b81b2b81dcfd94c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/EPFO-Bets-on-Performance-Incentives-for-Higher-Returns/6988e4c2b81b2b81dcfd94c2</guid><description>The Employees' Provident Fund Organisation (EPFO) is implementing performance-linked incentives for fund managers and revising benchmark methodologies. This strategic shift aims to boost returns on its Rs 31 trillion corpus by actively managing investments, separating tenor from yield, and dynamically allocating funds based on performance. Concurrently, EPFO is exploring diversification into emerging 'sunrise' sectors and alternative asset classes, moving beyond its historical conservative approach to enhance income generation for its nearly 30 crore members.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:32:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988e4c2b81b2b81dcfd94c1_1770579290345.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's DPDP Act Forces Hotel Contract Overhauls Amidst Data Liability Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-DPDP-Act-Forces-Hotel-Contract-Overhauls-Amidst-Data-Liability-Fears/6988df2db81b2b81dcfd91a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-DPDP-Act-Forces-Hotel-Contract-Overhauls-Amidst-Data-Liability-Fears/6988df2db81b2b81dcfd91a1</guid><description>Indian hotel owners are aggressively renegotiating long-standing agreements with international operators and booking platforms due to the Digital Personal Data Protection (DPDP) Act. The urgency stems from a critical need to clarify data protection responsibilities and bolster defenses against guest data breaches. This regulatory shift highlights the hospitality sector's vulnerability, where decades-old contracts clash with modern privacy mandates, potentially escalating compliance costs and legal disputes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:08:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988df2db81b2b81dcfd91a0_1770578004163.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GLP-1 Disruption: Food Giants Face Bifurcated Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GLP-1-Disruption-Food-Giants-Face-Bifurcated-Future/6988df1db81b2b81dcfd90f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GLP-1-Disruption-Food-Giants-Face-Bifurcated-Future/6988df1db81b2b81dcfd90f2</guid><description>The widespread adoption of GLP-1 medications is fundamentally reshaping consumer eating habits, compelling food and beverage companies to adapt rapidly or risk obsolescence. This seismic shift is creating a clear bifurcation: companies embracing nutrient-dense offerings and precise portioning, like PepsiCo and innovators such as Conagra and Nestlé, are poised for growth. Conversely, those reliant on high-volume, calorie-dense products face shrinking demand and margin erosion. Analysts project significant market shifts, with weight-loss drug sales potentially reaching $200 billion by 2035, underscoring the imperative for strategic agility.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:08:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988df1db81b2b81dcfd90f1_1770577848268.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Pact: Strategic Energy Autonomy Meets Market Access</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Strategic-Energy-Autonomy-Meets-Market-Access/6988d2f3b81b2b81dcfd84c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Strategic-Energy-Autonomy-Meets-Market-Access/6988d2f3b81b2b81dcfd84c1</guid><description>India and the United States have announced a framework for an interim trade agreement, a move expected to reduce tariffs and deepen economic ties. Union Commerce Minister Piyush Goyal emphasized that decisions regarding India's energy imports, including Russian crude oil, are solely made by domestic buyers and are not dictated by this trade pact. This strategic decoupling allows India to diversify energy sources while securing preferential market access and enhancing its competitive edge. The agreement, however, introduces new geopolitical considerations and analyst skepticism regarding India's energy sourcing commitments and the scale of US import pledges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:16:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988d2f3b81b2b81dcfd84c0_1770574716637.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CreditAccess India Eyes Investor Exit Amid Microfinance Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CreditAccess-India-Eyes-Investor-Exit-Amid-Microfinance-Shift/6988cd4fb81b2b81dcfd829e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CreditAccess-India-Eyes-Investor-Exit-Amid-Microfinance-Shift/6988cd4fb81b2b81dcfd829e</guid><description>CreditAccess India BV is actively seeking strategic investors to facilitate exits for long-term shareholders, signaling a proactive approach to liquidity and future growth. Its primary operating subsidiary, CreditAccess Grameen, India's largest microfinance institution, is navigating a cautious microfinance sector recovery, aiming to expand its retail finance offerings. The move supports CreditAccess Grameen's ambitious growth plans and diversification strategy amid evolving market conditions and regulatory frameworks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:52:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988cd4fb81b2b81dcfd829d_1770573279925.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Budget Surge Met by VC Funding Gap for Indian Startups</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Budget-Surge-Met-by-VC-Funding-Gap-for-Indian-Startups/6988cb6eb81b2b81dcfd80f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Budget-Surge-Met-by-VC-Funding-Gap-for-Indian-Startups/6988cb6eb81b2b81dcfd80f1</guid><description>The 2026-27 Union Budget allocates a record ₹7.85 lakh crore to defence, emphasizing large-scale indigenous production and technological advancement. Niti Aayog member VK Saraswat highlighted this push, but simultaneously underscored a critical shortfall in venture capital support for maturing defence startups. This creates a dual narrative of robust government investment clashing with private capital's perceived hesitation, potentially impacting scaling and innovation despite the sector's growth trajectory. The market's muted reaction post-budget suggests investor caution regarding these underlying dynamics.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:44:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988cb6eb81b2b81dcfd80f0_1770572790379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Rebalance: Capital Seesaw to Impact Tata Motors, HDFC AMC, Info Edge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-Rebalance-Capital-Seesaw-to-Impact-Tata-Motors-HDFC-AMC-Info-Edge/6988c6bfb81b2b81dcfd7eb5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-Rebalance-Capital-Seesaw-to-Impact-Tata-Motors-HDFC-AMC-Info-Edge/6988c6bfb81b2b81dcfd7eb5</guid><description>The upcoming rebalancing of the Nifty Next 50 index is projected to inject significant capital into specific stocks, with Tata Motors anticipated to receive approximately ₹1,296 crore in passive inflows, followed by HDFC Asset Management Company with an estimated ₹734 crore. Conversely, Info Edge (India) is poised for substantial outflows, estimated at ₹716 crore. The Nifty Midcap 100 is also set for changes, with multiple additions expected. These shifts, officially announced in late February, will become effective on March 30, forcing portfolio adjustments by index fund managers and potentially influencing sector valuations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:24:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988c6bfb81b2b81dcfd7eb4_1770571635494.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Oil Tussle Looms as Goyal Cites Concession Safeguards</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Deal-Oil-Tussle-Looms-as-Goyal-Cites-Concession-Safeguards/6988c3ebb81b2b81dcfd7cea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Deal-Oil-Tussle-Looms-as-Goyal-Cites-Concession-Safeguards/6988c3ebb81b2b81dcfd7cea</guid><description>Union Minister Piyush Goyal navigated US demands regarding Russian oil purchases, emphasizing that trade pacts allow for "re-balancing of concessions." The interim India-US trade agreement has already yielded immediate tariff reductions for Indian exporters, with further cuts anticipated, fueling optimism for increased bilateral trade and investment despite the oil-related conditionalities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:12:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988c3ebb81b2b81dcfd7ce9_1770570828703.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Tata Sons Silence Fuels Conglomerate Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/RBI/RBIs-Tata-Sons-Silence-Fuels-Conglomerate-Uncertainty/6988bce4b81b2b81dcfd7a77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/RBI/RBIs-Tata-Sons-Silence-Fuels-Conglomerate-Uncertainty/6988bce4b81b2b81dcfd7a77</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's ongoing silence regarding Tata Sons' application to de-register as an upper-layer NBFC, despite a missed September 2025 listing deadline, fosters significant regulatory ambiguity. Concurrently, a newly framed interim trade agreement between India and the United States introduces calibrated agricultural market access, sparking apprehension among domestic farmers over potential price impacts and the inclusion of genetically modified ingredients. This dual scenario injects uncertainty into major corporate structures and the agricultural sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:42:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988bce4b81b2b81dcfd7a76_1770569099737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Pharma Leaders: Innovation Now Essential, Not Optional</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indian-Pharma-Leaders-Innovation-Now-Essential-Not-Optional/6988b927b81b2b81dcfd785b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indian-Pharma-Leaders-Innovation-Now-Essential-Not-Optional/6988b927b81b2b81dcfd785b</guid><description>Top Indian pharmaceutical leaders, gathered at a book launch event, declared that innovation is now a critical necessity, not a mere choice, for the sector's future growth. The discussion highlighted the urgent need to invest in research and development, moving beyond a strong generics base to compete globally, particularly against China's rapid advancements.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:26:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988b927b81b2b81dcfd785a_1770568138298.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Bets Down Under: Global FMCG Ambition Fuels Australian Beverage Buy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Bets-Down-Under-Global-FMCG-Ambition-Fuels-Australian-Beverage-Buy/6988b658b81b2b81dcfd7683</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Bets-Down-Under-Global-FMCG-Ambition-Fuels-Australian-Beverage-Buy/6988b658b81b2b81dcfd7683</guid><description>Reliance Consumer Products Limited (RCPL) has acquired a majority stake in Australia's Goodness Group Global (GGG) for A$32 million, expanding its international FMCG footprint. The deal injects GGG's health-focused brands, Nexba and PACE, into RCPL's portfolio, aiming to leverage Reliance's scale for global expansion, particularly in India. This move underscores RCPL's ambition to compete in the rapidly growing, high-margin 'better-for-you' beverage segment, despite GGG's recent profitability challenges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:14:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988b658b81b2b81dcfd7682_1770567451928.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCI's Profit Surges 24% on Strong Logistics Segments Despite Revenue Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/TCIs-Profit-Surges-24percent-on-Strong-Logistics-Segments-Despite-Revenue-Dip/6988aa25b81b2b81dcfd72d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/TCIs-Profit-Surges-24percent-on-Strong-Logistics-Segments-Despite-Revenue-Dip/6988aa25b81b2b81dcfd72d7</guid><description>Transport Corporation of India (TCI) reported a robust 24% year-on-year jump in consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹476 Mn for Q3 FY2026, and a 33% rise to ₹1,478 Mn for 9M FY2026. This came despite a 4% YoY revenue decline in Q3 to ₹10,115 Mn, though 9M revenue grew 6% to ₹12,174 Mn. The Freight division faced headwinds, with flat Q3 revenue and declining EBITDA, while the Supply Chain and Seaways divisions demonstrated strong growth. Management projects 10-12% revenue and profit growth ahead.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:22:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988aa25b81b2b81dcfd72d6_1770564304860.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Aviation Boost, ICT Hopes, Tariff Pains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-US-Trade-Deal-Aviation-Boost-ICT-Hopes-Tariff-Pains/6988a22db81b2b81dcfd702b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-US-Trade-Deal-Aviation-Boost-ICT-Hopes-Tariff-Pains/6988a22db81b2b81dcfd702b</guid><description>The interim India-US trade agreement signals a shift in bilateral commerce, with India forecasting significant demand for civil aviation and ICT products. While the pact aims to reduce tariffs, a new 18% levy on Indian goods, though reduced from previous highs, could pressure sectors like textiles and leather. India's USD 500 billion "intent to purchase" from the US remains contingent on competitive pricing, while specific sectors like pharmaceuticals and aircraft parts see tariff elimination.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:48:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988a22db81b2b81dcfd702a_1770562234227.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai Property Market Hits Record Stamp Duty Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mumbai-Property-Market-Hits-Record-Stamp-Duty-Revenue/69889aa9b81b2b81dcfd6d29</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mumbai-Property-Market-Hits-Record-Stamp-Duty-Revenue/69889aa9b81b2b81dcfd6d29</guid><description>Mumbai's property market achieved its highest-ever stamp duty collection for January, surpassing Rs 1,012 crore despite an 8% year-on-year drop in registrations. The financial capital saw 11,219 property transactions, with larger ticket deals and a growing share of premium homes driving revenue. This sustained market resilience points to strong end-user confidence.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:16:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69889aa9b81b2b81dcfd6d28_1770560294338.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market Sees Record Turnover Amid Shrinking Cap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Market-Sees-Record-Turnover-Amid-Shrinking-Cap/698899c0b81b2b81dcfd6b9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Market-Sees-Record-Turnover-Amid-Shrinking-Cap/698899c0b81b2b81dcfd6b9e</guid><description>January 2026 saw Indian equity markets record their highest average daily turnover in 15 months, driven by retail investor activity and a FPI return spurred by the India-US trade deal. However, this surge in trading volume contrasted sharply with a 4% contraction in market capitalization and a pronounced narrowing of investor focus towards fewer, large-cap stocks. While sectors like metals and PSU banks outperformed, domestic demand-driven sectors and broader market segments experienced significant drawdowns, reflecting a market prioritizing selectivity over breadth amid heightened volatility and valuation concerns.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:12:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698899c0b81b2b81dcfd6b9d_1770560082769.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tinna Rubber Q3 Skyrockets: Revenue Up 13%, PAT Soars 63%; IOCL Order Boosts Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tinna-Rubber-Q3-Skyrockets-Revenue-Up-13percent-PAT-Soars-63percent-IOCL-Order-Boosts-Outlook/69889239b81b2b81dcfd6912</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tinna-Rubber-Q3-Skyrockets-Revenue-Up-13percent-PAT-Soars-63percent-IOCL-Order-Boosts-Outlook/69889239b81b2b81dcfd6912</guid><description>Tinna Rubber &amp; Infrastructure Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 13% YoY to ₹139 Cr and PAT surging 63% to ₹13 Cr, driven by strong margin expansion. However, 9MFY26 consolidated PAT dipped 1% due to international JV start-up costs. The company unveiled 'Vision 2028' targeting ₹1,000 Cr revenue by FY28 and over 18% EBITDA margins. A key highlight was securing a ₹75.79 Cr work order from Indian Oil Corporation Limited for crumb rubber modifier supply.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:40:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69889239b81b2b81dcfd6911_1770558147766.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GST Law Creates SaaS vs. Ride-Hailing Tax Clash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-GST-Law-Creates-SaaS-vs-Ride-Hailing-Tax-Clash/69888c23b81b2b81dcfd6686</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-GST-Law-Creates-SaaS-vs-Ride-Hailing-Tax-Clash/69888c23b81b2b81dcfd6686</guid><description>The Internet and Mobile Association of India (IAMAI) is urging the Finance Ministry and GST Council to re-evaluate the applicability of India's Goods and Services Tax (GST) on app-based mobility services. IAMAI contends that the current 5% GST on rides booked through digital platforms disproportionately affects driver earnings and consumer affordability. The core issue lies in the interpretation of the Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) model, where direct driver-passenger payment mechanisms conflict with the GST law's requirement for aggregators to remit tax, creating significant operational uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:14:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69888c23b81b2b81dcfd6685_1770556600720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PVR INOX Elevates Oscar Fest: Cinema's New Cultural Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVR-INOX-Elevates-Oscar-Fest-Cinemas-New-Cultural-Hub/69888bb6b81b2b81dcfd6572</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVR-INOX-Elevates-Oscar-Fest-Cinemas-New-Cultural-Hub/69888bb6b81b2b81dcfd6572</guid><description>PVR INOX is significantly expanding its Oscar Film Festival in 2026, rebranding it as a national theatrical property. This move acknowledges a growing Indian appetite for international cinema, moving beyond niche audiences. The four-week event across 23 cities and 58 cinemas aims to position multiplexes as cultural hubs, using OTT-fueled content discovery to drive demand for premium theatrical experiences and diversified revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:12:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69888bb6b81b2b81dcfd6571_1770556506728.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Tiruppur Exporters Eye Doubled Exports Amidst Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tiruppur-Exporters-Eye-Doubled-Exports-Amidst-Competition/6988895ab81b2b81dcfd6399</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tiruppur-Exporters-Eye-Doubled-Exports-Amidst-Competition/6988895ab81b2b81dcfd6399</guid><description>The finalization of an India-US bilateral trade framework is poised to significantly energize Tamil Nadu's garment export sector. Exporters in Tiruppur anticipate a doubling of shipments to the United States, reaching approximately ₹30,000 crore within three years, potentially creating five lakh new jobs. This optimistic outlook stems from reduced import duties on textiles and apparel, positioning India more favorably against key competitors like Bangladesh and Vietnam in the lucrative U.S. market. However, sustained growth hinges on navigating global competition and managing input cost volatility.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:02:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988895ab81b2b81dcfd6398_1770555900154.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Elderly Mis-selling Sparks RBI Crackdown on Bank Insurance Sales</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Elderly-Mis-selling-Sparks-RBI-Crackdown-on-Bank-Insurance-Sales/69887e1bb81b2b81dcfd6055</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Elderly-Mis-selling-Sparks-RBI-Crackdown-on-Bank-Insurance-Sales/69887e1bb81b2b81dcfd6055</guid><description>An alleged mis-selling incident involving a 90-year-old customer at Canara Bank, with a life insurance policy carrying an unusually long maturity date of 2124, has intensified scrutiny on bancassurance practices. The Reserve Bank of India is preparing comprehensive guidelines to address aggressive sales tactics and ensure product suitability, following a surge in customer grievances across the financial sector. This case highlights critical vulnerabilities for senior citizens and prompts a review of sales targets driving potentially unethical practices.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:14:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69887e1bb81b2b81dcfd6054_1770552999764.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godrej Properties: Resilient Demand Powers Growth Amidst Market Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-Resilient-Demand-Powers-Growth-Amidst-Market-Shift/69887ad7b81b2b81dcfd5e7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-Resilient-Demand-Powers-Growth-Amidst-Market-Shift/69887ad7b81b2b81dcfd5e7d</guid><description>Godrej Properties demonstrates robust growth, exceeding sales booking targets and strategically expanding its land portfolio. Despite a market shift from rapid post-pandemic expansion to sustainable momentum, the company reports a 23% rise in net profit for the December quarter, even as total income saw a dip. This performance is underpinned by strong customer collections and a healthy project delivery pipeline, positioning Godrej Properties favorably within the evolving Indian real estate sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69887ad7b81b2b81dcfd5e7c_1770552161232.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chandrasekaran's Tata Tenure: Continuity Meets Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Chandrasekarans-Tata-Tenure-Continuity-Meets-Crisis/69886dafb81b2b81dcfd5afa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Chandrasekarans-Tata-Tenure-Continuity-Meets-Crisis/69886dafb81b2b81dcfd5afa</guid><description>Natarajan Chandrasekaran's leadership at the $180-billion Tata Group has been extended until 2032, signaling a focus on continuity by the Tata Trusts. However, this extension arrives as the conglomerate navigates a complex array of fresh challenges, from the AI-driven transformation of its IT services arm to the revival of Air India and intensifying competition in the electric vehicle sector. The mandate is clear: move beyond consolidation to proactive resolution of issues testing the group's financial health and reputation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 11:04:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69886dafb81b2b81dcfd5af9_1770548812173.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India FPIs Return: Trade Deal Spurs Inflow Amid Valuation Worries</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-FPIs-Return-Trade-Deal-Spurs-Inflow-Amid-Valuation-Worries/69886bcfb81b2b81dcfd5952</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-FPIs-Return-Trade-Deal-Spurs-Inflow-Amid-Valuation-Worries/69886bcfb81b2b81dcfd5952</guid><description>Foreign portfolio investors resumed buying Indian equities in February 2026, investing Rs 8,129 crore after months of outflows. A newly announced US trade deal and positive budget sentiment fueled this reversal. However, concerns over India's high valuations relative to emerging market peers, currency stability, and global economic uncertainties temper the outlook for sustained inflows.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 10:56:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69886bcfb81b2b81dcfd5951_1770548308276.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Growth: Ethics vs. Rapid Deployment Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Growth-Ethics-vs-Rapid-Deployment-Race/69885f43b81b2b81dcfd5575</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Growth-Ethics-vs-Rapid-Deployment-Race/69885f43b81b2b81dcfd5575</guid><description>India's burgeoning AI sector is accelerating, fueled by a $70 billion infrastructure investment and a plan to train professionals across 500 universities. Leaders at the upcoming AI summit emphasize that rapid deployment must be balanced with stringent ethical standards, transparency, and explainability. While sector-specific AI models are emerging, the challenge lies in embedding accountability to ensure sustainable, trust-based growth amidst global competition.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 10:02:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69885f43b81b2b81dcfd5574_1770545196688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Tax Reforms: Simplification Masks Enforcement Shift, Business Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Tax-Reforms-Simplification-Masks-Enforcement-Shift-Business-Caution/69885f25b81b2b81dcfd5498</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Tax-Reforms-Simplification-Masks-Enforcement-Shift-Business-Caution/69885f25b81b2b81dcfd5498</guid><description>India's direct tax system is undergoing significant simplification and modernization, with a new Income Tax Act set to take effect April 1, 2026. While lauded for enhancing clarity and ease of doing business, these sweeping changes also suggest a potential shift towards more robust enforcement and refined dispute resolution. Businesses are advised to scrutinize the implications of retrospective clarifications and evolving penalty structures amid this transformative period for Indian taxation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 10:02:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69885f25b81b2b81dcfd5497_1770545126263.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Top Firms Gain ₹4.55 Lakh Crore as Reliance Leads Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Top-Firms-Gain-455-Lakh-Crore-as-Reliance-Leads-Rally/69885e2fb81b2b81dcfd52dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Top-Firms-Gain-455-Lakh-Crore-as-Reliance-Leads-Rally/69885e2fb81b2b81dcfd52dd</guid><description>Indian equities surged last week, lifting the market valuation of eight of the top 10 most valued firms by Rs 4.55 lakh crore. Reliance Industries spearheaded the gains, contributing significantly to the BSE benchmark's 3.53% rise. Meanwhile, IT heavyweights Tata Consultancy Services and Infosys experienced valuation erosion amid global tech stock weakness and AI concerns.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:58:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69885e2fb81b2b81dcfd52dc_1770544875206.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's US Tariff Cut: Strategic Win or Negotiated Necessity?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-US-Tariff-Cut-Strategic-Win-or-Negotiated-Necessity/69885dbeb81b2b81dcfd519a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-US-Tariff-Cut-Strategic-Win-or-Negotiated-Necessity/69885dbeb81b2b81dcfd519a</guid><description>India's export competitiveness is set to receive a boost following an interim trade framework with the US, which slashes tariffs on most Indian goods to 18% from a previous high of 50%. This reduction, however, comes with significant Indian concessions and mixed sectorial impacts. While sectors like textiles and capital goods are poised to gain, the crucial IT sector faces headwinds from AI advancements, highlighting the nuanced outcome of this trade recalibration. The deal positions India favorably against competitors like China, which faces tariffs of 35% or higher.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:56:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69885dbeb81b2b81dcfd5199_1770544732421.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Leverages Future Trillions in Trade Talks, Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Leverages-Future-Trillions-in-Trade-Talks-Risks-Loom/698857a1b81b2b81dcfd4f1b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Leverages-Future-Trillions-in-Trade-Talks-Risks-Loom/698857a1b81b2b81dcfd4f1b</guid><description>India's Commerce Minister highlights negotiating from strength using a $35 trillion economic future projection, bolstered by a new US tariff deal. This strategy shifts leverage from current power to future potential. However, achieving these ambitious targets faces headwinds from global economic shifts, structural domestic challenges, and the inherent uncertainty of sustained high growth. The approach aims to secure better trade terms amidst a volatile international trade environment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:30:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698857a1b81b2b81dcfd4f1a_1770543136671.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jeena Sikho Lifecare Skyrockets 92% Revenue, Eyes Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Jeena-Sikho-Lifecare-Skyrockets-92percent-Revenue-Eyes-Global-Expansion/698853e2b81b2b81dcfd4cee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Jeena-Sikho-Lifecare-Skyrockets-92percent-Revenue-Eyes-Global-Expansion/698853e2b81b2b81dcfd4cee</guid><description>Jeena Sikho Lifecare reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with revenues soaring 92% YoY to ₹221.66 Crore and PAT jumping 405% to ₹66.73 Crore. The company showcased strong operational growth, improved YoY margins, and announced significant capacity expansion plans, including international diversification, while maintaining a debt-free status.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:14:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698853e2b81b2b81dcfd4ced_1770542192454.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSBs' Record Profit Surge: FDI Hike, Growth Drivers Scrutinized</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSBs-Record-Profit-Surge-FDI-Hike-Growth-Drivers-Scrutinized/69885114b81b2b81dcfd4b01</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSBs-Record-Profit-Surge-FDI-Hike-Growth-Drivers-Scrutinized/69885114b81b2b81dcfd4b01</guid><description>Public Sector Banks (PSBs) are poised to achieve a historic combined profit exceeding ₹2 lakh crore in FY26, building on sustained growth and improved asset quality [cite: Input]. Credit expansion is robust at 12%, with deposit growth at 10% [cite: Input]. The government is exploring a hike in Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) limits for PSBs to 49%, a move aimed at bolstering capital access. Despite this strong performance, the sector faces scrutiny over competitive pressures, deposit mobilization challenges, and evolving regulatory landscapes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:02:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69885114b81b2b81dcfd4b00_1770541471106.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titan Eyes $2 Billion Watch Sales Post-EU Trade Deal, Swiss Luxury Boom Expected</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Eyes-2-Billion-Watch-Sales-Post-EU-Trade-Deal-Swiss-Luxury-Boom-Expected/6988509cb81b2b81dcfd49cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Eyes-2-Billion-Watch-Sales-Post-EU-Trade-Deal-Swiss-Luxury-Boom-Expected/6988509cb81b2b81dcfd49cb</guid><description>Titan Company anticipates a significant rise in Indian sales for luxury Swiss watches, driven by the India-EU Free Trade Agreement which lowers import duties. The Tata group firm aims to boost overall watch sales to $2 billion by FY30, heavily leaning on premiumization and expanding its Helios and Helios Luxe formats. This strategic push positions Swiss brands to become more competitive, potentially reshaping India's premium watch market.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:00:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988509cb81b2b81dcfd49ca_1770541339438.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Reshapes Global Aerospace: Delhi Ascends</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-US-Trade-Deal-Reshapes-Global-Aerospace-Delhi-Ascends/69884a0cb81b2b81dcfd4725</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-US-Trade-Deal-Reshapes-Global-Aerospace-Delhi-Ascends/69884a0cb81b2b81dcfd4725</guid><description>The India-U.S. trade agreement unlocks zero-duty access for Indian aerospace components into the American market, fundamentally altering global supply chain dynamics. This strategic shift elevates India to parity with established Asian and European hubs, driving increased sourcing by major OEMs like Boeing and Airbus. Concurrently, the pact is expected to stimulate substantial new aircraft orders from India's rapidly expanding aviation sector, projecting billions in future fleet expansion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:32:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69884a0cb81b2b81dcfd4724_1770539686416.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T's Strategic Pivot: Data Centers, Green Energy Fueling Future Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandTs-Strategic-Pivot-Data-Centers-Green-Energy-Fueling-Future-Growth/6988499bb81b2b81dcfd45c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandTs-Strategic-Pivot-Data-Centers-Green-Energy-Fueling-Future-Growth/6988499bb81b2b81dcfd45c2</guid><description>Infrastructure giant Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T) is making substantial investments in high-growth sectors. The company plans to commission 18 MW of data center capacity by March-end, bringing its total to 32 MW, backed by a Rs 1,000 crore capital expenditure. Concurrently, L&amp;T is advancing its green energy ambitions with an indigenous 4 MW electrolyzer stack upgrade to 8-10 MW, anticipating significant future orders. These strategic expansions in digital infrastructure and sustainable energy underscore a forward-looking diversification strategy, even as the company navigates a Q3 profit decline attributed to a one-time Rs 1,191 crore provision for new labor codes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:30:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988499bb81b2b81dcfd45c1_1770539522353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>E-Way Bill Surge: India's Economy Accelerates, Supply Chain Strain Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/E-Way-Bill-Surge-Indias-Economy-Accelerates-Supply-Chain-Strain-Looms/698843f2b81b2b81dcfd432d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/E-Way-Bill-Surge-Indias-Economy-Accelerates-Supply-Chain-Strain-Looms/698843f2b81b2b81dcfd432d</guid><description>India's e-way bill generation saw a significant surge in January, reaching 136.83 million, its second-highest monthly total. This robust growth, up 42.6% year-on-year, reflects strong consumption-led demand and improved economic activity. Experts interpret this as a positive sign for GST collections and overall economic health, aligning with optimistic GDP growth forecasts. However, the rapid increase also points to potential strain on supply chains and logistics networks, warranting a closer look at underlying sustainability and operational efficiency.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:06:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698843f2b81b2b81dcfd432c_1770538195419.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>