<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:43:06 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Global Markets Tumble: AI Fears, Layoffs Spark Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Tumble-AI-Fears-Layoffs-Spark-Sell-Off/6985449ee769d12df1d4a8d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Tumble-AI-Fears-Layoffs-Spark-Sell-Off/6985449ee769d12df1d4a8d6</guid><description>Global equities extended significant losses as investors grappled with fears of AI impacting software profits and a surge in US layoffs to a 17-year high. Asian markets, including South Korea's Kospi and Japan's Nikkei, saw sharp declines. Precious metals and cryptocurrencies experienced severe volatility and price drops, reflecting a broad risk-off sentiment. Futures indicate continued weakness in US markets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:32:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985449ee769d12df1d4a8d5_1770341653889.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Telcos Demand 10x Call Rate Hike Amid Fraud Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Telcos-Demand-10x-Call-Rate-Hike-Amid-Fraud-Surge/69854336e769d12df1d4a6e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Telcos-Demand-10x-Call-Rate-Hike-Amid-Fraud-Surge/69854336e769d12df1d4a6e8</guid><description>Indian telecom operators are demanding a tenfold increase in international incoming call termination charges (ITC), proposing to raise the rate from ₹0.65 to ₹4-5 per minute. This aggressive push is driven by the perceived misuse of current low rates for widespread international telecom fraud and spam, alongside a significant imbalance in call traffic volumes. Operators argue the existing structure leads to revenue leakage and financial strain, particularly with currency depreciation. The proposed hike aims to act as a deterrent to fraudulent traffic and realign India's charges with global benchmarks, with minimal expected impact on domestic consumers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:26:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69854336e769d12df1d4a6e7_1770341268000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Tumbles 16% From Record Highs as Dollar Rebounds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Tumbles-16percent-From-Record-Highs-as-Dollar-Rebounds/698542b6e769d12df1d4a551</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Tumbles-16percent-From-Record-Highs-as-Dollar-Rebounds/698542b6e769d12df1d4a551</guid><description>Silver prices have sharply reversed, shedding 16% from recent record highs to hover near $65 per ounce. A resurgent US Dollar, fueled by hawkish Fed expectations and eased geopolitical tensions, is weighing on the white metal. Increased margin requirements by CME Group and potential crypto-related liquidations also contributed to the steep decline. Analysts suggest a technical correction, with UBS forecasting volatility but maintaining a $105/oz target for March 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:24:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698542b6e769d12df1d4a550_1770341148614.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Demographic Dividend at Risk: Higher Ed Underfunded</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Demographic-Dividend-at-Risk-Higher-Ed-Underfunded/6985423fe769d12df1d4a3ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Demographic-Dividend-at-Risk-Higher-Ed-Underfunded/6985423fe769d12df1d4a3ef</guid><description>A Reserve Bank of India report highlights a critical misallocation of educational funds across Indian states, potentially squandering the nation's demographic dividend. Despite a growing youth population poised to drive economic growth, spending increasingly favors foundational school education over higher education and vocational training. This imbalance, observed across youthful, intermediate, and ageing states alike, risks future unemployment and productivity gaps, undermining the very economic potential the demographic dividend represents. The data suggests a national strategic misstep, prioritizing short-term enrollment over long-term skill development and innovation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:22:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985423fe769d12df1d4a3ee_1770341052578.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 16th FC Prioritizes GDP Over Demographics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-16th-FC-Prioritizes-GDP-Over-Demographics/698541d1e769d12df1d4a281</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-16th-FC-Prioritizes-GDP-Over-Demographics/698541d1e769d12df1d4a281</guid><description>The 16th Finance Commission has recalibrated India's fiscal devolution formula, placing significant emphasis on a state's contribution to national GDP, a departure from previous models. This shift prioritizes economic efficiency, potentially redistributing funds towards high-growth states while adjusting allocations for population, area, and income disparities. Concerns persist regarding fiscally unsustainable subsidies, though a push for an independent Fiscal Council is notably absent.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:20:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698541d1e769d12df1d4a280_1770340955942.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economic Tightrope: Growth Forecasts, Sectoral Shifts &amp; Geopolitical Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Tightrope-Growth-Forecasts-Sectoral-Shifts-and-Geopolitical-Capital/6985415ce769d12df1d4a103</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Tightrope-Growth-Forecasts-Sectoral-Shifts-and-Geopolitical-Capital/6985415ce769d12df1d4a103</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman projects realistic growth, citing strong capital expenditure (capex) implementation. However, private sector investment is visibly shifting from core manufacturing to "frontier sectors." Capital inflows remain sensitive to geopolitical signaling, with recent US-India dialogue influencing market sentiment. The IT sector faces AI-driven disruption risks, while regulatory bodies intensify scrutiny on market dominance. Subsidy reforms and state debt management present ongoing data integration and fiscal challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:18:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985415ce769d12df1d4a102_1770340844765.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>10 Stocks Eye: Hero MotoCorp, LIC, Airtel Q3 Results Spark Market Moves</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/10-Stocks-Eye-Hero-MotoCorp-LIC-Airtel-Q3-Results-Spark-Market-Moves/69853d97e769d12df1d49dde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/10-Stocks-Eye-Hero-MotoCorp-LIC-Airtel-Q3-Results-Spark-Market-Moves/69853d97e769d12df1d49dde</guid><description>Indian markets are poised for a cautious opening, with GIFT Nifty signaling lower trade. A host of blue-chip companies, including Hero MotoCorp, Federal Bank, Bharti Airtel, and LIC, have reported their third-quarter FY26 financial results. The outcomes present a mixed picture, with strong revenue growth for many, yet some also falling short of analyst profit expectations. Investors are closely assessing these developments ahead of the budget.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:02:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69853d97e769d12df1d49ddd_1770339875768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget STT Hike Fuels Hybrid Funds Amidst Gold's Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Budget-STT-Hike-Fuels-Hybrid-Funds-Amidst-Golds-Volatility/69853d1be769d12df1d49c6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Budget-STT-Hike-Fuels-Hybrid-Funds-Amidst-Golds-Volatility/69853d1be769d12df1d49c6a</guid><description>Early 2026 markets grapple with budget-induced volatility and a Securities Transaction Tax (STT) hike on F&amp;O trades, channeling investor interest towards multi-asset funds, buoyed by gold's performance. However, aggressive hybrid funds present a case for long-term risk-adjusted returns, as rising derivative costs penalize high-churn strategies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:00:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69853d1be769d12df1d49c69_1770339691207.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zota Health: Investor Bets on Growth Amidst Widening Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zota-Health-Investor-Bets-on-Growth-Amidst-Widening-Losses/6985387ae769d12df1d498ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zota-Health-Investor-Bets-on-Growth-Amidst-Widening-Losses/6985387ae769d12df1d498ae</guid><description>Zota Health Care successfully raised ₹350 crore through a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP), boosting FII holdings to 8.1% and DII holdings to 7.2%. The company's DAVAINDIA generic pharmacy network, now contributing 74% of revenue, is expanding rapidly. Despite a 98% YoY sales surge to ₹143 crore in Q3FY26, the company reported a widened net loss of ₹30 crore, raising concerns about the profitability of its low-margin, high-volume strategy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:40:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985387ae769d12df1d498ad_1770339062851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Cold Chain: Urban Surge Tests Legacy Logistics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Cold-Chain-Urban-Surge-Tests-Legacy-Logistics/6985386ce769d12df1d497fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Cold-Chain-Urban-Surge-Tests-Legacy-Logistics/6985386ce769d12df1d497fd</guid><description>India's cold chain market, projected for robust growth, faces a critical inflection point. Rapid demand from quick commerce and pharmaceuticals necessitates a shift towards urban micro-fulfillment centers, challenging traditional large-scale, commodity-focused cold storage. Companies like Snowman Logistics and Mahindra Logistics are adapting their strategies, investing in capacity and operational efficiency, but future success hinges on mastering integrated, multi-temperature logistics for fragmented, high-speed delivery networks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:40:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985386ce769d12df1d497fc_1770338484373.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Textiles Rally on US Tariff Cut, Valuations Pose Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-Textiles-Rally-on-US-Tariff-Cut-Valuations-Pose-Risk/698537f5e769d12df1d4968b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-Textiles-Rally-on-US-Tariff-Cut-Valuations-Pose-Risk/698537f5e769d12df1d4968b</guid><description>A recent US-India trade deal slashed textile tariffs to 18% from 50%, poised to boost Indian exporters like Indo Count, Welspun Living, and Gokaldas Exports by restoring volumes and margins. However, these companies currently trade at premium valuations, outstripping historical averages and industry peers, suggesting potential headwinds despite the positive trade outlook. The EU-India FTA further brightens the long-term export prospects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:38:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698537f5e769d12df1d4968a_1770338373663.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Growth Engine Shifts Gears Amidst Fiscal Prudence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Growth-Engine-Shifts-Gears-Amidst-Fiscal-Prudence/69853688e769d12df1d494a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Growth-Engine-Shifts-Gears-Amidst-Fiscal-Prudence/69853688e769d12df1d494a0</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 doubles down on capital expenditure (capex) with a record Rs 12.22 lakh crore allocation, aiming to sustain economic growth. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman highlighted nascent signs of private sector investment picking up, particularly in frontier sectors. The budget also includes policy clarifications on Sovereign Gold Bonds (SGBs) and an increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives to curb speculation. Global investor sentiment appears to be cautiously optimistic, with interest from Nordic funds noted, and the rupee showing recovery post diplomatic engagements. The nominal GDP growth target of 10% is deemed realistic by the Finance Minister.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:32:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69853688e769d12df1d4949f_1770338075863.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bengal Fiscal Deficit Dips Below 3% Amidst Grant Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Bengal-Fiscal-Deficit-Dips-Below-3percent-Amidst-Grant-Surge/69853434e769d12df1d491e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Bengal-Fiscal-Deficit-Dips-Below-3percent-Amidst-Grant-Surge/69853434e769d12df1d491e3</guid><description>West Bengal has projected a fiscal deficit of 2.91% of its Gross State Domestic Product (GSDP) for FY27, a milestone not achieved since FY18. This reduction below the 3% threshold is attributed to restrained revenue expenditure growth and a substantial 115.75% surge in grants-in-aid from the Centre. The state's GSDP is forecast to expand by 8%, with capital expenditure planned to increase by over 42%. While fiscal prudence is emphasized, the significant reliance on central transfers raises questions about the long-term sustainability of these fiscal improvements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:22:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69853434e769d12df1d491e2_1770337440122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>