<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 01:44:49 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Gold Flows Signal Caution as India Eyes Earnings Rebound</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Flows-Signal-Caution-as-India-Eyes-Earnings-Rebound/69a4e3003d2913aa7c21dd8c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Flows-Signal-Caution-as-India-Eyes-Earnings-Rebound/69a4e3003d2913aa7c21dd8c</guid><description>January 2026 marked a significant shift as gold ETF inflows in India surpassed those into equity mutual funds for the first time, totaling ₹24,040 crore against ₹24,028 crore. This unprecedented move indicates a potential rise in investor risk aversion, overshadowing the consensus optimism for an earnings-led market recovery in 2026. While sectors like financials, industrials, and auto are projected to show strong earnings growth, elevated valuations, particularly in small and mid-caps, coupled with the sustained flight to gold, suggest a cautious undertone prevails. The Reserve Bank of India's decision to hold interest rates steady at 5.25% and benign inflation forecasts offer stability, but investor behavior signals a preference for capital preservation over aggressive growth chasing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 01:08:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e3003d2913aa7c21dd8b_1772413955592.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SFO Tech Secures ₹750 Cr for Expansion Amidst EMS Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SFO-Tech-Secures-750-Cr-for-Expansion-Amidst-EMS-Boom/69a4e2ff3d2913aa7c21dd74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SFO-Tech-Secures-750-Cr-for-Expansion-Amidst-EMS-Boom/69a4e2ff3d2913aa7c21dd74</guid><description>SFO Technologies secured over ₹750 crore in a funding round led by Trident Growth Partners and Amicus Capital Partners. The capital infusion is earmarked for significant manufacturing capacity expansion and backward integration into component manufacturing over the next two years. This strategic move positions SFO to bolster its global footprint as India's electronics manufacturing services sector witnesses rapid growth, driven by global supply chain realignments and increasing demand for sophisticated, resilient manufacturing partners.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 01:08:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e2ff3d2913aa7c21dd73_1772413912020.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Bullishness Meets Market Headwinds: Atul &amp; Pidilite Analyzed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Tech-Bullishness-Meets-Market-Headwinds-Atul-and-Pidilite-Analyzed/69a4e2f83d2913aa7c21dd5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Tech-Bullishness-Meets-Market-Headwinds-Atul-and-Pidilite-Analyzed/69a4e2f83d2913aa7c21dd5d</guid><description>Angel One analysts have issued bullish technical recommendations for Atul Ltd and Pidilite Industries, citing positive chart patterns and indicator signals. However, a deeper dive reveals significant headwinds, including heightened geopolitical tensions impacting the broader market, elevated valuations for both firms, and specific operational concerns such as declining exports for Pidilite and subdued long-term growth for Atul. Despite positive short-term technical setups, a cautious institutional perspective is warranted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 01:08:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e2f83d2913aa7c21dd5c_1772413867192.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LPG Vulnerability Outstrips Crude Oil in Hormuz Crisis; Macros at Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/LPG-Vulnerability-Outstrips-Crude-Oil-in-Hormuz-Crisis-Macros-at-Risk/69a4e28c3d2913aa7c21dcac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/LPG-Vulnerability-Outstrips-Crude-Oil-in-Hormuz-Crisis-Macros-at-Risk/69a4e28c3d2913aa7c21dcac</guid><description>India's energy security faces a heightened threat, with Liquefied Petroleum Gas (LPG) imports proving far more vulnerable to Strait of Hormuz disruptions than crude oil. While crude supplies are buffered by significant inventories, nearly all of India's LPG transit the critical chokepoint, lacking comparable strategic reserves. This exposure directly impacts the nation's import bill, potentially widening the current account deficit and pressuring the rupee, with analysts warning of significant macroeconomic fallout if tensions persist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 01:06:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e28c3d2913aa7c21dcab_1772413731424.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Storms Batter Indian Equities; E2W Race Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitical-Storms-Batter-Indian-Equities-E2W-Race-Intensifies/69a4e0a83d2913aa7c21db4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitical-Storms-Batter-Indian-Equities-E2W-Race-Intensifies/69a4e0a83d2913aa7c21db4d</guid><description>Heightened geopolitical tensions in West Asia are directly impacting Indian markets, pushing crude oil prices higher and creating sector-specific headwinds, particularly for oil marketing companies, aviation, and paint manufacturers. The electric two-wheeler segment is witnessing a significant shift, with Ola Electric losing market share to established players like TVS Motor and Bajaj Auto. Maruti Suzuki continues to grapple with production constraints amidst strong demand, while Adani Power faces scrutiny over its Bangladesh power deal. SpiceJet navigates ongoing legal financial obligations, and Abbott India expands its diabetes drug offerings amidst evolving market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 00:58:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e0a83d2913aa7c21db4c_1772413692298.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI's Derivatives Stance: Stability Over Speculation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-Derivatives-Stance-Stability-Over-Speculation/69a4e0733d2913aa7c21dabd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-Derivatives-Stance-Stability-Over-Speculation/69a4e0733d2913aa7c21dabd</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey signaled a deliberate pause in further derivatives market actions, prioritizing policy stability and impact analysis of recent measures. The regulator's focus remains squarely on curbing speculative excesses within options trading, particularly index and weekly expiries. Concurrently, SEBI is bolstering the SME IPO framework through enhanced due diligence and is poised to deliberate on conflict of interest report recommendations. The central bank's new bank guarantee rules for proprietary trading are also under SEBI's watchful eye, aiming to balance risk mitigation with market liquidity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 00:57:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e0733d2913aa7c21dabc_1772413147784.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Bets on Merchant Bankers for SME IPO Integrity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/SEBI-Bets-on-Merchant-Bankers-for-SME-IPO-Integrity/69a4e0653d2913aa7c21da8c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/SEBI-Bets-on-Merchant-Bankers-for-SME-IPO-Integrity/69a4e0653d2913aa7c21da8c</guid><description>SEBI is enhancing oversight of SME Initial Public Offerings by placing greater responsibility on merchant bankers to conduct thorough due diligence. Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey emphasized that isolated incidents should not deter legitimate enterprises from accessing capital markets. The regulator is implementing stricter measures, including third-party monitoring and LODR framework reviews, to bolster intermediary discipline and ensure market integrity. This strategy aligns with India's position as a leading global IPO market, aiming to foster growth through improved gatekeeping rather than restrictive regulations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 00:57:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e0653d2913aa7c21da8b_1772413143963.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Business Paradox: Macro Stability, Micro Failure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Business-Paradox-Macro-Stability-Micro-Failure/69a4dffd3d2913aa7c21d9cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Business-Paradox-Macro-Stability-Micro-Failure/69a4dffd3d2913aa7c21d9cd</guid><description>India maintains impressive macroeconomic stability, yet struggles with a crippling microeconomic business environment. Decades-old constitutional structures, particularly the Concurrent List, foster jurisdictional confusion and administrative inertia. This gridlock, combined with bureaucratic incompetence, actively deters the private investment essential for sustained growth, leaving the nation far below required investment rates and trailing its East Asian peers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 00:55:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4dffd3d2913aa7c21d9cc_1772413037169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Iran Strike Fuels Market Fear: Oil, Defense Stocks Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Iran-Strike-Fuels-Market-Fear-Oil-Defense-Stocks-Surge/69a4dfea3d2913aa7c21d9b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Iran-Strike-Fuels-Market-Fear-Oil-Defense-Stocks-Surge/69a4dfea3d2913aa7c21d9b2</guid><description>A targeted strike eliminating Iran's supreme leader and top commanders has dramatically shifted geopolitical focus from its nuclear program to regime stability. This event is injecting significant uncertainty into global markets, leading to a surge in oil prices and increased demand for safe-haven assets. Defense sector stocks are experiencing heightened interest, though analysts caution about the sustainability of gains. The immediate aftermath signals a period of elevated volatility as markets price in a substantial geopolitical risk premium.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 00:55:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4dfea3d2913aa7c21d9b1_1772413061261.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jhunjhunwala's Bet: High-Conviction Stakes Face Valuation Peril</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Jhunjhunwalas-Bet-High-Conviction-Stakes-Face-Valuation-Peril/69a4d9563d2913aa7c21d7ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Jhunjhunwalas-Bet-High-Conviction-Stakes-Face-Valuation-Peril/69a4d9563d2913aa7c21d7ef</guid><description>Rekha Jhunjhunwala's portfolio shows a steadfast commitment to Valor Estate and Aptech, stocks that have experienced significant price corrections. While Valor Estate's high valuation is justified by its land bank and a recent profit turnaround post-demerger, the company trades at a premium compared to industry peers. Aptech, facing the disruptive threat of generative AI in its core training business, also shows signs of financial recovery. The market questions whether Jhunjhunwala's long-term conviction can overcome these structural challenges and extreme valuations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 00:27:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4d9563d2913aa7c21d7ee_1772411633662.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>