<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:43:07 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Miners' AI Pivot: Riot, Core Scientific Brace for Earnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Miners-AI-Pivot-Riot-Core-Scientific-Brace-for-Earnings/69a5593c3d2913aa7c22651a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Miners-AI-Pivot-Riot-Core-Scientific-Brace-for-Earnings/69a5593c3d2913aa7c22651a</guid><description>Riot Platforms and Core Scientific, prominent Bitcoin miners, are set to report their latest financial results, with investors keenly watching their strategic pivot into AI infrastructure and high-density colocation (HDC). This transition leverages their data center expertise, signaling a potential shift away from core mining operations. Core Scientific faces scrutiny regarding its future mining focus, especially after a failed acquisition, while Riot is significantly expanding its data center capacity. The upcoming US jobs report will also provide macroeconomic context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:32:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5593c3d2913aa7c226519_1772444065859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VIP Industries Clarifies Carlton Trademark Battle Amidst Safari License</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VIP-Industries-Clarifies-Carlton-Trademark-Battle-Amidst-Safari-License/69a558f83d2913aa7c226450</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VIP-Industries-Clarifies-Carlton-Trademark-Battle-Amidst-Safari-License/69a558f83d2913aa7c226450</guid><description>VIP Industries is clarifying ongoing legal battles over the 'Carlton' trademark for travel luggage in India. The company has secured permission to sell its existing 'Carlton' branded inventory by June 1, 2026, but faces potential customer confusion following Safari Industries' acquisition of a license for the brand. VIP's global operations and overseas registrations remain unaffected by the Indian trademark dispute.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:31:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a558f83d2913aa7c22644f_1772443969277.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Razorpay IPO Clears Legal Hurdle, Sets Stage for Public Debut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Razorpay-IPO-Clears-Legal-Hurdle-Sets-Stage-for-Public-Debut/69a558af3d2913aa7c2263fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Razorpay-IPO-Clears-Legal-Hurdle-Sets-Stage-for-Public-Debut/69a558af3d2913aa7c2263fc</guid><description>Payment gateway major Razorpay secured a significant legal victory as the Supreme Court dismissed the Enforcement Directorate's appeal, upholding the Karnataka High Court's order that quashed money-laundering proceedings. This development removes a key regulatory overhang, paving the way for Razorpay's anticipated initial public offering (IPO). The company, last valued at $7.5 billion, is preparing to list by late 2026 after completing its reverse-flip to India, aiming to raise over $700 million. This legal clarity is crucial for investor confidence in the competitive Indian fintech market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:30:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a558af3d2913aa7c2263fb_1772443992497.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Strait of Hormuz Closure Sparks Energy Market Chaos</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Strait-of-Hormuz-Closure-Sparks-Energy-Market-Chaos/69a558a93d2913aa7c2263e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Strait-of-Hormuz-Closure-Sparks-Energy-Market-Chaos/69a558a93d2913aa7c2263e1</guid><description>The Strait of Hormuz blockade has rendered OPEC+'s modest production increase symbolic, creating a critical energy supply crunch. Brent crude neared $80, with potential to exceed $100. Dwindling spare capacity, primarily held by Saudi Arabia, and low European gas storage exacerbate market vulnerabilities. LNG markets face severe disruption, threatening Asian and European imports.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:30:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a558a93d2913aa7c2263e0_1772444242948.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Protein Surge: From Gyms to Everyday Wellness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Protein-Surge-From-Gyms-to-Everyday-Wellness/69a5571c3d2913aa7c226165</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Protein-Surge-From-Gyms-to-Everyday-Wellness/69a5571c3d2913aa7c226165</guid><description>India's protein consumption is undergoing a profound shift, moving beyond gym culture to become a daily wellness staple across demographics and geographies. Market research indicates significant growth, outpacing earlier forecasts, fueled by rising health awareness, especially post-COVID, and a strong premiumization trend. Product innovation in convenient formats like bars and RTDs, coupled with a growing acceptance of plant-based alternatives, is democratizing access. Tier 2 and Tier 3 cities are now mirroring metro growth rates, signalling a nationwide protein awakening.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:23:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5571c3d2913aa7c226164_1772443515035.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Niva Bupa Faces IRDAI Scrutiny, Stock Dips Amid Governance Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Niva-Bupa-Faces-IRDAI-Scrutiny-Stock-Dips-Amid-Governance-Concerns/69a557143d2913aa7c226147</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Niva-Bupa-Faces-IRDAI-Scrutiny-Stock-Dips-Amid-Governance-Concerns/69a557143d2913aa7c226147</guid><description>Niva Bupa Health Insurance is under regulatory scrutiny following a Show Cause Notice and Letter of Advice from the IRDAI, citing alleged violations of health insurance, policyholder interest, and corporate governance norms. While the company asserts no immediate financial impact, its stock fell, reflecting investor caution. This action occurs amidst the IRDAI's intensified oversight of the health insurance sector, with peer companies also facing compliance issues.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:23:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a557143d2913aa7c226146_1772443510891.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emcure Pharma, Roche Ink India Distribution Deal for Nephrology Therapies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Emcure-Pharma-Roche-Ink-India-Distribution-Deal-for-Nephrology-Therapies/69a556803d2913aa7c225eca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Emcure-Pharma-Roche-Ink-India-Distribution-Deal-for-Nephrology-Therapies/69a556803d2913aa7c225eca</guid><description>Emcure Pharmaceuticals has entered a strategic distribution agreement with Roche India for select nephrology and transplant medicine products. Effective April 1, 2026, the deal allows Emcure to distribute Roche's established brands, aiming to broaden patient access to vital treatments for chronic kidney disease and transplant care, thereby complementing Emcure's existing portfolio.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:21:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a556803d2913aa7c225ec9_1772443369553.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Canada Forge $50B Trade Pact Amidst Geopolitical Storm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Canada-Forge-50B-Trade-Pact-Amidst-Geopolitical-Storm/69a5560f3d2913aa7c225e14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Canada-Forge-50B-Trade-Pact-Amidst-Geopolitical-Storm/69a5560f3d2913aa7c225e14</guid><description>India and Canada have agreed to a strategic economic partnership targeting $50 billion in bilateral trade by 2030, prioritizing the acceleration of Comprehensive Economic Partnership Agreement (CEPA) negotiations. This pact emphasizes critical mineral cooperation and investment flows, signaling a commitment to economic resilience and supply chain security in an era of heightened global geopolitical instability. Canadian pension funds' substantial investment in India underscores confidence in the nation's growth trajectory, while the agreement aims to create significant new opportunities in both economies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:19:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5560f3d2913aa7c225e13_1772443587694.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Insurers Face New Underwriting Scrutiny Post-Moratorium Cut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurers-Face-New-Underwriting-Scrutiny-Post-Moratorium-Cut/69a552563d2913aa7c225c1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurers-Face-New-Underwriting-Scrutiny-Post-Moratorium-Cut/69a552563d2913aa7c225c1a</guid><description>The Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority of India (IRDAI) has significantly shortened the health insurance moratorium period from eight to five years, effective April 1, 2024. This regulatory shift, while enhancing policyholder protection against claim rejection due to non-disclosure or misrepresentation, compels insurers to fundamentally re-evaluate their underwriting processes. With a reduced window to scrutinize policyholder disclosures, companies must now prioritize robust data analytics and upfront risk assessment to manage potential adverse selection and maintain profitability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:03:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a552563d2913aa7c225c19_1772442636856.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hormuz Insurance Halt: India's Oil Costs Soar Amid Gulf Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hormuz-Insurance-Halt-Indias-Oil-Costs-Soar-Amid-Gulf-Risk/69a550ef3d2913aa7c225a63</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hormuz-Insurance-Halt-Indias-Oil-Costs-Soar-Amid-Gulf-Risk/69a550ef3d2913aa7c225a63</guid><description>Escalating geopolitical tensions have led to the withdrawal of war-risk insurance for Persian Gulf transit by leading maritime insurers, effective March 5, 2026. This move directly elevates India's already substantial oil import costs, as nearly half its crude supply transits the Strait of Hormuz. The heightened risk environment is compounded by India's reliance on external P&amp;I insurance, amplifying vulnerability to global insurance market shifts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:57:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a550ef3d2913aa7c225a62_1772442271009.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Groww Bets on 'Responsible AI' Amidst Fintech Diversification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Groww-Bets-on-Responsible-AI-Amidst-Fintech-Diversification/69a550e93d2913aa7c225a4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Groww-Bets-on-Responsible-AI-Amidst-Fintech-Diversification/69a550e93d2913aa7c225a4c</guid><description>Investment platform Groww is expanding its technological frontier with GR1, an AI co-pilot in beta, emphasizing a 'responsible intelligence' approach. This move aligns with a broader strategy to diversify revenue streams beyond core broking, focusing on wealth management, lending, and secondary bond markets. Groww's cautious integration of AI prioritizes user control and regulatory adherence, differentiating its strategy from broader market hype and aiming to deepen engagement across its expanding product suite.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a550e93d2913aa7c225a4b_1772441953206.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitics Ground Indian Aviation Stocks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Geopolitics-Ground-Indian-Aviation-Stocks/69a54f073d2913aa7c225853</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Geopolitics-Ground-Indian-Aviation-Stocks/69a54f073d2913aa7c225853</guid><description>Intensified Middle East conflict and subsequent airspace closures sent Indian aviation and travel stocks into a sharp decline on Monday. InterGlobe Aviation (IndiGo) saw its shares dip 7.5%, while SpiceJet, Ixigo, and Easy Trip Planners faced drops of up to 13.5%. This geopolitical shock exacerbates existing industry vulnerabilities, including thin margins, high fuel costs, and currency sensitivity, posing sustained risks to profitability and revenue visibility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:49:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a54f073d2913aa7c225852_1772441481762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ravinder Heights Q3 FY26: Consolidated Profit ₹12.48 Cr, Revenue ₹21.97 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ravinder-Heights-Q3-FY26-Consolidated-Profit-1248-Cr-Revenue-2197-Cr/69a54eff3d2913aa7c22583c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ravinder-Heights-Q3-FY26-Consolidated-Profit-1248-Cr-Revenue-2197-Cr/69a54eff3d2913aa7c22583c</guid><description>Ravinder Heights Limited reported its unaudited financial results for Q3 FY26, showcasing a consolidated profit after tax of ₹12.48 crore on revenue of ₹21.97 crore. However, its standalone operations reported a net loss of ₹0.15 crore for the same period. The company, primarily involved in real estate development, is also evaluating the impact of new labour codes on its business.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:49:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a54eff3d2913aa7c22583b_1772441694753.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Force Motors Feb Sales Up 8% On Domestic Demand; Exports Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Force-Motors-Feb-Sales-Up-8percent-On-Domestic-Demand-Exports-Dip/69a54d1f3d2913aa7c225713</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Force-Motors-Feb-Sales-Up-8percent-On-Domestic-Demand-Exports-Dip/69a54d1f3d2913aa7c225713</guid><description>Force Motors reported February 2026 sales figures, showing a robust 8.06% year-on-year increase in total vehicle sales to 3,890 units. This growth was primarily fueled by an 8.63% rise in domestic sales, indicating sustained market demand. However, export volumes saw a significant decline of 17.72%, a trend that warrants monitoring.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:41:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a54d1f3d2913aa7c225712_1772441206093.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Shock Sends Indian Bonds Lower, RBI Faces Policy Conundrum</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Geopolitical-Shock-Sends-Indian-Bonds-Lower-RBI-Faces-Policy-Conundrum/69a54b2b3d2913aa7c2255a4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Geopolitical-Shock-Sends-Indian-Bonds-Lower-RBI-Faces-Policy-Conundrum/69a54b2b3d2913aa7c2255a4</guid><description>Geopolitical tensions in the Middle East have triggered a surge in Brent crude prices to near $77 per barrel, directly impacting Indian debt markets. The benchmark 10-year Indian government bond yield climbed to 6.7042%, reversing recent gains and dimming prospects for an imminent Reserve Bank of India (RBI) rate cut. While current inflation remains within the RBI's target band, sustained high energy costs pose an imported inflation risk, creating a complex policy dilemma for the central bank.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:32:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a54b2b3d2913aa7c2255a3_1772440773862.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Prices Spike Amid Geopolitical Fears, Exceeding Supply Realities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Spike-Amid-Geopolitical-Fears-Exceeding-Supply-Realities/69a549e03d2913aa7c225423</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Spike-Amid-Geopolitical-Fears-Exceeding-Supply-Realities/69a549e03d2913aa7c225423</guid><description>Global oil prices are escalating, not just from Iran's direct output but heavily influenced by a speculative 'fear premium' tied to geopolitical tensions in West Asia. The Strait of Hormuz, a critical transit point, is the nexus of this vulnerability, potentially driving prices far beyond immediate supply deficits. This volatility poses significant economic risks, particularly for energy-importing nations like India, as historical patterns show sustained price premiums during crises. While underlying market fundamentals appear stable, short-term risk perception is dictating market direction, a dynamic that could override baseline price forecasts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:27:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a549e03d2913aa7c225422_1772440153877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Tumble Amid Geopolitics; Oil Spikes, Rupee Weakens</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Tumble-Amid-Geopolitics-Oil-Spikes-Rupee-Weakens/69a549783d2913aa7c2253af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Tumble-Amid-Geopolitics-Oil-Spikes-Rupee-Weakens/69a549783d2913aa7c2253af</guid><description>The Indian equity market suffered a broad-based sell-off, with the Sensex and Nifty plummeting over 1% on February 28, 2026. This downturn was primarily triggered by intensified Iran-Israel conflict, pushing crude oil prices to multi-month highs and weakening the Indian rupee. The India VIX, a measure of market volatility, surged nearly 22%. While upstream oil producers saw gains, sectors like IT, Auto, and Paints faced significant pressure due to geopolitical risks, supply chain fears, and rising input costs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:25:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a549783d2913aa7c2253ae_1772440067388.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cameco, India ink C$2.6B uranium deal amid nuclear expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Cameco-India-ink-C26B-uranium-deal-amid-nuclear-expansion/69a548f83d2913aa7c225319</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Cameco-India-ink-C26B-uranium-deal-amid-nuclear-expansion/69a548f83d2913aa7c225319</guid><description>Cameco Corporation has signed a C$2.6 billion uranium supply agreement to deliver 22 million pounds of reactor fuel to India between 2027 and 2035. This landmark deal aligns with India's strategy to significantly expand its nuclear power capacity to 100 GW by 2047, addressing a growing demand that outstrips domestic production. The agreement also signifies a diplomatic thaw between Canada and India and broadens cooperation across strategic sectors, positioning Cameco within a tightening global uranium market driven by energy security concerns.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:23:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a548f83d2913aa7c225318_1772440184532.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anlon Healthcare Board to Consider Stock Split, Bonus Shares on March 6</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Anlon-Healthcare-Board-to-Consider-Stock-Split-Bonus-Shares-on-March-6/69a5461a3d2913aa7c225138</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Anlon-Healthcare-Board-to-Consider-Stock-Split-Bonus-Shares-on-March-6/69a5461a3d2913aa7c225138</guid><description>Anlon Healthcare Limited has announced a Board Meeting for March 6, 2026, to discuss significant corporate actions. The agenda includes a potential stock split, recommending an increase in authorized share capital, and approving the issuance of bonus equity shares. The company will also close its trading window for designated persons.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:11:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5461a3d2913aa7c225137_1772439173461.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Modern Dairies Promoter Group Ups Stake By 28 Lakh Shares Via Warrants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Modern-Dairies-Promoter-Group-Ups-Stake-By-28-Lakh-Shares-Via-Warrants/69a544b13d2913aa7c224f6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Modern-Dairies-Promoter-Group-Ups-Stake-By-28-Lakh-Shares-Via-Warrants/69a544b13d2913aa7c224f6d</guid><description>Modern Dairies Limited announced that members of its promoter and promoter group have acquired 28,00,000 equity shares worth ₹14 crore by exercising rights from convertible warrants. These transactions, occurring on February 26-27, 2026, signal increased promoter confidence following a prior preferential issuance and strategic alignment with company growth. The move consolidates shareholding among key entities within the promoter family.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:05:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a544b13d2913aa7c224f6c_1772438883028.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axtel Industries Declares Rs 12 Interim Dividend for FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Axtel-Industries-Declares-Rs-12-Interim-Dividend-for-FY26/69a544af3d2913aa7c224f57</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Axtel-Industries-Declares-Rs-12-Interim-Dividend-for-FY26/69a544af3d2913aa7c224f57</guid><description>Axtel Industries' Board of Directors has approved an interim dividend of Rs. 12.00 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. This payout, equivalent to 120% of the face value, signals a positive return for shareholders. The decision was made during a board meeting on March 2, 2026, with March 9, 2026, set as the record date.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:05:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a544af3d2913aa7c224f56_1772438812074.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Summer Power Crunch Looms: Demand Surge vs. Supply Gaps</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Summer-Power-Crunch-Looms-Demand-Surge-vs-Supply-Gaps/69a544443d2913aa7c224e9f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Summer-Power-Crunch-Looms-Demand-Surge-vs-Supply-Gaps/69a544443d2913aa7c224e9f</guid><description>As India braces for summer, JM Financial has highlighted Adani Power, Adani Green, Tata Power, Torrent Power, and JSW Energy as key utilities. However, forecasts point to above-normal temperatures and below-normal rainfall, potentially driving peak demand to new highs of 285 GW. Despite capacity additions, a projected incremental generation shortfall and risks from hydro output decline raise concerns about evening power deficits, creating a complex outlook for these energy majors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:03:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a544443d2913aa7c224e9e_1772438717871.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd. Faces Record Slump; Analysts See Value Amidst Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Eternal-Ltd-Faces-Record-Slump-Analysts-See-Value-Amidst-Volatility/69a5443a3d2913aa7c224e85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Eternal-Ltd-Faces-Record-Slump-Analysts-See-Value-Amidst-Volatility/69a5443a3d2913aa7c224e85</guid><description>Eternal Ltd. shares have suffered an unprecedented ten-session losing streak, shedding 15.5% of their value. Despite this bearish momentum, brokerage Bernstein maintains an 'outperform' rating and a ₹370 price target, seeing the current dip as a favorable risk-reward scenario for long-term investors. The firm cites heightened competition and AI integration uncertainties as key drivers for the recent correction, suggesting major risks are now factored into the stock's valuation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5443a3d2913aa7c224e84_1772439197512.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCLTech Wins Americas ServiceNow Partner Awards for AI &amp; Services; $14.5B Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTech-Wins-Americas-ServiceNow-Partner-Awards-for-AI-and-Services-145B-Revenue/69a543c33d2913aa7c224dd8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTech-Wins-Americas-ServiceNow-Partner-Awards-for-AI-and-Services-145B-Revenue/69a543c33d2913aa7c224dd8</guid><description>HCLTech has been honored with two prestigious 2026 ServiceNow Partner of the Year awards for the Americas: AI Customer Value Partner and Service Provider of the Year. These accolades underscore the company's deep expertise in leveraging the ServiceNow platform, particularly its advanced AI integration capabilities for enterprise clients. The announcement comes as HCLTech reported consolidated revenues of $14.5 billion for the 12 months ending December 2025, reflecting its significant market presence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 08:01:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a543c33d2913aa7c224dd7_1772438813606.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Energy Lifeline Strained: Hormuz Tensions Spark Inflation-Fiscal Dilemma</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Energy-Lifeline-Strained-Hormuz-Tensions-Spark-Inflation-Fiscal-Dilemma/69a541f43d2913aa7c224b4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Energy-Lifeline-Strained-Hormuz-Tensions-Spark-Inflation-Fiscal-Dilemma/69a541f43d2913aa7c224b4f</guid><description>Escalating tensions around the Strait of Hormuz critically expose India's heavy reliance on Middle Eastern energy supplies, with nearly 50% of crude oil and significant LNG/LPG imports transiting this chokepoint. This vulnerability forces a stark government choice between fueling inflation via higher fuel prices or straining fiscal balances through duty cuts. While oil marketing companies, aviation, and hospitality face immediate headwinds, the defense sector emerges as a strategic beneficiary amid rising geopolitical uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:53:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a541f43d2913aa7c224b4e_1772438295702.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Honda Scooters Ride 34% Sales Surge Amidst Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Honda-Scooters-Ride-34percent-Sales-Surge-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/69a541e53d2913aa7c224b36</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Honda-Scooters-Ride-34percent-Sales-Surge-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/69a541e53d2913aa7c224b36</guid><description>Honda Motorcycle &amp; Scooter India (HMSI) posted a significant 34% year-over-year increase in total sales for February 2026, reaching 567,351 units. Domestic sales contributed 513,190 units, with exports adding 54,161. Despite this volume growth, HMSI's performance lags behind key competitors in percentage terms, signaling an intensifying competitive environment and evolving market dynamics, particularly in the crucial scooter segment and the rapidly growing electric vehicle sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:53:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a541e53d2913aa7c224b35_1772438134695.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Clean Max IPO Plunges: Investor Caution Amid Geopolitical Storm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Clean-Max-IPO-Plunges-Investor-Caution-Amid-Geopolitical-Storm/69a541e33d2913aa7c224b1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Clean-Max-IPO-Plunges-Investor-Caution-Amid-Geopolitical-Storm/69a541e33d2913aa7c224b1e</guid><description>Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions commenced trading on Monday with an 8.83% discount to its IPO price, listing at ₹960 on the NSE and ₹952 on the BSE. The stock's value further eroded, hitting an intraday low of ₹761.80 and a market capitalization of ₹8,965 crore. This weak debut, the fifth discount listing in 2026, reflects a broader investor wariness towards new offerings amid escalating geopolitical tensions in the Middle East and a spike in crude oil prices, which are impacting the secondary market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:53:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a541e33d2913aa7c224b1d_1772438428644.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Exits Japanese JV Amid Ag Tech Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Exits-Japanese-JV-Amid-Ag-Tech-Shift/69a541e23d2913aa7c224b07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Exits-Japanese-JV-Amid-Ag-Tech-Shift/69a541e23d2913aa7c224b07</guid><description>Mitsubishi Mahindra Agricultural Machinery, a joint venture of Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, will cease operations by the first half of fiscal 2027. The decision cites long-term non-viability driven by shifting global demand and industry pressures. This exit may allow Mahindra &amp; Mahindra to refocus resources on more promising segments or markets, particularly as the global agricultural equipment sector rapidly embraces automation and smart farming technologies. The parent company maintains strong domestic market positions and enjoys a positive analyst outlook, despite this international divestment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:53:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a541e23d2913aa7c224b06_1772438125916.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Krystal Integrated Services Approves ₹300 Cr QIP, Hikes Capital by ₹4 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Krystal-Integrated-Services-Approves-300-Cr-QIP-Hikes-Capital-by-4-Cr/69a53db83d2913aa7c22487f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Krystal-Integrated-Services-Approves-300-Cr-QIP-Hikes-Capital-by-4-Cr/69a53db83d2913aa7c22487f</guid><description>Krystal Integrated Services members have overwhelmingly approved a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) to raise up to ₹300 crore and an increase in authorized share capital by ₹4 crore. This capital infusion is slated to bolster working capital, facilitate debt repayment, and fund potential acquisitions, signaling strategic growth for the integrated facility management provider.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:35:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a53db83d2913aa7c22487e_1772437106753.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Swiggy Shares Plunge 26% YTD Amidst QC Losses, Analysts Cite Overreaction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Swiggy-Shares-Plunge-26percent-YTD-Amidst-QC-Losses-Analysts-Cite-Overreaction/69a53cc53d2913aa7c22465f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Swiggy-Shares-Plunge-26percent-YTD-Amidst-QC-Losses-Analysts-Cite-Overreaction/69a53cc53d2913aa7c22465f</guid><description>Swiggy's share price has plummeted to an all-time low of ₹285.85, marking a 26% year-to-date decline in 2026, significantly underperforming the BSE Sensex. This downturn stems from higher-than-expected losses in its quick commerce (QC) division, which overshadowed improvements in food delivery (FD) and a healthy balance sheet. While management aims for QC contribution breakeven by Q1 FY27, analysts are cutting earnings estimates, citing intense competition. Competitors like Blinkit are prioritizing profitability, while Zepto gears up for an IPO.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:31:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a53cc53d2913aa7c22465e_1772436862078.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India GDP Revised Downward; Consumption Weakness, Debt Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Revised-Downward-Consumption-Weakness-Debt-Risks-Loom/69a53cbd3d2913aa7c224645</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Revised-Downward-Consumption-Weakness-Debt-Risks-Loom/69a53cbd3d2913aa7c224645</guid><description>India's GDP series revision adjusts the economy's nominal size downward, reflecting methodological upgrades. While real growth forecasts remain robust, analysts at Nomura flag persistent post-pandemic consumption softness. This trend, coupled with a rising government debt-to-GDP ratio now projected around 78% by 2026-27, presents a contrasting narrative to the Reserve Bank of India's assessment of steady growth and economic slack. The divergence highlights potential investor risks amidst underlying demand vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:31:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a53cbd3d2913aa7c224644_1772437174436.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Urban Company Faces Supply Deluge Post-IPO Price Breach</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Urban-Company-Faces-Supply-Deluge-Post-IPO-Price-Breach/69a53cb83d2913aa7c22462e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Urban-Company-Faces-Supply-Deluge-Post-IPO-Price-Breach/69a53cb83d2913aa7c22462e</guid><description>Urban Company Ltd. shares breached their ₹103 IPO price on March 2, 2026, signaling investor pressure. The primary threat is the impending release of 66% of the company's equity on March 17th, valued at over ₹9,600 crore, which could overwhelm market demand. Recent quarterly losses and high valuation metrics compound the bearish outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a53cb83d2913aa7c22462d_1772436805539.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Krystal Integrated Gets Nod for ₹300 Cr QIP, Boosts Capital to ₹190 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Krystal-Integrated-Gets-Nod-for-300-Cr-QIP-Boosts-Capital-to-190-Cr/69a53cb73d2913aa7c224617</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Krystal-Integrated-Gets-Nod-for-300-Cr-QIP-Boosts-Capital-to-190-Cr/69a53cb73d2913aa7c224617</guid><description>Krystal Integrated Services Limited shareholders have overwhelmingly approved proposals to increase the company's authorized share capital to ₹190 crore from ₹150 crore and to raise up to ₹300 crore through a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP). This move positions the company to access significant capital for expansion, debt repayment, and working capital needs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:31:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a53cb73d2913aa7c224616_1772436776784.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Surge Rattles India Stocks, Exposes Economic Fragility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Surge-Rattles-India-Stocks-Exposes-Economic-Fragility/69a53bce3d2913aa7c2244e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Surge-Rattles-India-Stocks-Exposes-Economic-Fragility/69a53bce3d2913aa7c2244e6</guid><description>Indian equity markets experienced a significant downturn, with the Sensex and Nifty dropping sharply as Brent crude oil prices surged past $82 per barrel. The escalation in geopolitical tensions, particularly concerning the Strait of Hormuz, fueled fears of supply disruptions. Sectors like paint, tyre, and state-run oil marketing companies faced severe pressure due to rising input costs and potential margin erosion. This event highlights India's vulnerability as a net oil importer, with implications for trade balance and inflation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:27:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a53bce3d2913aa7c2244e5_1772436808606.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aramco Strike Fuels Oil Surge; Geopolitical Risk Premium Grows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Aramco-Strike-Fuels-Oil-Surge-Geopolitical-Risk-Premium-Grows/69a53aea3d2913aa7c224384</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Aramco-Strike-Fuels-Oil-Surge-Geopolitical-Risk-Premium-Grows/69a53aea3d2913aa7c224384</guid><description>An apparent drone strike targeted Saudi Aramco's Ras Tanura refinery, causing a minor, contained fire. The incident immediately sent oil prices surging, with Brent crude jumping to multi-month highs. This event reignites concerns over critical energy infrastructure vulnerability in the Middle East and the sustained geopolitical risk premium influencing global markets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:23:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a53aea3d2913aa7c224383_1772436316203.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Middle East Conflict Sparks Pakistan Market Plunge, Exposes Energy Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Middle-East-Conflict-Sparks-Pakistan-Market-Plunge-Exposes-Energy-Vulnerability/69a53a723d2913aa7c2242d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Middle-East-Conflict-Sparks-Pakistan-Market-Plunge-Exposes-Energy-Vulnerability/69a53a723d2913aa7c2242d0</guid><description>The Pakistan Stock Exchange's benchmark KSE-100 index experienced a sharp decline, losing over 15,000 points, triggering a temporary trading halt. Escalating Middle East geopolitical tensions and the subsequent threat to oil supply routes were the primary catalysts. This event significantly exacerbates Pakistan's vulnerability as a heavy importer of energy, directly impacting fuel prices, currency stability, and inflationary pressures. Regional markets also reacted negatively, with several Gulf exchanges seeing substantial losses or suspensions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:21:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a53a723d2913aa7c2242cf_1772436200410.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Beezaasan Explotech Approves ₹52.64 Cr Share Allotment For 34.84% Asawara Earthtech Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Beezaasan-Explotech-Approves-5264-Cr-Share-Allotment-For-3484percent-Asawara-Earthtech-Stake/69a53a5f3d2913aa7c2242b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Beezaasan-Explotech-Approves-5264-Cr-Share-Allotment-For-3484percent-Asawara-Earthtech-Stake/69a53a5f3d2913aa7c2242b2</guid><description>Beezaasan Explotech Limited's board has approved the allotment of 22,30,641 equity shares, valued at ₹52.64 crore, to acquire a 34.84% stake in Asawara Earthtech Limited via a share swap. This move signals Beezaasan's strategic expansion into the infrastructure development sector by integrating Asawara Earthtech's operations, consequently increasing its paid-up capital.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:21:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a53a5f3d2913aa7c2242b1_1772436461172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharti Airtel's Mittal Wins GSMA Award, Validating Emerging Market Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtels-Mittal-Wins-GSMA-Award-Validating-Emerging-Market-Push/69a538843d2913aa7c2240bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtels-Mittal-Wins-GSMA-Award-Validating-Emerging-Market-Push/69a538843d2913aa7c2240bd</guid><description>Sunil Bharti Mittal, Founder &amp; Chairman of Bharti Enterprises, has been honored with the GSMA Lifetime Achievement Award. This recognition celebrates his instrumental role in scaling Bharti Airtel into a global telecom leader, particularly across India and Africa. The award highlights the company's strategic expansion and operational prowess in high-growth emerging markets, underscoring Mittal's influence on the industry's evolution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:13:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a538843d2913aa7c2240bc_1772435753347.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Housing Finance Allots ₹503 Cr NCDs; Boosts Funding Base</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Housing-Finance-Allots-503-Cr-NCDs-Boosts-Funding-Base/69a538823d2913aa7c2240a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Housing-Finance-Allots-503-Cr-NCDs-Boosts-Funding-Base/69a538823d2913aa7c2240a6</guid><description>Bajaj Housing Finance Limited has allotted ₹503.42 crore in Secured Redeemable Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) with a 7.25% annual interest rate. The move bolsters the company's funding base and is slated for listing on the BSE Wholesale Debt Market, offering transparency to debenture holders.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:13:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a538823d2913aa7c2240a5_1772435960859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airtel's Bullish Outlook: Diversification Amidst Sector Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airtels-Bullish-Outlook-Diversification-Amidst-Sector-Growth/69a536a63d2913aa7c223ea1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airtels-Bullish-Outlook-Diversification-Amidst-Sector-Growth/69a536a63d2913aa7c223ea1</guid><description>Motilal Oswal and other analysts have reiterated 'Buy' ratings on Bharti Airtel, setting target prices between ₹2,300 and ₹2,455. Key catalysts include anticipated telecom tariff hikes and the potential Jio Platforms IPO. The company's significant diversification into fintech via a ₹20,000 crore investment in its NBFC arm, Airtel Money, signals a strategic shift, though it triggered a notable stock price correction. Despite this, the firm's dominant market position, growing ARPU, and expansion in 5G services underpin a positive sector outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 07:05:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a536a63d2913aa7c223ea0_1772435265290.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>