<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:32 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India-US Trade Pact Spurs Semiconductor, Data Center Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-US-Trade-Pact-Spurs-Semiconductor-Data-Center-Growth/69881421b81b2b81dcfd0fe3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-US-Trade-Pact-Spurs-Semiconductor-Data-Center-Growth/69881421b81b2b81dcfd0fe3</guid><description>India's semiconductor and data center ambitions are set for a significant boost following the interim trade framework agreement with the US. Pan IIT Alumni India highlights the deal as a catalyst for deeper tech collaboration and supply chain resilience, aligning with recent Union Budget measures. This strategic move aims to attract global investment and leverage India's manufacturing capabilities amidst shifting global supply chains.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:42:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69881421b81b2b81dcfd0fe2_1770525923723.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Veolia Secures Mumbai Water Deal, Eyes 60% Demand by 2030</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Veolia-Secures-Mumbai-Water-Deal-Eyes-60percent-Demand-by-2030/698813aeb81b2b81dcfd0ef1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Veolia-Secures-Mumbai-Water-Deal-Eyes-60percent-Demand-by-2030/698813aeb81b2b81dcfd0ef1</guid><description>Veolia Environnement is set to supply 60% of Mumbai's drinking water by 2030, with two major treatment facilities due online by 2029-2030. This partnership leverages Veolia's technological expertise and operational models to meet escalating urban demand in India's vast water sector. The contract underscores Veolia's ambition to more than double its Indian business by 2030, capitalizing on government initiatives and stringent environmental regulations driving market growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:40:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698813aeb81b2b81dcfd0ef0_1770525797168.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Doubles Deep Tech Startup Window, Boosts Capital Access</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Doubles-Deep-Tech-Startup-Window-Boosts-Capital-Access/69880a47b81b2b81dcfd0807</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Doubles-Deep-Tech-Startup-Window-Boosts-Capital-Access/69880a47b81b2b81dcfd0807</guid><description>India has significantly updated its startup framework, doubling the recognition period for deep tech companies to 20 years and increasing the revenue threshold for tax and grant benefits to ₹3 billion. This move aims to align policy with the long gestation periods of science-led ventures and bolster the nation's deep tech ecosystem through combined regulatory reform and public capital, including the ₹1 trillion RDI Fund. A new India Deep Tech Alliance, backed by major venture firms and Nvidia, also signals growing private sector commitment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:00:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69880a47b81b2b81dcfd0806_1770523377243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Century Enka Profits Soar 69% YoY on Margin Expansion Despite Revenue Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Century-Enka-Profits-Soar-69percent-YoY-on-Margin-Expansion-Despite-Revenue-Dip/6987fd28b81b2b81dcfd00a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Century-Enka-Profits-Soar-69percent-YoY-on-Margin-Expansion-Despite-Revenue-Dip/6987fd28b81b2b81dcfd00a1</guid><description>Century Enka reported a significant Q3-FY26 profit surge of 69.3% YoY to INR 237 Mn, fueled by a robust EBITDA margin expansion to 9.93%. This turnaround occurred despite a 16.6% YoY revenue decline to INR 4,117 Mn. For 9M-FY26, net profit grew 2.8% YoY to INR 614 Mn with improved margins. Management foresees better demand in Q4-FY26 but faces margin pressure from imports and rising raw material costs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:04:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987fd28b81b2b81dcfd00a0_1770519964454.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Profit Jumps 24.5% Amidst Rival Rally: NIM Pressure Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Profit-Jumps-245percent-Amidst-Rival-Rally-NIM-Pressure-Mounts/6987f63bb81b2b81dcfcfb87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Profit-Jumps-245percent-Amidst-Rival-Rally-NIM-Pressure-Mounts/6987f63bb81b2b81dcfcfb87</guid><description>State Bank of India (SBI) reported a robust 24.5% year-on-year net profit growth in Q3 FY26, reaching a record high. This surge was driven by a 15.7% increase in advances, fueled by strong retail and SME loan growth. However, the bank, along with its rivals like Punjab National Bank (PNB), HDFC Bank, and Kotak Mahindra Bank, is navigating pressure on Net Interest Margins (NIMs) due to RBI's rate cut measures. SBI's Return on Assets (ROA) stood at 1.19%, trailing HDFC Bank and Kotak Mahindra Bank.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:34:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987f63bb81b2b81dcfcfb86_1770518281329.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Two-Wheeler Leaders Face Margin Squeeze Amidst Premium Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Two-Wheeler-Leaders-Face-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Premium-Valuations/6987f62cb81b2b81dcfcfb03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Two-Wheeler-Leaders-Face-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Premium-Valuations/6987f62cb81b2b81dcfcfb03</guid><description>Indian two-wheeler manufacturers TVS Motor, Hero MotoCorp, and Bajaj Auto have posted robust sales growth for the December 2025 quarter, driven by festive demand and policy tailwinds. TVS Motor led with a 27.5% sales volume increase and 37.1% revenue growth. However, rising commodity costs, one-time labor code expenses, and increasingly premium valuations, particularly for TVS Motor, present significant headwinds. While new model launches offer future promise, analysts signal caution regarding the sustainability of margins and the high multiples across the sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:34:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987f62cb81b2b81dcfcfb02_1770518171825.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>