<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:54:22 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Waaree Energies bags 500MW solar module order for FY27 supply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Waaree-Energies-bags-500MW-solar-module-order-for-FY27-supply/699c4b67ee97f501b0eba910</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Waaree-Energies-bags-500MW-solar-module-order-for-FY27-supply/699c4b67ee97f501b0eba910</guid><description>Waaree Energies, India's largest solar module manufacturer, announced it has secured a significant order for 500 MW of solar modules. The supply is slated for the fiscal year 2026-27. While this order underscores the company's continued role in powering future renewable projects, the commercial value remains undisclosed, and revenue recognition is in a future fiscal year, presenting near-term financial clarity challenges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:43:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4b67ee97f501b0eba90f_1771850710048.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Go Digit General Insurance to meet analysts on Feb 26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Go-Digit-General-Insurance-to-meet-analysts-on-Feb-26/699c4b5bee97f501b0eba8f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Go-Digit-General-Insurance-to-meet-analysts-on-Feb-26/699c4b5bee97f501b0eba8f5</guid><description>Go Digit General Insurance Limited will engage with analysts and institutional investors on February 26, 2026, in Mumbai. The meetings, hosted by Kotak and IIFL, aim to provide insights into the company's strategy and performance. This engagement comes post its IPO and amidst ongoing growth in the Indian general insurance sector, making it a key event for investors tracking the company's market positioning and future outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:43:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4b5bee97f501b0eba8f4_1771850731982.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Omnitech Engineering IPO: Growth Fuelled by Debt, Risks Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Omnitech-Engineering-IPO-Growth-Fuelled-by-Debt-Risks-Ahead/699c4b06ee97f501b0eba82f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Omnitech-Engineering-IPO-Growth-Fuelled-by-Debt-Risks-Ahead/699c4b06ee97f501b0eba82f</guid><description>Omnitech Engineering launches its ₹583 crore IPO on February 25, with shares priced between ₹216-₹227. Funds will bolster debt repayment and establish two new manufacturing facilities. Despite a strong order book and significant export revenue, the company's elevated 1.60 debt-to-equity ratio and premium valuation raise questions. Competitors like Azad Engineering and MTAR Technologies, while trading at higher multiples, often exhibit lower leverage, presenting a complex investment picture.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Biocon's Biosimilar Push Faces Fierce GLP-1 Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biocons-Biosimilar-Push-Faces-Fierce-GLP-1-Competition/699c4a7cee97f501b0eba754</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biocons-Biosimilar-Push-Faces-Fierce-GLP-1-Competition/699c4a7cee97f501b0eba754</guid><description>Biocon Biologics is intensifying its global expansion strategy by focusing on market share gains for new biosimilars and preparing for a multi-country rollout of semaglutide. The company anticipates improved EBITDA margins, reaching 28%, driven by a shift to high-margin geographies and reduced R&amp;D expenditure following a significant corporate integration. However, Biocon navigates a fiercely competitive GLP-1 drug market dominated by giants and contends with structural challenges in the broader biosimilar landscape, raising questions about the sustainability of its projected growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:39:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4a7cee97f501b0eba753_1771850512996.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Solar Tariffs: Commerce Dept. Preliminary Ruling Spurs Trade Tensions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/US-Solar-Tariffs-Commerce-Dept-Preliminary-Ruling-Spurs-Trade-Tensions/699c4a08ee97f501b0eba664</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/US-Solar-Tariffs-Commerce-Dept-Preliminary-Ruling-Spurs-Trade-Tensions/699c4a08ee97f501b0eba664</guid><description>The U.S. Commerce Department has unveiled its preliminary findings on whether solar cells and panels imported from India, Laos, and Indonesia benefit from unfair government subsidies. This decision, central to a trade case initiated by domestic manufacturers, signals a potential shift in global solar supply dynamics. While petitioners aim to protect U.S. investments and jobs, the ruling could influence import costs and the pace of renewable energy deployment across the nation. The investigation is a critical step in addressing alleged trade malpractices impacting the U.S. solar manufacturing sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Silver Touch Technologies Wins Major FSSAI Digital Transformation Contract</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silver-Touch-Technologies-Wins-Major-FSSAI-Digital-Transformation-Contract/699c4979ee97f501b0eba552</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silver-Touch-Technologies-Wins-Major-FSSAI-Digital-Transformation-Contract/699c4979ee97f501b0eba552</guid><description>Silver Touch Technologies has bagged a strategic digital transformation contract from the Food Safety and Standards Authority of India (FSSAI). The company will act as the Managed Service Provider (MSP) for FSSAI's portals and applications, encompassing development, enhancement, operations, and maintenance. This long-term engagement is anticipated to provide significant revenue visibility and continuity for Silver Touch, bolstering its presence in government digital projects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:35:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4979ee97f501b0eba551_1771851017196.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Uber India Leverages Software Dashcam to Boost Safety</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Uber-India-Leverages-Software-Dashcam-to-Boost-Safety/699c492cee97f501b0eba450</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Uber-India-Leverages-Software-Dashcam-to-Boost-Safety/699c492cee97f501b0eba450</guid><description>Uber is enhancing its safety initiative in India with the introduction of 'RecordMyRide,' a feature turning drivers' smartphones into encrypted dashcams, bypassing costly hardware. This software-centric approach aims for rapid adoption and scalability. Concurrently, Uber is expanding its 'Uber Teens' program, which offers supervised rides for minors and has seen 20% quarter-on-quarter growth. These moves underscore Uber's strategic focus on leveraging technology to address market-specific safety concerns and build rider trust.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:33:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c492cee97f501b0eba44f_1771850317392.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's SIP Surge: The 'Procrastination Penalty' in Wealth Building</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-SIP-Surge-The-Procrastination-Penalty-in-Wealth-Building/699c4923ee97f501b0eba435</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-SIP-Surge-The-Procrastination-Penalty-in-Wealth-Building/699c4923ee97f501b0eba435</guid><description>Mutual fund SIP inflows in India reached ₹31,002 crore in January 2026, with 9.92 crore accounts and ₹16.36 lakh crore in AUM. This highlights the growing importance of systematic investing. However, a critical 'procrastination penalty' emerges when investors delay starting SIPs. Calculations show that a ₹1 crore retirement corpus by age 60 requires a monthly investment that escalates dramatically with delayed starts. Starting at 25 demands ₹1,000 monthly, while a 30-year-old needs ₹2,000, and a 40-year-old faces a steep ₹7,500 requirement, assuming a 15% annual return. Step-up SIPs can mitigate some of this impact, but the core challenge remains the compounding lost due to delayed entry. This penalty is exacerbated by increasing volatility in equity markets, potentially forcing late starters into riskier investment choices to compensate for lost time, diverging from the disciplined, long-term ethos of SIPs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:33:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4923ee97f501b0eba434_1771850144256.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Uttar Pradesh Ascends as India's Aviation Nexus with Jewar Airport</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Uttar-Pradesh-Ascends-as-Indias-Aviation-Nexus-with-Jewar-Airport/699c47abee97f501b0eba211</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Uttar-Pradesh-Ascends-as-Indias-Aviation-Nexus-with-Jewar-Airport/699c47abee97f501b0eba211</guid><description>Uttar Pradesh is establishing itself as India's leading aviation hub with Prime Minister Modi set to inaugurate the Noida International Airport at Jewar next month. This facility is poised to become the nation's largest airport, significantly enhancing the state's capacity for both passenger and cargo operations. The development marks a critical step in bolstering regional connectivity and economic growth, positioning Uttar Pradesh as a key gateway for national and international trade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:27:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c47abee97f501b0eba210_1771850179363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Subsidizes Export Compliance for MSMEs Amid FTA Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Subsidizes-Export-Compliance-for-MSMEs-Amid-FTA-Boom/699c475fee97f501b0eba163</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Subsidizes-Export-Compliance-for-MSMEs-Amid-FTA-Boom/699c475fee97f501b0eba163</guid><description>India has launched a significant initiative, funding up to 75% of international compliance costs for micro and small exporters to boost global shipments. This move, part of the ₹25,060 crore Export Promotion Mission (EPM) and its TRACE measure, offers partial reimbursement up to ₹25 lakh annually per importer-exporter code. The subsidy aims to mitigate non-tariff barriers like Europe's REACH and CBAM, thereby facilitating market access and leveraging the nation's recently finalized nine Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) with various countries, including the EU, UK, and New Zealand. This policy supports India's ambition to reach $2 trillion in exports within the next 6-7 years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:26:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c475fee97f501b0eba162_1771849699147.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's EV Race: Budget Brands Overtake Tesla, BYD Amidst Regulatory Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Chinas-EV-Race-Budget-Brands-Overtake-Tesla-BYD-Amidst-Regulatory-Shift/699c4746ee97f501b0eba110</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Chinas-EV-Race-Budget-Brands-Overtake-Tesla-BYD-Amidst-Regulatory-Shift/699c4746ee97f501b0eba110</guid><description>In China's fiercely competitive 2025 electric vehicle market, value-oriented models from Geely Auto and Wuling Motor Holdings have surged to the top sales positions, eclipsing higher-priced offerings from industry giants BYD and Tesla. Geely's Xingyuan EV sold over 465,000 units, while Wuling's Mini EV achieved 435,000 sales. This shift coincides with a significant regulatory crackdown on price wars, including a ban on selling vehicles below production cost, and a reduction in tax incentives for EV buyers starting in 2026, signaling a new era focused on value and sustainability. Tesla's Model Y and BYD's Seagull saw sales decline despite premium features and pricing strategies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:25:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4746ee97f501b0eba10f_1771849676171.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Inc's 9.1% Pay Hike Hides Precision Pay Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Incs-91percent-Pay-Hike-Hides-Precision-Pay-Shift/699c473fee97f501b0eba0f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Incs-91percent-Pay-Hike-Hides-Precision-Pay-Shift/699c473fee97f501b0eba0f5</guid><description>India Inc's average salary increment is projected at 9.1% for 2026, a period of "normalization" according to EY. However, this figure masks a significant strategic pivot. Global Capability Centers (GCCs) lead with 10.4% increases, driven by demand for digital skills. The true narrative lies in "precision pay," where companies are sharpening differentiation through skill premiums (up to 40% for AI/ML), increased variable pay (16.1% of fixed pay), and robust performance metrics, creating a bifurcated reward system that favors specialized talent and high performers. Attrition, though moderating, remains voluntary and opportunity-driven.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:25:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c473fee97f501b0eba0f4_1771849835349.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Niva Bupa Shareholders Vote on Director Appointment, CEO Remuneration Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Niva-Bupa-Shareholders-Vote-on-Director-Appointment-CEO-Remuneration-Hike/699c46abee97f501b0eba013</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Niva-Bupa-Shareholders-Vote-on-Director-Appointment-CEO-Remuneration-Hike/699c46abee97f501b0eba013</guid><description>Niva Bupa Health Insurance is seeking shareholder approval via postal ballot for appointing Roger William John Davis as Non-Executive Director and revising MD &amp; CEO Krishnan Ramachandran's remuneration for FY2025-26. The proposed total package for Mr. Ramachandran, including fixed pay and performance bonuses, amounts to approximately ₹13.93 crore. Shareholders can cast their votes remotely from February 25 to March 26, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:23:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c46abee97f501b0eba012_1771849708236.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Puretrop Fruits ₹22 Cr Buyback Approved; Tender Offer Starts March 23</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Puretrop-Fruits-22-Cr-Buyback-Approved-Tender-Offer-Starts-March-23/699c4630ee97f501b0eb9f32</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Puretrop-Fruits-22-Cr-Buyback-Approved-Tender-Offer-Starts-March-23/699c4630ee97f501b0eb9f32</guid><description>Puretrop Fruits Limited has approved a share buyback program of up to 11,00,000 equity shares at ₹200 per share, totalling ₹22 crore. The buyback, commencing around March 23, 2026, via tender offer, aims to return surplus cash to shareholders and potentially boost Earnings Per Share (EPS). This move follows recent strong quarterly profits, though longer-term growth metrics show mixed performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:21:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4630ee97f501b0eb9f31_1771849400182.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sebi's PMS Review Signals Maturation, Stricter Oversight Ahead</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sebis-PMS-Review-Signals-Maturation-Stricter-Oversight-Ahead/699c44aaee97f501b0eb9cc4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sebis-PMS-Review-Signals-Maturation-Stricter-Oversight-Ahead/699c44aaee97f501b0eb9cc4</guid><description>India's Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) is undertaking a significant review of its Portfolio Managers Regulations, with proposed changes anticipated by its June 2026 board meeting. This initiative reflects the sector's rapid expansion, now managing Rs 10.5 trillion, and aims to bolster governance, curb mis-selling, and enhance investor protection. The tightened oversight could lead to industry consolidation, favoring well-capitalized entities and potentially impacting smaller players' competitive edge.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:14:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c44aaee97f501b0eb9cc3_1771849072165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MSMEs Pivot Credit to Working Capital, Signaling Maturation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MSMEs-Pivot-Credit-to-Working-Capital-Signaling-Maturation/699c4431ee97f501b0eb9bb9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MSMEs-Pivot-Credit-to-Working-Capital-Signaling-Maturation/699c4431ee97f501b0eb9bb9</guid><description>Micro, small, and medium enterprises are increasingly deploying credit lines for working capital management, specifically for receivables and inventory financing, rather than upfront capacity expansion. This trend, identified as a sign of maturation and formalization, is prompting lenders to redesign products into flexible, cash-flow-based facilities. Real-time risk assessment and a move away from informal credit are shaping a more dynamic and resilient MSME financial ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:12:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4431ee97f501b0eb9bb8_1771849099313.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Pivot: India's Key Exports Shielded by Sectoral Exemptions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Pivot-Indias-Key-Exports-Shielded-by-Sectoral-Exemptions/699c4413ee97f501b0eb9b67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Pivot-Indias-Key-Exports-Shielded-by-Sectoral-Exemptions/699c4413ee97f501b0eb9b67</guid><description>The United States is implementing revised tariff measures, allowing over $34 billion in Indian exports to remain largely tariff-free, primarily in the pharmaceutical, electronics, and civil aviation sectors. This strategic recalibration, enacted via Section 122 of the Trade Act of 1974, follows a Supreme Court decision that altered the US tariff landscape. While overall trade volumes show robust growth, the selective nature of these exemptions signals a shift from broad levies to targeted trade management, potentially bolstering India's competitive position in high-value export markets and mitigating risks from previous broad-based tariffs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:12:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4413ee97f501b0eb9b66_1771849350505.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motherson's Advanced Lighting Plant Promises Tech Edge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mothersons-Advanced-Lighting-Plant-Promises-Tech-Edge/699c440eee97f501b0eb9aed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mothersons-Advanced-Lighting-Plant-Promises-Tech-Edge/699c440eee97f501b0eb9aed</guid><description>Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd's joint venture, Marelli Motherson Automotive Lighting India Pvt Ltd (MMLI), inaugurated a new 8,200 sq meter automotive lighting facility in Sanand, Gujarat. This plant will manufacture advanced exterior lighting systems, including India's first single-piece, end-to-end Daytime Running Lights (DRL) and Rear Combination Lamps (RCL), alongside the localization of the slimmest headlamp module. The facility integrates global innovation with local manufacturing, leveraging Motherson's 50% stake in the JV with Marelli Europe S.p.A. Sustainable operations are emphasized with rooftop solar power. The announcement saw a modest 1.08% rise in Samvardhana Motherson's share price.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Economy: Stable Momentum Masks Divergent Trends</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Economy-Stable-Momentum-Masks-Divergent-Trends/699c439fee97f501b0eb9a1b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Economy-Stable-Momentum-Masks-Divergent-Trends/699c439fee97f501b0eb9a1b</guid><description>India's economic momentum held at 51.2 in January 2026, bolstered by a 6.2% rise in Goods and Services Tax (GST) collections to ₹1.93 lakh crore, driven by resilient rural sales. However, this stability is juxtaposed by rising urban and youth unemployment rates and a slowdown in industrial activity, evidenced by easing core sector growth to 4%. Exports saw marginal growth, contributing to a widening trade deficit. Upcoming GDP revisions are keenly watched for a clearer economic picture.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:10:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c439fee97f501b0eb9a1a_1771848819110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Torrent Diagnostics Enters Crowded Indian Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Torrent-Diagnostics-Enters-Crowded-Indian-Market/699c438aee97f501b0eb99a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Torrent-Diagnostics-Enters-Crowded-Indian-Market/699c438aee97f501b0eb99a6</guid><description>Torrent Group has launched Torrent Diagnostics in Navi Mumbai, inaugurating India's claimed largest National Reference Laboratory. The 100,000 sq ft facility spans 15 disciplines with 3,500+ tests, featuring advanced tech like NGS and TEM. This move positions Torrent in the rapidly growing Indian diagnostics market, projected at $15-16 billion by FY30 with a 12% CAGR, driven by preventive care and technological adoption. However, it enters a highly competitive, fragmented landscape, facing established players and margin pressures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:09:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c438aee97f501b0eb99a5_1771848754199.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Energy Transition: Multi-Speed Pace Creates Uneven Investment Landscape</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Transition-Multi-Speed-Pace-Creates-Uneven-Investment-Landscape/699c4371ee97f501b0eb9988</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Energy-Transition-Multi-Speed-Pace-Creates-Uneven-Investment-Landscape/699c4371ee97f501b0eb9988</guid><description>India's push for clean electricity is accelerating, yet progress is uneven. A recent analysis by IEEFA and Ember highlights a "multi-speed" transition, with leading states like Karnataka and Delhi outperforming in renewable deployment and grid readiness, while others like West Bengal and Jharkhand lag significantly. This divergence, driven by resource endowments and institutional capacity, necessitates targeted policy interventions and presents complex challenges for sustained sector-wide growth and investment. Utilities' financial health remains a critical bottleneck for many states, impacting their ability to procure renewable energy effectively.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:09:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4371ee97f501b0eb9987_1771848911502.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Hospitals Face Contractual Shake-up After Court Ruling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Hospitals-Face-Contractual-Shake-up-After-Court-Ruling/699c42eeee97f501b0eb984b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Hospitals-Face-Contractual-Shake-up-After-Court-Ruling/699c42eeee97f501b0eb984b</guid><description>The Madras High Court has deemed non-compete and non-solicitation clauses in doctor employment contracts unlawful, citing violations of the Indian Contract Act. This decision, which imposed ₹1 lakh in costs on MIOT Hospitals, challenges established hospital practices and signals a move towards greater physician autonomy. The ruling arrives amid increasing regulatory scrutiny on the healthcare sector, impacting operational strategies and physician retention models.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:07:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c42eeee97f501b0eb984a_1771848630272.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPL Ltd Board Shake-up: Kripalu Named Director, Bakshi Tapped as MD &amp; CEO</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EPL-Ltd-Board-Shake-up-Kripalu-Named-Director-Bakshi-Tapped-as-MD-and-CEO/699c42ecee97f501b0eb9834</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EPL-Ltd-Board-Shake-up-Kripalu-Named-Director-Bakshi-Tapped-as-MD-and-CEO/699c42ecee97f501b0eb9834</guid><description>EPL Limited is undergoing a major leadership overhaul. Members will vote on appointing Anand Kripalu as a Non-Executive Director and Hemant Bakshi as the new Managing Director &amp; Global Chief Executive Officer. These appointments, effective early 2026, signify a planned succession and strategic strengthening of the company's top management.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:07:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c42ecee97f501b0eb9833_1771849595465.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cheesecake Factory Bakery's India Push: High Stakes in Premium Dessert Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cheesecake-Factory-Bakerys-India-Push-High-Stakes-in-Premium-Dessert-Market/699c4299ee97f501b0eb96f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cheesecake-Factory-Bakerys-India-Push-High-Stakes-in-Premium-Dessert-Market/699c4299ee97f501b0eb96f8</guid><description>The Cheesecake Factory Bakery is launching an ambitious expansion in India via a partnership with The Gourmet Café, planning 55 outlets with a $60 million investment over five years. This move targets India's fast-growing premium dessert market, projecting ₹200-250 crore in revenue. However, this aggressive strategy confronts significant challenges, including intense local competition, consumer price sensitivity, evolving health trends, and a complex regulatory environment, all while the parent company trades with a P/E ratio around 19-20.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:05:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4299ee97f501b0eb96f7_1771848976110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Noida Airport Inauguration Signals Uttar Pradesh's Mega Infrastructure Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airport-Inauguration-Signals-Uttar-Pradeshs-Mega-Infrastructure-Push/699c428dee97f501b0eb96e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airport-Inauguration-Signals-Uttar-Pradeshs-Mega-Infrastructure-Push/699c428dee97f501b0eb96e1</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi is set to inaugurate the Noida International Airport in Jewar next month, a project slated to become India's largest. The expansion from two to five planned runways underscores a strategic vision, backed by substantial government investment and a public-private partnership model. This development is positioned to catalyze significant economic growth, job creation, and regional transformation in Uttar Pradesh, though its ultimate scale will be benchmarked against global aviation giants. The project's success hinges on navigating the complexities inherent in large-scale PPP infrastructure developments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:05:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c428dee97f501b0eb96e0_1771848502540.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Pharma Ambition: Quality vs. Scale in Global Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Pharma-Ambition-Quality-vs-Scale-in-Global-Shift/699c4274ee97f501b0eb96be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Pharma-Ambition-Quality-vs-Scale-in-Global-Shift/699c4274ee97f501b0eb96be</guid><description>India's pharmaceutical sector is pivoting from its 'pharmacy of the world' role to becoming an innovator, backed by ambitious government initiatives like Biopharma Shakti (₹10,000 Cr) and PRIP (₹5,000 Cr). Minister J.P. Nadda emphasized anchoring global supply chains through quality, reliability, and trust. However, the sector grapples with historical USFDA scrutiny, lower R&amp;D investment relative to global giants, and the complex task of establishing unquestionable trust amid geopolitical shifts and market diversification efforts. The Nifty Pharma Index shows resilience, trading at a P/E of 35.77, but future leadership hinges on overcoming these fundamental quality and innovation challenges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:05:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c4274ee97f501b0eb96bd_1771848683847.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola's Battery Gamble: A High-Risk Pivot Amidst Industrial Giants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Olas-Battery-Gamble-A-High-Risk-Pivot-Amidst-Industrial-Giants/699c41feee97f501b0eb9603</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Olas-Battery-Gamble-A-High-Risk-Pivot-Amidst-Industrial-Giants/699c41feee97f501b0eb9603</guid><description>Ola Electric's ambitious pivot into battery manufacturing is met with intense competition and significant execution challenges. While bolstered by government PLI schemes, the company faces industrial behemoths like Reliance, Tata, and JSW, who are aggressively scaling up gigafactories with substantial capacity plans dwarfing Ola's roadmap. Investor concerns mount over Ola's history of ceding ground to competitors and strategic pivots, coupled with operational issues and cash burn, casting doubt on its ability to compete effectively against well-capitalized incumbents in the booming Indian EV battery market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:03:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c41feee97f501b0eb9602_1771848498848.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mojro Secures $3M Series A Amidst Logistics Tech Funding Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mojro-Secures-3M-Series-A-Amidst-Logistics-Tech-Funding-Squeeze/699c410bee97f501b0eb944b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mojro-Secures-3M-Series-A-Amidst-Logistics-Tech-Funding-Squeeze/699c410bee97f501b0eb944b</guid><description>Mojro, an AI-driven B2B SaaS platform for logistics planning and optimization, has closed a $3 million Series A funding round led by IAN Alpha Fund. The capital injection, which also saw participation from existing investors including 1Crowd, is designated for expansion into the US and Southeast Asia, enhancement of its AI-powered platform, and team growth. Founded in 2016, Mojro differentiates itself with over 60% of its revenue originating from international markets and a technology stack combining advanced operations research and machine learning.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c410bee97f501b0eb944a_1771848441373.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fractal Analytics Launches PiEvolve AI, Sets MLE-Bench Records</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-Launches-PiEvolve-AI-Sets-MLE-Bench-Records/699c3ddeee97f501b0eb90e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-Launches-PiEvolve-AI-Sets-MLE-Bench-Records/699c3ddeee97f501b0eb90e3</guid><description>Fractal Analytics has unveiled PiEvolve, its autonomous machine learning engine, demonstrating top-tier performance on OpenAI's MLE-Bench. The launch highlights Fractal's commitment to AI innovation, achieving high scores with remarkable computational efficiency. This positions the company at the forefront of enterprise AI solutions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:45:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3ddeee97f501b0eb90e2_1771847482229.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Patel Engg Secures ₹910 Cr Dam Contract Amidst Financial Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Patel-Engg-Secures-910-Cr-Dam-Contract-Amidst-Financial-Risks/699c3dcdee97f501b0eb90c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Patel-Engg-Secures-910-Cr-Dam-Contract-Amidst-Financial-Risks/699c3dcdee97f501b0eb90c6</guid><description>Patel Engineering Limited (PEL) has been declared the lowest bidder for the ₹910.08 crore Renukaji Dam Project, reinforcing its substantial order book exceeding ₹15,123 crore. This award aligns with sector tailwinds in hydropower development. However, PEL's high promoter pledging (86.6%), significant contingent liabilities (~₹2,681 crore), and modest ROE raise financial concerns. While analysts present a mixed view with price targets varying widely, cautious observation is advised given past stock volatility despite contract wins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:45:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3dcdee97f501b0eb90c5_1771848144500.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCC Concept Gets NSE Listing Approval; Trading Starts Feb 25</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/TCC-Concept-Gets-NSE-Listing-Approval-Trading-Starts-Feb-25/699c3dc1ee97f501b0eb90ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/TCC-Concept-Gets-NSE-Listing-Approval-Trading-Starts-Feb-25/699c3dc1ee97f501b0eb90ae</guid><description>TCC Concept Limited has received official approval from the National Stock Exchange (NSE) for listing and trading of its equity shares. The company's shares will commence trading on the NSE from February 25, 2026, covering over 4.75 crore shares. This move is set to enhance the company's market accessibility and visibility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:45:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3dc1ee97f501b0eb90ad_1771847241953.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Microsoft bets on AI to upskill engineers, not replace them</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microsoft-bets-on-AI-to-upskill-engineers-not-replace-them/699c3d2aee97f501b0eb8fa8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microsoft-bets-on-AI-to-upskill-engineers-not-replace-them/699c3d2aee97f501b0eb8fa8</guid><description>Microsoft's President Brad Smith asserts that artificial intelligence will augment, not replace, software engineers and IT professionals, emphasizing skill enhancement over job elimination. This strategy aims to 'uplevel' the profession by automating routine tasks, freeing up developers for complex design, architecture, and security roles. Unlike competitors like Amazon, which anticipates workforce reductions due to AI-driven efficiency, Microsoft's approach targets increased productivity and potentially higher wages for skilled workers. The company's P/E ratio of approximately 24.85, lower than its historical average, suggests investors are scrutinizing the profitability of its significant AI investments, particularly amidst recent market volatility affecting tech stocks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:42:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3d2aee97f501b0eb8fa7_1771847333910.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Demand Stable? India's Bullion Market Faces Global Price Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Demand-Stable-Indias-Bullion-Market-Faces-Global-Price-Pressures/699c3c71ee97f501b0eb8e16</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Demand-Stable-Indias-Bullion-Market-Faces-Global-Price-Pressures/699c3c71ee97f501b0eb8e16</guid><description>India's Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman stated gold demand remains within traditional bounds, unaffected by price spikes, supported by a robust external sector. However, global trends indicate aggressive central bank accumulation and geopolitical factors are the primary price drivers. While household purchases persist, driven by cultural factors, a significant volume decline in Indian gold imports from April-December 2025, despite a value increase, suggests price sensitivity. Forecasts place gold prices between $4,700-$6,500 for 2026, with persistent demand from official reserves and investors seeking hedges against inflation and currency depreciation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:39:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3c71ee97f501b0eb8e15_1771848050253.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PAN Misuse Threatens Indian Digital Economy's Trust</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/PAN-Misuse-Threatens-Indian-Digital-Economys-Trust/699c3c31ee97f501b0eb8d48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/PAN-Misuse-Threatens-Indian-Digital-Economys-Trust/699c3c31ee97f501b0eb8d48</guid><description>Unnoticed PAN misuse for loans threatens India's digital economy. Unfamiliar loan inquiries and credit score dips signal identity fraud, impacting lenders and consumer trust. Proactive credit report checks are crucial, but systemic solutions are needed to combat widespread data leaks and protect financial integrity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:38:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3c31ee97f501b0eb8d47_1771846850423.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tariffs Roil Markets: Bitcoin, Equities Dive; Gold Rallies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Tariffs-Roil-Markets-Bitcoin-Equities-Dive-Gold-Rallies/699c3c22ee97f501b0eb8d29</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Tariffs-Roil-Markets-Bitcoin-Equities-Dive-Gold-Rallies/699c3c22ee97f501b0eb8d29</guid><description>On Monday, February 23, 2026, the cryptocurrency market experienced significant volatility, mirroring U.S. equity futures. Bitcoin tumbled sharply to $64,270 shortly after midnight UTC before recovering to $66,300, a pattern seen in S&amp;P 500 futures. This sell-off was driven by heightened geopolitical concerns, including President Trump's announcement of new 15% global tariffs and increased military presence near Iran, which fueled a rush toward safe-haven assets like gold. Altcoins, such as Solana, succumbed to low liquidity, dropping 7-8% and contributing to $270 million in liquidations. Gold futures, conversely, rose to their highest level since late January, with silver tracking its movement, showcasing a flight to safety.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:38:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3c22ee97f501b0eb8d28_1771847010348.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Carlsberg Eyes $700M India IPO Amidst High Local Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Carlsberg-Eyes-700M-India-IPO-Amidst-High-Local-Valuations/699c3c02ee97f501b0eb8cc9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Carlsberg-Eyes-700M-India-IPO-Amidst-High-Local-Valuations/699c3c02ee97f501b0eb8cc9</guid><description>Carlsberg A/S is advancing plans for a potential $700 million initial public offering (IPO) of its Indian subsidiary. The move aims to leverage India's high local market valuations, driven by strong demographic trends and a growing appetite for premium beverages. Appointed advisors Kotak Mahindra Capital, JPMorgan, and Citigroup will guide the process, with a DRHP possibly filed by May. Carlsberg India, the country's second-largest brewer with a 22% market share and $1.1 billion in revenue, seeks to unlock value in a rapidly expanding market, though intense competition and regulatory hurdles persist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:37:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3c02ee97f501b0eb8cc8_1771846820101.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Collateral Clampdown Sparks Broker Pushback, SEBI Review</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/RBIs-Collateral-Clampdown-Sparks-Broker-Pushback-SEBI-Review/699c3bf9ee97f501b0eb8caa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/RBIs-Collateral-Clampdown-Sparks-Broker-Pushback-SEBI-Review/699c3bf9ee97f501b0eb8caa</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's (RBI) stringent new lending rules for capital market intermediaries (CMIs), effective April 1, 2026, mandate 100% collateral for bank credit and prohibit funding for proprietary trading. These measures, aimed at reducing systemic risk, have raised alarm among stockbrokers citing increased costs and reduced liquidity. SEBI Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey has confirmed SEBI is reviewing broker feedback, though the RBI maintains a firm stance, indicating no immediate policy changes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:37:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3bf9ee97f501b0eb8ca9_1771846810778.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Power Sector: Tech Surge Meets DISCOM Financial Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Sector-Tech-Surge-Meets-DISCOM-Financial-Strain/699c3b26ee97f501b0eb8a79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Sector-Tech-Surge-Meets-DISCOM-Financial-Strain/699c3b26ee97f501b0eb8a79</guid><description>India's power sector is advancing rapidly with AI integration and a significant shift to green energy, boosting generation capacity and transmission networks. However, the Comptroller and Auditor General (CAG) K Sanjay Murthy stressed the critical need for operational efficiencies and financial sustainability among Distribution Companies (DISCOMs). Despite early signs of recovery, the deep-seated financial vulnerabilities of DISCOMs present a significant risk, potentially undermining the sector's modernization and ambitious growth targets. This dynamic underscores a key tension between technological progress and underlying financial fragility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:33:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3b26ee97f501b0eb8a78_1771846818849.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airtel Bets Big on Lending: Rs 20K Cr for NBFC Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airtel-Bets-Big-on-Lending-Rs-20K-Cr-for-NBFC-Push/699c3b12ee97f501b0eb8a60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airtel-Bets-Big-on-Lending-Rs-20K-Cr-for-NBFC-Push/699c3b12ee97f501b0eb8a60</guid><description>Bharti Airtel is injecting Rs 20,000 crore into its newly licensed NBFC, Airtel Money Limited, over the next few years. This strategic move aims to build a large-scale digital lending platform, leveraging the company's extensive customer base and data analytics capabilities to address India's significant formal credit gap. Airtel will hold a 70% stake in the NBFC, with the promoter group holding the remainder. The company's existing digital credit engine has already disbursed over ₹9,000 crore.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:33:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3b12ee97f501b0eb8a5f_1771846542884.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Enhances Security Post ₹590 Cr Govt Fund Flaw</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Enhances-Security-Post-590-Cr-Govt-Fund-Flaw/699c3b0bee97f501b0eb8a45</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Enhances-Security-Post-590-Cr-Govt-Fund-Flaw/699c3b0bee97f501b0eb8a45</guid><description>IDFC First Bank is introducing advanced system-driven controls for high-value branch transactions, mandating digital customer confirmation via its mobile app. This response follows the identification of a ₹590 crore financial discrepancy involving Haryana government accounts. A KPMG forensic audit is ongoing to ascertain accountability, with preliminary findings suggesting the issue was confined to operational levels and did not involve senior management.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:33:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c3b0bee97f501b0eb8a44_1771846545784.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>