<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:49:46 +0000</pubDate><item><title>AI Shift: Auto Insurers Face Divergent Futures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/AI-Shift-Auto-Insurers-Face-Divergent-Futures/699800c9057e346edab3c7bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/AI-Shift-Auto-Insurers-Face-Divergent-Futures/699800c9057e346edab3c7bf</guid><description>The rise of artificial intelligence and autonomous vehicles is creating a stark divergence in the auto insurance sector. Incumbents such as Progressive and Allstate, heavily reliant on traditional auto insurance models, face significant headwinds as accident prediction shifts from human error to technology. Their market valuations reflect these concerns, with lower P/E ratios and cautious analyst sentiment. Conversely, specialized insurers and reinsurers like RenaissanceRe, Hamilton, and Kinsale Capital are navigating this transition with different business models, potentially offering more resilient or specialized avenues in the evolving insurance landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:35:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699800c9057e346edab3c7be_1771569535609.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Federal Bank Tax Refund Fuels Rally, But Sector Headwinds Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Federal-Bank-Tax-Refund-Fuels-Rally-But-Sector-Headwinds-Loom/699800a7057e346edab3c79e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Federal-Bank-Tax-Refund-Fuels-Rally-But-Sector-Headwinds-Loom/699800a7057e346edab3c79e</guid><description>Federal Bank shares climbed following the announcement of a ₹686 crore tax refund from the Income Tax Department, bolstering its financial position. This event reinforces its recent Q3FY26 performance, which saw a 9% rise in net profit. Despite strong historical outperformance and an optimistic analyst consensus rating, the bank faces broader sector challenges including moderating credit growth and margin pressures that warrant cautious observation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:35:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699800a7057e346edab3c79d_1771569501960.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paras Defence Deepens Niche with Thermal Solutions Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Paras-Defence-Deepens-Niche-with-Thermal-Solutions-Acquisition/6998009a057e346edab3c762</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Paras-Defence-Deepens-Niche-with-Thermal-Solutions-Acquisition/6998009a057e346edab3c762</guid><description>Paras Defence and Space Technologies' share price saw an uptick following its acquisition of a 49% stake in Himanshi Thermal Solutions Private Limited. This move signifies a strategic push into vertical integration, specifically targeting advanced thermal management and precision metal fabrication crucial for high-technology defense and aerospace applications. Himanshi Thermal's expertise in liquid cold plates and specialized heat treatment is expected to bolster Paras Defence's capabilities in mission-critical systems, complementing its existing product lines. The acquisition aims to unlock new growth avenues by enhancing system-level integration and reducing reliance on external suppliers in a sector demanding stringent precision and long qualification cycles. Analyst views suggest this is a capability-led integration, critical for the performance and reliability of increasingly dense defense electronics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:35:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998009a057e346edab3c761_1771569456965.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KPI Green Energy: Project Wins Masking Market Pressure?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Project-Wins-Masking-Market-Pressure/69980099057e346edab3c74b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Project-Wins-Masking-Market-Pressure/69980099057e346edab3c74b</guid><description>KPI Green Energy announced the successful commissioning of a 92.4 MW wind power project for Ayana Renewable Power Four and secured substantial new orders from Adani Group companies. Despite this operational momentum and a strong project pipeline, KPI Green's stock has experienced a notable decline over the past month, trading below its peers and historical performance benchmarks. The company's valuation metrics, particularly its P/E ratio, appear competitive against the Indian market and sector averages, yet technical indicators suggest investor caution. This report examines the divergence between KPI Green's expanding capacity and its market valuation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:35:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69980099057e346edab3c74a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UBL Bets on Malt Security: Rajasthan Malthouse Eyes 2028</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UBL-Bets-on-Malt-Security-Rajasthan-Malthouse-Eyes-2028/69980032057e346edab3c66e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UBL-Bets-on-Malt-Security-Rajasthan-Malthouse-Eyes-2028/69980032057e346edab3c66e</guid><description>United Breweries Limited (UBL) is investing significantly with Soufflet Malt in a new malthouse in South Rajasthan, targeting a mid-2028 commissioning. This strategic move aims to strengthen backward integration and secure malt supply for flagship brands like Kingfisher, creating 400 jobs and engaging over 50,000 farmers. The initiative signals long-term growth conviction, though it occurs as UBL trades at a premium valuation, prompting cautious analyst sentiment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:33:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69980032057e346edab3c66d_1771569316004.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amazon Tops Walmart in Revenue, But AWS is the Real King</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazon-Tops-Walmart-in-Revenue-But-AWS-is-the-Real-King/6997ffaa057e346edab3c53b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazon-Tops-Walmart-in-Revenue-But-AWS-is-the-Real-King/6997ffaa057e346edab3c53b</guid><description>Amazon.com Inc. has officially claimed the top spot for annual revenue, surpassing Walmart with $716.9 billion for its fiscal year ending December 2025. This milestone, however, is largely attributed to the powerhouse performance of Amazon Web Services (AWS), which contributed approximately $128.7 billion in sales, a sector where Walmart does not compete. While Amazon's e-commerce scale is immense, attracting 2.7 billion monthly visits, the "revenue victory" highlights the significant impact of its cloud computing division on its overall financial standing, a stark contrast to Walmart's retail-centric model. Investor sentiment, measured by market capitalization, continues to favor technology giants like Nvidia, which holds a market cap exceeding $4.5 trillion, dwarfing both retail behemoths.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:31:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997ffaa057e346edab3c53a_1771569194523.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NFIL Stock: Growth Forecasts Meet Valuation Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/NFIL-Stock-Growth-Forecasts-Meet-Valuation-Hurdles/6997ffa9057e346edab3c524</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/NFIL-Stock-Growth-Forecasts-Meet-Valuation-Hurdles/6997ffa9057e346edab3c524</guid><description>Navin Fluorine International (NFIL) is poised for multi-year expansion driven by its robust CDMO pipeline, refrigerant gas capacity increases, and sustained agrochemical momentum. Brokerage PL Capital maintains an 'Accumulate' rating with a target of ₹7,038, projecting an 18% revenue CAGR through FY28. However, the company must navigate stretched valuations and the critical execution of significant future investments, including the scaling Chemours partnership for advanced cooling fluids.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997ffa9057e346edab3c523_1771569312110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Brazil Forge Critical Minerals &amp; AI Alliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Brazil-Forge-Critical-Minerals-and-AI-Alliance/6997ff4d057e346edab3c4ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Brazil-Forge-Critical-Minerals-and-AI-Alliance/6997ff4d057e346edab3c4ba</guid><description>Brazil and India are escalating bilateral cooperation, focusing on securing a larger share in the critical minerals value chain and shaping the future of artificial intelligence. This strategic alignment aims to counter existing global power structures in resource extraction and technological development, with both nations pushing for more inclusive governance frameworks and value-added processing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:29:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997ff4d057e346edab3c4b9_1771569132329.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPL Consolidates Crop Protection Amid Debt Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/UPL-Consolidates-Crop-Protection-Amid-Debt-Headwinds/6997feb9057e346edab3c416</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/UPL-Consolidates-Crop-Protection-Amid-Debt-Headwinds/6997feb9057e346edab3c416</guid><description>UPL Limited is undertaking a significant reorganization, merging its global and local crop protection businesses to enhance operational focus and simplify its corporate structure, particularly given overlapping shareholders like ADIA and TPG. This strategic move aims to unlock value and navigate the substantial debt incurred from the $4 billion Arysta acquisition, amidst modest projected revenue growth for FY2025-26. The company's subsidiary, Advanta, is also pursuing an IPO, potentially raising around $500 million.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:27:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997feb9057e346edab3c415_1771568962478.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Qualcomm Taps India for Auto Chips, Diversifies Supply Chain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Taps-India-for-Auto-Chips-Diversifies-Supply-Chain/6997fe44057e346edab3c39f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Taps-India-for-Auto-Chips-Diversifies-Supply-Chain/6997fe44057e346edab3c39f</guid><description>Qualcomm Technologies, Inc. has inked a deal with Tata Electronics to produce automotive semiconductor modules at Tata's new OSAT facility in Assam, India. This collaboration marks a significant stride for Qualcomm in diversifying its manufacturing footprint away from traditional East Asian hubs, addressing global supply chain vulnerabilities. For Tata Electronics, it signifies a crucial step into advanced semiconductor packaging, targeting the burgeoning automotive and AI sectors, aligning with India's 'Make in India' initiative.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:25:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997fe44057e346edab3c39e_1771568858844.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold's Technical Sell-Off Clashes with Robust 2026 Bullish Forecasts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Technical-Sell-Off-Clashes-with-Robust-2026-Bullish-Forecasts/6997fcdd057e346edab3c2e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Technical-Sell-Off-Clashes-with-Robust-2026-Bullish-Forecasts/6997fcdd057e346edab3c2e3</guid><description>Gold futures are experiencing immediate downside pressure, breaking below key technical support levels and prompting a 'sell-on-rise' strategy around ₹1,55,500. This short-term bearish sentiment stands in stark contrast to the overwhelmingly bullish outlook from major financial institutions, which collectively forecast significant price appreciation for gold throughout 2026, driven by persistent inflation concerns, central bank demand, and geopolitical uncertainties. The divergence highlights a potential market inflection point where immediate technical signals conflict with longer-term fundamental drivers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:19:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997fcdd057e346edab3c2e2_1771568469794.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Novartis US Expansion: Political Claim Meets Corporate Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novartis-US-Expansion-Political-Claim-Meets-Corporate-Reality/6997f952057e346edab3c032</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novartis-US-Expansion-Political-Claim-Meets-Corporate-Reality/6997f952057e346edab3c032</guid><description>President Donald Trump claimed Novartis is constructing 11 U.S. plants due to his tariff policies, a statement made during a Georgia rally. Novartis, however, offered a more measured response, confirming ongoing "progress" and "groundbreakings" for facilities in North Carolina, California, and a new radioligand therapy site in Florida. The company did not explicitly corroborate the specific number of plants or directly attribute the investments to the administration's trade measures, echoing its prior $23 billion commitment last year. This divergence prompts a closer look at the actual drivers of corporate expansion versus political messaging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:04:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f952057e346edab3c031_1771567695607.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pharma Stocks Rally: Lupin, Biocon, Torrent Pharma Show Technical Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-Stocks-Rally-Lupin-Biocon-Torrent-Pharma-Show-Technical-Strength/6997f93c057e346edab3c016</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-Stocks-Rally-Lupin-Biocon-Torrent-Pharma-Show-Technical-Strength/6997f93c057e346edab3c016</guid><description>The Indian pharmaceutical sector is outperforming broader markets, with the Nifty Pharma index gaining 3.5% in February. Select large-cap stocks like Lupin, Biocon, and Torrent Pharmaceuticals are exhibiting robust technical setups and positive analyst sentiment. Lupin is capitalizing on emerging therapy opportunities, Biocon is demonstrating strength in biosimilars, and Torrent Pharma has achieved new highs following strong quarterly results. However, sector-wide challenges such as U.S. pricing pressures and increasing competition necessitate a cautious approach.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:03:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997f93c057e346edab3c015.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCLTech Taps Nvidia for AI Edge: VisionX 2.0 Launched</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTech-Taps-Nvidia-for-AI-Edge-VisionX-20-Launched/6997f934057e346edab3bffd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTech-Taps-Nvidia-for-AI-Edge-VisionX-20-Launched/6997f934057e346edab3bffd</guid><description>HCLTech unveiled VisionX 2.0, an advanced multi-modal AI edge platform developed in collaboration with Nvidia. This platform integrates sophisticated computer vision, vision language models, and edge-optimized generative AI, leveraging Nvidia's AI computing stack for real-time inference and enhanced security in industrial settings. The move comes as HCLTech’s MD foresees AI-driven deflation but also significant new growth opportunities, positioning the company to capitalize on evolving market demands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:03:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f934057e346edab3bffc_1771567682130.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Data Patterns Soars on Defence Contracts, But Risks Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Data-Patterns-Soars-on-Defence-Contracts-But-Risks-Emerge/6997f927057e346edab3bfb4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Data-Patterns-Soars-on-Defence-Contracts-But-Risks-Emerge/6997f927057e346edab3bfb4</guid><description>Data Patterns' shares rallied on robust Q3 FY26 results, marked by 48% revenue growth and an all-time high order book of ₹1,868 crore, propelled by defence sector modernization. However, an 84% year-on-year decline in the Development segment, coupled with a high P/E ratio of approximately 66, signals potential headwinds beneath the surface of strong execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:03:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f927057e346edab3bfb3_1771567630896.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quant Strategies: India's Market Prowess Amidst Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Quant-Strategies-Indias-Market-Prowess-Amidst-Volatility/6997f91b057e346edab3bf99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Quant-Strategies-Indias-Market-Prowess-Amidst-Volatility/6997f91b057e346edab3bf99</guid><description>Quantitative investment strategies are increasingly influencing India's equity markets, offering a systematic, data-driven approach. UTI AMC, through its dynamic multi-factor framework, leverages algorithms to rotate between fundamental and market-driven factors, aiming for adaptive portfolio construction. While quant strategies promise discipline, their effectiveness in India is highly sensitive to market regimes and prone to operational challenges like high turnover and liquidity management. Despite these headwinds, the Indian quant market is poised for significant growth, though specific fund strategies face performance scrutiny and regulatory oversight.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:03:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997f91b057e346edab3bf98.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kalpataru Projects: Upgrade Masks Margin Squeeze &amp; High Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kalpataru-Projects-Upgrade-Masks-Margin-Squeeze-and-High-Valuation/6997f91b057e346edab3bf82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kalpataru-Projects-Upgrade-Masks-Margin-Squeeze-and-High-Valuation/6997f91b057e346edab3bf82</guid><description>Anand Rathi initiated a 'Buy' rating on Kalpataru Projects International with a price target of ₹1,408, citing robust order inflows totaling ₹19,500 crore YTD FY26 and improving balance sheet metrics, including a ₹454 crore YoY reduction in net debt to ₹2,240 crore. However, a deeper look reveals a Q3 FY26 consolidated revenue of ₹6,665 crore and a concerning contraction in operating margins, alongside a P/E ratio of approximately 23x, which appears stretched when benchmarked against leaner competitors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:03:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f91b057e346edab3bf81_1771567585946.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amazon Edges Walmart in Revenue as AI Race Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazon-Edges-Walmart-in-Revenue-as-AI-Race-Intensifies/6997f8da057e346edab3bef2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazon-Edges-Walmart-in-Revenue-as-AI-Race-Intensifies/6997f8da057e346edab3bef2</guid><description>Amazon has reported higher annual revenue than Walmart for the first time, with $716.9 billion against Walmart's $713.2 billion. This milestone is overshadowed by the escalating AI competition, where Amazon is investing heavily in internal infrastructure ($200 billion for 2026), drawing investor scrutiny and causing stock volatility. Walmart, conversely, is pursuing a partnership-driven AI strategy with firms like OpenAI and Google, aiming for quicker integration and capital efficiency. This divergence in approach is redefining their rivalry.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:02:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f8da057e346edab3bef1_1771567448838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW Enters EV Bus Market Amidst Passenger Vehicle Delays</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-Enters-EV-Bus-Market-Amidst-Passenger-Vehicle-Delays/6997f8a5057e346edab3be94</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-Enters-EV-Bus-Market-Amidst-Passenger-Vehicle-Delays/6997f8a5057e346edab3be94</guid><description>JSW Greentech has achieved a crucial CMVR Type Approval Certificate from ARAI for its inaugural 12-metre electric bus, enabling entry into India's commercial vehicle sector. This move aligns with the group's broader sustainable mobility ambitions, though it contrasts with reported delays in its passenger vehicle segment due to import regulatory issues. The electric bus, the JSW 12M 51+D AC SDX, is designed for high-capacity urban transit and will be produced at a new Maharashtra facility. This development occurs within a rapidly expanding Indian EV market, heavily supported by government incentives for both buses and trucks, yet faces intense competition from established players.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:01:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f8a5057e346edab3be93_1771567396733.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI-Powered Probe Uncovers Rs 13K Cr Tax Fraud in Indian Restaurants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Powered-Probe-Uncovers-Rs-13K-Cr-Tax-Fraud-in-Indian-Restaurants/6997f856057e346edab3bdc5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Powered-Probe-Uncovers-Rs-13K-Cr-Tax-Fraud-in-Indian-Restaurants/6997f856057e346edab3bdc5</guid><description>A routine tax check in Hyderabad has escalated into a nationwide investigation, revealing widespread tax evasion by restaurants. Leveraging AI and advanced data analytics, tax officials reconstructed over ₹13,000 crore in deleted cash transactions from an estimated ₹2.43 lakh crore billed over six years. This sophisticated probe underscores the growing efficacy of digital forensic tools in detecting sophisticated financial fraud, potentially impacting compliance across the hospitality sector and beyond. The Central Board of Direct Taxes (CBDT) is now expanding its technological capabilities to tackle evolving evasion tactics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:59:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997f856057e346edab3bdc4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCG: Growth Fuels Expansion Amidst KKR's Strategic Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HCG-Growth-Fuels-Expansion-Amidst-KKRs-Strategic-Shift/6997f7ca057e346edab3bcf3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HCG-Growth-Fuels-Expansion-Amidst-KKRs-Strategic-Shift/6997f7ca057e346edab3bcf3</guid><description>Healthcare Global Enterprises Ltd (HCG) posted a 13% year-over-year revenue increase in Q3 FY26, driven by an 8% rise in patient volumes and a 5% boost in Average Revenue Per Patient (ARPP) to ₹84,208. EBITDA grew 24% to ₹110 crore with margins expanding to 17.3%. However, EBT declined 53% to a negative ₹6 crore due to higher depreciation and finance costs. The company plans 1,000 new beds and a rights issue up to ₹420 crore to strengthen its balance sheet, a move expected to enhance financial flexibility. KKR's new promoter status signals potential strategic transformation, prompting Geojit to upgrade its rating to 'Buy' with a target price of ₹724.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:57:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f7ca057e346edab3bcf2_1771567160666.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Madras HC Mandates Corruption Probe, Igniting Governance Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Madras-HC-Mandates-Corruption-Probe-Igniting-Governance-Concerns/6997f7c9057e346edab3bcd9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Madras-HC-Mandates-Corruption-Probe-Igniting-Governance-Concerns/6997f7c9057e346edab3bcd9</guid><description>The Madras High Court has ordered the Directorate of Vigilance and Anti-Corruption (DVAC) to register a criminal case against Tamil Nadu Minister KN Nehru, citing substantial evidence provided by the Enforcement Directorate (ED) regarding alleged large-scale corruption. The court criticized the state's delay in initiating action, highlighting serious governance implications for infrastructure and municipal service projects within Tamil Nadu.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:57:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f7c9057e346edab3bcd8_1771567156566.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SpiceJet's Market Share Surge: Lease-Heavy Growth Masks Financial Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJets-Market-Share-Surge-Lease-Heavy-Growth-Masks-Financial-Strain/6997f73e057e346edab3bbfd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJets-Market-Share-Surge-Lease-Heavy-Growth-Masks-Financial-Strain/6997f73e057e346edab3bbfd</guid><description>SpiceJet has more than doubled its domestic market share to 4.3% by December 2025, driven by a 56% capacity expansion and fleet augmentation. However, this operational resurgence occurs against a backdrop of sustained net losses, significant negative shareholder equity, and a high dependency on aircraft leasing, raising critical questions about the long-term financial sustainability of its growth strategy. The airline's on-time performance also lags behind key competitors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:55:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997f73e057e346edab3bbfc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lenskart Valuation Under Scrutiny Amidst Bullish Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskart-Valuation-Under-Scrutiny-Amidst-Bullish-Outlook/6997f6f5057e346edab3bb2d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskart-Valuation-Under-Scrutiny-Amidst-Bullish-Outlook/6997f6f5057e346edab3bb2d</guid><description>Motilal Oswal initiated coverage on Lenskart with a 'Buy' rating and a Rs 600 target, citing strong growth, limited competition, and a vast underpenetrated market. However, the firm's bullish stance hinges on a high 55x FY28 earnings valuation, which raises questions about its sustainability amidst operational challenges and a competitive retail environment. While Lenskart boasts vertical integration and a large addressable market, potential headwinds from raw material dependence and subsidiary performance warrant cautious investor assessment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:53:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f6f5057e346edab3bb2c_1771566965406.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Punch EV Facelift Launched: Strategy, Rivals &amp; Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Punch-EV-Facelift-Launched-Strategy-Rivals-and-Future/6997f6d6057e346edab3bb0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Punch-EV-Facelift-Launched-Strategy-Rivals-and-Future/6997f6d6057e346edab3bb0b</guid><description>Tata Motors has launched the 2026 Punch EV facelift in India, introducing design enhancements, a new 12.3-inch touchscreen, and subtle range improvements to bolster its position in the competitive entry-level electric vehicle market. While retaining its core appeal, the updated model sees a price adjustment, posing a test for consumer acceptance in a cost-sensitive segment. This strategic refresh aims to counter rivals and pave the way for Tata's broader EV ambitions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:53:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f6d6057e346edab3bb0a_1771566920978.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India PMI Surges, But Inflation Divergence Signals Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-PMI-Surges-But-Inflation-Divergence-Signals-Caution/6997f6b3057e346edab3baba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-PMI-Surges-But-Inflation-Divergence-Signals-Caution/6997f6b3057e346edab3baba</guid><description>India's Composite PMI reached a three-month high of 59.3 in February, fueled by robust manufacturing demand. However, services sector new business moderated, while input costs surged, particularly in services, reaching 15-month and two-and-a-half-year highs respectively. This dual trend of strong manufacturing alongside services headwinds and accelerating inflation keeps the Reserve Bank of India vigilant.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:52:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f6b3057e346edab3bab9_1771566925248.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bhatia Comms Retail: Offline Model Faces E-commerce Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bhatia-Comms-Retail-Offline-Model-Faces-E-commerce-Headwinds/6997f24a057e346edab3b90c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bhatia-Comms-Retail-Offline-Model-Faces-E-commerce-Headwinds/6997f24a057e346edab3b90c</guid><description>Bhatia Communications &amp; Retail (India) Limited, a prominent Indian electronics retailer, maintains a high customer conversion rate with its "touch-and-feel" offline model and robust financials, including a debt-free balance sheet. Despite 9M FY26 sales growth of 24% and profit up 12%, the company's recent stock performance has been weak, contrasting with strong 5-year returns. A 'Sell' rating from MarketsMojo and 'Strong Sell' technical indicators signal potential headwinds as e-commerce continues to capture market share, raising questions about the long-term sustainability of its expansion strategy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:34:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f24a057e346edab3b90b_1771565774610.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Statiq Raises $18M to Export Hardware, Target Global EV Charging</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Statiq-Raises-18M-to-Export-Hardware-Target-Global-EV-Charging/6997f122057e346edab3b864</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Statiq-Raises-18M-to-Export-Hardware-Target-Global-EV-Charging/6997f122057e346edab3b864</guid><description>EV charging network operator Statiq has secured $18 million in blended equity and debt funding, led by Tenacity Ventures. The capital will drive expansion of its DC fast charger network in India, support proprietary hardware exports, and fund international pilot deployments, notably in the UAE. This investment also signals a sharpened focus on operational reliability and unit economics within the competitive EV infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:29:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997f122057e346edab3b863_1771565474666.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Battery Aadhaar: Tech Compliance Or Mineral Control?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Battery-Aadhaar-Tech-Compliance-Or-Mineral-Control/6997f08f057e346edab3b789</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Battery-Aadhaar-Tech-Compliance-Or-Mineral-Control/6997f08f057e346edab3b789</guid><description>India's 'Battery Aadhaar' proposes a digital identity for EV batteries to enhance traceability and recycling, aligning with global standards. However, concerns persist that the system could become a mere ledger of dependence, given India's significant import reliance for critical minerals. Furthermore, the compliance burden threatens to marginalize Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs) and exclude the informal recycling sector, potentially hindering both strategic autonomy and domestic manufacturing resilience.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:26:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997f08f057e346edab3b788.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maharashtra Pushes AI in Agriculture to Scale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Maharashtra-Pushes-AI-in-Agriculture-to-Scale/6997ef23057e346edab3b697</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Maharashtra-Pushes-AI-in-Agriculture-to-Scale/6997ef23057e346edab3b697</guid><description>Maharashtra is transitioning from pilot programs to widespread implementation of artificial intelligence in agriculture. The state's Mahayagri AI Policy 2025-2029 aims to reach millions of farmers with AI-powered mobile platforms offering personalized advisories, pest alerts, and market intelligence. This strategic move, backed by an interoperable data exchange and traceability infrastructure, seeks to enhance food security and climate resilience. The initiative targets attracting significant investment to co-develop scalable solutions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:20:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997ef23057e346edab3b696_1771564926706.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ONGC Hits 52-Week High Amid Geopolitical Jitters, But Future Outlook Faces Price Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Hits-52-Week-High-Amid-Geopolitical-Jitters-But-Future-Outlook-Faces-Price-Headwinds/6997ea21057e346edab3b459</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Hits-52-Week-High-Amid-Geopolitical-Jitters-But-Future-Outlook-Faces-Price-Headwinds/6997ea21057e346edab3b459</guid><description>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) shares have ascended to a 52-week high, buoyed by a 6% rally over two trading days and a 16% surge in the past month, significantly outperforming the Nifty 50. This performance is largely attributed to escalating geopolitical tensions between the US and Iran, which have driven crude oil prices higher. Despite the immediate gains and positive brokerage sentiment with multiple 'Buy' ratings, a divergence exists between current price drivers and forecasted long-term oil price declines, presenting a key analytical challenge.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:59:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997ea21057e346edab3b458.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>V-Mart Retail: Turnaround Hopes Face Deepening Valuation Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/V-Mart-Retail-Turnaround-Hopes-Face-Deepening-Valuation-Gap/6997ea1b057e346edab3b442</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/V-Mart-Retail-Turnaround-Hopes-Face-Deepening-Valuation-Gap/6997ea1b057e346edab3b442</guid><description>V-Mart Retail reported a resilient third quarter with revenue up 9.7% year-on-year to ₹1,126 crore and net profit climbing 22.8% to ₹87.99 crore. Despite this, the stock traded lower, highlighting persistent investor skepticism. Analyst firm Axis Direct initiated coverage with a 'Buy' rating and a ₹760 target, citing rural recovery potential and GST benefits. However, V-Mart's five-year return is nil, and it has underperformed the Nifty significantly, raising questions about the sustainability of any turnaround against a backdrop of intense competition and evolving consumer dynamics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997ea1b057e346edab3b441_1771563676416.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric's Market Share Collapse Sparks Survival Doubts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-Market-Share-Collapse-Sparks-Survival-Doubts/6997e9c0057e346edab3b378</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-Market-Share-Collapse-Sparks-Survival-Doubts/6997e9c0057e346edab3b378</guid><description>Ola Electric's market share has plummeted to under 6%, a dramatic fall from its previous dominance. The company reported a 55% year-on-year revenue decline in Q3 FY26, with net losses widening sequentially. This operational reset, including significant retail footprint reduction, is seen as a reactive measure against aggressive competitors and persistent quality concerns. Analysts widely rate the stock 'Sell', citing survival risks and a prolonged, challenging turnaround. The stock has lost over 60% from its IPO price.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:57:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997e9c0057e346edab3b377_1771563556744.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PB Fintech Soars on Kotak Upgrade Amid Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/PB-Fintech-Soars-on-Kotak-Upgrade-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/6997e9a2057e346edab3b35c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/PB-Fintech-Soars-on-Kotak-Upgrade-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/6997e9a2057e346edab3b35c</guid><description>PB Fintech shares gained over 2% on Friday, February 20, 2026, driven by a Kotak Institutional Equities upgrade from 'Reduce' to 'Add'. This followed robust third-quarter FY2026 results, which saw new business premiums surge 45% year-on-year. Despite the positive sentiment, the company's high price-to-earnings ratio and competitive industry dynamics remain key areas of focus for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:57:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997e9a2057e346edab3b35b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ASML's EUV Monopoly Faces Geopolitical Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ASMLs-EUV-Monopoly-Faces-Geopolitical-Headwinds/6997e8b5057e346edab3b20e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ASMLs-EUV-Monopoly-Faces-Geopolitical-Headwinds/6997e8b5057e346edab3b20e</guid><description>ASML Holding NV continues to command the global high-end chip manufacturing equipment market, driven by its sole provision of essential Extreme Ultraviolet (EUV) lithography machines. Fueled by insatiable artificial intelligence demand and the relentless pursuit of advanced computing power, ASML's order books remain robust, projecting years of stable revenue. However, the company's unique, almost unassailable market position is increasingly entangled in global geopolitical tensions and faces scrutiny over the sustainability of its dominance in a strategic industry.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:53:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997e8b5057e346edab3b20d_1771563337357.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Insurers Face Commission Reckoning: Digital Edge Over Legacy Gains Traction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurers-Face-Commission-Reckoning-Digital-Edge-Over-Legacy-Gains-Traction/6997e8b4057e346edab3b1f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurers-Face-Commission-Reckoning-Digital-Edge-Over-Legacy-Gains-Traction/6997e8b4057e346edab3b1f7</guid><description>India's insurance market stands at a critical regulatory juncture, with the IRDAI set to restructure commissions by September 2026 to curb mis-selling. This overhaul targets commission-heavy distribution channels and bancassurance partnerships, creating a divergence between digitally-native insurers like Go Digit and ICICI Lombard, and legacy players such as New India Assurance and Care Health, which face structural headwinds and capital adequacy concerns. The shift mandates a focus on policyholder value over upfront incentives, forcing a strategic recalibration across the industry.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:53:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997e8b4057e346edab3b1f6_1771563444403.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Federal Bank Secures ₹686 Cr Tax Refund</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Federal-Bank-Secures-686-Cr-Tax-Refund/6997e7c6057e346edab3b0e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Federal-Bank-Secures-686-Cr-Tax-Refund/6997e7c6057e346edab3b0e9</guid><description>Federal Bank announced the receipt of income tax refund orders totaling ₹686.31 crore, inclusive of interest. This significant inflow follows directives from the Income Tax Appellate Tribunal (ITAT) concerning assessment years 2011-12 through 2013-14. The resolution brings closure to a protracted tax matter, providing a notable boost to the bank's liquidity and financial reserves, at a time when the broader Indian banking sector demonstrates robust performance and asset quality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:49:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997e7c6057e346edab3b0e8_1771563075189.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Bad Bank: First Payouts Hide Costly Resolution Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Bad-Bank-First-Payouts-Hide-Costly-Resolution-Reality/6997e7c3057e346edab3b0d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Bad-Bank-First-Payouts-Hide-Costly-Resolution-Reality/6997e7c3057e346edab3b0d2</guid><description>India Debt Resolution Co Ltd (IDRCL) has completed its first resolutions, distributing approximately Rs 330 crore to banks. However, these initial recoveries followed substantial haircuts, with Metenere Ltd seeing a 95% reduction on acquired debt and Helios Photo Voltaic facing a 97% haircut. These deep discounts underscore the immense cost and complexity involved in unwinding the nation's legacy stressed assets, with beneficiary banks like State Bank of India, Bank of Baroda, and Punjab National Bank receiving payouts based on these reduced recovery values.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:49:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997e7c3057e346edab3b0d1_1771563078040.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Labour Codes: Compliance Burden Rises</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Labour-Codes-Compliance-Burden-Rises/6997e661057e346edab3afe6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Labour-Codes-Compliance-Burden-Rises/6997e661057e346edab3afe6</guid><description>India's four consolidated labor codes, effective November 21, 2025, aim to simplify compliance but introduce significant new burdens for employers. Businesses face increased costs due to revised wage definitions and expanded social security mandates. While lauded for modernization, the transition presents challenges, particularly for SMEs, with potential for higher litigation and uneven implementation across states, signaling a complex new regulatory era.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:43:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997e661057e346edab3afe5_1771562721743.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Breach Signals Near-Term Weakness: Target Sectors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-Breach-Signals-Near-Term-Weakness-Target-Sectors/6997e310057e346edab3ae96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-Breach-Signals-Near-Term-Weakness-Target-Sectors/6997e310057e346edab3ae96</guid><description>The Nifty index has fallen below its 20-day moving average, marking a potential turn in market sentiment. Analysts point to critical support levels at 25,100 and 24,718 for the Nifty, while Bank Nifty faces headwinds. Investors are advised to target underperforming sectors like Information Technology, Real Estate, and Fast-Moving Consumer Goods, and consider hedging strategies as global geopolitical tensions and FII outflows increase market volatility. The India VIX has seen a notable jump, reinforcing cautious sentiment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:29:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997e310057e346edab3ae95.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>