<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:33:56 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Unlock 2026 Gains: ICICI Securities Reveals 7 Top Stock Bets with UP TO 32% Upside!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Unlock-2026-Gains-ICICI-Securities-Reveals-7-Top-Stock-Bets-with-UP-TO-32percent-Upside/694e8004e10c98d0788e9285</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Unlock-2026-Gains-ICICI-Securities-Reveals-7-Top-Stock-Bets-with-UP-TO-32percent-Upside/694e8004e10c98d0788e9285</guid><description>ICICI Securities anticipates a robust recovery for Indian equities in 2026, projecting a 15% CAGR in corporate earnings. The brokerage highlights factors like increased retail investor participation and the potential ₹2 lakh crore infusion from the 8th Pay Commission. Based on this optimistic outlook, ICICI Securities has identified seven high-conviction stock ideas, including Bank of Baroda, Bajaj Finance, Bharti Airtel, Dalmia Bharat, NRB Bearings, Phoenix Mills, and KPIT Technologies, with potential upsides ranging up to 32%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:21:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8004e10c98d0788e9284_1766752416040.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>🚨 Stocks Explode: Top Price-Volume Breakouts Revealed for Tomorrow! Don't Miss Out!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Stocks-Explode-Top-Price-Volume-Breakouts-Revealed-for-Tomorrow-Dont-Miss-Out/694e7c04e10c98d0788e8dff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Stocks-Explode-Top-Price-Volume-Breakouts-Revealed-for-Tomorrow-Dont-Miss-Out/694e7c04e10c98d0788e8dff</guid><description>Indian stock markets closed lower for the third consecutive session as investors remained cautious before the Q3 earnings season. Despite overall market fatigue after recent highs, several stocks showed significant price and volume breakouts. Indian Railway Finance Corp Ltd, Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd, and Hindustan Copper Ltd were among the top gainers, displaying strong upward momentum supported by high trading volumes, signalling potential focus for the next trading day.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:03:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7c04e10c98d0788e8dfe_1766751308797.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIFT City Bonds: $68 Billion Institutional Giant — Will Retail Get a Slice?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/GIFT-City-Bonds-68-Billion-Institutional-Giant-Will-Retail-Get-a-Slice/694e7ac6e10c98d0788e8ca8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/GIFT-City-Bonds-68-Billion-Institutional-Giant-Will-Retail-Get-a-Slice/694e7ac6e10c98d0788e8ca8</guid><description>The bond market at India's GIFT City is predominantly institutional, facilitating offshore debt for corporates. With $68 billion outstanding and $7 billion raised in FY24-25, regulators are enhancing investor protection through stricter disclosure and rating norms. While retail access is limited, future avenues like bond fractionalisation and tokenisation are being explored to evolve investor participation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:57:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7ac6e10c98d0788e8ca7_1766750983657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LIC Partners with Sahaj to Revolutionize Rural Insurance Access: HUGE Impact on Bharat's Financial Inclusion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Partners-with-Sahaj-to-Revolutionize-Rural-Insurance-Access-HUGE-Impact-on-Bharats-Financial-Inclusion/694e796fe10c98d0788e8a3c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Partners-with-Sahaj-to-Revolutionize-Rural-Insurance-Access-HUGE-Impact-on-Bharats-Financial-Inclusion/694e796fe10c98d0788e8a3c</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has joined forces with Sahaj Insurance Services, a corporate agent. This strategic alliance aims to distribute LIC's life insurance products across India's rural and semi-urban regions through Sahaj's extensive network of 4.5 lakh digitally enabled centers. The partnership seeks to make insurance simpler, more accessible, and inclusive for all citizens, boosting financial inclusion and social security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:53:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e796fe10c98d0788e8a3b_1766751061708.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Affordable Housing Dream: Can Budget 2026 Make It a Reality?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Affordable-Housing-Dream-Can-Budget-2026-Make-It-a-Reality/694e79c0e10c98d0788e8b55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Affordable-Housing-Dream-Can-Budget-2026-Make-It-a-Reality/694e79c0e10c98d0788e8b55</guid><description>India's housing affordability is improving due to lower interest rates and income growth, but rising costs and supply constraints persist. Real estate developers and housing finance companies are urging the government, in the upcoming Union Budget 2026-27, to revive tax incentives like those under PMAY 1.0 and revise the definition of affordable housing, which currently has a ₹45 lakh cap, to sustain momentum in the sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:50:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e79c0e10c98d0788e8b54_1766752061746.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCI Supercharges Gurugram Cold Chain: Mega New Facility Unlocks Growth for Pharma &amp; Quick Commerce!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TCI-Supercharges-Gurugram-Cold-Chain-Mega-New-Facility-Unlocks-Growth-for-Pharma-and-Quick-Commerce/694e78e6e10c98d0788e8938</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TCI-Supercharges-Gurugram-Cold-Chain-Mega-New-Facility-Unlocks-Growth-for-Pharma-and-Quick-Commerce/694e78e6e10c98d0788e8938</guid><description>Transport Corporation of India (TCI) has significantly expanded its cold chain warehousing business by inaugurating a 1.5 lakh sq ft facility in Taj Nagar, Gurugram. This state-of-the-art facility is designed to cater to high-demand sectors including quick commerce, pharmaceuticals, food and beverages, and dairy. Operated by TCI Cold Chain Solutions Ltd., a joint venture with Mitsui &amp; Co Ltd, the facility offers multi-temperature storage and a flexible pay-as-you-use model, strengthening TCI's logistics capabilities in the NCR region.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:50:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e78e6e10c98d0788e8937_1766750793524.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Clean Energy Secret: Is Grid Power Ready for the Big Switch?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Clean-Energy-Secret-Is-Grid-Power-Ready-for-the-Big-Switch/694e7872e10c98d0788e87e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Clean-Energy-Secret-Is-Grid-Power-Ready-for-the-Big-Switch/694e7872e10c98d0788e87e7</guid><description>India's ambitious clean energy goals are now shifting focus from creating capacity to ensuring grid readiness. N Venu, MD &amp; CEO of Hitachi Energy India, explains that strengthening the grid with high-voltage transmission, energy storage, and digital substations is crucial. This is vital to reliably deliver renewable power to meet rising demand from industry and the booming data center sector, ensuring India's energy transition is successful and sustainable towards its net-zero targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:49:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7872e10c98d0788e87e6_1766750960263.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LIC Seals Deal to Revolutionize Rural Insurance Access Across India!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Seals-Deal-to-Revolutionize-Rural-Insurance-Access-Across-India/694e784ee10c98d0788e8792</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Seals-Deal-to-Revolutionize-Rural-Insurance-Access-Across-India/694e784ee10c98d0788e8792</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has partnered with Sahaj Insurance Services Private Limited to significantly boost insurance access in rural and semi-urban areas. Leveraging Sahaj's extensive network of digitally enabled centers, this collaboration aims to make LIC's life insurance products more understandable and manageable for citizens, especially in regions with low insurance awareness, thereby furthering financial inclusion and social security in India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:49:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e784ee10c98d0788e8791_1766750597708.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tractor Sales Skyrocket: ICRA Predicts Massive 17% Growth Fueled by Tax Cuts &amp; Monsoon Magic!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tractor-Sales-Skyrocket-ICRA-Predicts-Massive-17percent-Growth-Fueled-by-Tax-Cuts-and-Monsoon-Magic/694e774de10c98d0788e860a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tractor-Sales-Skyrocket-ICRA-Predicts-Massive-17percent-Growth-Fueled-by-Tax-Cuts-and-Monsoon-Magic/694e774de10c98d0788e860a</guid><description>Rating agency ICRA has significantly boosted its tractor industry growth forecast for FY26 to 15-17%, a sharp increase from the previous 8-10% estimate and the 7% seen last year. This optimism stems from strong recent performance, including a 30% jump in November wholesale volumes. Key drivers include a reduced GST on tractors making them more affordable, a robust Southwest Monsoon boosting farm income, and anticipated pre-buying due to upcoming stricter emission norms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:46:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e774de10c98d0788e8609_1766750093504.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Tumbles! 📉 Indian Currency Plunges Against US Dollar – What's Driving the Fall &amp; What it Means for Your Wallet!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Tumbles-Indian-Currency-Plunges-Against-US-Dollar-Whats-Driving-the-Fall-and-What-it-Means-for-Your-Wallet/694e767ee10c98d0788e84aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Tumbles-Indian-Currency-Plunges-Against-US-Dollar-Whats-Driving-the-Fall-and-What-it-Means-for-Your-Wallet/694e767ee10c98d0788e84aa</guid><description>The Indian Rupee depreciated by 15 paise to close at 89.86 against the US dollar on Friday. The weakening was driven by a downturn in domestic stock markets, consistent outflows of foreign funds, and rising crude oil prices. The dollar index saw a slight increase, while Brent crude prices edged higher. Foreign institutional investors sold Indian equities worth ₹1,721.26 crore, further pressuring the rupee.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:42:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e767ee10c98d0788e84a9_1766750101516.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DP World's $5 Billion India Push: Deeper Integration and Multimodal Logistics Set to Transform Trade!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DP-Worlds-5-Billion-India-Push-Deeper-Integration-and-Multimodal-Logistics-Set-to-Transform-Trade/694e72f2e10c98d0788e80f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DP-Worlds-5-Billion-India-Push-Deeper-Integration-and-Multimodal-Logistics-Set-to-Transform-Trade/694e72f2e10c98d0788e80f2</guid><description>DP World is significantly expanding its India operations, aiming for deeper integration through higher-value supply chain solutions and multimodal offerings. The multinational logistics firm is bullish on India's trade growth, committing an additional $5 billion to its existing $3 billion investment. This expansion focuses on enhancing predictability and resilience for customers by leveraging its extensive infrastructure, including ports, rail, containers, and warehousing, to create an end-to-end logistics network. This strategic move positions India as a key manufacturing and export hub, anticipating increased contributions to DP World's global business.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:25:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e72f2e10c98d0788e80f1_1766749004011.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver to EXPLODE? Rich Dad Poor Dad Author Robert Kiyosaki Reveals Shocking Price Target!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-to-EXPLODE-Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad-Author-Robert-Kiyosaki-Reveals-Shocking-Price-Target/694e7237e10c98d0788e7f44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-to-EXPLODE-Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad-Author-Robert-Kiyosaki-Reveals-Shocking-Price-Target/694e7237e10c98d0788e7f44</guid><description>Robert Kiyosaki, author of "Rich Dad Poor Dad," believes silver's rally is just beginning, predicting prices could hit $200 per ounce by 2026. He recently purchased silver at $70 per ounce, having first invested in 1965 when prices were under a dollar. Kiyosaki urges investors to conduct their own research, emphasizing learning from mistakes to build wealth. Silver futures recently surged to a record ₹2,32,741 per kg on the MCX, exceeding $75 per ounce globally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:24:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7237e10c98d0788e7f43_1766749105888.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sun Pharma's Bold FY26 Growth Plan: Innovation Bets Meet US Pricing Storm!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sun-Pharmas-Bold-FY26-Growth-Plan-Innovation-Bets-Meet-US-Pricing-Storm/694e72f3e10c98d0788e811d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sun-Pharmas-Bold-FY26-Growth-Plan-Innovation-Bets-Meet-US-Pricing-Storm/694e72f3e10c98d0788e811d</guid><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries targets mid- to high-single digit consolidated revenue growth in FY26, emphasizing investment in its innovative medicines pipeline and R&amp;D. This guidance comes amidst evolving US pharmaceutical pricing policies, including proposed mandatory models aimed at curbing drug costs, which could impact the company's significant revenue from branded pharmaceuticals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:24:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e72f3e10c98d0788e811c_1766749007378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Family Businesses Unlock Growth: Independent Directors Key to Future Success?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Family-Businesses-Unlock-Growth-Independent-Directors-Key-to-Future-Success/694e7257e10c98d0788e7f92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Family-Businesses-Unlock-Growth-Independent-Directors-Key-to-Future-Success/694e7257e10c98d0788e7f92</guid><description>A Deloitte report highlights that Indian family-run businesses need better succession planning and governance to ensure continuity and growth. It suggests that independent directors are crucial for bringing objectivity, transparency, and professional expertise to boards, helping to separate family interests from business decisions, manage risks, and build investor trust for future expansion and generational transitions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:24:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7257e10c98d0788e7f91_1766749387072.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Rewires Russia Ties: Oil Imports Plummeting, Trade Balance Shifts Dramatically!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Rewires-Russia-Ties-Oil-Imports-Plummeting-Trade-Balance-Shifts-Dramatically/694e7027e10c98d0788e7ce3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Rewires-Russia-Ties-Oil-Imports-Plummeting-Trade-Balance-Shifts-Dramatically/694e7027e10c98d0788e7ce3</guid><description>India is enacting a significant shift in its trade strategy with Russia, anticipating a sharp decline in crude oil imports from December 2025. Refiners are diversifying suppliers, increasingly sourcing from the Middle East, Africa, Canada, and the US, which has become a key supplier. While overall bilateral trade is growing robustly, driven by sectors beyond energy, India's trade deficit with Russia has widened substantially. Defence cooperation remains a critical component of the relationship.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:15:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7027e10c98d0788e7ce2_1766748270977.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kuku FM's Revenue Triples to ₹242 Cr! Massive Ad Spends Fuel Growth, But Losses Swell – IPO Plans Near?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kuku-FMs-Revenue-Triples-to-242-Cr-Massive-Ad-Spends-Fuel-Growth-But-Losses-Swell-IPO-Plans-Near/694e6f97e10c98d0788e7bc9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kuku-FMs-Revenue-Triples-to-242-Cr-Massive-Ad-Spends-Fuel-Growth-But-Losses-Swell-IPO-Plans-Near/694e6f97e10c98d0788e7bc9</guid><description>Audio platform Kuku FM reported a strong financial year, with operating revenue nearly tripling to Rs 242 crore in FY25, a 175% jump. However, aggressive advertising spending led to expenses doubling, causing net losses to widen by 59% to Rs 153 crore. With over 10 million paying subscribers, the company is preparing for a significant Rs 3,000 crore IPO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:11:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6f97e10c98d0788e7bc8_1766748209618.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Creative Exports Soar! Jewellery, Toys Power $12.5B Surge as UAE Becomes Top Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Indias-Creative-Exports-Soar-Jewellery-Toys-Power-125B-Surge-as-UAE-Becomes-Top-Market/694e6ec4e10c98d0788e7a84</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Indias-Creative-Exports-Soar-Jewellery-Toys-Power-125B-Surge-as-UAE-Becomes-Top-Market/694e6ec4e10c98d0788e7a84</guid><description>India's exports of creative goods surged 7.3% to $12.5 billion in the first seven months of FY26, driven by fashion accessories, jewellery, carpets, and toys. The United Arab Emirates has emerged as the largest market, capturing a 31% share, surpassing the US. This growth highlights India's increasing role in global creative goods trade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:09:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6ec4e10c98d0788e7a83_1766747913115.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Parabolic Run Ending in 2026? Nilesh Shah Reveals Surprising Outlook!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Parabolic-Run-Ending-in-2026-Nilesh-Shah-Reveals-Surprising-Outlook/694e6b97e10c98d0788e761c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Parabolic-Run-Ending-in-2026-Nilesh-Shah-Reveals-Surprising-Outlook/694e6b97e10c98d0788e761c</guid><description>Nilesh Shah, Managing Director of Kotak Mahindra AMC, believes the extraordinary parabolic surge in gold and silver prices may not continue into 2026. Despite this, he maintains a positive outlook for both precious metals, citing sustained central bank buying for gold and robust industrial demand, particularly from the electric vehicle sector, for silver. Shah advises investors to adhere to asset allocation principles, diversifying portfolios across real estate, debt, equity, and precious metals. This comes as gold prices recently hit ₹1.39 lakh per 10 grams and silver surged past ₹2.33 lakh per kg on MCX.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:51:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6b97e10c98d0788e761b_1766747136927.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Railway &amp; PSU Stocks Plummet 50%! Spark Private Wealth Sees Hidden Value – Your Buying Guide?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Railway-and-PSU-Stocks-Plummet-50percent-Spark-Private-Wealth-Sees-Hidden-Value-Your-Buying-Guide/694e6ba4e10c98d0788e7663</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Railway-and-PSU-Stocks-Plummet-50percent-Spark-Private-Wealth-Sees-Hidden-Value-Your-Buying-Guide/694e6ba4e10c98d0788e7663</guid><description>Devang Mehta of Spark Private Wealth Management sees significant value opportunities in railway and Public Sector Undertaking (PSU) stocks. These sectors have seen corrections of 30-50%, much deeper than the broader market's median 24% fall. Mehta emphasizes that the investment case has shifted from mere seasonality to strong fundamentals like revenue growth and order books, making them attractive for investors focused on earnings visibility and cash flow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:51:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6ba4e10c98d0788e7662_1766747219849.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Snaps Losing Streak! Defence &amp; Metal Soar, But IT/Auto Stocks Falter - What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Snaps-Losing-Streak-Defence-and-Metal-Soar-But-ITAuto-Stocks-Falter-Whats-Next/694e6b07e10c98d0788e7514</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Snaps-Losing-Streak-Defence-and-Metal-Soar-But-ITAuto-Stocks-Falter-Whats-Next/694e6b07e10c98d0788e7514</guid><description>Indian benchmark indices concluded the week with modest gains, breaking a three-week losing streak. However, Friday saw the market end near day's lows, with the Nifty slipping below 26,050 and Sensex falling 367 points. Defence and metal stocks led sectoral gains, while IT and auto shares dragged the indices down for the third consecutive session. Several midcap stocks showed significant movement, both positive and negative.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:51:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6b07e10c98d0788e7513_1766746964172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FY27 Economic Boom: Economists Reveal Secret Growth Driver &amp; Rupee's Shocking Stability!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-Economic-Boom-Economists-Reveal-Secret-Growth-Driver-and-Rupees-Shocking-Stability/694e6b1de10c98d0788e7555</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-Economic-Boom-Economists-Reveal-Secret-Growth-Driver-and-Rupees-Shocking-Stability/694e6b1de10c98d0788e7555</guid><description>Economists from HDFC Bank and Union Bank of India forecast India's real GDP growth to normalize between 6.5% and 7% in fiscal year 2026-27, driven primarily by consumption. They anticipate nominal GDP growth to rise, supporting earnings and credit. The Indian Rupee is projected to trade in a stable 90-93 range against the US dollar by FY27, supported by a balance of payments surplus.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:51:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6b1de10c98d0788e7554_1766747010758.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manappuram Finance Fuels Growth: Rs 250 Cr Boost for Subsidiary, New CFO Hired!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-Fuels-Growth-Rs-250-Cr-Boost-for-Subsidiary-New-CFO-Hired/694e6a6be10c98d0788e73c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-Fuels-Growth-Rs-250-Cr-Boost-for-Subsidiary-New-CFO-Hired/694e6a6be10c98d0788e73c0</guid><description>Manappuram Finance announced a significant Rs 250 crore investment in its subsidiary, Asirvad Micro Finance, to fuel its expansion. The company also appointed Buvanesh Tharashankar as Group Chief Financial Officer, bringing nearly three decades of banking experience. Additionally, Manappuram Finance's board approved a proposal to hike its borrowing limit up to Rs 75,000 crore, bolstering its capacity for future lending and growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:48:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6a6be10c98d0788e73bf_1766746941789.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SME IPO Frenzy! 78% GMP on E to E Transportation Infra, Dhara Rail &amp; Apollo Techno IPOs - Big Listing Gains Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SME-IPO-Frenzy-78percent-GMP-on-E-to-E-Transportation-Infra-Dhara-Rail-and-Apollo-Techno-IPOs-Big-Listing-Gains-Ahead/694e69f1e10c98d0788e72a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SME-IPO-Frenzy-78percent-GMP-on-E-to-E-Transportation-Infra-Dhara-Rail-and-Apollo-Techno-IPOs-Big-Listing-Gains-Ahead/694e69f1e10c98d0788e72a5</guid><description>Three SME IPOs, E to E Transportation Infrastructure, Dhara Rail Projects, and Apollo Techno Industries, are drawing significant investor interest in India's primary market. E to E Transportation Infrastructure leads with a commanding Grey Market Premium (GMP) of up to 78%, followed by Dhara Rail Projects at 18% and Apollo Techno Industries at over 9%. These strong GMPs suggest potential substantial listing gains for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:47:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e69f1e10c98d0788e72a4_1766746781526.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AC Prices Set for Major Shift: New Rules &amp; Tax Cuts Spark Buyer Dilemma</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-AC-Prices-Set-for-Major-Shift-New-Rules-and-Tax-Cuts-Spark-Buyer-Dilemma/694e6ac9e10c98d0788e74ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-AC-Prices-Set-for-Major-Shift-New-Rules-and-Tax-Cuts-Spark-Buyer-Dilemma/694e6ac9e10c98d0788e74ac</guid><description>India's air conditioner market faces price changes starting January 2026 due to stricter energy efficiency norms from the Bureau of Energy Efficiency (BEE). While these new standards require more expensive components, a recent cut in Goods and Services Tax (GST) to 18% from 28% is expected to largely offset the price increase, potentially keeping new AC prices similar to pre-GST levels. Some manufacturers foresee broader cost pressures, however.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:47:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6ac9e10c98d0788e74ab_1766747184490.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unveils Massive EV Charging Network: Over 27,000 Stations Installed at Petrol Pumps!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Unveils-Massive-EV-Charging-Network-Over-27000-Stations-Installed-at-Petrol-Pumps/694e69b9e10c98d0788e71d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Unveils-Massive-EV-Charging-Network-Over-27000-Stations-Installed-at-Petrol-Pumps/694e69b9e10c98d0788e71d3</guid><description>India significantly expanded its electric vehicle charging infrastructure in 2025, installing over 27,000 new stations at existing petrol pumps. This initiative, supported by the FAME-II scheme and direct investments from oil marketing companies, aims to boost EV adoption by making charging convenient and accessible. The rollout includes integrated mobility hubs offering various fuel types and facilities, enhancing future transportation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:45:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e69b9e10c98d0788e71d2_1766746641537.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Corporate Map Rewired: Shocking 2025 Demerger Deals From Tata To Adani - What You MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Corporate-Map-Rewired-Shocking-2025-Demerger-Deals-From-Tata-To-Adani-What-You-MUST-Know/694e690ce10c98d0788e7010</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Corporate-Map-Rewired-Shocking-2025-Demerger-Deals-From-Tata-To-Adani-What-You-MUST-Know/694e690ce10c98d0788e7010</guid><description>2025 was a landmark year for corporate restructuring in India, with major firms like Tata Motors, Hindustan Unilever, ITC, and Vedanta executing key demergers to unlock business value. Reliance Industries and Adani Group also led significant mergers, reshaping sectors from media to cement. These strategic moves altered ownership structures and market rankings, positioning companies for future growth and investors for significant portfolio shifts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:42:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e690ce10c98d0788e700f_1766746665893.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Midcap Mayhem! 5 Indian Stocks Crash Over 30% in 2025 - Is Your Portfolio Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Midcap-Mayhem-5-Indian-Stocks-Crash-Over-30percent-in-2025-Is-Your-Portfolio-Safe/694e68e0e10c98d0788e6f87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Midcap-Mayhem-5-Indian-Stocks-Crash-Over-30percent-in-2025-Is-Your-Portfolio-Safe/694e68e0e10c98d0788e6f87</guid><description>Indian midcap stocks faced significant pressure in 2025, with the Nifty Midcap 100 underperforming the Nifty 50. Five key stocks, including Oracle Financial Services Software, Kalyan Jewellers India, Premier Energies, Dixon Technologies, and Supreme Industries, have seen their values plummet by more than 30% over the past year, raising concerns for investors. Despite some strong quarterly results, significant market corrections have impacted these companies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:42:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e68e0e10c98d0788e6f86_1766746575030.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Hits Stunning 15-Year High: AI &amp; EV Boom Ignites Red Metal Rally!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Copper-Hits-Stunning-15-Year-High-AI-and-EV-Boom-Ignites-Red-Metal-Rally/694e68d4e10c98d0788e6f58</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Copper-Hits-Stunning-15-Year-High-AI-and-EV-Boom-Ignites-Red-Metal-Rally/694e68d4e10c98d0788e6f58</guid><description>Hindustan Copper shares reached a 15-year peak of ₹480.85, driven by surging global copper prices and robust demand from AI and electric vehicles. Mine disruptions have created global supply shortages, while domestic revival plans at the Rakha mine support growth prospects. Analysts foresee continued upward momentum despite high valuations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:41:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e68d4e10c98d0788e6f57_1766746602019.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹2 Lakh Crore Exodus: Will FII Selling Frenzy END in India by 2026?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2-Lakh-Crore-Exodus-Will-FII-Selling-Frenzy-END-in-India-by-2026/694e6733e10c98d0788e6c89</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2-Lakh-Crore-Exodus-Will-FII-Selling-Frenzy-END-in-India-by-2026/694e6733e10c98d0788e6c89</guid><description>Foreign investors have pulled out nearly ₹2 lakh crore from six key Indian sectors in 2025, including IT, FMCG, and power. This sharp selloff has intensified debate on whether the trend will reverse by year-end or continue into 2026. While some experts foresee a potential shift due to anticipated interest rate cuts and a weaker dollar, others remain cautious about market valuations and earnings growth. Domestic inflows via SIPs continue, but focus on large caps and IPOs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:34:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6733e10c98d0788e6c88_1766746132125.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Tumble: Sensex and Nifty Plunge Amidst Investor Uncertainty!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Tumble-Sensex-and-Nifty-Plunge-Amidst-Investor-Uncertainty/694e6374e10c98d0788e67fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Tumble-Sensex-and-Nifty-Plunge-Amidst-Investor-Uncertainty/694e6374e10c98d0788e67fb</guid><description>India's benchmark stock indices experienced a significant downturn today. The Sensex fell by 367.25 points to 85,041.45, and the Nifty declined by 99.80 points to 26,042.30, indicating potential investor caution and a bearish market sentiment. This is a developing story.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:17:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6374e10c98d0788e67fa_1766745025458.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GRM Overseas Delights Investors: Massive 2:1 Bonus Share Payout &amp; Stellar Q2 Profits Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GRM-Overseas-Delights-Investors-Massive-21-Bonus-Share-Payout-and-Stellar-Q2-Profits-Revealed/694e6310e10c98d0788e66ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GRM-Overseas-Delights-Investors-Massive-21-Bonus-Share-Payout-and-Stellar-Q2-Profits-Revealed/694e6310e10c98d0788e66ca</guid><description>GRM Overseas has successfully allotted 12.27 crore bonus shares in a 2:1 ratio, granting shareholders two free shares for every one held. This follows strong Q2 FY26 results, with revenue rising 16.2% to ₹372.1 crore and profit after tax jumping 60.5% to ₹14.8 crore, driven by a 72% export surge. The company's stock has already delivered over 150% year-to-date returns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:17:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6310e10c98d0788e66c9_1766744932969.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India REIT Market Poised for Explosive Growth: Landmark Reforms to Unlock Trillions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-REIT-Market-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth-Landmark-Reforms-to-Unlock-Trillions/694e633fe10c98d0788e6767</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-REIT-Market-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth-Landmark-Reforms-to-Unlock-Trillions/694e633fe10c98d0788e6767</guid><description>India's Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT) market is set for major expansion following a milestone 2025 with five listings and $18 billion in market capitalization. Crucial reforms from January 2026 will reclassify REITs as equities, aligning with global standards and attracting significant institutional investment. Strong distribution yields of 6-7% and the upcoming introduction of Small and Medium REITs (SM REITs) are projected to drive market growth beyond $30 billion, positioning REITs as a mainstream asset class.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:16:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e633fe10c98d0788e6766_1766745055626.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ceigall India Rockets! Dual Wins in ₹613Cr Highway &amp; ₹550Cr Solar Projects Fuel Stock Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ceigall-India-Rockets-Dual-Wins-in-613Cr-Highway-and-550Cr-Solar-Projects-Fuel-Stock-Surge/694e62c5e10c98d0788e6613</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ceigall-India-Rockets-Dual-Wins-in-613Cr-Highway-and-550Cr-Solar-Projects-Fuel-Stock-Surge/694e62c5e10c98d0788e6613</guid><description>Shares of Ceigall India Ltd gained after its subsidiary received a provisional certificate from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for a ₹613 crore highway project in Punjab. This project is set for commercial operations from December 22, 2025. Additionally, the company secured a ₹550 crore solar power project bid in Madhya Pradesh.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:16:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e62c5e10c98d0788e6612_1766745026772.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold's Shocking Role in 2025! Multi-Asset Funds Beat Equities – What's Next for 2026?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Golds-Shocking-Role-in-2025-Multi-Asset-Funds-Beat-Equities-Whats-Next-for-2026/694e61cfe10c98d0788e6471</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Golds-Shocking-Role-in-2025-Multi-Asset-Funds-Beat-Equities-Whats-Next-for-2026/694e61cfe10c98d0788e6471</guid><description>Multi-asset funds delivered over 16% returns in 2025, significantly outpacing pure equity funds, largely thanks to a 10-15% allocation in gold and silver. While equities faced volatility and debt offered steady income, precious metals became the key differentiator. Looking to 2026, fund managers anticipate a need for dynamic allocation across quality equities, debt, metals, and global assets to navigate evolving market conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:12:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e61cfe10c98d0788e6470_1766744739205.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea's AGR Dues Relief: Will It Save the Telecom Giant or Just Delay the Inevitable?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Ideas-AGR-Dues-Relief-Will-It-Save-the-Telecom-Giant-or-Just-Delay-the-Inevitable/694e6140e10c98d0788e6369</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Ideas-AGR-Dues-Relief-Will-It-Save-the-Telecom-Giant-or-Just-Delay-the-Inevitable/694e6140e10c98d0788e6369</guid><description>Vodafone Idea faces a critical challenge despite potential government relief on its Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) dues. Experts believe the reassessment, which could halve the dues to around ₹40,000 crore, along with a possible moratorium, is a short-term fix. The company's larger debt of ₹2 trillion, including significant future spectrum payment obligations, alongside the need for substantial tariff hikes to boost Average Revenue Per User (ARPU) to ₹300 and fresh equity infusion, are key to its long-term survival. The market anxiously awaits clarity as March 2026 nears, highlighting the importance of maintaining a competitive telecom landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:11:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6140e10c98d0788e6368_1766744457163.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Gas Network Skyrockets! 25,000+ Km Pipeline Achieved, Fueling Energy Security!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Gas-Network-Skyrockets-25000-Km-Pipeline-Achieved-Fueling-Energy-Security/694e60b7e10c98d0788e6223</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Gas-Network-Skyrockets-25000-Km-Pipeline-Achieved-Fueling-Energy-Security/694e60b7e10c98d0788e6223</guid><description>India has significantly expanded its natural gas pipeline network, now spanning over 25,429 km, with an additional 10,459 km under construction. This major infrastructure push aims to enhance national energy security and promote cleaner fuel access across the country. The government has also implemented a "One Nation, One Grid, One Tariff" system to standardize transportation charges, ensuring fairer pricing for consumers regardless of their location.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:05:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e60b7e10c98d0788e6222_1766744379077.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rico Auto EXPLODES 13% Toward Record High! Massive Volume Surge - What's Driving This Rally?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Rico-Auto-EXPLODES-13percent-Toward-Record-High-Massive-Volume-Surge-Whats-Driving-This-Rally/694e5b82e10c98d0788e5c10</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Rico-Auto-EXPLODES-13percent-Toward-Record-High-Massive-Volume-Surge-Whats-Driving-This-Rally/694e5b82e10c98d0788e5c10</guid><description>Rico Auto Industries shares surged 13% to a fresh 52-week high of ₹141.65 on heavy volumes, nearing its record peak. The auto component manufacturer is experiencing a boost from strong domestic automotive demand, robust OEM partnerships, favorable GST changes, and significant investments by major players like Maruti Suzuki and Tata Motors. The positive outlook for the Indian auto sector, projected to reach $300 billion by 2026, is further supporting the company's performance, with government initiatives like the PLI scheme also providing tailwinds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:43:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e5b82e10c98d0788e5c0f_1766743155162.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal's Top Stock Picks: KNR Constructions, Castrol, VIP Industries &amp; Market Forecast!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Motilal-Oswals-Top-Stock-Picks-KNR-Constructions-Castrol-VIP-Industries-and-Market-Forecast/694e5b1ee10c98d0788e5b4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Motilal-Oswals-Top-Stock-Picks-KNR-Constructions-Castrol-VIP-Industries-and-Market-Forecast/694e5b1ee10c98d0788e5b4c</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services, through Siddhartha Khemka, has identified KNR Constructions, Castrol India, and VIP Industries as key stock calls. KNR Constructions is highlighted for its asset monetization, Castrol India for potential management changes post-open offer, and VIP Industries for a turnaround under new ownership, though execution is critical. Khemka anticipates a lackluster broader market until early 2026, emphasizing company-specific catalysts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:43:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e5b1ee10c98d0788e5b4b_1766742877265.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Banks' Secret Weapon: How They Beat Private Lenders in Profit Margins During RBI Rate Cuts!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Secret-Weapon-How-They-Beat-Private-Lenders-in-Profit-Margins-During-RBI-Rate-Cuts/694e5b44e10c98d0788e5ba9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Secret-Weapon-How-They-Beat-Private-Lenders-in-Profit-Margins-During-RBI-Rate-Cuts/694e5b44e10c98d0788e5ba9</guid><description>Public sector banks (PSBs) have demonstrated greater resilience than private lenders during the Reserve Bank of India's rate-cut cycle, effectively protecting their Net Interest Margins (NIMs). This outperformance is attributed to PSBs' stronger base of low-cost CASA deposits and stable funding structures, which allowed them to better absorb falling lending yields compared to private banks that rely more on market-linked deposits. While both faced margin compression, PSBs experienced a significantly smaller decline.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:39:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e5b44e10c98d0788e5ba8_1766743073427.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Thirst Crisis: Beverage Giants Heineken, Carlsberg, Diageo Face Grim Water Reality!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Thirst-Crisis-Beverage-Giants-Heineken-Carlsberg-Diageo-Face-Grim-Water-Reality/694e58a2e10c98d0788e5849</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Thirst-Crisis-Beverage-Giants-Heineken-Carlsberg-Diageo-Face-Grim-Water-Reality/694e58a2e10c98d0788e5849</guid><description>Major beverage companies like Heineken, Carlsberg, and Diageo are facing significant water scarcity challenges in India, particularly in Rajasthan. This forces them to increase water efficiency, invest in replenishment projects, and potentially impacts production costs amid growing demand and limited freshwater resources in the country. Local communities also face severe water shortages, sometimes blaming industries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:33:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e58a2e10c98d0788e5848_1766742362554.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>