<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:57:28 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Hazoor Multi Projects Posts Mixed Results Amid Subsidiary Exit &amp; Debt Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hazoor-Multi-Projects-Posts-Mixed-Results-Amid-Subsidiary-Exit-and-Debt-Rise/698e1fea19b91b0643401a23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hazoor-Multi-Projects-Posts-Mixed-Results-Amid-Subsidiary-Exit-and-Debt-Rise/698e1fea19b91b0643401a23</guid><description>Hazoor Multi Projects Limited (HMPL) reported a mixed financial performance for Q3 FY26. Standalone revenue surged 33.84% YoY to ₹7,597 lakhs, but standalone PAT dipped 13.42%. Consolidated revenue fell 15.67%, though PAT rose 138.09% driven by a tax credit. However, consolidated PAT margins contracted significantly, and debt-to-equity climbed to 0.73, with Interest Service Coverage Ratio turning negative (-0.87) in Q3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ducon Infratech Posts Steep Profit Drop, Auditor Flags Investment Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ducon-Infratech-Posts-Steep-Profit-Drop-Auditor-Flags-Investment-Valuation/698e1f7219b91b064340024a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ducon-Infratech-Posts-Steep-Profit-Drop-Auditor-Flags-Investment-Valuation/698e1f7219b91b064340024a</guid><description>Ducon Infratechnologies Limited reported a sharp decline in third-quarter earnings, with standalone net profit falling 65.64% year-on-year to ₹39.86 Lakhs. Consolidated net profit dropped 32.15% to ₹231.24 Lakhs. Revenue also saw declines across standalone and consolidated figures. The company's auditor flagged an 'Emphasis of Matters' concerning investments valued at cost rather than fair value, totaling ₹500 Lakhs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ONGC Surges on Record Dividend, Profit Jump; Revenue Edges Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Surges-on-Record-Dividend-Profit-Jump-Revenue-Edges-Up/698e1efc19b91b06434001ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Surges-on-Record-Dividend-Profit-Jump-Revenue-Edges-Up/698e1efc19b91b06434001ce</guid><description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) reported a robust 22.56% year-on-year surge in consolidated net profit to ₹11,946 crore for Q3 FY'26. The company also declared its highest-ever cumulative interim dividend for FY'26 at 245%. However, consolidated gross revenue saw a marginal 0.13% rise YoY, with standalone revenues declining. Lower crude oil and gas price realisations impacted performance despite operational progress and new gas monetization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jiya Eco-Products Reports Nil Revenue Amidst Corporate Insolvency Proceedings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Jiya-Eco-Products-Reports-Nil-Revenue-Amidst-Corporate-Insolvency-Proceedings/698e1eb319b91b0643400140</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Jiya-Eco-Products-Reports-Nil-Revenue-Amidst-Corporate-Insolvency-Proceedings/698e1eb319b91b0643400140</guid><description>Jiya Eco-Products Limited disclosed its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, revealing a stark zero revenue from operations. The company remains under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) since May 2023, with its Board of Directors' powers suspended. The Resolution Professional reported a net loss of ₹1.13 Lakhs for the quarter on nil income, against a profit in the previous quarter. No future outlook is provided due to the ongoing insolvency proceedings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jyoti Resins Posts Flat Q3 Revenue, Margin Dip Amidst Brand Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Jyoti-Resins-Posts-Flat-Q3-Revenue-Margin-Dip-Amidst-Brand-Push/698e1e8419b91b0643400127</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Jyoti-Resins-Posts-Flat-Q3-Revenue-Margin-Dip-Amidst-Brand-Push/698e1e8419b91b0643400127</guid><description>Jyoti Resins &amp; Adhesives reported a subdued Q3 FY26 with flattish revenue and volume growth year-on-year. While unit economics were deemed good, investors expressed significant disappointment over stagnant revenue and earnings per share since FY24. The company's EBITDA margins compressed from 32-34% to 25-26% due to increased ATL and BTL marketing expenditures, a strategic move management believes is necessary for long-term market share and brand building towards a ₹500 crore revenue target. A debt-free company with ₹170 crore in cash, Jyoti Resins is undertaking brownfield expansion to boost capacity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CMS Info Systems: Revenue Climbs 6.3% Amid Profit Dip; Secures ₹1000 Cr SBI Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CMS-Info-Systems-Revenue-Climbs-63percent-Amid-Profit-Dip-Secures-1000-Cr-SBI-Order/698e1e8219b91b064340011f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CMS-Info-Systems-Revenue-Climbs-63percent-Amid-Profit-Dip-Secures-1000-Cr-SBI-Order/698e1e8219b91b064340011f</guid><description>CMS Info Systems reported a 6.3% YoY revenue growth to ₹618.22 Cr in Q3 FY26, but consolidated PAT declined 38.3% to ₹57.40 Cr, impacted by ₹11.11 Cr in exceptional wage code costs and industry pressures. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹2.75 per share and secured a significant ₹1,000 Cr, 10-year contract with SBI for ATM cash solutions. Management sees Q3 FY26 as a financial bottom, anticipating sequential gains and a FY27 revenue goal of ₹2,800 Cr.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Autoriders International Sees 113% Profit Jump, Announces 5:1 Bonus Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Autoriders-International-Sees-113percent-Profit-Jump-Announces-51-Bonus-Issue/698e1e0b19b91b06433fed0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Autoriders-International-Sees-113percent-Profit-Jump-Announces-51-Bonus-Issue/698e1e0b19b91b06433fed0b</guid><description>Autoriders International reported a robust Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit soaring 113.33% YoY to ₹235.01 lacs on 18.92% revenue growth. Nine-month PAT rose 26.15%. The company also approved a 5:1 bonus issue and extended a ₹5 crore loan to its subsidiary, Solareco Energy Private Limited. Standalone results mirrored consolidated figures. No forward-looking guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ONGC Payouts ₹7,863 Cr Dividend; Profit Surge Masking Deep Liabilities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Payouts-7863-Cr-Dividend-Profit-Surge-Masking-Deep-Liabilities/698e1d1d19b91b06433fa749</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Payouts-7863-Cr-Dividend-Profit-Surge-Masking-Deep-Liabilities/698e1d1d19b91b06433fa749</guid><description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) announced a second interim dividend of ₹6.25 per share, totaling ₹7,863 Crore. While consolidated net profit surged 22.57% YoY to ₹11,946 Crore for Q3 FY26, standalone revenue slipped 6.45% and PAT saw a marginal 1.57% rise. Investors should note significant contingent liabilities of ₹14,600 Crore for arbitration and ₹8,613 Crore for tax disputes, alongside operational complexities in subsidiaries and a stalled JV block.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GAIL Appoints New CMD Amid Profit Pressure: Will Projects Focus Drive Turnaround?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GAIL-Appoints-New-CMD-Amid-Profit-Pressure-Will-Projects-Focus-Drive-Turnaround/698e1d1a19b91b06433fa72f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GAIL-Appoints-New-CMD-Amid-Profit-Pressure-Will-Projects-Focus-Drive-Turnaround/698e1d1a19b91b06433fa72f</guid><description>Deepak Gupta assumes leadership of GAIL (India) Limited as Chairman and Managing Director from March 1, 2026, succeeding Sandeep Kumar Gupta. This appointment by the Ministry of Petroleum and Natural Gas aims to ensure leadership continuity. However, the transition coincides with GAIL's Q3 results revealing a decline in gas marketing EBIT and a widening loss in petrochemicals, presenting a critical challenge for the new CMD. Gupta, previously Director (Projects), brings extensive experience in large-scale project execution to navigate these financial headwinds in India's expanding natural gas sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Shivam Autotech Raises ₹45 Cr Via Debentures from Alpha Alternatives Fund</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shivam-Autotech-Raises-45-Cr-Via-Debentures-from-Alpha-Alternatives-Fund/698e1ca219b91b06433f8dbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shivam-Autotech-Raises-45-Cr-Via-Debentures-from-Alpha-Alternatives-Fund/698e1ca219b91b06433f8dbb</guid><description>Shivam Autotech Limited has approved the private placement of 4,500 unlisted, secured, redeemable, optionally convertible debentures (OCDs) worth ₹45 crore. The issuance, allotted to Alpha Alternatives Structured Credit Opportunities Fund, carries a 10% annual interest rate and a tenure of up to 18 months, with a 12-month lock-in. This move aims to bolster the company's capital structure and liquidity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ONGC Posts Mixed Q3 Results, Declares ₹6.25 Dividend Amid Revenue Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Results-Declares-625-Dividend-Amid-Revenue-Dip/698e1c2f19b91b06433e4689</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Results-Declares-625-Dividend-Amid-Revenue-Dip/698e1c2f19b91b06433e4689</guid><description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) reported its unaudited financial results for Q3 FY26. Standalone revenue dipped 6.46% YoY to ₹31,546.51 Crore, though PAT saw a marginal 1.59% rise to ₹8,371.85 Crore with improved operating margins. Consolidated PAT surged 22.57% to ₹11,946.42 Crore on slightly higher revenue. The board declared a second interim dividend of ₹6.25 per share for FY25-26, amounting to a ₹7,863 Crore payout.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI's KCC Overhaul: Digital Push Meets Banking Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-KCC-Overhaul-Digital-Push-Meets-Banking-Risks/698e1bf419b91b06433e40e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-KCC-Overhaul-Digital-Push-Meets-Banking-Risks/698e1bf419b91b06433e40e5</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has proposed significant revisions to the Kisan Credit Card (KCC) scheme, aiming to enhance credit access for marginal farmers. The draft framework introduces flexible credit limits between ₹10,000 to ₹50,000, standardizes crop seasons, and extends the KCC tenure to six years. A key focus is the integration of technological expenses and an increased emphasis on digital channels for credit drawdown, aligning with a broader national strategy for financial inclusion in agriculture. However, the move raises potential concerns for the banking sector regarding increased credit risk and operational complexities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI's Risk-Based Deposit Premiums to Reshape Indian Banking</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Risk-Based-Deposit-Premiums-to-Reshape-Indian-Banking/698e1bb519b91b06433e38cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Risk-Based-Deposit-Premiums-to-Reshape-Indian-Banking/698e1bb519b91b06433e38cb</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is introducing a risk-based deposit insurance premium structure, effective April 2026, replacing the long-standing flat rate. This significant reform, championed by expert committees for years, aims to curb moral hazard by aligning premiums with bank risk profiles. Scheduled Commercial Banks will face tiered assessments, potentially lowering costs for safer institutions. Co-operative and Regional Rural Banks will also be categorized, though with a more quantitative risk focus. The move is expected to foster greater financial discipline across the banking sector, albeit with potential implications for competitive dynamics and transparency.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:28:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698dfb60b357b56a644dd4f0_1770917703724.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Trade Credibility Erodes Amid Policy Chaos</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Trade-Credibility-Erodes-Amid-Policy-Chaos/698e1b8b19b91b06433e3866</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Trade-Credibility-Erodes-Amid-Policy-Chaos/698e1b8b19b91b06433e3866</guid><description>The U.S. House of Representatives delivered a rare rebuke to President Trump's tariff policies, voting to terminate his use of national emergency powers. This move, coupled with an impending Supreme Court ruling on executive authority and a pattern of transactional trade practices, intensifies doubts about the durability of U.S. trade commitments. Allies and partners are increasingly seeking more predictable relationships, viewing U.S. agreements as provisional, thereby eroding America's institutional credibility on the global stage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lupin Q3: Consolidated Profit Soars 39%, Standalone Hit by ₹633 Cr Litigation Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Q3-Consolidated-Profit-Soars-39percent-Standalone-Hit-by-633-Cr-Litigation-Costs/698e1a4b19b91b06433dcc00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Q3-Consolidated-Profit-Soars-39percent-Standalone-Hit-by-633-Cr-Litigation-Costs/698e1a4b19b91b06433dcc00</guid><description>Lupin Limited reported divergent Q3 FY26 results. Consolidated revenue surged 24.3% YoY to ₹71,675.2M, with PAT up 38.7% to ₹11,805.1M. However, standalone PAT fell 35.6% YoY to ₹7,174.5M, heavily impacted by ₹6,338.4M in exceptional charges for litigation settlements and labour code adjustments. The company also announced strategic acquisitions in the UK and a pending deal in the Netherlands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:22:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698df9e264745d8f8c18bf00_1770920198827.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GKB Ophthalmics Surges on Consolidated Profit Turnaround, Standalone Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/GKB-Ophthalmics-Surges-on-Consolidated-Profit-Turnaround-Standalone-Dips/698e1a4b19b91b06433dcbf2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/GKB-Ophthalmics-Surges-on-Consolidated-Profit-Turnaround-Standalone-Dips/698e1a4b19b91b06433dcbf2</guid><description>GKB Ophthalmics Limited reported a robust turnaround in its consolidated results for Q3 FY26, posting a profit of ₹70.72 Lakhs compared to a loss last year. Revenue from operations surged by 120.1% YoY to ₹5,679.35 Lakhs. However, standalone operations saw a 41.4% YoY revenue decline, though profitability improved due to other income and subsidiary recovery. The company is progressing with the winding up of its material subsidiary, GSV Ophthalmics, recovering ₹7.95 Crores of investment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:22:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e1a4b19b91b06433dcbf1_1770921176666.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PNC Reports Massive Q3 Loss on ₹17.5 Cr Content Inventory Write-Down</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PNC-Reports-Massive-Q3-Loss-on-175-Cr-Content-Inventory-Write-Down/698e19dd19b91b06433dc948</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PNC-Reports-Massive-Q3-Loss-on-175-Cr-Content-Inventory-Write-Down/698e19dd19b91b06433dc948</guid><description>Pritish Nandy Communications (PNC) reported a substantial net loss of ₹10.22 Cr in Q3 FY26, primarily driven by a significant ₹17.56 Cr write-down of its content inventory. Standalone revenue surged YoY to ₹9.77 Cr, but the net loss widened considerably. Consolidated revenue also rose to ₹7.68 Cr with a net loss of ₹10.18 Cr. The company cited changing content consumption trends favouring OTT originals over older libraries. While management claims no impact on cash flows or ongoing operations, this event underscores significant market shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Foods &amp; Inns Q3 Revenue Drops 18% Amidst Tariff Woes; Frozen Foods Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Foods-and-Inns-Q3-Revenue-Drops-18percent-Amidst-Tariff-Woes-Frozen-Foods-Surge/698e195b19b91b06433dc895</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Foods-and-Inns-Q3-Revenue-Drops-18percent-Amidst-Tariff-Woes-Frozen-Foods-Surge/698e195b19b91b06433dc895</guid><description>Foods &amp; Inns Limited reported an 18% year-on-year revenue decline to ₹145 crore for Q3 FY26, primarily due to deferred orders from US customers facing tariff uncertainty. Average realisations also fell approximately 16.5%. However, the company's frozen food segment exhibited robust volume growth of around 35% YoY in Q3. For the nine months ending December 2025, revenue declined marginally by 2% YoY to ₹559 crore, while sales tonnage grew 11%. The company is expanding spray-drying capacity and sees a positive outlook for mango pulp.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:18:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e195b19b91b06433dc894_1770920807455.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ONGC Declares ₹7,863 Cr Dividend, Consolidated PAT Surges 22.57% Amidst Liabilities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Declares-7863-Cr-Dividend-Consolidated-PAT-Surges-2257percent-Amidst-Liabilities/698e193d19b91b06433dc863</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Declares-7863-Cr-Dividend-Consolidated-PAT-Surges-2257percent-Amidst-Liabilities/698e193d19b91b06433dc863</guid><description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) declared a ₹7,863 Crore interim dividend as consolidated profit after tax soared 22.57% to ₹11,946 Crore for Q3 FY26. However, the company faces substantial contingent liabilities, including a ₹14,600 Crore arbitration demand and over ₹18,810 Crore in disputed service tax/GST levies. Standalone revenue saw a slight dip, contrasting with consolidated growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:17:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e193d19b91b06433dc862.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Surge: AWS Bets Big as Agentic AI Promises Enterprise ROI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Surge-AWS-Bets-Big-as-Agentic-AI-Promises-Enterprise-ROI/698e190719b91b06433dc7f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Surge-AWS-Bets-Big-as-Agentic-AI-Promises-Enterprise-ROI/698e190719b91b06433dc7f1</guid><description>Amazon Web Services (AWS) is amplifying its India strategy with a $12.7 billion cloud infrastructure investment by 2030, positioning 2026 as a defining year for the nation's AI ambitions, particularly agentic AI. This push aligns with India's government initiatives to foster AI development through subsidized compute and policy support, aiming to transform the country into a global AI deployment hub. While AWS focuses on enabling measurable enterprise outcomes via advanced AI systems like Zomato's Nugget, the sector faces intense competition, evolving security risks, and the challenge of rapid technological depreciation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:16:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e190719b91b06433dc7f0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aditya Infotech Revenue Plunges 85%, Yet Profits Surge 37% Amid Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aditya-Infotech-Revenue-Plunges-85percent-Yet-Profits-Surge-37percent-Amid-Expansion/698e181719b91b06433dc41b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aditya-Infotech-Revenue-Plunges-85percent-Yet-Profits-Surge-37percent-Amid-Expansion/698e181719b91b06433dc41b</guid><description>Aditya Infotech Limited (CPPLUS) reported a dramatic 84.89% YoY decline in consolidated revenue for Q3 FY26 to ₹1,391.10M. Paradoxically, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) surged 37.16% YoY to ₹959.80M, signaling improved margins. Standalone operations showed strong growth, with revenue up 40.61% and PAT up 33.07%. Key strategic moves include an MoU for an electric cable JV, a ₹750M greenfield project in Kadapa for CCTV components, and a ₹500M capacity expansion. A significant ₹411.87M customs duty demand and penalties pose a notable risk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:12:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e181719b91b06433dc41a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sudarshan Chemical Q3 Profit Plunges, FY26 Guidance Cut Amid Demand Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Sudarshan-Chemical-Q3-Profit-Plunges-FY26-Guidance-Cut-Amid-Demand-Slump/698e178819b91b06433dc217</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Sudarshan-Chemical-Q3-Profit-Plunges-FY26-Guidance-Cut-Amid-Demand-Slump/698e178819b91b06433dc217</guid><description>Sudarshan Chemical Industries reported a challenging Q3 FY26, with revenue at ₹1,683 Cr and adjusted EBITDA at ₹77 Cr (11.8% margin). The nine-month period saw a 0.4% revenue dip and a stark 74% fall in adjusted EBITDA to ₹66 Cr, leading to a ₹157 Cr PBT loss. Management cited weak pigment demand and high inventory levels but expressed optimism for recovery. The integration of Heubach is progressing, with cost savings identified, but FY26 EBITDA guidance for the acquired group was lowered. A key strategy is reducing finished goods inventory by €30-40 Mn, aiming to bolster cash flow and reduce debt, though it may temporarily impact reported EBITDA.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e178819b91b06433dc216_1770920517720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EID Parry's Q3 Sees Strong Consolidated Growth, Standalone Lags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/EID-Parrys-Q3-Sees-Strong-Consolidated-Growth-Standalone-Lags/698e177d19b91b06433dc1e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/EID-Parrys-Q3-Sees-Strong-Consolidated-Growth-Standalone-Lags/698e177d19b91b06433dc1e6</guid><description>E.I.D. Parry's Q3 FY26 saw a robust 18.3% YoY consolidated revenue jump to ₹10,316 Cr and 18.6% PAT growth to ₹232.15 Cr. However, standalone operations reported an 8.8% revenue decline, though net loss narrowed due to reduced exceptional items. Key events include Coromandel International's acquisition of NACL Industries and an expected dividend inflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:10:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e177d19b91b06433dc1e5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aditya Infotech Surges on Strong Q3 Growth, Expansion Plans Face Regulatory Hurdle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aditya-Infotech-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Growth-Expansion-Plans-Face-Regulatory-Hurdle/698e172219b91b06433dc02a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aditya-Infotech-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Growth-Expansion-Plans-Face-Regulatory-Hurdle/698e172219b91b06433dc02a</guid><description>Aditya Infotech Limited delivered a stellar Q3 FY25, with consolidated revenue soaring 67.7% YoY to ₹1391.1 Crore and PAT up 50.9% to ₹95.98 Crore. The company is pushing strategic initiatives, including a JV for electric cables and a greenfield project for CCTV components in Kadapa. However, it faces a significant ₹400+ Crore demand for custom duty and penalties, for which it plans to appeal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:08:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e172219b91b06433dc029_1770920543264.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yasho Industries Swings to Profit on 35% Revenue Surge in Q3 FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Yasho-Industries-Swings-to-Profit-on-35percent-Revenue-Surge-in-Q3-FY26/698e168b19b91b06433dbefd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Yasho-Industries-Swings-to-Profit-on-35percent-Revenue-Surge-in-Q3-FY26/698e168b19b91b06433dbefd</guid><description>Yasho Industries Ltd. announced its Q3 FY26 results, showcasing a strong performance with revenue surging 34.99% YoY to ₹201.97 Cr. The company achieved a significant turnaround in profitability, reporting a Profit After Tax (PAT) of ₹449.60 lakh, a reversal from a loss in the prior year. EBITDA margins improved to 16.65% driven by cost discipline and operational efficiencies. Exports contributed significantly at 61% of revenue. The company also announced its Pakhajan R&amp;D lab is fully operational.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:06:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e168b19b91b06433dbefc_1770920438513.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Power Plant Faces SC Scrutiny Amid Environmental Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Plant-Faces-SC-Scrutiny-Amid-Environmental-Concerns/698e163619b91b06433daa99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Plant-Faces-SC-Scrutiny-Amid-Environmental-Concerns/698e163619b91b06433daa99</guid><description>The Supreme Court has deferred judgment on Adani Group's proposed Uttar Pradesh thermal power plant, emphasizing a balance between development and environmental protection. Activists cite risks to wildlife and forests, while the court seeks robust scientific assessments and safeguards. This case highlights the increasing regulatory and environmental scrutiny facing India's thermal power sector as the nation navigates energy demands and sustainability goals. Adani Power's stock shows recent gains, supported by analyst 'Buy' ratings, yet faces ongoing evaluation of its compliance and growth strategies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:04:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698df5c759cae8ede4b4cb9b_1770918309299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CP PLUS Q3 Revenue Surges 51%, Plans JV Amidst ₹308 Cr Duty Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CP-PLUS-Q3-Revenue-Surges-51percent-Plans-JV-Amidst-308-Cr-Duty-Demand/698e163019b91b06433da55a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CP-PLUS-Q3-Revenue-Surges-51percent-Plans-JV-Amidst-308-Cr-Duty-Demand/698e163019b91b06433da55a</guid><description>Aditya Infotech Limited (CPPLUS) posted a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue leaping 51.2% YoY to ₹13,911 million and PAT rising 37.2% to ₹959.8 million. The company is forming a 50:50 JV with Orient Cables for electric cables and its subsidiary, AIL Dixon Technologies, will invest ₹1.25 billion in a new Kadapa facility for housing components and capacity expansion. Investors are monitoring a ₹308.58 million contingent liability from a customs duty demand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:04:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e163019b91b06433da559_1770920436874.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Pension Funds Targets Stability via Alternatives</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/SBI-Pension-Funds-Targets-Stability-via-Alternatives/698e161219b91b06433d9b13</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/SBI-Pension-Funds-Targets-Stability-via-Alternatives/698e161219b91b06433d9b13</guid><description>SBI Pension Funds is expanding its investment universe to include Alternative Investment Funds (AIFs) and gold/silver ETFs. This strategic move, supported by revised PFRDA guidelines, aims to enhance portfolio stability and diversification rather than chase high returns. The initiative aligns with a global trend of pension funds shifting away from equities and addresses India's growing demographic need for secure retirement planning. SBI Pension Funds targets a threefold increase in its assets under management within six years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:04:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e161219b91b06433d9b12_1770920698417.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aditya Infotech Surges 37% Revenue, Boosts Margins; Ups FY26 Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Aditya-Infotech-Surges-37percent-Revenue-Boosts-Margins-Ups-FY26-Outlook/698e154119b91b06433d5e97</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Aditya-Infotech-Surges-37percent-Revenue-Boosts-Margins-Ups-FY26-Outlook/698e154119b91b06433d5e97</guid><description>Aditya Infotech reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue jumping 37.3% YoY to ₹1,139.1 crore and EBITDA soaring 98.7% to ₹144.6 crore. EBITDA margins expanded by 391 basis points to 12.7%. The company revised its full-year FY26 revenue growth projection to the upper end of 25-30% and raised EBITDA margin guidance to 11-12%. Key strategic initiatives include a collaboration with Qualcomm for AI-enabled security solutions and expansion into rural markets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:00:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e154119b91b06433d5e96_1770920083892.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRCTC Profit Climbs Amid Margin Squeeze, Stock Stumbles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRCTC-Profit-Climbs-Amid-Margin-Squeeze-Stock-Stumbles/698e152719b91b06433d5dfd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRCTC-Profit-Climbs-Amid-Margin-Squeeze-Stock-Stumbles/698e152719b91b06433d5dfd</guid><description>Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation (IRCTC) posted a 15.61% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹394 crore for Q3 FY26, alongside an 18.36% revenue surge. However, EBITDA margins compressed due to higher operational costs from expanding lower-margin catering and tourism segments. Despite broad segment growth and a significant legal victory, the stock closed down 1.01% on the results day and remains significantly behind the broader market over the past year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:00:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e152719b91b06433d5dfc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NATCO Pharma: Q3 Surge Masks Nine-Month Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/NATCO-Pharma-Q3-Surge-Masks-Nine-Month-Profit-Slump/698e144519b91b06433d5af4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/NATCO-Pharma-Q3-Surge-Masks-Nine-Month-Profit-Slump/698e144519b91b06433d5af4</guid><description>NATCO Pharma posted a net profit of ₹151.3 crore for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025, a 14.3% increase from the prior year. Revenue climbed 36.3% to ₹647.30 crore. However, the nine-month net profit declined 22.2% to ₹1,149.50 crore despite a modest revenue rise. The board approved an interim dividend of ₹1.50 per share and reappointed key leadership.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:56:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e144519b91b06433d5af3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SpiceJet Revenue Leaps 84% QoQ, But Losses Widen Dramatically</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Revenue-Leaps-84percent-QoQ-But-Losses-Widen-Dramatically/698e13d819b91b06433d59c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Revenue-Leaps-84percent-QoQ-But-Losses-Widen-Dramatically/698e13d819b91b06433d59c1</guid><description>SpiceJet Limited reported a significant top-line surge in Q3FY26, with total revenue climbing 84% quarter-on-quarter to INR 1,523 Cr. Passenger and ancillary revenues also saw substantial QoQ growth. However, the operational turnaround remains elusive as the net loss widened to INR 268 Cr, driven by an 836% QoQ surge in aircraft lease rentals, particularly wet lease costs. EBITDA remained negative, underscoring persistent financial challenges despite improved operational metrics like load factors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:54:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e13d819b91b06433d59c0_1770919993130.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VMS TMT Faces IPO Fund Scrutiny as Stock Plunges 50% Post-Listing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/VMS-TMT-Faces-IPO-Fund-Scrutiny-as-Stock-Plunges-50percent-Post-Listing/698e13bb19b91b06433d5907</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/VMS-TMT-Faces-IPO-Fund-Scrutiny-as-Stock-Plunges-50percent-Post-Listing/698e13bb19b91b06433d5907</guid><description>VMS TMT LIMITED announced its Q3 FY26 unaudited standalone results, showing a 10.42% quarter-on-quarter revenue increase to ₹202.13 crore. Profit After Tax (PAT) for the quarter was ₹8.04 crore. However, the company is under scrutiny following a disclosure by its monitoring agency, CARE Ratings, regarding a ₹2.81 crore deviation in the utilization of IPO proceeds. Funds meant for loan repayment were reportedly used for working capital, though the company states all facilities were subsequently repaid. The stock continues to trade significantly below its IPO issue price of ₹99, closing at ₹51.01 on February 10, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:54:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e13bb19b91b06433d5906_1770919500759.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CP Capital Q3 PAT Skyrockets 44% on Robust Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CP-Capital-Q3-PAT-Skyrockets-44percent-on-Robust-Revenue-Growth/698e13aa19b91b06433d58ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CP-Capital-Q3-PAT-Skyrockets-44percent-on-Robust-Revenue-Growth/698e13aa19b91b06433d58ca</guid><description>CP Capital Limited posted a stellar Q3FY26, with consolidated PAT surging 43.9% YoY to Rs. 1,249.71 Lakhs on 41.2% revenue growth. While standalone lending operations showed resilience with 17.8% interest income growth, margins saw a slight YoY dip. The company maintains a positive outlook for Q4FY26, focusing on capital deployment and cost optimization for long-term shareholder value.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:53:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e13aa19b91b06433d58c9_1770919453789.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SpiceJet Posts 77% Revenue Jump, But Auditor Warns of Going Concern Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Posts-77percent-Revenue-Jump-But-Auditor-Warns-of-Going-Concern-Risk/698e12ce19b91b06433d562f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Posts-77percent-Revenue-Jump-But-Auditor-Warns-of-Going-Concern-Risk/698e12ce19b91b06433d562f</guid><description>SpiceJet Limited reported a robust 77% quarter-on-quarter revenue growth to INR 1,384 Crore for Q3 FY26, alongside a 58% reduction in net loss to INR 268 Crore. This operational momentum was driven by significant capacity expansion and improved load factors. However, the company's financial health remains under severe scrutiny as auditors issued a Qualified Conclusion and raised substantial doubt about its ability to continue as a going concern due to accumulated losses and negative working capital.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:50:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e12ce19b91b06433d562e_1770919911655.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Triton Valves Surges on Stellar Q3; Recommends 3:1 Bonus Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triton-Valves-Surges-on-Stellar-Q3-Recommends-31-Bonus-Share/698e126e19b91b06433d463f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triton-Valves-Surges-on-Stellar-Q3-Recommends-31-Bonus-Share/698e126e19b91b06433d463f</guid><description>Triton Valves posted a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated PAT surging 147% YoY to ₹263.93 lakh, driven by a 25.6% revenue jump. Consolidated revenue for nine months rose 21.1%. Standalone PAT saw a YoY dip in Q3 due to an exceptional charge of ₹151.78 lakh for gratuity liabilities. The company also celebrated its 50th year by recommending a 3:1 bonus share issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:48:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e126e19b91b06433d463e_1770919397739.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Panther Industrial Products Reports Zero Revenue for 9 Months, Auditors Flag Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Panther-Industrial-Products-Reports-Zero-Revenue-for-9-Months-Auditors-Flag-Concern/698e11db19b91b06433d051d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Panther-Industrial-Products-Reports-Zero-Revenue-for-9-Months-Auditors-Flag-Concern/698e11db19b91b06433d051d</guid><description>Panther Industrial Products Ltd disclosed unaudited financials showing zero revenue for the first nine months ending December 31, 2025. Auditors highlighted this operational gap, while management confirmed revenue is expected by year-end. The balance sheet reveals negative reserves and significant long-term borrowings. Investors await year-end performance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:46:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e11db19b91b06433d051c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Electronics posts 94% revenue jump, but Q3 profit margins shrink</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Electronics-posts-94percent-revenue-jump-but-Q3-profit-margins-shrink/698e116619b91b06433d03b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Electronics-posts-94percent-revenue-jump-but-Q3-profit-margins-shrink/698e116619b91b06433d03b4</guid><description>Artificial Electronics Intelligent Material Limited (AEIM) reported a robust 94.53% YoY revenue growth to ₹6,429.60 Lakhs in Q3 FY26. However, PAT grew by a slower 48.19% YoY to ₹1,444.93 Lakhs, leading to margin compression to 22.37% from 29.26%. Quarterly EPS fell 5.91% due to dilution. In contrast, the nine-month period saw PAT soar 775.74% to ₹2,480.49 Lakhs with margin expansion. The company also raised ₹28.50 Crores and ₹39.02 Crores via preferential issues in FY25.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:44:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e116619b91b06433d03b3_1770919250985.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kerala Ayurveda Revenue Jumps 21%, But Margins Squeezed by Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Kerala-Ayurveda-Revenue-Jumps-21percent-But-Margins-Squeezed-by-Investments/698e10f019b91b06433cdc3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Kerala-Ayurveda-Revenue-Jumps-21percent-But-Margins-Squeezed-by-Investments/698e10f019b91b06433cdc3d</guid><description>Kerala Ayurveda Ltd (KAL) posted a 20.7% year-on-year revenue growth to Rs. 108.7 Crs. YTD Dec'25, driven by its Global E-Product and Health Services businesses. However, reported EBITDA margins compressed due to significant investments in digital marketing, technology, and talent, alongside higher interest and depreciation, leading to a PBT of Rs. -8.4 Crs. The company plans to strengthen its balance sheet by converting Rs. 20 Crs. of promoter debt to equity and acquiring the remaining 26% stake in Ayurvedagram Heritage Wellness Centre for Rs. 10 Crs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:42:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e10f019b91b06433cdc3c_1770919347891.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's US LNG Deal Hinges on Price; Trade-Offs Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-US-LNG-Deal-Hinges-on-Price-Trade-Offs-Loom/698e10ec19b91b06433cdc25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-US-LNG-Deal-Hinges-on-Price-Trade-Offs-Loom/698e10ec19b91b06433cdc25</guid><description>India's primary gas importer, Petronet LNG, will only acquire U.S. liquefied natural gas if prices are deemed competitive for consumers. This stance arises as India seeks to leverage its position to reduce energy costs, despite a U.S. offer to cut tariffs in exchange for increased imports. The nation faces skepticism regarding its ambitious $500 billion import pledge, with analysts warning of potential trade distortions as India aims to significantly boost natural gas's share in its energy mix.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:42:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e10ec19b91b06433cdc24_1770918810551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>