<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:45:21 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Director Reddy Discharged from Liquor Policy Case</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Director-Reddy-Discharged-from-Liquor-Policy-Case/69a511983d2913aa7c2213f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Director-Reddy-Discharged-from-Liquor-Policy-Case/69a511983d2913aa7c2213f3</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma announced that its Non-Executive Director, P. Sarath Chandra Reddy, has been discharged from the Delhi Liquor Policy case by a CBI court. The court found no material evidence against him, significantly easing a key legal overhang for the company. This development removes a direct judicial concern for the director and, by extension, the company.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:27:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a511983d2913aa7c2213f2_1772426084420.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharti Airtel: Strategic Bets Overshadow NBFC Wobble</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtel-Strategic-Bets-Overshadow-NBFC-Wobble/69a511373d2913aa7c221329</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtel-Strategic-Bets-Overshadow-NBFC-Wobble/69a511373d2913aa7c221329</guid><description>Bharti Airtel's stock experienced a sharp decline following its entry into the non-banking financial company (NBFC) sector, erasing significant market value. However, recent investor communications suggest this sell-off may be overblown. Analysts highlight strategic capital allocation towards subsidiaries like Airtel Money and strengthening core holdings in Indus Towers and Airtel Africa as long-term value drivers, potentially outweighing immediate concerns over new ventures. The company also signaled a move towards a progressive dividend policy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:25:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a511373d2913aa7c221328_1772425857556.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Fog Over Yardeni's 'Roaring 2020s'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Fog-Over-Yardenis-Roaring-2020s/69a511303d2913aa7c22130c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Fog-Over-Yardenis-Roaring-2020s/69a511303d2913aa7c22130c</guid><description>Economist Ed Yardeni predicts a subsiding of geopolitical tensions, advocating profit-taking in commodities and anticipating benefits for oil-importing nations like India. He maintains an optimistic 'roaring 2020s' outlook for the decade, seeing current market fluctuations as buying opportunities. However, persistent geopolitical risks, particularly concerning oil supply routes vital to India, and stretched equity valuations in emerging markets introduce significant headwinds to this sanguine view.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:25:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a511303d2913aa7c22130b_1772425703263.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Rockets Amid Mideast Crisis, India's Vulnerability Exposed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-Rockets-Amid-Mideast-Crisis-Indias-Vulnerability-Exposed/69a5112a3d2913aa7c2212f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-Rockets-Amid-Mideast-Crisis-Indias-Vulnerability-Exposed/69a5112a3d2913aa7c2212f5</guid><description>Missile strikes on commercial vessels near the Strait of Hormuz have ignited a sharp surge in global crude oil prices, with Brent crude nearing $80 a barrel on March 2, 2026. Analysts predict further gains, potentially exceeding $100, as geopolitical tensions escalate. Despite the immediate price shock, structural market shifts, including robust US shale output and existing inventories, suggest this event may not trigger the same widespread economic impact seen in 2008 or 2022. However, India faces acute vulnerability due to its heavy reliance on the Strait of Hormuz for critical energy imports, particularly LPG and LNG.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:25:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5112a3d2913aa7c2212f4_1772425692867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>West Asia War Squeezes Indian Rice Exporters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/West-Asia-War-Squeezes-Indian-Rice-Exporters/69a511253d2913aa7c2212de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/West-Asia-War-Squeezes-Indian-Rice-Exporters/69a511253d2913aa7c2212de</guid><description>Escalating geopolitical tensions in West Asia are severely impacting India's multi-billion dollar rice export sector. Prominent exporters LT Foods, KRBL, and Chaman Lal Setia Exports saw their stock prices decline sharply as trade routes face disruption and costs surge. Companies with substantial Middle Eastern market dependence, particularly for basmati rice, are bearing the brunt of this instability, forcing strategic shifts in export terms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:25:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a511253d2913aa7c2212dd_1772425641715.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>InfoBeans Technologies Approves 3:1 Bonus Issue, Capital Soars To ₹970 Crore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/InfoBeans-Technologies-Approves-31-Bonus-Issue-Capital-Soars-To-970-Crore/69a511233d2913aa7c2212c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/InfoBeans-Technologies-Approves-31-Bonus-Issue-Capital-Soars-To-970-Crore/69a511233d2913aa7c2212c7</guid><description>InfoBeans Technologies' Board of Directors approved the allotment of 7.27 crore bonus equity shares in a 3:1 ratio. This significant issuance boosts the company's paid-up share capital from ₹242.40 crore to ₹969.59 crore, reflecting strong financial performance and a commitment to enhancing shareholder value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:25:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a511233d2913aa7c2212c6_1772425646412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Skyscraper Boom: Economic Omen or Fundamental Growth?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Skyscraper-Boom-Economic-Omen-or-Fundamental-Growth/69a510493d2913aa7c22116d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Skyscraper-Boom-Economic-Omen-or-Fundamental-Growth/69a510493d2913aa7c22116d</guid><description>India is leading global skyscraper construction, with over 400 major projects underway across key cities. This surge, while impressive, is drawing comparisons to the Skyscraper Index, a theory linking tall building completion to economic downturns. However, unlike past speculative bubbles, India's boom is supported by rapid urbanisation, a growing middle class, and significant housing demand. Despite these fundamentals, the sector's high valuations warrant scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:21:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a510493d2913aa7c22116c_1772425385588.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitics Spook Retail; SIP Discipline Tested Amidst Sectoral Weakness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitics-Spook-Retail-SIP-Discipline-Tested-Amidst-Sectoral-Weakness/69a50fc13d2913aa7c2210d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitics-Spook-Retail-SIP-Discipline-Tested-Amidst-Sectoral-Weakness/69a50fc13d2913aa7c2210d0</guid><description>Indian equity markets experienced a sharp sell-off on Monday, March 2, 2026, driven by escalating geopolitical tensions in West Asia. Benchmark indices Nifty 50 and Sensex plunged, mirroring global risk aversion and a surge in crude oil prices. While experts advise maintaining Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) to leverage rupee cost averaging, the immediate market reaction highlights retail investor anxiety versus institutional opportunism, with underlying sectoral weaknesses becoming more apparent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:19:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a50fc13d2913aa7c2210cf_1772425293966.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aadhar Housing: Promoter Exit, New Investor &amp; Valuation Paradox</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aadhar-Housing-Promoter-Exit-New-Investor-and-Valuation-Paradox/69a50bf93d2913aa7c220ed3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aadhar-Housing-Promoter-Exit-New-Investor-and-Valuation-Paradox/69a50bf93d2913aa7c220ed3</guid><description>Aadhar Housing Finance experienced a significant ownership change with BCP Topco VII divesting its entire 75.2% stake. UAE-based AXDI LDII SPV acquired 10.18% at a discount, coinciding with a ~4% stock drop. Despite this, the company leads the fast-growing affordable housing segment, boasting ₹28,790 crore in AUM as of December 2025. Analysts maintain a 'Strong Buy' consensus with price targets suggesting over 27% upside, yet the discount entry by the new investor warrants scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:03:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a50bf93d2913aa7c220ed2_1772424362094.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Technologies Partners WHIS for SDV; Accelerates Auto Software Innovation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tata-Technologies-Partners-WHIS-for-SDV-Accelerates-Auto-Software-Innovation/69a50a913d2913aa7c220de9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tata-Technologies-Partners-WHIS-for-SDV-Accelerates-Auto-Software-Innovation/69a50a913d2913aa7c220de9</guid><description>Tata Technologies has announced a strategic partnership with WITTENSTEIN High Integrity Systems (WHIS) to advance Software-Defined Vehicle (SDV) development. The collaboration integrates WHIS's safety-certified SAFE RTOS® into Tata Technologies' automotive software stack, aiming to accelerate innovation and help manufacturers meet stringent safety standards like ISO 26262 for next-generation mobility solutions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:57:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a50a913d2913aa7c220de8_1772424089693.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Storm Brews Volatility Ahead of Holi Market Closure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Storm-Brews-Volatility-Ahead-of-Holi-Market-Closure/69a509bd3d2913aa7c220ccb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Storm-Brews-Volatility-Ahead-of-Holi-Market-Closure/69a509bd3d2913aa7c220ccb</guid><description>Indian equity markets anticipate a sharp, volatile opening on Monday, March 2, 2026, as escalating Middle East tensions dominate investor sentiment. The National Stock Exchange (NSE) and BSE will observe a full market holiday for Holi on Tuesday, March 3rd, with trading resuming Wednesday, March 4th. While the Multi-Commodity Exchange (MCX) will operate its evening session, the National Commodity &amp; Derivatives Exchange (NCDEX) remains closed all day, highlighting varied operational impacts during the festive closure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:53:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a509bd3d2913aa7c220cca_1772423750941.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIC Re Exits War Zones, Signals Reinsurance Market Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-Exits-War-Zones-Signals-Reinsurance-Market-Strain/69a509a03d2913aa7c220cae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-Exits-War-Zones-Signals-Reinsurance-Market-Strain/69a509a03d2913aa7c220cae</guid><description>State-owned General Insurance Corporation of India (GIC Re) is ceasing marine hull war risk coverage in several high-risk maritime regions, including the Persian Gulf, Black Sea, and Red Sea, effective March 3rd. This move signals a significant shift in the reinsurance market's risk appetite amid heightened geopolitical tensions. Shipowners face the prospect of higher insurance premiums and operational challenges as coverage becomes scarcer and more expensive in these critical trade arteries, potentially impacting global supply chains.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a509a03d2913aa7c220cad_1772423745390.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Carbon Market: Design Flaws Risk Ineffective Pricing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Carbon-Market-Design-Flaws-Risk-Ineffective-Pricing/69a5084f3d2913aa7c220b4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Carbon-Market-Design-Flaws-Risk-Ineffective-Pricing/69a5084f3d2913aa7c220b4d</guid><description>India launched its first national Carbon Credit Trading Scheme (CCTS), employing an intensity-based, baseline-and-credit model for sectors like aluminum and cement. Companies earn credits for outperforming emission intensity targets. However, this design risks allowing absolute emissions to rise even as intensity falls, potentially leading to an oversupply of credits, depressed prices, and insufficient incentive for deep decarbonisation. Weak institutional oversight and enforcement further challenge its credibility and ability to meet global climate pressures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:47:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5084f3d2913aa7c220b4c_1772423359524.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC Orders CBI Probe Into DLF Project; Sector Faces Renewed Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-Orders-CBI-Probe-Into-DLF-Project-Sector-Faces-Renewed-Scrutiny/69a508373d2913aa7c220b30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-Orders-CBI-Probe-Into-DLF-Project-Sector-Faces-Renewed-Scrutiny/69a508373d2913aa7c220b30</guid><description>The Supreme Court has directed a CBI investigation into DLF's 'The Primus DLF Garden City' project in Gurugram, citing potential widespread irregularities. This judicial intervention follows numerous homebuyer complaints regarding project delays and incomplete infrastructure, with the court emphasizing that current issues might only be the 'tip of the iceberg.' The probe, overseen by the CBI Director, is mandated to submit findings by April 25, 2026, signaling a significant escalation in regulatory oversight for major developers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:47:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a508373d2913aa7c220b2f_1772423371402.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto February Sales Surge 27%; YTD Volume Up 9%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-February-Sales-Surge-27percent-YTD-Volume-Up-9percent/69a5056c3d2913aa7c22098e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-February-Sales-Surge-27percent-YTD-Volume-Up-9percent/69a5056c3d2913aa7c22098e</guid><description>Bajaj Auto reported a substantial 27% year-on-year increase in total vehicle sales for February 2026, selling 4,48,259 units. Both the two-wheeler and commercial vehicle segments showed robust growth. Year-to-date, the company's sales rose by 9% to 46,72,290 units, indicating a healthy overall performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5056c3d2913aa7c22098d_1772422641717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hormuz Fears Spike Aluminium Prices Amid Geopolitical Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hormuz-Fears-Spike-Aluminium-Prices-Amid-Geopolitical-Volatility/69a501b63d2913aa7c2207aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hormuz-Fears-Spike-Aluminium-Prices-Amid-Geopolitical-Volatility/69a501b63d2913aa7c2207aa</guid><description>Escalating Middle Eastern tensions, with a focus on the Strait of Hormuz, have injected a geopolitical risk premium into aluminium prices. While this highlights the region's 9% share of global production and its reliance on critical shipping lanes, historical analysis suggests actual supply disruptions are less probable than market jitters. Concurrently, other industrial metals like zinc, with specific supply chain vulnerabilities linked to Iran, face volatility. Despite short-term price surges, underlying demand drivers for industrial metals remain strong, suggesting current market reactions may be overstating long-term risk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:19:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a501b63d2913aa7c2207a9_1772421698461.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitics, Techs Sink India Markets: Mid/Small Caps Face Deeper Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitics-Techs-Sink-India-Markets-MidSmall-Caps-Face-Deeper-Risk/69a501b33d2913aa7c220792</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitics-Techs-Sink-India-Markets-MidSmall-Caps-Face-Deeper-Risk/69a501b33d2913aa7c220792</guid><description>Indian equity markets are poised for a sharp gap-down opening as geopolitical tensions in West Asia intensify, coinciding with a critical breach of the 200-day moving average across major indices. Analysts warn of significant downside risk, particularly for mid and small-cap stocks, whose stretched valuations and India's macro vulnerabilities – including oil price spikes and persistent FII outflows – amplify the bearish outlook. Volatility is expected to surge ahead of the Holi holiday and weekly Nifty expiry.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:19:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a501b33d2913aa7c220791_1772421672828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Stocks: AI Divergence Fuels Caution Amidst Sector Rebound</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-AI-Divergence-Fuels-Caution-Amidst-Sector-Rebound/69a501363d2913aa7c2206f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-AI-Divergence-Fuels-Caution-Amidst-Sector-Rebound/69a501363d2913aa7c2206f3</guid><description>The Nifty IT index has seen a steep correction, losing 19% year-to-date, underperforming the broader Nifty. While fears of AI disruption causing revenue erosion persist, a divergence is emerging: IT services firms are poised to benefit from AI implementation, with clients favoring 'build' over 'buy.' This shift offers system integrators a net positive volume opportunity, potentially allowing them to gain share from SaaS providers, even as some major players like Salesforce signal moderated growth. Despite a 19.5% plunge in February, the sector is showing signs of rebound driven by oversold valuations and bargain hunting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a501363d2913aa7c2206f2_1772421563070.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KVS Castings Unit-2 operational; capacity surges to 19,200 MTPA</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KVS-Castings-Unit-2-operational-capacity-surges-to-19200-MTPA/69a5003f3d2913aa7c2205be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KVS-Castings-Unit-2-operational-capacity-surges-to-19200-MTPA/69a5003f3d2913aa7c2205be</guid><description>KVS Castings Limited has successfully commenced commercial operations at its new manufacturing facility, Unit-2, in Uttarakhand, effective March 2, 2026. This expansion marks a significant milestone, more than doubling the company's total installed production capacity to 19,200 Metric Tonnes per Annum (MTPA) from the existing 7,200 MTPA. The move aligns with the capital expenditure objectives outlined in its Initial Public Offer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:13:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5003f3d2913aa7c2205bd_1772421287523.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Surges on Conflict; Safe Haven Status Faces Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-on-Conflict-Safe-Haven-Status-Faces-Scrutiny/69a5003e3d2913aa7c2205a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-on-Conflict-Safe-Haven-Status-Faces-Scrutiny/69a5003e3d2913aa7c2205a8</guid><description>Escalating US-Israel-Iran tensions propelled spot gold and silver prices significantly on March 2, 2026, driven by safe-haven demand and rising crude oil costs. While spot markets saw substantial gains, domestic futures showed divergence. Analysts warn of potential profit-taking if de-escalation occurs, noting that while gold is a primary safe haven, currencies like the Swiss franc and Japanese yen are also attracting defensive flows, and the US dollar's appeal is conditional amidst increased volatility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:13:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5003e3d2913aa7c2205a7_1772421497537.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland February Sales Surge 28% on M&amp;HCV Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ashok-Leyland-February-Sales-Surge-28percent-on-MandHCV-Strength/69a4ff533d2913aa7c2204e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ashok-Leyland-February-Sales-Surge-28percent-on-MandHCV-Strength/69a4ff533d2913aa7c2204e5</guid><description>Ashok Leyland reported robust sales for February 2026, with domestic vehicle sales growing 28% year-on-year to 20,314 units. The Medium and Heavy Commercial Vehicles (M&amp;HCV) segment was a key driver, posting a 31% surge. Combined domestic and export sales also saw a healthy 24% increase, signaling strong market demand across segments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 03:09:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4ff533d2913aa7c2204e4_1772421088167.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quantum Strategy Shifts Amid Iran Conflict: Gold Surges, Oil Spikes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Quantum-Strategy-Shifts-Amid-Iran-Conflict-Gold-Surges-Oil-Spikes/69a4fd0a3d2913aa7c2203bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Quantum-Strategy-Shifts-Amid-Iran-Conflict-Gold-Surges-Oil-Spikes/69a4fd0a3d2913aa7c2203bb</guid><description>Heightened US-Iran geopolitical tensions are forcing significant portfolio adjustments. Quantum Strategy, anticipating prolonged conflict and supply chain disruptions, is increasing allocations to gold and hard assets by 10%, while favoring Australian and Singaporean dollars over the US dollar. The firm remains underweight global equities but holds long positions in Asia. This strategic pivot comes as oil prices surge and shipping costs escalate due to threats to critical energy infrastructure and transit routes, particularly the Strait of Hormuz.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 02:59:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4fd0a3d2913aa7c2203ba_1772420482445.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prism Johnson Sells 51% Raheja QBE Stake for ₹324 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Prism-Johnson-Sells-51percent-Raheja-QBE-Stake-for-324-Cr/69a4fc7f3d2913aa7c22032d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Prism-Johnson-Sells-51percent-Raheja-QBE-Stake-for-324-Cr/69a4fc7f3d2913aa7c22032d</guid><description>Prism Johnson Limited will sell its entire 51% stake in Raheja QBE General Insurance Company Limited for ₹324 crore to QBE Holdings (AAP) Pty Limited. This transaction marks the end of the joint venture with Australia's QBE Group in the general insurance sector. The divestment is expected to be completed within nine months, pending shareholder and IRDAI approvals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 02:57:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4fc7f3d2913aa7c22032c_1772420356370.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors Signs MoU for 40 Green Hydrogen Trucks at VOC Port</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Motors-Signs-MoU-for-40-Green-Hydrogen-Trucks-at-VOC-Port/69a4faa53d2913aa7c220202</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Motors-Signs-MoU-for-40-Green-Hydrogen-Trucks-at-VOC-Port/69a4faa53d2913aa7c220202</guid><description>Tata Motors has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with V.O. Chidambaranar Port Authority (VOCPA) to deploy 40 green hydrogen-powered heavy-duty trucks. This significant step aims to decarbonise port operations and bolster India's net-zero emissions goal in the maritime sector. VOCPA will establish critical infrastructure, including a 2 MW electrolyzer and a hydrogen refueling station, to support this phased deployment over the next two years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 02:49:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4faa53d2913aa7c220201_1772419850929.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitics Ignite Oil Rally, Triggering Broader Market Selloff</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Geopolitics-Ignite-Oil-Rally-Triggering-Broader-Market-Selloff/69a4fa323d2913aa7c22019f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Geopolitics-Ignite-Oil-Rally-Triggering-Broader-Market-Selloff/69a4fa323d2913aa7c22019f</guid><description>Oil prices surged Monday as a brewing West Asian conflict intensified, pushing Brent crude above $79. Gold and Treasury futures also climbed as investors sought safety. The conflict's impact on the Strait of Hormuz threatens critical oil flows, raising inflation and economic growth concerns. U.S. stock futures declined, reflecting broader market anxiety amplified by ongoing banking sector fears and AI stock volatility, with a significant week of U.S. economic data looming.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 02:47:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4fa323d2913aa7c22019e_1772419832774.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Auto Sales Soar, But Geopolitical Clouds Gather</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Sales-Soar-But-Geopolitical-Clouds-Gather/69a4f6823d2913aa7c21f124</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Sales-Soar-But-Geopolitical-Clouds-Gather/69a4f6823d2913aa7c21f124</guid><description>India's leading automakers posted robust February 2026 sales figures, fueled by substantial export growth and steady domestic demand. Maruti Suzuki led with an 11.1% increase in total sales, largely due to a 56% export surge. Hyundai, Tata Motors, M&amp;M, and Toyota also reported double-digit percentage gains. However, escalating geopolitical tensions in the Middle East present a significant, unquantified threat to future momentum, supply chains, and input costs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 02:31:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4f6823d2913aa7c21f123_1772418850421.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPFO Weighs Yield Loss in Rs 1,250 Cr Buyback</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/EPFO-Weighs-Yield-Loss-in-Rs-1250-Cr-Buyback/69a4f6813d2913aa7c21f0eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/EPFO-Weighs-Yield-Loss-in-Rs-1250-Cr-Buyback/69a4f6813d2913aa7c21f0eb</guid><description>The Employees Provident Fund Organisation's (EPFO) investment committee has sanctioned participation in a Rs 1,250 crore voluntary buyback of Delhi Mumbai Expressway Development Limited (DMEDL) non-convertible debentures. The final call rests with the Central Board of Trustees (CBT) on Monday, which will also declare the interest rate for its 30 crore members. This decision hinges on balancing immediate liquidity gains against a potential yield reduction, with current NCDs yielding 7.97% versus an estimated reinvestment rate of 7.6%.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 02:31:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4f6813d2913aa7c21f0ea_1772418796397.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hormuz Insurance Hikes Signal Global Trade Chokehold</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Hormuz-Insurance-Hikes-Signal-Global-Trade-Chokehold/69a4f6743d2913aa7c21eff2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Hormuz-Insurance-Hikes-Signal-Global-Trade-Chokehold/69a4f6743d2913aa7c21eff2</guid><description>Insurers are issuing cancellation notices and hiking war-risk premiums significantly due to Persian Gulf hostilities, creating a de facto Strait of Hormuz closure. This escalation jeopardizes global energy supply chains, with India facing critical vulnerability for its crude oil and LPG imports. Analysts warn of sustained price volatility, potential inflation spikes, and stalled global maritime trade, contrasting historical market resilience with current systemic risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 02:31:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4f6743d2913aa7c21eff1_1772418822717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Siemens Energy, Polycab: Top Picks Amidst Sector Tailwinds &amp; Geopolitical Crosscurrents</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Siemens-Energy-Polycab-Top-Picks-Amidst-Sector-Tailwinds-and-Geopolitical-Crosscurrents/69a4f6713d2913aa7c21efa5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Siemens-Energy-Polycab-Top-Picks-Amidst-Sector-Tailwinds-and-Geopolitical-Crosscurrents/69a4f6713d2913aa7c21efa5</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services has named Siemens Energy and Polycab India as its premier stock recommendations for the week commencing March 2, 2026. Siemens Energy is positioned to benefit from T&amp;D capex and energy transition, supported by a robust order backlog. Polycab is capitalizing on market share gains in Cables &amp; Wires, driven by distribution and product portfolio strength. Both companies face evolving market dynamics, including commodity price fluctuations and broader economic conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 02:31:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4f6713d2913aa7c21efa4_1772418794884.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's SEBI Tightens Insider Trading, Seeks Foreign Capital Amid Outflows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Indias-SEBI-Tightens-Insider-Trading-Seeks-Foreign-Capital-Amid-Outflows/69a4f2b23d2913aa7c21e5a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Indias-SEBI-Tightens-Insider-Trading-Seeks-Foreign-Capital-Amid-Outflows/69a4f2b23d2913aa7c21e5a0</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) Chair Tuhin Kanta Pandey is signaling a more robust crackdown on insider trading, including holding banks and consulting firms accountable, while simultaneously accelerating efforts to simplify foreign investment entry. This dual strategy aims to restore market confidence and reverse substantial foreign portfolio investor (FPI) outflows experienced in 2025. Recent data shows a rebound in FPI inflows in February 2026, but significant challenges remain in attracting sticky capital amidst global competition and domestic retail investor losses in derivatives trading.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 02:15:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4f2b23d2913aa7c21e59f_1772417864586.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rajputana Stainless IPO: Debt Focus Amidst Promoter Sale?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rajputana-Stainless-IPO-Debt-Focus-Amidst-Promoter-Sale/69a4f23a3d2913aa7c21e4f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rajputana-Stainless-IPO-Debt-Focus-Amidst-Promoter-Sale/69a4f23a3d2913aa7c21e4f2</guid><description>Rajputana Stainless begins its ₹255 crore IPO journey, setting a price band of ₹116-₹122. The Gujarat-based firm plans to channel funds into establishing a stainless steel seamless pipe facility and significantly repaying debt, signaling a strategic deleveraging alongside expansion. Promoters are also divesting ₹76 crore via an Offer for Sale, a move that warrants investor scrutiny for its implications on future growth capital and promoter commitment. The company aims for a ₹1,019 crore market cap upon listing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 02:13:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4f23a3d2913aa7c21e4f1_1772417731592.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amazon India's Fee Cut Signals Aggressive Land Grab</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Amazon-Indias-Fee-Cut-Signals-Aggressive-Land-Grab/69a4f2333d2913aa7c21e4d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Amazon-Indias-Fee-Cut-Signals-Aggressive-Land-Grab/69a4f2333d2913aa7c21e4d8</guid><description>Effective March 16, Amazon India is eliminating referral fees for sellers on products priced under ₹1,000, expanding a prior policy covering items below ₹300. This move, impacting over 125 million products, aims to attract small businesses and entrepreneurs, particularly in tier-2 and tier-3 cities. The strategy is a direct response to intense competition from Flipkart and Reliance, signaling a focus on market share expansion in India's rapidly growing e-commerce sector, even at the cost of immediate revenue from these transactions. This initiative is part of Amazon's broader commitment to invest heavily in the Indian market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 02:13:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4f2333d2913aa7c21e4d7_1772417718868.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Halts F&amp;O Reforms: Weighing Speculation vs. Economic Purpose</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Halts-FandO-Reforms-Weighing-Speculation-vs-Economic-Purpose/69a4eab53d2913aa7c21e1f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Halts-FandO-Reforms-Weighing-Speculation-vs-Economic-Purpose/69a4eab53d2913aa7c21e1f4</guid><description>SEBI Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey has announced a pause on new Futures and Options (F&amp;O) segment reforms, opting for a "wait and watch" strategy. This move prioritizes assessing the impact of recently implemented risk management measures, particularly concerning "hyperactivity" in short-dated options that may not serve significant economic purposes. The regulator will gather and analyze data before considering further policy adjustments, signaling a period of regulatory stability for Indian derivatives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 01:41:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4eab53d2913aa7c21e1f3_1772415817468.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Review Sparks MF Scheme Overhaul Amid Tax, Flexibility Clash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SEBI-Review-Sparks-MF-Scheme-Overhaul-Amid-Tax-Flexibility-Clash/69a4e9533d2913aa7c21e0a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SEBI-Review-Sparks-MF-Scheme-Overhaul-Amid-Tax-Flexibility-Clash/69a4e9533d2913aa7c21e0a9</guid><description>India's market regulator, SEBI, is reviewing industry feedback on the planned closure of solution-oriented mutual fund schemes and the introduction of lifecycle funds. Fund houses highlight potential investor tax burdens from mergers and operational challenges, while lifecycle funds face scrutiny over tax efficiency due to disparate equity and debt taxation, and potential inflexibility. SEBI Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey has signaled openness to discussion, indicating a possible reassessment of the directives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 01:35:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e9533d2913aa7c21e0a8_1772415456204.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Flows Signal Caution as India Eyes Earnings Rebound</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Flows-Signal-Caution-as-India-Eyes-Earnings-Rebound/69a4e3003d2913aa7c21dd8c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Flows-Signal-Caution-as-India-Eyes-Earnings-Rebound/69a4e3003d2913aa7c21dd8c</guid><description>January 2026 marked a significant shift as gold ETF inflows in India surpassed those into equity mutual funds for the first time, totaling ₹24,040 crore against ₹24,028 crore. This unprecedented move indicates a potential rise in investor risk aversion, overshadowing the consensus optimism for an earnings-led market recovery in 2026. While sectors like financials, industrials, and auto are projected to show strong earnings growth, elevated valuations, particularly in small and mid-caps, coupled with the sustained flight to gold, suggest a cautious undertone prevails. The Reserve Bank of India's decision to hold interest rates steady at 5.25% and benign inflation forecasts offer stability, but investor behavior signals a preference for capital preservation over aggressive growth chasing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 01:08:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e3003d2913aa7c21dd8b_1772413955592.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SFO Tech Secures ₹750 Cr for Expansion Amidst EMS Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SFO-Tech-Secures-750-Cr-for-Expansion-Amidst-EMS-Boom/69a4e2ff3d2913aa7c21dd74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SFO-Tech-Secures-750-Cr-for-Expansion-Amidst-EMS-Boom/69a4e2ff3d2913aa7c21dd74</guid><description>SFO Technologies secured over ₹750 crore in a funding round led by Trident Growth Partners and Amicus Capital Partners. The capital infusion is earmarked for significant manufacturing capacity expansion and backward integration into component manufacturing over the next two years. This strategic move positions SFO to bolster its global footprint as India's electronics manufacturing services sector witnesses rapid growth, driven by global supply chain realignments and increasing demand for sophisticated, resilient manufacturing partners.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 01:08:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e2ff3d2913aa7c21dd73_1772413912020.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Bullishness Meets Market Headwinds: Atul &amp; Pidilite Analyzed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Tech-Bullishness-Meets-Market-Headwinds-Atul-and-Pidilite-Analyzed/69a4e2f83d2913aa7c21dd5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Tech-Bullishness-Meets-Market-Headwinds-Atul-and-Pidilite-Analyzed/69a4e2f83d2913aa7c21dd5d</guid><description>Angel One analysts have issued bullish technical recommendations for Atul Ltd and Pidilite Industries, citing positive chart patterns and indicator signals. However, a deeper dive reveals significant headwinds, including heightened geopolitical tensions impacting the broader market, elevated valuations for both firms, and specific operational concerns such as declining exports for Pidilite and subdued long-term growth for Atul. Despite positive short-term technical setups, a cautious institutional perspective is warranted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 01:08:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e2f83d2913aa7c21dd5c_1772413867192.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LPG Vulnerability Outstrips Crude Oil in Hormuz Crisis; Macros at Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/LPG-Vulnerability-Outstrips-Crude-Oil-in-Hormuz-Crisis-Macros-at-Risk/69a4e28c3d2913aa7c21dcac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/LPG-Vulnerability-Outstrips-Crude-Oil-in-Hormuz-Crisis-Macros-at-Risk/69a4e28c3d2913aa7c21dcac</guid><description>India's energy security faces a heightened threat, with Liquefied Petroleum Gas (LPG) imports proving far more vulnerable to Strait of Hormuz disruptions than crude oil. While crude supplies are buffered by significant inventories, nearly all of India's LPG transit the critical chokepoint, lacking comparable strategic reserves. This exposure directly impacts the nation's import bill, potentially widening the current account deficit and pressuring the rupee, with analysts warning of significant macroeconomic fallout if tensions persist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 01:06:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e28c3d2913aa7c21dcab_1772413731424.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Storms Batter Indian Equities; E2W Race Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitical-Storms-Batter-Indian-Equities-E2W-Race-Intensifies/69a4e0a83d2913aa7c21db4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitical-Storms-Batter-Indian-Equities-E2W-Race-Intensifies/69a4e0a83d2913aa7c21db4d</guid><description>Heightened geopolitical tensions in West Asia are directly impacting Indian markets, pushing crude oil prices higher and creating sector-specific headwinds, particularly for oil marketing companies, aviation, and paint manufacturers. The electric two-wheeler segment is witnessing a significant shift, with Ola Electric losing market share to established players like TVS Motor and Bajaj Auto. Maruti Suzuki continues to grapple with production constraints amidst strong demand, while Adani Power faces scrutiny over its Bangladesh power deal. SpiceJet navigates ongoing legal financial obligations, and Abbott India expands its diabetes drug offerings amidst evolving market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 00:58:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e0a83d2913aa7c21db4c_1772413692298.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI's Derivatives Stance: Stability Over Speculation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-Derivatives-Stance-Stability-Over-Speculation/69a4e0733d2913aa7c21dabd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-Derivatives-Stance-Stability-Over-Speculation/69a4e0733d2913aa7c21dabd</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey signaled a deliberate pause in further derivatives market actions, prioritizing policy stability and impact analysis of recent measures. The regulator's focus remains squarely on curbing speculative excesses within options trading, particularly index and weekly expiries. Concurrently, SEBI is bolstering the SME IPO framework through enhanced due diligence and is poised to deliberate on conflict of interest report recommendations. The central bank's new bank guarantee rules for proprietary trading are also under SEBI's watchful eye, aiming to balance risk mitigation with market liquidity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 00:57:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4e0733d2913aa7c21dabc_1772413147784.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>