<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:19:41 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Rupee Weakness Tied to Global Flux, CEA Nageswaran Cites</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Weakness-Tied-to-Global-Flux-CEA-Nageswaran-Cites/697f8daf47db7081af64324b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Weakness-Tied-to-Global-Flux-CEA-Nageswaran-Cites/697f8daf47db7081af64324b</guid><description>The Indian rupee's recent depreciation is attributed by Chief Economic Adviser V. Anantha Nageswaran primarily to global economic headwinds and volatile capital flows, rather than domestic fiscal measures. While acknowledging the rupee is "punching below its weight," Nageswaran noted its weaker value provides a buffer against global tariffs and bolsters export competitiveness. A sustained currency recovery hinges on improved global sentiment, potentially aided by a resolution to trade tensions with the United States. Despite near-term volatility, the government views the current exchange rate as consistent with growth objectives.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:01:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f8daf47db7081af64324a_1769979665158.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Shifts Buyback Tax to Capital Gains, Aims for Investor Fairness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Shifts-Buyback-Tax-to-Capital-Gains-Aims-for-Investor-Fairness/697f8e9647db7081af64344d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Shifts-Buyback-Tax-to-Capital-Gains-Aims-for-Investor-Fairness/697f8e9647db7081af64344d</guid><description>The Indian government has moved to reclassify proceeds from share buybacks from dividend income to capital gains, a significant policy shift announced in the Budget 2026-27. This change ensures individual investors are taxed only on profits, exempting their principal investment. While intended to provide fairness and encourage capital return mechanisms, the government has introduced higher tax rates for promoters to prevent arbitrage, setting effective rates at 22% for corporate promoters and 30% for non-corporate promoters.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f8e9647db7081af64344c_1769977928163.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Spurs Tier-II/III Cities With ₹5,000 Cr/Region</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Spurs-Tier-IIIII-Cities-With-5000-CrRegion/697fb05647db7081af648469</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Spurs-Tier-IIIII-Cities-With-5000-CrRegion/697fb05647db7081af648469</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 has unveiled a significant initiative to develop 'city economic regions' (CERs) in India's Tier-II and Tier-III cities. An allocation of ₹5,000 crore per region over five years is designated to foster economic growth and structured urban development. Seven key urban clusters have been identified for this push, signalling a strategic focus on unlocking the potential of secondary urban centres.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:00:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697fb05647db7081af648468_1769976044269.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Traceable Gold: Betts Family Forges New Standard</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Traceable-Gold-Betts-Family-Forges-New-Standard/697f90ed47db7081af643b06</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Traceable-Gold-Betts-Family-Forges-New-Standard/697f90ed47db7081af643b06</guid><description>Amidst surging gold prices and heightened ESG scrutiny, Dan and Charlie Betts are championing S.M.O. gold, a system designed to guarantee traceable and responsibly sourced precious metals. Leveraging their family's centuries-old refining legacy, the brothers are implementing rigorous chain-of-custody audits and ESG benchmarks to differentiate gold from mines like Endeavour Mining and Bellevue Gold, responding to growing consumer and industry demand for ethical provenance in a market historically plagued by opacity and illicit activities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:57:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f90ed47db7081af643b05_1769975823497.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Urban Hubs to Drive Real Estate Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Budget-2026-Urban-Hubs-to-Drive-Real-Estate-Growth/697fac9547db7081af647d73</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Budget-2026-Urban-Hubs-to-Drive-Real-Estate-Growth/697fac9547db7081af647d73</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 prioritizes urban agglomerations as growth engines, signaling a strategic pivot away from direct real estate incentives. A key allocation of ₹5,000 crore targets infrastructure development in Tier 2 and 3 cities, aiming to stimulate residential, retail, and hospitality sectors. The budget also emphasizes enhanced regional connectivity through seven high-speed rail corridors and proposes monetizing public sector assets via dedicated REITs to attract institutional investment and broaden development opportunities across India.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:52:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697fac9547db7081af647d72_1769975531058.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Duty Cuts Bolster Electronics, Dixon Eyes Stability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Budget-2026-Duty-Cuts-Bolster-Electronics-Dixon-Eyes-Stability/697fac3747db7081af647c4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Budget-2026-Duty-Cuts-Bolster-Electronics-Dixon-Eyes-Stability/697fac3747db7081af647c4f</guid><description>India's Budget 2026 introduces a critical two-year extension for concessional customs duties on key imported electronics components, set to expire in March. This move, detailed in the Finance Bill, 2026 memorandum, directly alleviates immediate price pressure risks for manufacturers of televisions, microwaves, and other consumer electronics. The extension, effective until March 2028, is a significant boost for the 'Make in India' initiative and ensures continued cost competitiveness for domestic producers like Dixon Technologies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:47:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697fac3747db7081af647c4e_1769975238035.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes NBFC Consolidation for Power Sector Scale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Eyes-NBFC-Consolidation-for-Power-Sector-Scale/697fac2147db7081af647b5e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Eyes-NBFC-Consolidation-for-Power-Sector-Scale/697fac2147db7081af647b5e</guid><description>The Indian budget has initiated a significant restructuring plan for state-owned non-banking financial companies REC Ltd and Power Finance Corp. Ltd. The move aims to consolidate operations, achieve greater scale, and modernize business models. This strategic overhaul is designed to unlock critical capital for the electricity sector's substantial investment needs, supporting both economic growth and the nation's energy transition objectives. While specifics are awaited, the proposal targets enhanced efficiency and risk management to bolster lending capacity for vital infrastructure projects.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:42:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697fac2147db7081af647b5d_1769974943857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Fiscal Prudence Over Populism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Fiscal-Prudence-Over-Populism/697fa9ca47db7081af646736</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Fiscal-Prudence-Over-Populism/697fa9ca47db7081af646736</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Union Budget 2026-27 eschews pre-election state-specific handouts, favoring fiscal prudence and targeted economic initiatives. The budget prioritizes manufacturing, infrastructure, and MSMEs, while addressing concerns over 'freebies' flagged by the Economic Survey. Despite initial market volatility driven by tax changes, the long-term focus remains on sustainable growth and India's global economic stature.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:32:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697fa9ca47db7081af646735_1769974305451.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paradip Port Authority: Record January Cargo</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Paradip-Port-Authority-Record-January-Cargo/697fa6f547db7081af646543</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Paradip-Port-Authority-Record-January-Cargo/697fa6f547db7081af646543</guid><description>Paradip Port Authority established a new monthly record, handling 14.44 million metric tonnes (MMT) of cargo in January 2025. This achievement surpasses the previous January 2024 record of 14.32 MMT, underscoring significant operational enhancements and the port's escalating importance in facilitating India's international trade. The surge reflects sustained infrastructure upgrades, process optimization, and improved stakeholder coordination.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697fa6f547db7081af646542_1769973610496.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Energy Security &amp; Growth Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Budget-2026-Energy-Security-and-Growth-Drive/697f934547db7081af6440e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Budget-2026-Energy-Security-and-Growth-Drive/697f934547db7081af6440e8</guid><description>Union Budget 2026, presented February 1st, reinforces India's commitment to decarbonisation and energy security, aiming to sustain robust economic growth. Petroleum Minister Hardeep Singh Puri highlighted key allocations, including ₹20,000 crore for Carbon Capture, Utilisation, and Storage (CCUS), and a significant increase in biofuel blending to 20%. The budget also prioritizes diversifying crude oil import sources, expanding the supplier base to 41 countries, a strategy aimed at navigating global energy turmoil.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f934547db7081af6440e7_1769973434281.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Finance Commission Realigns State Funds With GDP Contribution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Finance-Commission-Realigns-State-Funds-With-GDP-Contribution/697f90f547db7081af643b17</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Finance-Commission-Realigns-State-Funds-With-GDP-Contribution/697f90f547db7081af643b17</guid><description>India's fiscal distribution is shifting. The 16th Finance Commission's new formula for 2026-31 heavily weights states' contribution to Gross Domestic Product (GDP), rewarding economic performance. Karnataka emerges as a prime beneficiary, securing substantial additional funds. Conversely, Madhya Pradesh and other populous states face reduced allocations. This represents a significant recalibration of Centre-state fiscal relations, prioritizing economic output alongside equity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:14:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f90f547db7081af643b16_1769973183428.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Space Budget Gets 10% Boost Amid Industry Call for Deeper Reforms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Space-Budget-Gets-10percent-Boost-Amid-Industry-Call-for-Deeper-Reforms/697f972c47db7081af644d4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Space-Budget-Gets-10percent-Boost-Amid-Industry-Call-for-Deeper-Reforms/697f972c47db7081af644d4a</guid><description>The Department of Space (DoS) has been allocated Rs 13,705.6 crore for fiscal year 2026-27, a 10% rise over revised estimates, signalling government commitment to advancing space missions and infrastructure. This budget prioritizes capital expenditure for projects like the Gaganyaan program and next-generation launch vehicles. However, key industry associations note the absence of direct fiscal incentives, urging for measures like GST rationalization and critical infrastructure status to spur private sector growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:07:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f972c47db7081af644d49_1769972833762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Elevates India Healthcare, MVT Hubs Drive Stock Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Budget-2026-Elevates-India-Healthcare-MVT-Hubs-Drive-Stock-Gains/697f977b47db7081af644e47</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Budget-2026-Elevates-India-Healthcare-MVT-Hubs-Drive-Stock-Gains/697f977b47db7081af644e47</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 targets healthcare as a primary economic growth driver, unveiling plans for Medical Value Tourism (MVT) hubs and the Biopharma SHAKTI initiative. With increased fiscal allocation, an emphasis on mental health, and a push for preventive care, the budget aims to bolster both global competitiveness and domestic healthcare access. This strategic reorientation has already spurred positive market reactions, with hospital stocks, including Apollo Hospitals, registering gains.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f977b47db7081af644e46_1769972581212.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Boosts India's Solar Power Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Budget-Boosts-Indias-Solar-Power-Push/697f978d47db7081af644edc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Budget-Boosts-Indias-Solar-Power-Push/697f978d47db7081af644edc</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 earmarks over 80% of the Ministry of New &amp; Renewable Energy's (MNRE) outlay for the PM Surya Ghar Muft Bijli Yojana and PM-KUSUM. This substantial allocation targets a significant expansion of distributed renewable energy (DRE), aiming to empower households and farmers while boosting clean energy consumption. The increased funding signals a strategic commitment to energy independence and domestic solar manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:46:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f978d47db7081af644edb_1769971528423.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts IB Funding 63% Amid Security Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Boosts-IB-Funding-63percent-Amid-Security-Overhaul/697f970347db7081af644c5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Boosts-IB-Funding-63percent-Amid-Security-Overhaul/697f970347db7081af644c5b</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 has allocated Rs 6,782 crore to the Intelligence Bureau (IB), a substantial 63% increase from the previous fiscal year. This surge, driven by the IB's critical role in counter-terrorism and internal security operations, precedes a comprehensive agency augmentation plan. The budget also enhances border infrastructure, modernizes immigration systems, and bolsters the Inter-Operable Criminal Justice System, reflecting a broader national security and technological upgrade strategy.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:40:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f970347db7081af644c5a_1769971204487.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindalco's $6B Push in Indian Aluminium, Copper</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindalcos-6B-Push-in-Indian-Aluminium-Copper/697f961347db7081af644a34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindalcos-6B-Push-in-Indian-Aluminium-Copper/697f961347db7081af644a34</guid><description>Aditya Birla Group's Hindalco Industries is committing $6 billion over five years to expand upstream aluminium and copper production within India. This significant capital outlay targets mining and primary processing, aiming to bolster the company's global standing and capitalize on burgeoning domestic industrial demand. The move signals a strategy to secure raw materials and build a more resilient supply chain, potentially reducing import reliance and influencing market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f961347db7081af644a33_1769971071005.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Budget Bets on Talent, Not Just Chips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Budget-Bets-on-Talent-Not-Just-Chips/697f95da47db7081af644948</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Budget-Bets-on-Talent-Not-Just-Chips/697f95da47db7081af644948</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 charts a course towards an AI-driven economy, emphasizing investments in semiconductors and advanced manufacturing. This ambitious plan critically depends on fostering widespread AI literacy and a skilled workforce, supported by new initiatives like 15,000 AI labs in schools and 10,000 technology fellowships, to solidify India's position as a global technology hub.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:36:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f95da47db7081af644947_1769970897263.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Semiconductor Mission to ₹40K Cr, Eyes Capability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Boosts-Semiconductor-Mission-to-40K-Cr-Eyes-Capability/697f95a347db7081af64484c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Boosts-Semiconductor-Mission-to-40K-Cr-Eyes-Capability/697f95a347db7081af64484c</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 allocated ₹40,000 crore to the India Semiconductor Mission (ISM) 2.0, marking a strategic shift from expanding manufacturing capacity to cultivating comprehensive capability. The initiative emphasizes developing Indian companies across the entire semiconductor value chain, including design, equipment, materials, and intellectual property (IP), aiming to enhance domestic ownership, resilience, and long-term strategic control.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f95a347db7081af64484b_1769970789445.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Raises Duty-Free Limits, Igniting Travel Retail Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Raises-Duty-Free-Limits-Igniting-Travel-Retail-Sector/697f952547db7081af6446da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Raises-Duty-Free-Limits-Igniting-Travel-Retail-Sector/697f952547db7081af6446da</guid><description>Effective February 2, 2026, India has significantly increased duty-free allowances for arriving passengers. Residents and tourists of Indian origin can now bring in goods valued up to ₹75,000, a substantial rise from ₹50,000. Foreign tourists also see an uplift, with their limit moving from ₹15,000 to ₹25,000. These changes, part of the Union Budget 2026, aim to reflect current economic realities and are expected to bolster the travel retail and tourism industries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:32:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f952547db7081af6446d9_1769970746175.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fiscal Future: 16th FC Report Reshapes State Finances</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Future-16th-FC-Report-Reshapes-State-Finances/697f943c47db7081af644507</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Future-16th-FC-Report-Reshapes-State-Finances/697f943c47db7081af644507</guid><description>The 16th Finance Commission has submitted its report, maintaining states' 41% share of central taxes while introducing a GDP contribution metric for distribution. The report advocates for outcome-based spending, fiscal discipline, and rationalization of schemes. The government has accepted these recommendations, including ₹1.4 lakh crore in grants for FY2026-27, signaling a recalibration of fiscal federalism.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:28:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f943c47db7081af644506_1769970467404.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Mega Infra Push Fuels Urban Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Budget-2026-Mega-Infra-Push-Fuels-Urban-Growth/697f93bd47db7081af6443a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Budget-2026-Mega-Infra-Push-Fuels-Urban-Growth/697f93bd47db7081af6443a9</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 allocates significant capital to key growth sectors. Over ₹21,625 crore is directed towards urban housing initiatives like PMAY-Urban and PMAY-Urban 2.0, aiming to accelerate project completion. A ₹10,000 crore Urban Challenge Fund and CPSE asset recycling via REITs are poised to revitalize urban redevelopment. Major transport upgrades include new Dedicated Freight Corridors and operationalizing 20 National Waterways, alongside a scheme to double coastal shipping's role. These measures collectively aim to integrate urban development with national sustainability goals.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:27:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f93bd47db7081af6443a8_1769970441975.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Budget Surge Triggers Stock Sell-Off on Unmet Expectations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Budget-Surge-Triggers-Stock-Sell-Off-on-Unmet-Expectations/697f935247db7081af64415c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Budget-Surge-Triggers-Stock-Sell-Off-on-Unmet-Expectations/697f935247db7081af64415c</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 dramatically increased India's defence expenditure to ₹7.84 lakh crore, a 15% rise. Despite this record allocation and a 21.8% jump in capital spending for modernization, the defence sector experienced a sharp correction on February 1, 2026. Investors reacted negatively to the capital expenditure hike falling short of aggressive expectations and a significant increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives, leading to substantial market capitalisation erosion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:24:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f935247db7081af64415b_1769970003496.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget: Fiscal Prudence, Tech Push, and Job Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Fiscal-Prudence-Tech-Push-and-Job-Concerns/697f936e47db7081af644232</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Fiscal-Prudence-Tech-Push-and-Job-Concerns/697f936e47db7081af644232</guid><description>The Indian Union Budget 2026-27 emphasizes fiscal consolidation, targeting a 4.3% deficit, and introduces significant incentives for the technology sector, including a tax holiday for data centers until 2047. However, concerns linger regarding the adequacy of funding for semiconductor manufacturing and the budget's capacity to deliver promised job growth, despite numerous skilling initiatives.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:22:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f936e47db7081af644231_1769970174708.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Health Budget: Nominal Gains Mask Real-Term Decline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Health-Budget-Nominal-Gains-Mask-Real-Term-Decline/697f91f447db7081af643e6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Health-Budget-Nominal-Gains-Mask-Real-Term-Decline/697f91f447db7081af643e6a</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 presents a nominal increase in health and AYUSH allocations, reaching approximately ₹1.06 lakh crore. However, this rise is substantially diminished when adjusted for high medical inflation, resulting in real-term funding levels that are less than actual spending in 2020-21. The sector's share of GDP and the total Union budget has also declined, signaling a reduced governmental priority for public health infrastructure and services despite the introduction of new initiatives like Biopharma Shakti.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:18:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f91f447db7081af643e69_1769969822948.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: Mfg Ecosystem Gets Major Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Budget-2026-Mfg-Ecosystem-Gets-Major-Boost/697f91de47db7081af643da3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Budget-2026-Mfg-Ecosystem-Gets-Major-Boost/697f91de47db7081af643da3</guid><description>The Indian Union Budget 2026-27 signals a strategic pivot towards bolstering the domestic manufacturing ecosystem. Key initiatives include a substantial increase in government capital expenditure to ₹12.2 lakh crore, alongside targeted policy interventions and financial architecture reforms designed to propel sectors like biopharma, semiconductors, electronics, and textiles. The strategy moves beyond episodic incentives to foster a comprehensive industrial environment, aiming to enhance competitiveness and reduce import dependence amid a complex global economic climate.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:18:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f91de47db7081af643da2_1769969769157.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Slashes Crop Insurance, Underfunds Key Farm Schemes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Budget-2026-Slashes-Crop-Insurance-Underfunds-Key-Farm-Schemes/697f900147db7081af643927</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Budget-2026-Slashes-Crop-Insurance-Underfunds-Key-Farm-Schemes/697f900147db7081af643927</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 allocated Rs 1.62 lakh crore to agriculture, a 7% increase. However, crucial crop insurance (PMFBY) funding was reduced, despite escalating crop damage from extreme weather. Allocations for natural farming remain marginal, and several key missions announced last year received zero funding. An AI tool for agriculture, Bharat-VISTAAR, received Rs 150 crore, raising concerns among farmer groups.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:10:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f900147db7081af643926_1769969407172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Govt Explores PSU Stake Cuts; STT Hike Jolts Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Govt-Explores-PSU-Stake-Cuts-STT-Hike-Jolts-Markets/697f8d6947db7081af6430bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Govt-Explores-PSU-Stake-Cuts-STT-Hike-Jolts-Markets/697f8d6947db7081af6430bb</guid><description>Government officials are examining options to reduce stakes in public sector undertakings (PSUs) below 51%, a move potentially enabled by the Economic Survey's call to redefine 'government company' status. This policy flexibility coincides with a significant increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options, which triggered a broad market decline. Meanwhile, the strategic divestment of IDBI Bank has entered its final phase, with financial bids expected imminently.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f8d6947db7081af6430ba_1769968635182.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Fiscal Consolidation Meets Tech &amp; Infra Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Fiscal-Consolidation-Meets-Tech-and-Infra-Push/697f8b4d47db7081af642be7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Fiscal-Consolidation-Meets-Tech-and-Infra-Push/697f8b4d47db7081af642be7</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman presented Budget 2026-27 with a primary focus on fiscal discipline, setting a deficit target of 4.3% of GDP. The budget signals a commitment to macroeconomic stability through reforms like capping off-budget borrowings and aims to foster growth via substantial investments in infrastructure and emerging technologies, including AI and critical minerals. Despite revenue shortfalls in the previous fiscal year, the government recalibrated spending to maintain its deficit target, emphasizing a predictable multi-year capex pipeline.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:54:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f8b4d47db7081af642be6_1769968345693.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026 Boosts Livestock, Fisheries Sectors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Budget-2026-Boosts-Livestock-Fisheries-Sectors/697f89e347db7081af64296f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Budget-2026-Boosts-Livestock-Fisheries-Sectors/697f89e347db7081af64296f</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 signals a major strategic pivot, prioritizing livestock and fisheries as key drivers of India's agricultural economy. With a substantial increase in allocation to the Ministry of Fisheries, Animal Husbandry, and Dairying, the budget introduces targeted measures to enhance productivity, expand veterinary infrastructure, and bolster export competitiveness in these sectors. These initiatives are designed to capitalize on recent growth and address existing challenges, aiming for broader rural economic development.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:52:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f89e347db7081af64296e_1769968346222.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Balances Fiscal Prudence with Capex Surge in Budget 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Balances-Fiscal-Prudence-with-Capex-Surge-in-Budget-2026/697f884747db7081af64255c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Balances-Fiscal-Prudence-with-Capex-Surge-in-Budget-2026/697f884747db7081af64255c</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 prioritizes fiscal discipline by targeting a deficit of 4.3% of GDP, a notable reduction from previous peaks. This consolidation is coupled with a record high capital expenditure of 4.4% of GDP, aimed at unlocking supply-side constraints and driving economic growth. Industry leaders in logistics and rail infrastructure welcomed the increased allocation, anticipating strengthened trade ecosystems and enhanced mobility. This approach signals a commitment to macroeconomic stability alongside ambitious development goals.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f884747db7081af64255b_1769968058320.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Fiscal Prudence Meets Growth Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Fiscal-Prudence-Meets-Growth-Ambition/697f882247db7081af64246e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Fiscal-Prudence-Meets-Growth-Ambition/697f882247db7081af64246e</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27, presented on February 1, 2026, charts a course of continuity and fiscal consolidation, setting a fiscal deficit target of 4.3% for FY27 and boosting public capital expenditure to ₹12.2 lakh crore. The budget emphasizes infrastructure development, strategic high-technology sectors, and capital market reforms, aiming to foster investment-led growth within a stable macroeconomic framework, despite a significant market downturn triggered by derivatives tax increases.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:46:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f882247db7081af64246d_1769967912744.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tax Future: New Act, Budget Reforms Confirmed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Future-New-Act-Budget-Reforms-Confirmed/697f880747db7081af6423b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Future-New-Act-Budget-Reforms-Confirmed/697f880747db7081af6423b5</guid><description>India's tax landscape is set for a major transformation with the confirmation of a new Income Tax Act effective April 2026. Budget 2026 delivered 63 amendments to existing laws, alongside reforms to the Minimum Alternate Tax (MAT) regime, a new voluntary scheme for foreign asset declaration, and integration of ICDS into Indian Accounting Standards. These changes aim to simplify compliance and facilitate a smoother transition to the new tax framework, impacting corporate tax, international transactions, and individual taxpayer obligations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:44:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f880747db7081af6423b4_1769967773240.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Revives 200 Legacy Clusters for Manufacturing Power Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-Revives-200-Legacy-Clusters-for-Manufacturing-Power-Boost/697f872947db7081af64219d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-Revives-200-Legacy-Clusters-for-Manufacturing-Power-Boost/697f872947db7081af64219d</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman unveiled plans to revive 200 legacy industrial clusters, a significant move to enhance India's manufacturing competitiveness. This initiative aims to bolster the sector through infrastructure and technology upgrades, addressing global supply chain shifts and competition from East Asian economies. The government is focused on increasing manufacturing's contribution to India's GDP, a critical step towards achieving the 'Viksit Bharat' vision.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:40:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f872947db7081af64219c_1769967625049.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fertilizer Subsidy Bill Surges Amid Global Price Hikes, Weak Rupee</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Fertilizer-Subsidy-Bill-Surges-Amid-Global-Price-Hikes-Weak-Rupee/697f871c47db7081af6420e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Fertilizer-Subsidy-Bill-Surges-Amid-Global-Price-Hikes-Weak-Rupee/697f871c47db7081af6420e0</guid><description>The Indian government faces a mounting fiscal challenge as its fertilizer subsidy bill for FY25-26 has surpassed estimates by over Rs 18,500 crore, reaching Rs 1,86,460 crore. This overshoot is driven by a combination of static domestic prices that fuel consumption, a significant increase in global fertilizer input costs, and the persistent depreciation of the Indian rupee.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f871c47db7081af6420df_1769967535606.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India Resumes Shanghai-Delhi Flights Amidst Diplomatic Thaw</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Resumes-Shanghai-Delhi-Flights-Amidst-Diplomatic-Thaw/697f8f8847db7081af6437e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Resumes-Shanghai-Delhi-Flights-Amidst-Diplomatic-Thaw/697f8f8847db7081af6437e8</guid><description>Air India has relaunched its direct Shanghai-Delhi flight, ending a nearly six-year hiatus. The inaugural flight carried over 230 passengers on a Boeing 787-8 Dreamliner, operating four times weekly. This service resumption is a tangible outcome of normalizing bilateral ties between India and China, following the resolution of border tensions and previous COVID-19 related suspensions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Eyes $2 Trillion Exports by 2032 Driven by Budget Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-2-Trillion-Exports-by-2032-Driven-by-Budget-Boost/697f8f3547db7081af64368d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-2-Trillion-Exports-by-2032-Driven-by-Budget-Boost/697f8f3547db7081af64368d</guid><description>Commerce Minister Piyush Goyal stated India is nearing its $2 trillion export target by 2032. The Union Budget 2026-27 is set to propel this growth, with key focuses on labour-intensive industries, services, and attracting foreign investment via data center tax holidays. This strategy aims to create jobs and boost domestic consumption.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Simplifies NRI Property Deal TDS</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Budget-2026-Simplifies-NRI-Property-Deal-TDS/697f8f2747db7081af6435fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Budget-2026-Simplifies-NRI-Property-Deal-TDS/697f8f2747db7081af6435fd</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 introduces a significant procedural reform for property transactions involving non-resident sellers. Resident buyers will now use their Permanent Account Number (PAN) for Tax Deducted at Source (TDS) compliance, eliminating the prior requirement to obtain a Tax Deduction and Collection Account Number (TAN). This change, effective October 1, 2026, aims to drastically reduce compliance burdens, speed up deal closures, and simplify the process for both buyers and sellers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Shifts Fiscal Anchor to Debt-to-GDP Ratio</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Shifts-Fiscal-Anchor-to-Debt-to-GDP-Ratio/697f869d47db7081af641f9a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Shifts-Fiscal-Anchor-to-Debt-to-GDP-Ratio/697f869d47db7081af641f9a</guid><description>India's latest Union Budget pivots its primary fiscal benchmark from deficit reduction to the debt-to-GDP ratio, targeting 55.6% by FY27. This strategic shift aims to free up resources by managing interest payments, yet comes as gross government borrowing surges to ₹17.2 lakh crore and interest outlays exceed capital expenditure projections. While the government touts fiscal prudence, the market reaction saw a notable jump in volatility.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:36:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f869d47db7081af641f99_1769967382009.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Chairman Sees Credit Growth Boost Post-Budget</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Chairman-Sees-Credit-Growth-Boost-Post-Budget/697f862847db7081af641e54</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Chairman-Sees-Credit-Growth-Boost-Post-Budget/697f862847db7081af641e54</guid><description>State Bank of India Chairman CS Setty anticipates that the Union Budget 2026's emphasis on services and manufacturing will spur corporate credit growth. While acknowledging bond market jitters over the government's ₹17.2 trillion borrowing target for FY27, Setty suggested that buybacks and T-bill adjustments could mitigate the impact. He also characterized the budget's fiscal assumptions as conservative, with understated revenue estimates.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:34:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f862847db7081af641e53_1769967274526.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MOIL Hikes Manganese Ore Prices, Stock Drops 8.8%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MOIL-Hikes-Manganese-Ore-Prices-Stock-Drops-88percent/697f85ad47db7081af641cd9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MOIL-Hikes-Manganese-Ore-Prices-Stock-Drops-88percent/697f85ad47db7081af641cd9</guid><description>State-owned MOIL Ltd has implemented a 5% price increase for most manganese ore grades, effective February 1, 2026, impacting ferro and chemical categories. While some specific grades like BG4584 and certain SMGR variants maintain January pricing, others like UKF532 see a 10% rise. The announcement preceded an 8.82% drop in MOIL's share price, reflecting market sensitivity to input cost adjustments within the steel sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:33:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f85ad47db7081af641cd8_1769967225847.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>