<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:24:29 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Slashes Import Red Tape: A Bold Move for US Trade Deal Success?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Slashes-Import-Red-Tape-A-Bold-Move-for-US-Trade-Deal-Success/694c25afe10c98d07887ddee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Slashes-Import-Red-Tape-A-Bold-Move-for-US-Trade-Deal-Success/694c25afe10c98d07887ddee</guid><description>India has announced significant reforms to simplify import quality checks, reducing paperwork and speeding up approvals. This move directly addresses concerns raised by the United States regarding "burdensome" requirements and comes as both nations negotiate a trade agreement. Jaxay Shah, Chairman of the Quality Council of India, highlighted the aim to make quality assurance faster and more transparent through technology.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:32:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c25afe10c98d07887dded_1766598828807.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SHOCKING LOW PRICES: India's Massive 10,900 E-Bus Tender Results Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/SHOCKING-LOW-PRICES-Indias-Massive-10900-E-Bus-Tender-Results-Revealed/694c2573e10c98d07887dda4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/SHOCKING-LOW-PRICES-Indias-Massive-10900-E-Bus-Tender-Results-Revealed/694c2573e10c98d07887dda4</guid><description>Convergence Energy Services Ltd (CESL) has concluded a major tender for 10,900 electric buses across five Indian cities under the PM E-Drive scheme. The discovered prices are significantly lower than initially estimated, with PMI Electro Mobility, EKA Mobility, and Olectra Greentech securing large orders. Despite a dispute involving OHM Global Mobility, the tender proceeds, aiming to accelerate electric public transport adoption and reduce operational costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:29:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c2573e10c98d07887dda3_1766598187360.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Trade TURBULENCE: Record Exports Face US Tariff Fury! Can New Deals Save the Day?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-TURBULENCE-Record-Exports-Face-US-Tariff-Fury-Can-New-Deals-Save-the-Day/694c1ec0e10c98d078853dc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-TURBULENCE-Record-Exports-Face-US-Tariff-Fury-Can-New-Deals-Save-the-Day/694c1ec0e10c98d078853dc3</guid><description>India's trade in 2025 saw record $825.25 billion exports, a 6.05% rise. However, US tariffs, escalating to 50%, posed major challenges, particularly for textiles and leather. Despite geopolitical headwinds and slow US trade talks, India is diversifying with new FTAs with the UK, Oman, and New Zealand, aiming to cushion the blow and secure future growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:01:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c1ec0e10c98d078853dc2_1766597124450.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gujarat Shatters Solar Records: 5 Lakh Homes Go Green, 1879 MW Powering Future! See How!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Gujarat-Shatters-Solar-Records-5-Lakh-Homes-Go-Green-1879-MW-Powering-Future-See-How/694c1d27e10c98d0787fe69f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Gujarat-Shatters-Solar-Records-5-Lakh-Homes-Go-Green-1879-MW-Powering-Future-See-How/694c1d27e10c98d0787fe69f</guid><description>Gujarat has installed over 5 lakh rooftop solar systems, totaling 1,879 MW capacity under the PM Surya Ghar: Muft Bijli Yojna. This achievement makes Gujarat the national leader in rooftop solar adoption, with over 11 lakh installations cumulatively. The state has met 50% of its March 2027 target for 10 lakh residential rooftop solar systems and provided ₹3,778 crore in subsidies, making solar accessible and affordable. Citizen-friendly policies, including waived charges and attractive subsidies, further boost adoption. Success stories will be highlighted at the upcoming Vibrant Gujarat Regional Conference in Rajkot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:56:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c1d27e10c98d0787fe69e_1766596413090.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Trade Triumphs: Delhi Secures Major Deals with New Zealand, UK, and Oman!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Triumphs-Delhi-Secures-Major-Deals-with-New-Zealand-UK-and-Oman/694c1755e10c98d0787e9a31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Triumphs-Delhi-Secures-Major-Deals-with-New-Zealand-UK-and-Oman/694c1755e10c98d0787e9a31</guid><description>India is strategically forging new trade agreements, focusing on swift, pragmatic deals with countries like New Zealand, the United Kingdom, and Oman. These agreements aim to boost India's market access for key sectors like gems, textiles, and pharmaceuticals, while securing investment and phased access for its partners' products. While negotiations with the US remain stalled, progress is noted with the EU, highlighting India's proactive approach to expanding global trade relationships.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:30:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c1755e10c98d0787e9a30_1766594515797.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI in 2026: Prepare for a Workplace Revolution! Your Job is About to Change Forever</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-in-2026-Prepare-for-a-Workplace-Revolution-Your-Job-is-About-to-Change-Forever/694c1603e10c98d0787e23e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-in-2026-Prepare-for-a-Workplace-Revolution-Your-Job-is-About-to-Change-Forever/694c1603e10c98d0787e23e1</guid><description>By 2026, Artificial Intelligence will transform workplaces, moving beyond innovation to embedding within daily workflows. Expect AI tools to become essential, akin to using a computer. Roles like 'query writers' will fade as 'semantic architects' emerge, defining data context. Human oversight and 'taste' will become crucial skills, distinguishing top talent as AI handles routine tasks, dramatically speeding up processes like meeting preparation from hours to mere minutes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:21:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c1603e10c98d0787e23e0_1766594856679.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Oman CEPA Unlocks $12.5 Billion Gulf Services Goldmine: SEPC Reveals Massive Opportunity!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Oman-CEPA-Unlocks-125-Billion-Gulf-Services-Goldmine-SEPC-Reveals-Massive-Opportunity/694c154de10c98d0787df360</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Oman-CEPA-Unlocks-125-Billion-Gulf-Services-Goldmine-SEPC-Reveals-Massive-Opportunity/694c154de10c98d0787df360</guid><description>India and Oman have signed a Comprehensive Economic Partnership Agreement (CEPA), creating an estimated $12.5 billion opportunity for Indian service providers in the Gulf. The Services Export Promotion Council (SEPC) anticipates significant growth in sectors like IT, business services, education, and healthcare, boosted by relaxed rules for professional mobility and intra-corporate transfers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:21:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c154de10c98d0787df35f_1766594400882.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Urgent Reforms Needed: Readers Demand Fairer Loan EMIs, Stronger Bank Trust &amp; Faster SEBI Scam Probes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Urgent-Reforms-Needed-Readers-Demand-Fairer-Loan-EMIs-Stronger-Bank-Trust-and-Faster-SEBI-Scam-Probes/694c153be10c98d0787dee4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Urgent-Reforms-Needed-Readers-Demand-Fairer-Loan-EMIs-Stronger-Bank-Trust-and-Faster-SEBI-Scam-Probes/694c153be10c98d0787dee4d</guid><description>Readers highlight critical issues facing India's financial sector. Concerns range from unfair floating-rate housing loan EMIs that automatically rise but require borrower action to decrease, to banks needing to rebuild trust for deposit growth amidst inflation. Additionally, a call for strengthened SEBI enforcement is made to expedite stock market scam investigations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:20:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c153be10c98d0787dee4c_1766593944908.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Opens Highway Riches! NHAI InvIT Gets SEBI Green Light, Retail Investors Can Now Own Road Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Opens-Highway-Riches-NHAI-InvIT-Gets-SEBI-Green-Light-Retail-Investors-Can-Now-Own-Road-Growth/694c14c5e10c98d0787dbbd4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Opens-Highway-Riches-NHAI-InvIT-Gets-SEBI-Green-Light-Retail-Investors-Can-Now-Own-Road-Growth/694c14c5e10c98d0787dbbd4</guid><description>National Highways Authority of India's (NHAI) Raajmarg Infra Investment Trust (RIIT) has received SEBI approval, allowing retail and domestic investors to participate in operational national highway assets. This move aims to monetize existing highways, recycle capital for future development, and broaden public investment in India's infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:16:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c14c5e10c98d0787dbbd3_1766594736986.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹530 Crore Bengaluru Deal Shakes Up Tech Hub: EAAA Alternatives Makes Massive Real Estate Play!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/530-Crore-Bengaluru-Deal-Shakes-Up-Tech-Hub-EAAA-Alternatives-Makes-Massive-Real-Estate-Play/694c0efee10c98d0787cc522</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/530-Crore-Bengaluru-Deal-Shakes-Up-Tech-Hub-EAAA-Alternatives-Makes-Massive-Real-Estate-Play/694c0efee10c98d0787cc522</guid><description>EAAA Alternatives, via its Rental Yield Plus fund, has acquired 376,000 sq ft of office space in Bengaluru's Embassy Manyata Business Park for ₹530 crore. This marks the fund's third investment, strengthening its presence in the prominent tech hub. Embassy REIT confirmed the divestment aligns with its capital recycling strategy, creating value for stakeholders. EAAA Alternatives, managing over ₹65,000 crore in assets, sees this as a strategic move to aggregate quality assets in resilient Indian markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:49:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c0efee10c98d0787cc521_1766592509390.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Rare Earths Grip Loosens... Slowly! Key Indian Industries Wait as Licenses Trickle Out</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Chinas-Rare-Earths-Grip-Loosens-Slowly-Key-Indian-Industries-Wait-as-Licenses-Trickle-Out/694c0e16e10c98d0787ca52a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Chinas-Rare-Earths-Grip-Loosens-Slowly-Key-Indian-Industries-Wait-as-Licenses-Trickle-Out/694c0e16e10c98d0787ca52a</guid><description>China is slowly issuing rare earth magnet export licenses to Indian companies, eight months after imposing restrictions. A few entities, including suppliers for Bosch, Honda, Maruti Suzuki, and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, have received approvals. India relies heavily on China for these critical materials used in automobiles, EVs, electronics, and defense. While many applications are pending, improving diplomatic relations may ease the process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:48:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c0e16e10c98d0787ca529_1766592673586.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Financial Pulse Check: Loan Rates, Bank Deposits &amp; SEBI's Trust Test!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Financial-Pulse-Check-Loan-Rates-Bank-Deposits-and-SEBIs-Trust-Test/694c0ebbe10c98d0787cc471</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Financial-Pulse-Check-Loan-Rates-Bank-Deposits-and-SEBIs-Trust-Test/694c0ebbe10c98d0787cc471</guid><description>Concerns rise over India's financial system as letters highlight issues. Floating-rate home loans face criticism for asymmetric EMI adjustments, favoring lenders. Banks grapple with weak deposit growth due to inflation fears, needing to rebuild customer trust. Meanwhile, the proposed Securities Markets Code, 2025, is welcomed, but calls intensify for SEBI to strengthen enforcement against market scams and improve investigation timelines to bolster investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:48:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c0ebbe10c98d0787cc470_1766592407112.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OYO Parent PRISM Secures Shareholder Nod for Massive Rs 6,650 Cr IPO!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/OYO-Parent-PRISM-Secures-Shareholder-Nod-for-Massive-Rs-6650-Cr-IPO/694c0c77e10c98d0787c5178</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/OYO-Parent-PRISM-Secures-Shareholder-Nod-for-Massive-Rs-6650-Cr-IPO/694c0c77e10c98d0787c5178</guid><description>PRISM, the parent company of hospitality major OYO, has received crucial shareholder approval to raise up to ₹6,650 crore through an Initial Public Offering (IPO). Shareholders also greenlit a 1:19 bonus issue of equity shares. This marks a significant step as PRISM, formerly Oravel Stays, intensifies preparations for its public listing after previous deferrals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:46:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c0c77e10c98d0787c5177_1766591793698.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Soars Ahead: Operations Stabilised, Ready for Holiday Rush &amp; New Long-Haul Flights!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Soars-Ahead-Operations-Stabilised-Ready-for-Holiday-Rush-and-New-Long-Haul-Flights/694c0216e10c98d0787b6084</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Soars-Ahead-Operations-Stabilised-Ready-for-Holiday-Rush-and-New-Long-Haul-Flights/694c0216e10c98d0787b6084</guid><description>IndiGo announced on December 24, 2025, that its operations are fully stabilised and ready for the upcoming holiday travel season. The airline is operating 2,100 to 2,200 flights daily, serving over a million customers every three days across 138 destinations. It successfully managed recent industry-wide disruptions, including dense fog, and is preparing to introduce its first Airbus A321XLR aircraft for longer routes, with plans to fly to Athens from Delhi and Mumbai starting January 23, 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:55:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c0216e10c98d0787b6083_1766589044571.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UltraTech Cement Unleashes Mega Expansion: India's Production Powerhouse Just Got Bigger! 🚀</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UltraTech-Cement-Unleashes-Mega-Expansion-Indias-Production-Powerhouse-Just-Got-Bigger/694c0126e10c98d0787b5ee9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UltraTech-Cement-Unleashes-Mega-Expansion-Indias-Production-Powerhouse-Just-Got-Bigger/694c0126e10c98d0787b5ee9</guid><description>UltraTech Cement, part of the Aditya Birla Group, has significantly boosted its production capabilities by commissioning an additional 1.8 million tonnes per annum (mtpa) of cement capacity. This expansion, split between its Dhule unit in Maharashtra (0.6 mtpa) and Nathdwara unit in Rajasthan (1.2 mtpa), raises the company's total domestic grey cement manufacturing capacity to an impressive 188.66 mtpa. With global capacity now at 194.06 mtpa, this move solidifies UltraTech's market leadership and its commitment to meeting India's growing infrastructure demands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:55:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c0126e10c98d0787b5ee8_1766589247787.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EU's Crypto Tax Law Kicks In: Reporting Mandatory From January 1st, Threatens Asset Seizure!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EUs-Crypto-Tax-Law-Kicks-In-Reporting-Mandatory-From-January-1st-Threatens-Asset-Seizure/694c015ce10c98d0787b5f34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EUs-Crypto-Tax-Law-Kicks-In-Reporting-Mandatory-From-January-1st-Threatens-Asset-Seizure/694c015ce10c98d0787b5f34</guid><description>The European Union's new crypto tax transparency law, DAC8, begins January 1st. Crypto service providers must report user data and transactions to tax authorities, who will share it across member states. This closes a reporting gap, offering authorities visibility similar to bank accounts, and non-compliance by users could lead to asset embargoes or seizure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:53:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c015ce10c98d0787b5f33_1766589307327.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fuel Demand Slows Sharply: Imports Rise as Gas Use Declines!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Fuel-Demand-Slows-Sharply-Imports-Rise-as-Gas-Use-Declines/694bfff2e10c98d0787b5d51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Fuel-Demand-Slows-Sharply-Imports-Rise-as-Gas-Use-Declines/694bfff2e10c98d0787b5d51</guid><description>India's petroleum product consumption growth has decelerated significantly to 1.4% in FY26, falling short of the historical 4% average. This slowdown, driven by fuel-efficient vehicles, CNG expansion, and electric mobility, has led to a rise in crude oil import dependence to 91%. Natural gas consumption also saw a 4.5% de-growth. However, lower crude oil prices have boosted marketing margins for Oil Marketing Companies (OMCs), supported by stable retail prices and government compensation for LPG under-recoveries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:45:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bfff2e10c98d0787b5d50_1766588549126.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fuel Network Shatters 1 Lakh Milestone: IOCL &amp; Nayara Fuel Rural Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Fuel-Network-Shatters-1-Lakh-Milestone-IOCL-and-Nayara-Fuel-Rural-Surge/694bff41e10c98d0787b5c5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Fuel-Network-Shatters-1-Lakh-Milestone-IOCL-and-Nayara-Fuel-Rural-Surge/694bff41e10c98d0787b5c5b</guid><description>India's fuel station network has surpassed 1 lakh outlets, with state-run Indian Oil Corporation (IOCL) and Rosneft-backed Nayara Energy leading a significant rural expansion. These companies account for over a third of their networks in villages. While IOCL has nearly 33% of its 41,000+ stations rural, Nayara Energy boasts about 31% of its 6,921 stations serving smaller towns. This expansion signals robust demand growth in India's automotive fuel sector, projected to increase by 5.37% annually until 2030.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:44:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bff41e10c98d0787b5c5a_1766588584256.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Prediction Dec 26: Bullish Bias Holds? Experts Reveal Crucial Support &amp; Resistance Levels!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Nifty-Prediction-Dec-26-Bullish-Bias-Holds-Experts-Reveal-Crucial-Support-and-Resistance-Levels/694bf9d4e10c98d0787b556d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Nifty-Prediction-Dec-26-Bullish-Bias-Holds-Experts-Reveal-Crucial-Support-and-Resistance-Levels/694bf9d4e10c98d0787b556d</guid><description>Indian stock markets, Sensex and Nifty, closed lower on Wednesday, December 24, ending a three-day rally amid volatile trade and subdued volumes. Analysts maintain a bullish outlook for Nifty's prediction on Friday, December 26, identifying support near 26,000 and resistance around 26,240-26,325. A stock-specific approach is recommended as the market anticipates consolidation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:24:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf9d4e10c98d0787b556c_1766587397037.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Panacea Biotech Scores Big: UNICEF Boosts Vaccine Orders by $8.9 Million!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Panacea-Biotech-Scores-Big-UNICEF-Boosts-Vaccine-Orders-by-89-Million/694bf949e10c98d0787b543f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Panacea-Biotech-Scores-Big-UNICEF-Boosts-Vaccine-Orders-by-89-Million/694bf949e10c98d0787b543f</guid><description>Panacea Biotec has received significant updates to its UNICEF contract for the WHO-pre-qualified Easyfive-TT pentavalent vaccine. Contract values for 2026 and 2027 have increased by a combined $5.25 million, and a new award for 2027 adds $3.68 million, totaling approximately $8.9 million in additional orders. This follows a substantial previous order for polio vaccines, strengthening the company's partnership with the UN agency. Panacea Biotec shares closed up 0.93%.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:24:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf949e10c98d0787b543e_1766586789087.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPF Claim Rejections Haunt Employees! Avoid These Costly Mistakes &amp; Secure Your Savings Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/EPF-Claim-Rejections-Haunt-Employees-Avoid-These-Costly-Mistakes-and-Secure-Your-Savings-Now/694bf992e10c98d0787b54c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/EPF-Claim-Rejections-Haunt-Employees-Avoid-These-Costly-Mistakes-and-Secure-Your-Savings-Now/694bf992e10c98d0787b54c8</guid><description>Many salaried employees face EPF claim rejections due to common, avoidable errors. Issues like incomplete KYC, name or bank details not matching EPFO records, inactive UAN, or incorrect withdrawal reasons are frequent culprits. Mismatched spellings between Aadhaar and PF portal, or invalid bank account details, can also lead to rejection. Employees are advised to meticulously check all personal and bank information, ensure their UAN is active and linked, and select correct withdrawal reasons. Submitting joint declaration forms for discrepancies and seeking guidance from employers or EPFO offices can help prevent these rejections and ensure timely access to PF savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:21:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf992e10c98d0787b54c7_1766587297852.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Novo Nordisk's Miracle Pill Approved: Stock Surges 9% – Is This the Future of Weight Loss?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisks-Miracle-Pill-Approved-Stock-Surges-9percent-Is-This-the-Future-of-Weight-Loss/694bf93be10c98d0787b540d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisks-Miracle-Pill-Approved-Stock-Surges-9percent-Is-This-the-Future-of-Weight-Loss/694bf93be10c98d0787b540d</guid><description>Novo Nordisk has received FDA approval for its new Wegovy weight-loss pill, a potential game-changer for the global obesity drug market. Clinical trials show the pill leads to an average 16.6% body weight loss over 64 weeks, surpassing competitor Eli Lilly's experimental pill. This convenient pill format may unlock the market for millions who avoid injections, positioning Novo Nordisk for a strong comeback.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:15:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf93be10c98d0787b540c_1766587016871.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Strikes Deal: Russian Crude Flows Back to Jamnagar Refinery Amid Sanctions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Reliance-Strikes-Deal-Russian-Crude-Flows-Back-to-Jamnagar-Refinery-Amid-Sanctions/694bf6d9e10c98d0787b50ab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Reliance-Strikes-Deal-Russian-Crude-Flows-Back-to-Jamnagar-Refinery-Amid-Sanctions/694bf6d9e10c98d0787b50ab</guid><description>Reliance Industries has resumed buying discounted Russian crude oil for its Jamnagar refinery in Gujarat. The company is sourcing barrels from non-sanctioned suppliers, a move expected to help stabilize India's overall purchases of Russian oil after a temporary halt due to international sanctions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:06:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf6d9e10c98d0787b50aa_1766586436122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Star's Sales Comeback: Early Wins Signal Hope, But What's Next for 2026?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Blue-Stars-Sales-Comeback-Early-Wins-Signal-Hope-But-Whats-Next-for-2026/694bf6b6e10c98d0787b507b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Blue-Stars-Sales-Comeback-Early-Wins-Signal-Hope-But-Whats-Next-for-2026/694bf6b6e10c98d0787b507b</guid><description>Blue Star Managing Director B Thiagarajan reports early signs of a pickup in air-conditioner sales after a difficult year for the industry. While the second half is expected to be better than the first, it won't fully compensate for the summer slowdown. Thiagarajan notes improved sales traction from the festive period through December and expresses optimism for the upcoming quarter and calendar year 2026, citing strong fundamentals. Challenges remain, including slower project finalisation and the upcoming energy label transition impacting costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:06:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf6b6e10c98d0787b507a_1766586675095.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Rs 1,000 Crore NCD Plan: Board Greenlights Draft Prospectus!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Adani-Enterprises-Rs-1000-Crore-NCD-Plan-Board-Greenlights-Draft-Prospectus/694bf177e10c98d0787b4ad3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Adani-Enterprises-Rs-1000-Crore-NCD-Plan-Board-Greenlights-Draft-Prospectus/694bf177e10c98d0787b4ad3</guid><description>Adani Enterprises Limited has approved the draft prospectus for its upcoming Non-Convertible Debenture (NCD) issuance, aiming to raise up to ₹1,000 crore. The fundraising plan includes a base issue of ₹500 crore with an option to retain an over-subscription of another ₹500 crore. The draft prospectus has been filed with the BSE, the National Stock Exchange of India, and the Securities and Exchange Board of India.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:49:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf177e10c98d0787b4ad2_1766584874144.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto Dealmaking Explodes: Record $8.6 Billion in M&amp;A Fueled by Landmark US Policy Shift!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-Dealmaking-Explodes-Record-86-Billion-in-MandA-Fueled-by-Landmark-US-Policy-Shift/694bf102e10c98d0787b49ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-Dealmaking-Explodes-Record-86-Billion-in-MandA-Fueled-by-Landmark-US-Policy-Shift/694bf102e10c98d0787b49ed</guid><description>Cryptocurrency mergers and acquisitions hit an all-time high of $8.6 billion in 2025, a significant jump from $2.17 billion the previous year. This surge is largely attributed to supportive regulatory developments from the Trump administration, which established a federal framework for stablecoins and tokenized assets. The favorable policy environment fueled 267 deals, an 18% increase, with major transactions including Deribit, Kraken's acquisition of NinjaTrader, and Ripple's significant purchase. Experts also cite a rush for licenses as financial institutions acquire firms to enter crypto markets amidst evolving global compliance rules like the EU's MiCA framework. Despite structural advancements and increased Total Value Locked (TVL) across ecosystems, 2025 saw stagnant large-cap token prices, highlighting a decoupling of network usage from market performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:46:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf102e10c98d0787b49ec_1766584759717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Logistics Giant Yatayat Corporation Eyes Stock Market Debut: IPO Filing Sparks Investor Buzz!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Logistics-Giant-Yatayat-Corporation-Eyes-Stock-Market-Debut-IPO-Filing-Sparks-Investor-Buzz/694bf0ade10c98d0787b48df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Logistics-Giant-Yatayat-Corporation-Eyes-Stock-Market-Debut-IPO-Filing-Sparks-Investor-Buzz/694bf0ade10c98d0787b48df</guid><description>Gujarat-based Yatayat Corporation India has filed preliminary IPO papers with SEBI to raise capital. The offering includes a fresh issue of 77 lakh shares and an offer-for-sale of 56 lakh shares by promoter Meena Praveen Aggarwal. Proceeds will primarily fund working capital needs and general corporate purposes. Yatayat Corporation reported significant profit growth in fiscal year 2025, with revenue increasing by 28.6 percent.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:46:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf0ade10c98d0787b48de_1766584659223.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IBBI's New Mandate: Beneficial Ownership Disclosure Now Key in Company Resolution Plans!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IBBIs-New-Mandate-Beneficial-Ownership-Disclosure-Now-Key-in-Company-Resolution-Plans/694bf05ce10c98d0787b47b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IBBIs-New-Mandate-Beneficial-Ownership-Disclosure-Now-Key-in-Company-Resolution-Plans/694bf05ce10c98d0787b47b5</guid><description>The Insolvency and Bankruptcy Board of India (IBBI) has made it mandatory to disclose beneficial ownership in resolution plans. This new rule requires identifying ultimate owners and their shareholding structures, aiming to curb opaque bids and prevent ineligible promoters from acquiring distressed companies. It enhances transparency and reduces post-resolution disputes, alongside requiring an affidavit for Section 32A eligibility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:39:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf05ce10c98d0787b47b4_1766584523122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Oil Tensions Rock Energy Flows: How India Is Masterfully Securing Cheaper Fuel!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Global-Oil-Tensions-Rock-Energy-Flows-How-India-Is-Masterfully-Securing-Cheaper-Fuel/694bf067e10c98d0787b4827</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Global-Oil-Tensions-Rock-Energy-Flows-How-India-Is-Masterfully-Securing-Cheaper-Fuel/694bf067e10c98d0787b4827</guid><description>India's oil refiners are skillfully navigating 2025's geopolitical and trade challenges, including US sanctions on Russian oil. By diversifying suppliers to the UAE, Saudi Arabia, the US, Brazil, and African nations, India is ensuring energy security and affordable fuel prices for its citizens, maintaining strategic autonomy amidst global volatility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf067e10c98d0787b4826_1766584662893.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Two-Wheeler Exports Surge 24%! Latin America &amp; Africa Fueling Massive Global Demand!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Two-Wheeler-Exports-Surge-24percent-Latin-America-and-Africa-Fueling-Massive-Global-Demand/694befbbe10c98d0787b46ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Two-Wheeler-Exports-Surge-24percent-Latin-America-and-Africa-Fueling-Massive-Global-Demand/694befbbe10c98d0787b46ea</guid><description>Indian two-wheeler exports have seen a remarkable 24% year-on-year growth from April to November 2025, driven by strong demand in key markets like Latin America and Africa. A total of 42,43,330 units were exported. Motorcycles accounted for 87% of these exports, showing a 27% increase, while scooters grew by 8%. Bajaj Auto Limited, TVS Motor Company, and Hero MotoCorp Limited are leading this export momentum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:38:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694befbbe10c98d0787b46e9_1766584527273.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NTPC Green Energy Ignites India's Power Grid: 69 MW Solar Capacity Comes Online!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/NTPC-Green-Energy-Ignites-Indias-Power-Grid-69-MW-Solar-Capacity-Comes-Online/694bea5ce10c98d0787b4228</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/NTPC-Green-Energy-Ignites-Indias-Power-Grid-69-MW-Solar-Capacity-Comes-Online/694bea5ce10c98d0787b4228</guid><description>NTPC Green Energy Limited has successfully commissioned an additional 69.04 MW of solar power capacity at its Khavda-I project in Gujarat. This expansion brings the total commercial operational capacity of the NTPC Green Energy Group to 7,996.30 MW, reinforcing its significant role in India's renewable energy landscape. The Khavda project is situated in a region known for its high solar potential and robust energy infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:16:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bea5ce10c98d0787b4227_1766582999976.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Castrol India Jumps as Big Players Launch 26% Stake Buyout Offer After BP Exits!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Castrol-India-Jumps-as-Big-Players-Launch-26percent-Stake-Buyout-Offer-After-BP-Exits/694bea1ee10c98d0787b41b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Castrol-India-Jumps-as-Big-Players-Launch-26percent-Stake-Buyout-Offer-After-BP-Exits/694bea1ee10c98d0787b41b0</guid><description>Motion JVCo, Stonepeak, and Canada Pension Plan Investment Board are launching an open offer to buy up to 26% of Castrol India for ₹194.04 per share. This follows British Petroleum's deal to sell a 65% stake in the global Castrol business to Stonepeak. Castrol India shares rose 1.81% to ₹189.30 on the NSE before the open offer announcement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:16:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bea1ee10c98d0787b41af_1766583304805.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 125 Crore South Delhi Bungalow: Select Group's Luxury Real Estate Power Play Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Rs-125-Crore-South-Delhi-Bungalow-Select-Groups-Luxury-Real-Estate-Power-Play-Revealed/694be973e10c98d0787b40bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Rs-125-Crore-South-Delhi-Bungalow-Select-Groups-Luxury-Real-Estate-Power-Play-Revealed/694be973e10c98d0787b40bc</guid><description>Select Group, through its subsidiary Select World Tours India Private Limited, has acquired a bungalow in South Delhi's Westend Colony for Rs 125 crore. The property spans 668.90 square meters and represents a significant investment in one of Delhi's most exclusive residential areas. The deal, registered on October 14, 2025, highlights continued interest in premium real estate assets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:13:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be973e10c98d0787b40bb_1766583188071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Urban Company IPO Buzz Fizzles? Stock Plunges 25% After Record Debut! What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Urban-Company-IPO-Buzz-Fizzles-Stock-Plunges-25percent-After-Record-Debut-Whats-Next/694be6a7e10c98d0787b3df8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Urban-Company-IPO-Buzz-Fizzles-Stock-Plunges-25percent-After-Record-Debut-Whats-Next/694be6a7e10c98d0787b3df8</guid><description>Urban Company, a leading service provider, expanded into products like air conditioners under its 'Native' brand and launched quick services 'InstaHelp' in 2025. After a stellar IPO, oversubscribed nearly 104X and listing at a 57% premium, the company returned to losses in Q2 FY26 due to heavy investment in new verticals. Facing competition and operational challenges, the stock has dropped 25.16% since its debut.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:05:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be6a7e10c98d0787b3df7_1766582624853.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Robot Masters: Local Code Drives World-Class Humanoids &amp; Robodogs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Robot-Masters-Local-Code-Drives-World-Class-Humanoids-and-Robodogs/694be389e10c98d0787b3a91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Robot-Masters-Local-Code-Drives-World-Class-Humanoids-and-Robodogs/694be389e10c98d0787b3a91</guid><description>Indian robotics startups are showcasing advanced humanoid and quadruped robots, often nicknamed 'robodogs,' at events like IIT Bombay's Techfest. While these companies excel at complex local programming and software development, they heavily rely on sourcing critical hardware components such as motors, actuators, and sensors from international markets, primarily China and Switzerland. Despite these supply chain challenges, the deployment of industrial robots in India has seen significant growth over the last decade, though humanoids remain a niche category primarily in the research and development phase.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:46:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be389e10c98d0787b3a90_1766582122690.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supreme Industries Bags ₹54 Crore BPCL LPG Cylinder Order: What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Supreme-Industries-Bags-54-Crore-BPCL-LPG-Cylinder-Order-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694be330e10c98d0787b39ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Supreme-Industries-Bags-54-Crore-BPCL-LPG-Cylinder-Order-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694be330e10c98d0787b39ed</guid><description>Supreme Industries Limited has received a significant repeat order from Bharat Petroleum Corporation Limited (BPCL) for supplying approximately 2 lakh 10-kg composite LPG cylinders. The Letter of Acceptance is valued at an estimated ₹54 crore. This contract is valid for six months and may be extended, bolstering the company's order book amid positive volume growth expectations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be330e10c98d0787b39ec_1766581108579.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal Predicts 2026 Market Boom: Unveils Top Sectors Poised for Explosive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Motilal-Oswal-Predicts-2026-Market-Boom-Unveils-Top-Sectors-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/694be2a1e10c98d0787b38e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Motilal-Oswal-Predicts-2026-Market-Boom-Unveils-Top-Sectors-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/694be2a1e10c98d0787b38e4</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services forecasts steady growth for Indian equity markets in 2026, following a year of consolidation in 2025. Key drivers include recovering corporate earnings, revived private investments, and supportive government policies. The brokerage prefers large-cap stocks, highlighting sectors like Financials, Consumer Discretionary, Automobiles, Industrials, Capital Goods, and IT Services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:42:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be2a1e10c98d0787b38e3_1766581762870.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GST SHOCKER! Auto Dealers' Profits SINGED, Investor Interest DIES as Court Fight LOOMS!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/GST-SHOCKER-Auto-Dealers-Profits-SINGED-Investor-Interest-DIES-as-Court-Fight-LOOMS/694be2c8e10c98d0787b3927</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/GST-SHOCKER-Auto-Dealers-Profits-SINGED-Investor-Interest-DIES-as-Court-Fight-LOOMS/694be2c8e10c98d0787b3927</guid><description>Auto dealers are suffering significant profit margin erosion and declining investor interest following the government's discontinuation of the compensation cess from GST on September 22. Listed dealers like Landmark Cars, Popular Vehicles, and Competent Automobiles have seen share prices fall as they incurred losses clearing old stock. The Federation of Automobile Dealers Associations has taken the issue to the Supreme Court seeking resolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:41:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be2c8e10c98d0787b3926_1766582225539.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Noida Airport: India's Mega Hub to Open Jan 2026! UP CM Confirms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airport-Indias-Mega-Hub-to-Open-Jan-2026-UP-CM-Confirms/694be1cae10c98d0787b3755</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airport-Indias-Mega-Hub-to-Open-Jan-2026-UP-CM-Confirms/694be1cae10c98d0787b3755</guid><description>Uttar Pradesh Chief Minister Yogi Adityanath announced that the Noida International Airport at Jewar will be inaugurated in January 2026. This facility will become Uttar Pradesh's fifth international airport and is set to be India's largest. Developed under a public-private partnership, the greenfield project in Gautam Buddh Nagar district has faced previous delays, with its first phase initially planned for September 2024. Adityanath highlighted the state's rapid infrastructure growth since 2017, with functional airports increasing from four to sixteen.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:39:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be1cae10c98d0787b3754_1766581906920.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBCC's Bold Dubai Move: $4 Million Land Buy Signals Global Real Estate Ambitions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCCs-Bold-Dubai-Move-4-Million-Land-Buy-Signals-Global-Real-Estate-Ambitions/694be1bfe10c98d0787b3721</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCCs-Bold-Dubai-Move-4-Million-Land-Buy-Signals-Global-Real-Estate-Ambitions/694be1bfe10c98d0787b3721</guid><description>State-owned NBCC (India) Ltd has officially stepped into the international real estate market by acquiring nearly 15,000 sq ft of land in Dubai for AED 15 million (approx. ₹37 crore). This strategic purchase, made through its subsidiary NBCC Overseas Real Estate LLC, is earmarked for a mixed-use development, marking a significant expansion of its business overseas.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:38:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be1bfe10c98d0787b3720_1766581044266.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>