<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:50 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Caplin Point Unit Gets USFDA Nod for $26M Desmopressin Injection</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Caplin-Point-Unit-Gets-USFDA-Nod-for-26M-Desmopressin-Injection/69a28951fa7d0695d1b0019d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Caplin-Point-Unit-Gets-USFDA-Nod-for-26M-Desmopressin-Injection/69a28951fa7d0695d1b0019d</guid><description>Caplin Point Laboratories' subsidiary, Caplin Steriles, has secured final USFDA approval for its Desmopressin Acetate Injection USP. This generic drug, used for haemophilia and diabetes insipidus, targets a US market with $26 million in sales. The approval is a significant step for Caplin Steriles, opening access to the lucrative US market and expected to boost revenue for the parent company.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:21:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a28951fa7d0695d1b0019c_1772259802464.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OpenAI Lands DoD Classified AI Deal as Anthropic Faces Ban</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/OpenAI-Lands-DoD-Classified-AI-Deal-as-Anthropic-Faces-Ban/69a288c4fa7d0695d1b00111</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/OpenAI-Lands-DoD-Classified-AI-Deal-as-Anthropic-Faces-Ban/69a288c4fa7d0695d1b00111</guid><description>OpenAI's agreement to deploy AI on US Department of Defense classified networks marks a significant expansion, occurring as President Trump orders a halt to Anthropic's government use, citing national security risks. This move sharpens the competitive edge in defense AI, with OpenAI securing a strategic partnership while grappling with stringent ethical safeguards. The landscape sees valuations soaring for private AI firms, fueling a global race for AI supremacy in military applications.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:18:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a288c4fa7d0695d1b00110_1772259806276.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Meta Navigates Privacy Shift: DPDP Act Triggers New Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Meta-Navigates-Privacy-Shift-DPDP-Act-Triggers-New-Scrutiny/69a2874efa7d0695d1afffe5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Meta-Navigates-Privacy-Shift-DPDP-Act-Triggers-New-Scrutiny/69a2874efa7d0695d1afffe5</guid><description>Meta Platforms (META) is navigating a significant regulatory pivot. India's Digital Personal Data Protection Act (DPDP) enables direct privacy enforcement, moving scrutiny beyond competition law's dominance arguments that previously framed cases like WhatsApp's 2021 policy update. This shift, coupled with global regulatory actions like EU fines totaling over €1.5 billion, pressures Meta's targeted advertising model. With a market cap of $1.64 trillion and a P/E ratio around 27.4, Meta's stock ($657.01) is under watch as it adapts to stricter data governance and user consent mandates, while competitors like Apple adopt more privacy-centric approaches.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:12:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2874efa7d0695d1afffe4_1772259434283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Products A/S Acquires India's Techcom Precision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Products-AS-Acquires-Indias-Techcom-Precision/69a286fbfa7d0695d1afff91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Products-AS-Acquires-Indias-Techcom-Precision/69a286fbfa7d0695d1afff91</guid><description>Steel Products A/S, a Danish industrial conglomerate, has completed the 100% acquisition of Techcom Precision India Private Limited. This strategic move signifies the Danish firm's entry into India's precision manufacturing market, leveraging Techcom's capabilities. ALMT Legal advised Steel Products A/S, while Rubicon Law LLC represented Techcom Precision India. The transaction underscores a growing trend of Danish industrial players expanding their presence in India's dynamic economy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a286fbfa7d0695d1afff90_1772259196891.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Bank Eyes Up to 2% More Stake in ICICI Pru Life</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Bank-Eyes-Up-to-2percent-More-Stake-in-ICICI-Pru-Life/69a2860afa7d0695d1affea1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Bank-Eyes-Up-to-2percent-More-Stake-in-ICICI-Pru-Life/69a2860afa7d0695d1affea1</guid><description>ICICI Bank's Board has greenlit the acquisition of an additional stake, potentially up to 2.0%, in its subsidiary, ICICI Prudential Life Insurance. This strategic move aims to solidify the Bank's majority shareholding, particularly against dilution risks from stock-based compensation plans at the life insurance arm. Regulatory approvals are now the key next step.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:07:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2860afa7d0695d1affea0_1772258926636.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Secures USFDA Nod for Key Generics; Combined Sales $23.2M</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Secures-USFDA-Nod-for-Key-Generics-Combined-Sales-232M/69a2824dfa7d0695d1affd1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Secures-USFDA-Nod-for-Key-Generics-Combined-Sales-232M/69a2824dfa7d0695d1affd1f</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences has received final USFDA approvals for Ivermectin Tablets USP (3 mg) and Dapsone Tablets USP (25 mg and 100 mg). These approvals grant market access in the United States for prescription medications used to treat parasitic worm infections and leprosy, respectively. The combined annual sales for these formulations were reported at $23.2 million. Manufacturing will be at Zydus's Ahmedabad facilities, with Viona Pharmaceuticals Inc. handling distribution. This marks a step in expanding its US generic drug portfolio.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:51:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2824dfa7d0695d1affd1e_1772257972179.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Xflow Secures $16.6M Series A for Cross-Border Payment Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Xflow-Secures-166M-Series-A-for-Cross-Border-Payment-Expansion/69a27f7bfa7d0695d1affbef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Xflow-Secures-166M-Series-A-for-Cross-Border-Payment-Expansion/69a27f7bfa7d0695d1affbef</guid><description>Xflow Payments India Pvt. Ltd. has closed a $16.6 million Series A funding round led by General Catalyst, with participation from PayPal Ventures and existing investors including Stripe and Lightspeed. The company achieved an $85 million valuation with this round, bringing its total funding to over $32 million. This capital infusion, coupled with final PA-CB regulatory authorization for both imports and exports, positions Xflow to scale its cross-border payment solutions for Indian businesses. The funding follows a reported tenfold growth in 2025, serving nearly 15,000 clients.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:39:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a27f7bfa7d0695d1affbee_1772257271288.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cognizant's Resurgence: AI Fuels Growth, But Valuation Nears Peers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cognizants-Resurgence-AI-Fuels-Growth-But-Valuation-Nears-Peers/69a27ea2fa7d0695d1affaf0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cognizants-Resurgence-AI-Fuels-Growth-But-Valuation-Nears-Peers/69a27ea2fa7d0695d1affaf0</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions closed 2025 with a robust 6.4% revenue growth in constant currency, reaching $21.1 billion, and expanded operating margins to 16.1%. CEO Ravi Kumar S.'s strategy, focused on AI-driven 'mega-deals' and operational efficiency, has reversed earlier challenges. For 2026, the company projects revenue growth of 4.0-6.5% in constant currency and margin expansion. This performance places it favorably against competitors like Infosys and HCLTech, though its valuation metrics are now converging.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:35:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a27ea2fa7d0695d1affaef_1772257095696.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEC Mandates Rapid Insider Trade Reporting for Foreign Execs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SEC-Mandates-Rapid-Insider-Trade-Reporting-for-Foreign-Execs/69a27785fa7d0695d1aff805</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SEC-Mandates-Rapid-Insider-Trade-Reporting-for-Foreign-Execs/69a27785fa7d0695d1aff805</guid><description>Effective March 18, 2026, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will enforce new regulations requiring executives and directors of foreign private issuers to promptly disclose their company stock transactions. This mandate, originating from the Holding Foreign Insiders Accountable Act, aligns reporting standards with those for U.S. executives, targeting insider trading concerns and aiming to protect American investors. The move signifies increased regulatory scrutiny for global companies operating within U.S. capital markets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:05:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a27785fa7d0695d1aff804_1772255410716.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Minerva Ventures Buys 8.58% Stake in Elitecon International</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Minerva-Ventures-Buys-858percent-Stake-in-Elitecon-International/69a27692fa7d0695d1aff720</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Minerva-Ventures-Buys-858percent-Stake-in-Elitecon-International/69a27692fa7d0695d1aff720</guid><description>Minerva Ventures Fund has acquired a substantial 8.5761% stake in Elitecon International Limited, comprising 137,088,605 shares. The investment, made through warrants and open market operations on February 27, 2026, signifies growing institutional interest in the tobacco and agro commodities player. This move could influence Elitecon's strategic direction.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:01:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a27692fa7d0695d1aff71f_1772254968721.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Power: ICRA Reaffirms 'AA; Stable' on ₹69,000 Crore Facilities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-ICRA-Reaffirms-AA-Stable-on-69000-Crore-Facilities/69a273c3fa7d0695d1aff5cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-ICRA-Reaffirms-AA-Stable-on-69000-Crore-Facilities/69a273c3fa7d0695d1aff5cf</guid><description>ICRA has reaffirmed Adani Power's 'ICRA AA; Stable' rating on its ₹58,000 crore bank facilities and assigned the same rating to ₹11,000 crore of proposed Non-Convertible Debentures. This brings the total rated credit facilities to ₹69,000 crore, underscoring the company's market leadership and strong operational efficiency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:49:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a273c3fa7d0695d1aff5ce_1772254458216.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Inflation Shock Rocks Markets; Fed Policy Dilemma Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Inflation-Shock-Rocks-Markets-Fed-Policy-Dilemma-Intensifies/69a271e8fa7d0695d1aff4cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Inflation-Shock-Rocks-Markets-Fed-Policy-Dilemma-Intensifies/69a271e8fa7d0695d1aff4cc</guid><description>A surprising jump in January Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) inflation has intensified Federal Reserve policy concerns, sending shockwaves through financial markets. The core PCE price index accelerated to 3.1% year-over-year, defying expectations of a continued disinflationary trend. This latest inflation print, coupled with ongoing debates about Artificial Intelligence's long-term impact on the labor market, creates a complex and uncertain outlook for interest rates and economic growth in 2026. The upcoming jobs report will be closely watched for further clues on the economy's resilience.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:41:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a271e8fa7d0695d1aff4cb_1772253792730.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CBI Probe Launched: Forged NOCs Spark Regulatory Overhaul Fears in Fuel Retail</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/CBI-Probe-Launched-Forged-NOCs-Spark-Regulatory-Overhaul-Fears-in-Fuel-Retail/69a27142fa7d0695d1aff3f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/CBI-Probe-Launched-Forged-NOCs-Spark-Regulatory-Overhaul-Fears-in-Fuel-Retail/69a27142fa7d0695d1aff3f1</guid><description>The Madras High Court has mandated a CBI investigation into a widespread racket involving forged No Objection Certificates (NOCs) used to secure explosive licenses for petrol stations across Tamil Nadu. This directive follows the court's finding that the state police investigation inadequately addressed the role of beneficiaries, who allegedly paid substantial sums for fraudulent documents. The probe signifies heightened regulatory oversight, potentially leading to stricter compliance requirements, license reviews, and increased operational risks for fuel retail operators and investors in the sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:38:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a27142fa7d0695d1aff3f0_1772253616370.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Tax Regime Shifts Focus from Tax Savings to Goals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-New-Tax-Regime-Shifts-Focus-from-Tax-Savings-to-Goals/69a270f2fa7d0695d1aff39c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-New-Tax-Regime-Shifts-Focus-from-Tax-Savings-to-Goals/69a270f2fa7d0695d1aff39c</guid><description>India's shift to a new tax regime has significantly altered the investment calculus for Public Provident Fund (PPF) and Equity Linked Savings Schemes (ELSS). With the removal of Section 80C deductions, the primary appeal of these instruments now rests on their inherent investment merits rather than tax advantages. This transition mandates a strategic re-evaluation, prioritizing goal-based planning and capital appreciation over mere tax arbitrage.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:37:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a270f2fa7d0695d1aff39b_1772253547535.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SpaceX Eyes Record IPO: Valuation Soars Amidst Visionary Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SpaceX-Eyes-Record-IPO-Valuation-Soars-Amidst-Visionary-Ambitions/69a2681efa7d0695d1aff067</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SpaceX-Eyes-Record-IPO-Valuation-Soars-Amidst-Visionary-Ambitions/69a2681efa7d0695d1aff067</guid><description>SpaceX is on track for a confidential IPO filing in March 2026, targeting a June listing with a valuation north of $1.75 trillion, potentially raising $50 billion. This would shatter existing records, with funds earmarked for Starship development, orbital AI data centers, and lunar base construction. Major financial institutions are slated to manage the offering, while a dual-class share structure is under consideration to maintain insider control. This move signals a significant shift in the space industry's public market presence, though questions linger regarding the sustainability of its lofty valuation against developmental risks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 03:59:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2681efa7d0695d1aff066_1772251275628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GDP Surge: New Math, Sectoral Splits, and Investor Realities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Surge-New-Math-Sectoral-Splits-and-Investor-Realities/69a263b2fa7d0695d1afeec5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Surge-New-Math-Sectoral-Splits-and-Investor-Realities/69a263b2fa7d0695d1afeec5</guid><description>India's economy grew 7.8% in Q3 FY26, bolstered by a revised GDP calculation framework with a 2022-23 base year. Manufacturing output surged 13.3%, with services expanding 9.5%, underscoring the economy's resilience. However, agriculture growth slowed to 1.4%, highlighting a widening sectoral divergence. This methodological overhaul, incorporating GST and administrative data, enhances accuracy but requires reassessment of historical performance, with FY24 growth now revised down to 7.2%. Consumer spending (8.7%) remains a key driver, while investment eased, indicating a recalibration of growth engines.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 03:40:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a263b2fa7d0695d1afeec4_1772250127907.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Lombard Rating Outlook Revised to Positive by AM Best</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/ICICI-Lombard-Rating-Outlook-Revised-to-Positive-by-AM-Best/69a261effa7d0695d1afeddb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/ICICI-Lombard-Rating-Outlook-Revised-to-Positive-by-AM-Best/69a261effa7d0695d1afeddb</guid><description>AM Best has upgraded the outlook on ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company's Financial Strength Rating (FSR) and Long-Term Issuer Credit Rating (ICR) to Positive from Stable. The company's ratings remain affirmed at B++ (Good) and "bbb+" (Good) respectively, with the India National Scale Rating (NSR) holding at aaa.IN (Exceptional). This move reflects AM Best's confidence in ICICI Lombard's robust capital generation and prudent capital management, which are expected to further strengthen its balance sheet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 03:33:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a261effa7d0695d1afedda_1772249690309.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Recalibrates GDP Metrics, Enhancing Economic Clarity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Recalibrates-GDP-Metrics-Enhancing-Economic-Clarity/69a25898fa7d0695d1afea9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Recalibrates-GDP-Metrics-Enhancing-Economic-Clarity/69a25898fa7d0695d1afea9b</guid><description>India's national accounts have been significantly revised, moving the Gross Domestic Product (GDP) base year from 2011-12 to 2022-23. This recalibration incorporates advanced data sources like GST and adopts methodologies such as double deflation to achieve greater accuracy. The updated framework promises a more representative reflection of the economy's structure, including the burgeoning digital and gig sectors, while also influencing growth projections and fiscal calculations. This significant overhaul aims to enhance India's economic measurement credibility on the global stage.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 02:53:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a25898fa7d0695d1afea9a_1772247317000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Growth Push: Infrastructure Ambition vs. Execution Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Push-Infrastructure-Ambition-vs-Execution-Gap/69a25029fa7d0695d1afce5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Push-Infrastructure-Ambition-vs-Execution-Gap/69a25029fa7d0695d1afce5d</guid><description>Prime Minister Modi's call for innovation and investment in infrastructure and financial markets signals India's ambition for developed nation status. While capital expenditure has surged and foreign investment flows into debt markets are robust, driven by index inclusions, structural challenges persist. The private sector's hesitant participation in infrastructure projects and persistent illiquidity, transparency, and access issues in the corporate bond market highlight a critical execution gap. The integration of AI and blockchain aims to bolster governance, but translating policy intent into tangible ground-level impact remains paramount for sustained economic growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 02:17:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a25029fa7d0695d1afce5c_1772245148816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>QSRs Pivot Dine-In: Margin Grab or Digital Bet Against Convenience?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/QSRs-Pivot-Dine-In-Margin-Grab-or-Digital-Bet-Against-Convenience/69a23c8efa7d0695d1afc7f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/QSRs-Pivot-Dine-In-Margin-Grab-or-Digital-Bet-Against-Convenience/69a23c8efa7d0695d1afc7f0</guid><description>Major Indian Quick Service Restaurant (QSR) chains are strategically re-emphasizing dine-in experiences, introducing exclusive menu items and targeted promotions to counter declining delivery profitability. This pivot aims to capture higher dine-in gross margins, estimated at 15-20% above delivery, driven by savings on aggregator commissions and reduced discounting. However, this shift occurs amidst intense competition from dominant delivery platforms, rising operational costs, and a consumer base increasingly swayed by digital convenience. Jubilant FoodWorks, Devyani International, Restaurant Brands Asia, and Speciality Restaurants are recalibrating their models, though the long-term success of recapturing footfall against ingrained delivery habits remains a significant question.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:53:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23c8efa7d0695d1afc7ef_1772240148880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Sneaker Boom: Premium Valuations Mask Rising Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Sneaker-Boom-Premium-Valuations-Mask-Rising-Risks/69a23c82fa7d0695d1afc7d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Sneaker-Boom-Premium-Valuations-Mask-Rising-Risks/69a23c82fa7d0695d1afc7d6</guid><description>India's sneaker market is expanding rapidly, shifting focus to premiumization and aspirational consumption, projected to reach US$4.5 billion by 2030. While Metro Brands, Campus Activewear, and Bata India are executing diverse strategies to capture growth, elevated valuations and sensitivity to macroeconomic shifts pose significant risks. Investors must weigh sustained premium pricing against the potential for demand compression in a discretionary spending environment, alongside intense competitive pressures from global players.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:53:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23c82fa7d0695d1afc7d5_1772240152000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Stocks Surge Amid Market Pressure on AI, ESG Catalysts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Indian-Stocks-Surge-Amid-Market-Pressure-on-AI-ESG-Catalysts/69a23b9efa7d0695d1afc61a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Indian-Stocks-Surge-Amid-Market-Pressure-on-AI-ESG-Catalysts/69a23b9efa7d0695d1afc61a</guid><description>Amidst a challenging week for Indian equity markets, marked by declines in the Sensex and Nifty, several leading brokerage firms have identified select stocks with substantial upside potential. These recommendations are anchored by companies leveraging advanced manufacturing capabilities, artificial intelligence integration, and strong sector-specific growth drivers. Key themes include robust electronics manufacturing expansion, burgeoning EdTech sector evolution, and the strategic adoption of AI in IT services, aiming to create value against a backdrop of global economic uncertainty and geopolitical concerns.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:49:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23b9efa7d0695d1afc619_1772240050727.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>City Gas Expansion: High-Stakes Growth or Valuation Traps?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/City-Gas-Expansion-High-Stakes-Growth-or-Valuation-Traps/69a23b82fa7d0695d1afc5f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/City-Gas-Expansion-High-Stakes-Growth-or-Valuation-Traps/69a23b82fa7d0695d1afc5f2</guid><description>The Indian city gas distribution sector is aggressively expanding into smaller cities and industrial areas, shifting focus from saturated metros. This strategic pivot, driven by cleaner fuel demand and policy support, has led to significant valuation differences among key players. Adani Total Gas commands a premium for its aggressive expansion, while Indraprastha Gas and Gujarat Gas offer stability. IRM Energy remains an early-stage play facing execution hurdles and lower returns. Investors face a choice between high-growth bets with execution risks and established, steadier performers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:49:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23b82fa7d0695d1afc5f1_1772240173876.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Agri-Finance Gap: Public Dominance Risks Private Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Agri-Finance-Gap-Public-Dominance-Risks-Private-Capital/69a23b6efa7d0695d1afc5ab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Agri-Finance-Gap-Public-Dominance-Risks-Private-Capital/69a23b6efa7d0695d1afc5ab</guid><description>India's agricultural sector is critically underfunded for climate adaptation, facing an annual gap estimated between $310-$365 billion by 2035. The agri-food system receives only 20% of required adaptation funds, with public finance dominating domestic efforts (98-99%). Private sector participation is minimal due to high investment risks, long gestation periods, and fragmented landholdings. Despite COP30 agreements to enhance domestic climate finance ecosystems through platforms like the Green Climate Fund, unlocking private capital remains a challenge.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:48:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23b6efa7d0695d1afc5aa_1772239985680.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Capital Account Strain: Valuations, Outflows Cloud Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Capital-Account-Strain-Valuations-Outflows-Cloud-Outlook/69a23b18fa7d0695d1afc51b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Capital-Account-Strain-Valuations-Outflows-Cloud-Outlook/69a23b18fa7d0695d1afc51b</guid><description>India's capital account is under significant strain, characterized by substantial Foreign Portfolio Investor (FPI) outflows and declining net Foreign Direct Investment (FDI). Despite recent RBI liberalization of External Commercial Borrowings (ECBs), the currency faces ongoing depreciation pressure. Elevated domestic market valuations, coupled with a competitive global investment landscape favoring developed economies, are key factors contributing to investor caution. Analysts anticipate continued volatility throughout 2026.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:47:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23b18fa7d0695d1afc51a_1772239966915.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India EV 2W: Powering Livelihoods &amp; Indigenous Industry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-EV-2W-Powering-Livelihoods-and-Indigenous-Industry/69a23b0dfa7d0695d1afc4ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-EV-2W-Powering-Livelihoods-and-Indigenous-Industry/69a23b0dfa7d0695d1afc4ff</guid><description>The Indian electric two-wheeler market is rapidly evolving from basic transport to critical economic assets. These vehicles are electrifying livelihoods, creating employment, and addressing urban challenges while simultaneously driving domestic industrialization. Despite past safety concerns and import reliance, the sector's growth is underpinned by strong government policy, innovation in battery technology, and a growing demand for sustainable, affordable mobility solutions. In 2025, approximately 1.28 million units were sold, marking an 11% year-on-year increase, though market leadership shifted from Ola Electric to TVS Motor.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:47:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23b0dfa7d0695d1afc4fe_1772239941168.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Solar Tariffs Hit India: Trade Deal Ambiguity Amid Duty Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Solar-Tariffs-Hit-India-Trade-Deal-Ambiguity-Amid-Duty-Surge/69a23392fa7d0695d1afc270</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Solar-Tariffs-Hit-India-Trade-Deal-Ambiguity-Amid-Duty-Surge/69a23392fa7d0695d1afc270</guid><description>The U.S. Department of Commerce has imposed preliminary countervailing duties (CVD) of 126% on solar imports from India, citing unfair government subsidies. This move significantly impacts Indian solar exporters, with key companies like Waaree Energies and Premier Energies experiencing sharp stock declines. While Union Commerce Minister Piyush Goyal stated the duties are outside the India-US trade deal and the situation is fluid, the action raises questions about bilateral trade relations and India's strategic export ambitions. The duties are expected to make US market access economically unviable for Indian manufacturers, potentially leading to domestic oversupply and necessitating a recalibration of export strategies. Despite these headwinds, India's long-term solar sector outlook remains robust, supported by strong domestic demand and government policies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:15:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23392fa7d0695d1afc26f_1772237835249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>R Systems Board Meeting March 6 to Consider Interim Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/R-Systems-Board-Meeting-March-6-to-Consider-Interim-Dividend/69a23133fa7d0695d1afc13a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/R-Systems-Board-Meeting-March-6-to-Consider-Interim-Dividend/69a23133fa7d0695d1afc13a</guid><description>R Systems International Limited has scheduled a Board Meeting for March 6, 2026, to deliberate on declaring an interim dividend. This move underscores the company's focus on shareholder returns, with the final decision pending board approval and assessment of financial performance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:05:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23133fa7d0695d1afc139_1772237210371.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>