<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:57:17 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Sattva Group Targets Mumbai Redevelopment with ₹11,000 Cr Pipeline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Sattva-Group-Targets-Mumbai-Redevelopment-with-11000-Cr-Pipeline/698afe6e757d40c78185c975</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Sattva-Group-Targets-Mumbai-Redevelopment-with-11000-Cr-Pipeline/698afe6e757d40c78185c975</guid><description>Sattva Group is expanding into Mumbai's redevelopment sector. The Bengaluru-based developer has a pipeline of six projects covering over 8 million sq ft with a gross development value of ₹11,000 crore. These projects aim to deliver over 4,500 homes, marking a significant entry into India's competitive property market. Construction is slated to begin in 2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:46:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698afe6e757d40c78185c974_1770716945104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nirlon Q3 Profit Surges 67% on Tax Gains, Declares INR 15 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nirlon-Q3-Profit-Surges-67percent-on-Tax-Gains-Declares-INR-15-Dividend/698afe62757d40c78185c8ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nirlon-Q3-Profit-Surges-67percent-on-Tax-Gains-Declares-INR-15-Dividend/698afe62757d40c78185c8ca</guid><description>Nirlon Limited reported a robust 67.3% year-on-year surge in Profit After Tax (PAT) to INR 2,754 Mn for the nine months ended December 31, 2025 (9M-FY26), significantly boosted by tax adjustments. Total income grew 5.1% YoY to INR 5,090 Mn, with an EBITDA margin of 78.53%. The company declared an interim dividend of INR 15 per share and anticipates stable license fee income from its premium IT and Financial Services real estate assets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Volvo Eyes Europe Sourcing Amid India-EU Trade Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Volvo-Eyes-Europe-Sourcing-Amid-India-EU-Trade-Deal/698afdeb757d40c78185c729</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Volvo-Eyes-Europe-Sourcing-Amid-India-EU-Trade-Deal/698afdeb757d40c78185c729</guid><description>Volvo Car India is strategically evaluating its global sourcing network, with a notable shift being considered from China to its European manufacturing hubs. This reassessment is directly influenced by the recent India-European Union (EU) Free Trade Agreement (FTA), which promises to reshape import economics. While the company maintains that no definitive decision has been made to abandon Chinese sourcing entirely, plans are firming up to import models and kits from Europe. This move is intended to capitalize on potential tariff reductions, expand the availability of petrol and hybrid vehicles in India, and offer them at more competitive price points. Volvo's Indian assembly facility in Hoskote, Bengaluru, will continue its local production operations, including for electric vehicles. The luxury carmaker faces ongoing inflationary pressures and currency fluctuations that may temper immediate price reductions, despite the FTA's long-term benefits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:44:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698afdeb757d40c78185c728_1770716758038.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dr. Agarwal's Health Care Posts Stellar Q3 Growth, PAT Surges 55%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Agarwals-Health-Care-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Growth-PAT-Surges-55percent/698afd9b757d40c78185c53d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Agarwals-Health-Care-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Growth-PAT-Surges-55percent/698afd9b757d40c78185c53d</guid><description>Dr. Agarwal's Health Care Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue from operations climbing 23% YoY to Rs. 530 Cr. PAT surged 55% YoY to Rs. 44 Cr, driven by a 21.3% rise in EBITDA to Rs. 155 Cr and improved margins. The company commissioned 14 new facilities, expanding its network to 253, and saw significant growth in high-end surgeries. Management expressed confidence in meeting annual guidance, with plans for further aggressive expansion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:42:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698afd9b757d40c78185c53c_1770716651302.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Escorts Kubota Approves Mega Greenfield Project, Declares ₹18 Special Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Approves-Mega-Greenfield-Project-Declares-18-Special-Dividend/698afd8a757d40c78185c45f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Approves-Mega-Greenfield-Project-Declares-18-Special-Dividend/698afd8a757d40c78185c45f</guid><description>Escorts Kubota's Board greenlit a ₹2,268 Cr Greenfield expansion in UP and declared an ₹18/share special dividend. Nine-month PAT surged 120% YoY to ₹2,073 Cr, boosted by a ₹1,004 Cr profit from asset sale. Revenue rose 10% to ₹8,572 Cr, funding future growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:42:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698afd8a757d40c78185c45e_1770716818585.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABFRL Q3 Loss Despite 8% Revenue Growth; Ethnic Segment Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/ABFRL-Q3-Loss-Despite-8percent-Revenue-Growth-Ethnic-Segment-Soars/698afd73757d40c78185c349</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/ABFRL-Q3-Loss-Despite-8percent-Revenue-Growth-Ethnic-Segment-Soars/698afd73757d40c78185c349</guid><description>Aditya Birla Fashion and Retail (ABFRL) reported Q3 FY26 revenue growth of 8% YoY to ₹2,374 crores, driven by a strong ethnic business that saw 22.7% margins. Despite overall EBITDA up 13%, the company posted a ₹141 crore loss, normalizing to ₹115 crores after a one-time item. Pantaloons showed early signs of recovery with 3% LTL sales, while new ventures and TCNS progress boosted confidence, though mixed demand environment and postponed sales posed challenges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:42:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698afd73757d40c78185c348_1770716587159.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Safari Industries Eyes ₹500 Cr Boost, Re-appoints MD Amidst CS Exit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Safari-Industries-Eyes-500-Cr-Boost-Re-appoints-MD-Amidst-CS-Exit/698afcf7757d40c78185c191</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Safari-Industries-Eyes-500-Cr-Boost-Re-appoints-MD-Amidst-CS-Exit/698afcf7757d40c78185c191</guid><description>Safari Industries (India) Ltd. announced board approvals for a ₹500 Crore Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) to fund growth. The board also recommended the re-appointment of Mr. Sudhir Jatia as Managing Director for another five years. In a significant operational update, the company approved a change in its Registrar and Share Transfer Agent to MUFG Intime India Private Limited, citing exponential growth. The resignation of Mr. Rameez Shaikh as Company Secretary was also accepted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:40:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698afcf7757d40c78185c190_1770716475948.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes $1T Exports Amid Trade Pacts, But Capacity &amp; Oil Pose Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Eyes-1T-Exports-Amid-Trade-Pacts-But-Capacity-and-Oil-Pose-Risks/698afcbe757d40c78185bf7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Eyes-1T-Exports-Amid-Trade-Pacts-But-Capacity-and-Oil-Pose-Risks/698afcbe757d40c78185bf7b</guid><description>India aims for $1 trillion in exports by fiscal year 2026-27, propelled by new trade agreements with the United States and the European Union that significantly reduce tariffs. While initial orders are materializing for sectors like chemicals and footwear, substantial manufacturing capacity constraints and a widening trade deficit with China present considerable challenges. Furthermore, geopolitical pressures concerning energy imports could introduce significant cost increases, potentially dampening the net economic benefit of these trade breakthroughs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:39:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698afcbe757d40c78185bf7a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Escorts Kubota Posts Robust Q3 Earnings, Unveils ₹2,268 Cr Greenfield Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Posts-Robust-Q3-Earnings-Unveils-2268-Cr-Greenfield-Expansion/698afcab757d40c78185be96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Posts-Robust-Q3-Earnings-Unveils-2268-Cr-Greenfield-Expansion/698afcab757d40c78185be96</guid><description>Escorts Kubota reported a solid Q3 FY26 with standalone revenue up 11.1% YoY to ₹3,261 Cr and net profit rising 12.1% to ₹362 Cr. Consolidated net profit surged 24.5% YoY to ₹358 Cr. The company declared a Special Dividend of ₹18 per share. Key strategic moves include board approval for a significant ₹2,268 Cr greenfield manufacturing facility in YEIDA, Uttar Pradesh, aimed at boosting tractor and construction equipment capacity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:38:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698afcab757d40c78185be95.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ddev Plastiks Ventures into BESS, Q3 Revenue Surges 17% to ₹733 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ddev-Plastiks-Ventures-into-BESS-Q3-Revenue-Surges-17percent-to-733-Cr/698afc9b757d40c78185bda2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ddev-Plastiks-Ventures-into-BESS-Q3-Revenue-Surges-17percent-to-733-Cr/698afc9b757d40c78185bda2</guid><description>Ddev Plastiks Industries reported a robust Q3 FY26, with revenue climbing 17% year-on-year to ₹733 crore, bolstered by strong PVC compound sales. The company is making a strategic foray into Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) manufacturing, planning a 5 GWh assembly plant with a ₹150-200 crore investment funded by internal accruals. Capacity expansions are also underway, adding 30,000 MTPA. Ddev Plastiks maintains a net debt-free status, with healthy ROE and ROCE figures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:38:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698afc9b757d40c78185bda1_1770716396291.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Safari Industries Eyes Rs 500 Cr QIP, MD Re-appointment Approved</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Safari-Industries-Eyes-Rs-500-Cr-QIP-MD-Re-appointment-Approved/698afbb5757d40c78185bb5e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Safari-Industries-Eyes-Rs-500-Cr-QIP-MD-Re-appointment-Approved/698afbb5757d40c78185bb5e</guid><description>Safari Industries' Board approved a Rs 500 Crore Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) to bolster capital. MD Sudhir Jatia's re-appointment for a five-year term was also greenlit. The company will transition its Registrar and Share Transfer Agent to MUFG Intime India, with Mr. Rameez Shaikh resigning as Company Secretary.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:34:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698afbb5757d40c78185bb5d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brandman Retail Lists Amidst Expansion Bets &amp; Profitability Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Brandman-Retail-Lists-Amidst-Expansion-Bets-and-Profitability-Concerns/698afb94757d40c78185ba9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Brandman-Retail-Lists-Amidst-Expansion-Bets-and-Profitability-Concerns/698afb94757d40c78185ba9c</guid><description>Brandman Retail's ₹86.09 crore IPO was massively oversubscribed by 114.5 times, signaling strong investor demand. The company plans to deploy substantial proceeds to open 15 new retail outlets and bolster working capital. However, this aggressive expansion strategy introduces significant execution risks. Amidst a competitive retail landscape and concerns over margin sustainability, investors weigh the immediate listing gains against long-term operational challenges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:34:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698afb94757d40c78185ba9b_1770716129813.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wockhardt Sees 205% Profit Surge Amid US Generic Business Exit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Wockhardt-Sees-205percent-Profit-Surge-Amid-US-Generic-Business-Exit/698afb19757d40c78185b8f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Wockhardt-Sees-205percent-Profit-Surge-Amid-US-Generic-Business-Exit/698afb19757d40c78185b8f9</guid><description>Wockhardt Limited reported a significant financial turnaround for Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit soaring 205% year-on-year to ₹61 Cr from ₹20 Cr in Q3 FY25. Standalone net profit also turned positive, reaching ₹28 Cr compared to a loss of ₹22 Cr in the prior year. The company's consolidated revenue grew 23.2% YoY to ₹888 Cr. However, results for the nine months include ₹107 Cr in exceptional items, primarily ₹97 Cr for exiting the US generic pharmaceutical business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:32:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698afb19757d40c78185b8f8_1770716017970.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Textile Stocks Tumble on US-Bangladesh Deal; Deeper FTAs Signal Resilience</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Textile-Stocks-Tumble-on-US-Bangladesh-Deal-Deeper-FTAs-Signal-Resilience/698afaa8757d40c78185b764</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Textile-Stocks-Tumble-on-US-Bangladesh-Deal-Deeper-FTAs-Signal-Resilience/698afaa8757d40c78185b764</guid><description>Indian textile shares experienced a sharp decline on February 10, 2026, driven by profit-taking and a US-Bangladesh reciprocal tariff agreement. Pearl Global Industries saw a 9% drop, with other major players like Arvind and Gokaldas Exports falling 6%. Despite this sector-specific sell-off, the market is increasingly focused on India's broader strategic advantages, including upcoming Free Trade Agreements with the EU and UK, which analysts believe will provide a more significant and sustainable competitive edge than minor adjustments in bilateral tariffs with Bangladesh.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:30:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698afaa8757d40c78185b763_1770715930077.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nile Ltd Shares Surge 10% as Q3 Profit Rockets 48%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nile-Ltd-Shares-Surge-10percent-as-Q3-Profit-Rockets-48percent/698afa29757d40c78185b5d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nile-Ltd-Shares-Surge-10percent-as-Q3-Profit-Rockets-48percent/698afa29757d40c78185b5d5</guid><description>Nile Ltd shares surged over 10% after the company posted a strong Q3 FY25 performance. Net profit jumped 47.5% year-on-year to ₹15 crore, driven by a 25.3% increase in revenue to ₹291.4 crore. Improved EBITDA margins also contributed to the market's positive reaction, overshadowing a separate announcement regarding the suspension of windmill operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:28:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698afa29757d40c78185b5d4_1770715749287.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Record Clean Energy Pipeline Masks Growing G7 Execution Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Record-Clean-Energy-Pipeline-Masks-Growing-G7-Execution-Gap/698af9b6757d40c78185b471</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Record-Clean-Energy-Pipeline-Masks-Growing-G7-Execution-Gap/698af9b6757d40c78185b471</guid><description>The global wind and utility-scale solar project pipeline reached a record 4.9 terawatts (TW) in 2025, marking an 11% year-on-year increase. However, this expansion is increasingly concentrated in emerging economies like China and India, which now account for a substantial majority of projects under construction. Conversely, G7 nations are significantly underperforming relative to their climate ambitions, facing substantial barriers to project delivery and struggling to translate stated goals into tangible capacity. Analysts highlight implementation risks, rising financing costs, and policy uncertainty as key impediments to translating the record pipeline into operational power, raising doubts about meeting 2030 climate targets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:26:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af9b6757d40c78185b470_1770715661796.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dual-Path Investing: SSY vs. Equities for Daughters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Dual-Path-Investing-SSY-vs-Equities-for-Daughters/698af93f757d40c78185b2f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Dual-Path-Investing-SSY-vs-Equities-for-Daughters/698af93f757d40c78185b2f7</guid><description>Parents face a stark choice for their daughters' financial future: Sukanya Samriddhi Yojana (SSY) promising a stable 8.2% annual interest and tax benefits, or equities offering higher, albeit volatile, long-term growth potential. While SSY provides predictable nominal returns, persistent inflation erodes its real value over decades. Equities, historically yielding 11-17%, face capital gains tax and significant market volatility, demanding emotional resilience. A balanced strategy is often advised, considering individual risk appetite and the long-term impact of inflation on guaranteed savings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:24:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af93f757d40c78185b2f6_1770715519272.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel: Margin Hopes Clouded by Coal Volatility and Import Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Margin-Hopes-Clouded-by-Coal-Volatility-and-Import-Risks/698af8cc757d40c78185b182</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Margin-Hopes-Clouded-by-Coal-Volatility-and-Import-Risks/698af8cc757d40c78185b182</guid><description>Tata Steel Managing Director T.V. Narendran anticipates stronger margins and higher steel prices in the March quarter. However, the company's optimism is juxtaposed against volatile coking coal prices, heavily influenced by Australian supply disruptions, and a growing concern over unfairly priced steel imports that could undermine domestic industry stability. While domestic demand remains robust, liquidity stresses in the MSME sector and ongoing regulatory scrutiny add layers of complexity to the outlook.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:22:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af8cc757d40c78185b181_1770715398244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nirlon Declares ₹15 Dividend Amidst Q3 PAT Drop, Revenue Edges Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nirlon-Declares-15-Dividend-Amidst-Q3-PAT-Drop-Revenue-Edges-Up/698af84c757d40c78185b012</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nirlon-Declares-15-Dividend-Amidst-Q3-PAT-Drop-Revenue-Edges-Up/698af84c757d40c78185b012</guid><description>Nirlon declared a ₹15 per share interim dividend. Q3 FY26 revenue rose 5.6% YoY to ₹17,311 lakh, but Profit After Tax (PAT) dropped 22.8% YoY to ₹6,932 lakh. For the nine months, revenue grew 5.1%, while PAT surged 26.2% driven by a Q2 tax reversal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:20:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af84c757d40c78185b011_1770715291116.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IHH Fuels India Healthtech with Fortis Catalyst Platform</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/IHH-Fuels-India-Healthtech-with-Fortis-Catalyst-Platform/698af7ef757d40c78185ae17</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/IHH-Fuels-India-Healthtech-with-Fortis-Catalyst-Platform/698af7ef757d40c78185ae17</guid><description>IHH Healthcare, through its subsidiary Fortis Healthcare, has launched IHH Catalyst (Fortis India Edition), a national platform aimed at fast-tracking patient-centric health-tech and med-tech solutions across India. The initiative seeks to move promising startups beyond pilot stages to real-world clinical validation and scalable implementation, leveraging Fortis's extensive network. This move aligns with India's robust healthcare sector growth, projected to reach $638 billion by 2025, and addresses the critical gap in translating innovation into widespread adoption within hospital systems.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:18:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af7ef757d40c78185ae16_1770715263864.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Multi-Asset Funds Shield Investors from Commodity Plunge, But Risks Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Multi-Asset-Funds-Shield-Investors-from-Commodity-Plunge-But-Risks-Linger/698af7d7757d40c78185ad6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Multi-Asset-Funds-Shield-Investors-from-Commodity-Plunge-But-Risks-Linger/698af7d7757d40c78185ad6d</guid><description>Multi-asset allocation funds have proven a robust shield against the recent dramatic downturn in gold and silver prices, offering superior returns compared to equity-focused funds. Nippon India Multi-Asset Allocation Fund, for instance, posted strong multi-year returns, outperforming category averages. However, the inherent volatility of commodities and the specific asset allocation within these funds pose ongoing risks. Investors are advised to maintain a long-term perspective and scrutinize underlying exposures as market uncertainties persist. Commodity prices have seen significant swings, with silver dropping ~25% in a single session and gold correcting ~10% recently, following earlier record highs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:18:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af7d7757d40c78185ad6c_1770715165094.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ethera Secures Rs 25 Cr From Bluestone, Eyes Retail Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ethera-Secures-Rs-25-Cr-From-Bluestone-Eyes-Retail-Expansion/698af706757d40c78185ab67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ethera-Secures-Rs-25-Cr-From-Bluestone-Eyes-Retail-Expansion/698af706757d40c78185ab67</guid><description>Bengaluru-based Ethera has secured Rs 25 crore in funding from Bluestone, with plans to aggressively expand its physical retail presence and enhance its design and technology infrastructure. The investment fuels growth in the burgeoning lab-grown diamond sector, where Ethera focuses on IGI-certified stones and BIS-hallmarked gold.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:14:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698af706757d40c78185ab66.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Edelweiss Financial Posts Strong Growth in AUM and PAT, Slashes Net Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Edelweiss-Financial-Posts-Strong-Growth-in-AUM-and-PAT-Slashes-Net-Debt/698af6e4757d40c78185aa51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Edelweiss-Financial-Posts-Strong-Growth-in-AUM-and-PAT-Slashes-Net-Debt/698af6e4757d40c78185aa51</guid><description>Edelweiss Financial Services Limited presented a multi-year performance overview, showcasing substantial growth in Assets Under Management (AUM) and Profit After Tax (PAT) across its key business verticals including Alternative Asset Management, Mutual Fund, General Insurance, and Life Insurance. The company also reported a significant reduction in Net Debt, down by approximately 60% from March 2020 to December 2025, signaling improved financial health and operational efficiency.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:14:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af6e4757d40c78185aa50_1770714977149.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Edelweiss Financial Charts Stellar Growth, Slashes Debt Over 60%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Edelweiss-Financial-Charts-Stellar-Growth-Slashes-Debt-Over-60percent/698af669757d40c78185a8d9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Edelweiss-Financial-Charts-Stellar-Growth-Slashes-Debt-Over-60percent/698af669757d40c78185a8d9</guid><description>Edelweiss Financial Services Limited unveiled a comprehensive performance update, showcasing significant growth across its diversified business segments. Assets Under Management (AUM) and Gross Written Premiums (GWP) have surged substantially from March 2020 to December 2025, with promising projections for March 2026. Notably, the company has aggressively reduced its net debt from ₹28,750 Cr to ₹11,170 Cr, signalling improved financial health. The presentation highlights strong forward momentum with projected PAT growth across its Alternative Asset Management, Mutual Fund, General Insurance, and Life Insurance businesses.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:12:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af669757d40c78185a8d8_1770714789459.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Edelweiss Financials Unpacks P&amp;L: Underlying Businesses Drive 20% PAT Growth Projection</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Edelweiss-Financials-Unpacks-PandL-Underlying-Businesses-Drive-20percent-PAT-Growth-Projection/698af5f5757d40c78185a752</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Edelweiss-Financials-Unpacks-PandL-Underlying-Businesses-Drive-20percent-PAT-Growth-Projection/698af5f5757d40c78185a752</guid><description>Edelweiss Financial Services Limited has detailed its Profit After Tax (PAT) structure, separating operating businesses from its holding company. The company projects a steady 20% Compound Annual Growth Rate (CAGR) for its underlying businesses' PAT, aiming for ₹600 Crore by FY26 based on a nine-month annualized run rate. Historical ROE for these core segments hovers around 25-27%, with a projected 25.0% for FY26. The corporate segment's PAT is expected to be volatile, ranging between INR (100) Crore and INR 100 Crore annually, driven by factors like capital gains and interest expenses. Exceptional items have been excluded from recent PAT figures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:10:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af5f5757d40c78185a751_1770714668658.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KPI Green Energy Wins UAE Data Centre Order for Solar-Battery System</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Wins-UAE-Data-Centre-Order-for-Solar-Battery-System/698af593757d40c78185a57a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Wins-UAE-Data-Centre-Order-for-Solar-Battery-System/698af593757d40c78185a57a</guid><description>KPI Green Energy's subsidiary, Sun Drops Energia Limited, has received a significant international order from FVE Lifecare General Trading LLC in the United Arab Emirates. The project involves supplying, installing, and commissioning a 33 kWp Solar Power System integrated with a 573 kWh Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) to power a containerized Data Centre Facility. This milestone highlights the company's expanding international footprint and its growing expertise in advanced clean energy solutions for mission-critical infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:08:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af593757d40c78185a579_1770714659816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ambika Cotton Mills Invests Rs 57 Cr in Specialty Yarn Capacity Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ambika-Cotton-Mills-Invests-Rs-57-Cr-in-Specialty-Yarn-Capacity-Expansion/698af578757d40c78185a46e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ambika-Cotton-Mills-Invests-Rs-57-Cr-in-Specialty-Yarn-Capacity-Expansion/698af578757d40c78185a46e</guid><description>Ambika Cotton Mills Limited is significantly boosting its production capabilities with a Rs 57 crore capacity expansion initiative. The company is adding 12,528 spindles focused on specialty yarn manufacturing, with one phase already commissioned and the other targeted for May 2026. This strategic move, entirely funded through internal accruals, will raise the company's total spindle capacity to 120,816, underscoring a strong commitment to future revenue growth and enhanced market presence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:08:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af578757d40c78185a46d_1770714571110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises Surges on PCB Push, Caution Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-Surges-on-PCB-Push-Caution-Looms/698af44a757d40c78185a21d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-Surges-on-PCB-Push-Caution-Looms/698af44a757d40c78185a21d</guid><description>Amber Enterprises India reported a 128% net profit surge to ₹84 crore in Q3 FY26, with revenue climbing 38% to ₹2,943 crore. Strategic ECMS approvals for crucial PCB manufacturing signal a pivot towards backward integration. However, a sharp rally has pushed technical indicators into overbought territory, prompting some analysts to advise profit-taking and caution against fresh buying at elevated levels.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af44a757d40c78185a21c_1770714298867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FIIs Nibble Back: India's Market Sees Foreign Capital Return Amidst Sectoral Crosswinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/FIIs-Nibble-Back-Indias-Market-Sees-Foreign-Capital-Return-Amidst-Sectoral-Crosswinds/698af41b757d40c78185a09e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/FIIs-Nibble-Back-Indias-Market-Sees-Foreign-Capital-Return-Amidst-Sectoral-Crosswinds/698af41b757d40c78185a09e</guid><description>Foreign institutional investors (FIIs) have resumed net buying in Indian equities in February 2026, injecting approximately ₹4,900.17 crore, a notable reversal from the ₹1.66 lakh crore in outflows witnessed throughout 2025. This renewed interest, catalyzed by the finalization of the India-US trade agreement and a robust domestic economic outlook, signals a potential exit from a consolidation phase. However, the return is selective, with headwinds in the IT and pharmaceutical sectors and intense competition in banking requiring careful navigation. India's strong projected GDP growth at 6.4% in FY27 underscores its appeal as a key emerging market, yet global economic slowdown and past valuation concerns necessitate a discerning investment approach.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:02:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af41b757d40c78185a09d_1770714318796.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hexaware Misses Q4 Revenue, Suffers $60M One-Offs Amid AI Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexaware-Misses-Q4-Revenue-Suffers-60M-One-Offs-Amid-AI-Pivot/698af412757d40c78185a020</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexaware-Misses-Q4-Revenue-Suffers-60M-One-Offs-Amid-AI-Pivot/698af412757d40c78185a020</guid><description>Hexaware Technologies reported a Q4 CY25 revenue of $389 million, a 1.5% sequential decline, impacted by seasonal factors and FX headwinds. Profitability was significantly hit by $60 million in one-off charges, including a $25 million earn-out reversal from the underperforming Softcrylic acquisition. Normalized EBITDA margin dropped 210 bps sequentially to 15.4%. Despite these headwinds, the company projects CY26 revenue growth to exceed 7.6%, driven by AI integration and a robust pipeline crossing $4 billion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:02:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af412757d40c78185a01f_1770714223687.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Edelweiss Q3 PAT Surges 112% on Strategic Investments &amp; IPO Filing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Edelweiss-Q3-PAT-Surges-112percent-on-Strategic-Investments-and-IPO-Filing/698af39d757d40c781859eb7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Edelweiss-Q3-PAT-Surges-112percent-on-Strategic-Investments-and-IPO-Filing/698af39d757d40c781859eb7</guid><description>Edelweiss Financial Services reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 112% year-on-year to INR 264 Cr. The nine-month PAT grew 57% to INR 459 Cr. Key strategic initiatives are underway, including Carlyle Group's INR 2,100 Cr investment in its housing finance arm, Nido Home Finance, and the filing of a Draft Red Herring Prospectus (DRHP) for its Alternative Asset Management business's IPO. The company also achieved a 15% reduction in its corporate book net debt and maintained strong liquidity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:00:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af39d757d40c781859eb6_1770714103562.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Futuristic Solutions Reports Profit Surge on ₹100 Cr Claim; Outlook Unclear</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Futuristic-Solutions-Reports-Profit-Surge-on-100-Cr-Claim-Outlook-Unclear/698af2ac757d40c781859d0d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Futuristic-Solutions-Reports-Profit-Surge-on-100-Cr-Claim-Outlook-Unclear/698af2ac757d40c781859d0d</guid><description>Futuristic Solutions Limited has reported a remarkable turnaround, posting a net profit of ₹54.54 Cr for Q3 FY26, a stark contrast to a net loss in the prior year. This dramatic shift was fueled by the realization of claims worth ₹100 Cr. However, the company provided no forward-looking guidance, leaving investors to question the sustainability of this performance beyond the one-off event. Total income soared to ₹113.17 Cr YoY.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:56:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af2ac757d40c781859d0c_1770713841447.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dhunseri Tea Q3 PAT Crashes 99.7%, Sees ₹711 Cr Consolidated Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Dhunseri-Tea-Q3-PAT-Crashes-997percent-Sees-711-Cr-Consolidated-Loss/698af1d7757d40c781859b54</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Dhunseri-Tea-Q3-PAT-Crashes-997percent-Sees-711-Cr-Consolidated-Loss/698af1d7757d40c781859b54</guid><description>Dhunseri Tea &amp; Industries reported a dismal Q3 FY2026, with standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeting 99.7% YoY to ₹193.68 lakhs and EPS falling to ₹2.21. Consolidated results were worse, swinging to a net loss of ₹711.51 lakhs from a substantial profit last year, despite a 15.32% revenue growth. The nine-month period showed strong standalone growth (revenue +310%, PAT +11,645%), but consolidated performance declined sharply, with revenue down 87% and PAT by 96.8%. Assets of Balijan (North) Tea Estate worth ₹3,500 lakhs have been classified as 'held for sale'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af1d7757d40c781859b53_1770713702159.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pyramid Technoplast Q3 Results: Volume Surges, Profits Dip Amidst Expansion Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pyramid-Technoplast-Q3-Results-Volume-Surges-Profits-Dip-Amidst-Expansion-Costs/698af1bc757d40c781859a4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pyramid-Technoplast-Q3-Results-Volume-Surges-Profits-Dip-Amidst-Expansion-Costs/698af1bc757d40c781859a4f</guid><description>Pyramid Technoplast reported a 5% YoY revenue increase to ₹162 Cr in Q3 FY26, driven by a 21% volume surge. However, PAT fell 4% to ₹4.8 Cr due to new plant commissioning costs and one-time expenses. For 9M FY26, revenue grew 15.7%. The company eyes margin improvement from recycling and solar plant initiatives. Future capex is planned at ₹10-20 Cr for FY27.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:52:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af1bc757d40c781859a4e_1770713594061.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indef Manufacturing Profit Plunges 22.7% Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indef-Manufacturing-Profit-Plunges-227percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth/698af151757d40c781859868</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indef-Manufacturing-Profit-Plunges-227percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth/698af151757d40c781859868</guid><description>Indef Manufacturing's consolidated profit after tax (PAT) for Q3 FY26 fell 22.7% year-on-year to ₹482.06 crore, despite a 6.2% revenue increase to ₹4,752.27 crore. This decline reflects margin compression, with Q3 FY26 PAT margins at 10.1% versus 13.9% in Q3 FY25. The acquisition of an 80% stake in Daedalus Lift &amp; Access Equipments and an exceptional item related to new labour codes contributed to the profitability squeeze.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:50:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af151757d40c781859867_1770713570621.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PCS Tech Revenue Falls, But Profit Jumps 34% On Other Income</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PCS-Tech-Revenue-Falls-But-Profit-Jumps-34percent-On-Other-Income/698af13f757d40c781859787</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PCS-Tech-Revenue-Falls-But-Profit-Jumps-34percent-On-Other-Income/698af13f757d40c781859787</guid><description>PCS Technology's Q3 FY26 results reveal a consolidated revenue dip of 3.5% year-on-year to ₹105.66 Lakhs. Despite this, consolidated Net Profit After Tax (PAT) saw a significant 34.6% increase, reaching ₹46.33 Lakhs. Standalone PAT also grew 28.2% to ₹45.27 Lakhs. The company, operating in ITes related Facility Management, highlighted that 'Other Income' frequently surpasses operational revenue, a key driver for the profit surge.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:50:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af13f757d40c781859786_1770713465658.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kiri Industries Secures Rs 6,195 Cr, Eyes Rs 11,700 Cr Copper &amp; Fertilizer Projects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kiri-Industries-Secures-Rs-6195-Cr-Eyes-Rs-11700-Cr-Copper-and-Fertilizer-Projects/698af0c9757d40c781859631</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kiri-Industries-Secures-Rs-6195-Cr-Eyes-Rs-11700-Cr-Copper-and-Fertilizer-Projects/698af0c9757d40c781859631</guid><description>Kiri Industries Limited has resolved its 11-year DyStar legal battle, securing a substantial US$ 689 million (approx. ₹6,195 Cr) inflow. This financial windfall fuels ambitious plans for greenfield Copper and Fertilizer Complexes in Gujarat, estimated at ₹11,700 Cr with environmental clearances obtained. While the existing dyes business faces margin pressures, the company pivots towards transformative growth, targeting a ~25% IRR for the new ventures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:48:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af0c9757d40c781859630_1770713428931.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samvardhana Motherson Hits Record Revenue, Expands Global Footprint</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Samvardhana-Motherson-Hits-Record-Revenue-Expands-Global-Footprint/698af052757d40c7818594b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Samvardhana-Motherson-Hits-Record-Revenue-Expands-Global-Footprint/698af052757d40c7818594b6</guid><description>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited achieved its highest-ever quarterly revenue of ₹31,409 crores in Q3 FY26, a 14% YoY surge. EBITDA grew 10% to ₹3,042 crores, and normalized PAT rose 21% to ₹1,061 crores. The company announced two new greenfield projects in Morocco and Pune, alongside ongoing integration of acquisitions and expansion in emerging markets. Net leverage remains a comfortable 1.1x.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698af052757d40c7818594b5_1770713273316.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SAMIL Posts Record Revenue on Global Expansion, Capex Rises</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SAMIL-Posts-Record-Revenue-on-Global-Expansion-Capex-Rises/698aefec757d40c7818592ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SAMIL-Posts-Record-Revenue-on-Global-Expansion-Capex-Rises/698aefec757d40c7818592ce</guid><description>Samvardhana Motherson International (SAMIL) achieved its highest-ever quarterly revenue in Q3 FY26, reaching ₹31,409 crore, a robust 14% year-on-year increase. This performance was propelled by diversified growth across automotive and non-automotive sectors and strategic capacity expansions, including new Greenfield projects in Morocco and Pune. While consolidated EBITDA stood at ₹3,042 crore and PAT at ₹1,061 crore, the company saw significant capital expenditure of ₹1,594 crore. SAMIL maintained a net leverage of 1.1x, with efforts focused on deleveraging amidst inflated working capital.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:44:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698aefec757d40c7818592cd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kiri Industries Secures ₹5,854 Cr DyStar Exit, Plans ₹13,300 Cr Mega Projects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kiri-Industries-Secures-5854-Cr-DyStar-Exit-Plans-13300-Cr-Mega-Projects/698aefda757d40c781859224</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kiri-Industries-Secures-5854-Cr-DyStar-Exit-Plans-13300-Cr-Mega-Projects/698aefda757d40c781859224</guid><description>Kiri Industries Limited booked a colossal ₹5,854.37 Crore exceptional gain in Q3 FY26 from the sale of its DyStar stake, which also led to the associate's cessation. While the core dyes business grappled with subdued performance, margin contraction, and input cost pressures, the company's board greenlit two ambitious greenfield projects—a Copper Complex and a Fertilizer Complex—with a combined investment of ₹13,300 Crore, signaling a major strategic pivot aligned with India's self-reliance goals. No dividend will be declared as funds are earmarked for these projects and tax liabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 08:44:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698aefda757d40c781859223_1770713135856.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>