<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:17:38 +0000</pubDate><item><title>US Visa Snag: India Pushes for Resolution Amidst H-1B Interview Disruptions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Visa-Snag-India-Pushes-for-Resolution-Amidst-H-1B-Interview-Disruptions/694ea639e10c98d0788ebf75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Visa-Snag-India-Pushes-for-Resolution-Amidst-H-1B-Interview-Disruptions/694ea639e10c98d0788ebf75</guid><description>India is actively discussing with the United States to resolve disruptions affecting Indian nationals due to the cancellation and rescheduling of H-1B visa interviews. Since December 15, the US has increased scrutiny of social media for H-1B and H-4 visa applicants, leading to postponed interviews, stranded professionals, family separations, and financial hardships. The Ministry of External Affairs has flagged these concerns to the US government.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:02:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ea639e10c98d0788ebf74_1766762152061.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PNB Flags ₹2,434 Crore Borrowal Fraud Linked to SREI Ex-Promoters! RBI Notified</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PNB-Flags-2434-Crore-Borrowal-Fraud-Linked-to-SREI-Ex-Promoters-RBI-Notified/694ea04be10c98d0788eb975</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PNB-Flags-2434-Crore-Borrowal-Fraud-Linked-to-SREI-Ex-Promoters-RBI-Notified/694ea04be10c98d0788eb975</guid><description>Punjab National Bank has reported a significant borrowal fraud of ₹2,434 crore to the Reserve Bank of India. The fraud involves the erstwhile promoters of SREI Equipment Finance and SREI Infrastructure Finance. PNB has confirmed making 100% provisions for the full outstanding amounts, while noting that the SREI entities have been resolved under NCLT.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:41:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ea04be10c98d0788eb974_1766760626610.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways' Bold Plan: Double Train Capacity in 48 Cities by 2030 – Get Ready for a Travel Revolution!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indian-Railways-Bold-Plan-Double-Train-Capacity-in-48-Cities-by-2030-Get-Ready-for-a-Travel-Revolution/694e9e1ee10c98d0788eb6f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indian-Railways-Bold-Plan-Double-Train-Capacity-in-48-Cities-by-2030-Get-Ready-for-a-Travel-Revolution/694e9e1ee10c98d0788eb6f0</guid><description>Indian Railways plans to double its originating train capacity in 48 major cities by 2030 to accommodate rapid travel growth. The Ministry will augment infrastructure, add platforms, create new terminals, and build maintenance facilities. This progressive expansion aims to meet future traffic demands and improve services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:34:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e9e1ee10c98d0788eb6ef_1766760065317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Investors Pour Record ₹3 Trillion into SIPs: Is This the End of Lump-Sum Investing?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Investors-Pour-Record-3-Trillion-into-SIPs-Is-This-the-End-of-Lump-Sum-Investing/694e99f9e10c98d0788eb29f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Investors-Pour-Record-3-Trillion-into-SIPs-Is-This-the-End-of-Lump-Sum-Investing/694e99f9e10c98d0788eb29f</guid><description>In 2025, investor preference dramatically shifted towards Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs), pushing inflows past a record ₹3 trillion, according to AMFI data. This surge in SIPs, especially into equity schemes, occurred as one-time lump-sum investments saw a significant decline amid market volatility. SIPs now represent a larger share of overall equity inflows, underscoring their growing importance for long-term wealth building.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:09:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e99f9e10c98d0788eb29e_1766758981137.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 IPO Boom! Govt Accelerates Green Energy Listings for PSU Giants NLC &amp; SJVN!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/2026-IPO-Boom-Govt-Accelerates-Green-Energy-Listings-for-PSU-Giants-NLC-and-SJVN/694e997be10c98d0788eb1e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/2026-IPO-Boom-Govt-Accelerates-Green-Energy-Listings-for-PSU-Giants-NLC-and-SJVN/694e997be10c98d0788eb1e5</guid><description>The Indian government plans to fast-track IPOs for PSU green energy subsidiaries in 2026. DIPAM is prioritizing NLC Green (H1) and SJVN Green (H2) listings, anticipating favorable market conditions. NLC India and SJVN are preparing for these significant public offerings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:08:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e997be10c98d0788eb1e4_1766758889408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Timex India Stake Sale Alert! Promoter Offloads Millions of Shares at ₹275 - What Investors Must Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Timex-India-Stake-Sale-Alert-Promoter-Offloads-Millions-of-Shares-at-275-What-Investors-Must-Know/694e98a1e10c98d0788eb0b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Timex-India-Stake-Sale-Alert-Promoter-Offloads-Millions-of-Shares-at-275-What-Investors-Must-Know/694e98a1e10c98d0788eb0b5</guid><description>Timex Group Luxury Watches BV, the promoter of Timex Group India Ltd, plans to sell up to 4.47% stake via an Offer for Sale (OFS) on December 29-30. The floor price is set at ₹275 per share, with an option to increase the sale size to nearly 8.93% if oversubscribed. Kotak Securities is managing the transaction on the BSE, following SEBI regulations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:08:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e98a1e10c98d0788eb0b4_1766758642720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal Mines Approval Speed-Up: Govt Scraps Key Red Tape, Boosts Production Hopes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-Mines-Approval-Speed-Up-Govt-Scraps-Key-Red-Tape-Boosts-Production-Hopes/694e97ade10c98d0788eaf37</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-Mines-Approval-Speed-Up-Govt-Scraps-Key-Red-Tape-Boosts-Production-Hopes/694e97ade10c98d0788eaf37</guid><description>India's government has amended rules to streamline approvals for opening coal and lignite mines. The Coal Controller's Organisation's prior permission requirement has been removed, with authority now resting with the concerned coal company's board. This reform is expected to cut mine operationalization time by up to two months, aiming to boost coal production and efficiency.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:01:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e97ade10c98d0788eaf36_1766758415963.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerage Sees Big Growth: Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals Rated BUY with ₹340 Target Price!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Brokerage-Sees-Big-Growth-Crompton-Greaves-Consumer-Electricals-Rated-BUY-with-340-Target-Price/694e96b2e10c98d0788ead5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Brokerage-Sees-Big-Growth-Crompton-Greaves-Consumer-Electricals-Rated-BUY-with-340-Target-Price/694e96b2e10c98d0788ead5b</guid><description>A brokerage firm has initiated coverage on Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals with a 'Buy' rating and a target price of ₹340. The recommendation highlights the company's "Crompton 2.0" strategy, focusing on premiumisation and innovation, alongside significant traction and growth potential in its solar rooftop and solar pumps businesses. Potential risks include commodity price volatility, competition, and policy dependence for solar ventures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:58:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e96b2e10c98d0788ead5a_1766758142004.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banking Squeeze Intensifies: Deposits Lag Loans by 200 BPS as RBI Data Reveals Tightness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banking-Squeeze-Intensifies-Deposits-Lag-Loans-by-200-BPS-as-RBI-Data-Reveals-Tightness/694e919de10c98d0788ea83e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banking-Squeeze-Intensifies-Deposits-Lag-Loans-by-200-BPS-as-RBI-Data-Reveals-Tightness/694e919de10c98d0788ea83e</guid><description>Latest RBI data for December 12 shows deposit growth slowing to 9.7% year-on-year while credit growth accelerated to 11.7%. This 200 basis points gap highlights persistent deposit tightness in India's banking system, pressuring banks to fund rising credit demand and potentially pushing savers towards equity markets for better returns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:36:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e919de10c98d0788ea83d_1766756838592.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's First Medical Tech University Set to Ignite Global Innovation Hub in Vizag!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-First-Medical-Tech-University-Set-to-Ignite-Global-Innovation-Hub-in-Vizag/694e8fb9e10c98d0788ea52e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-First-Medical-Tech-University-Set-to-Ignite-Global-Innovation-Hub-in-Vizag/694e8fb9e10c98d0788ea52e</guid><description>India's first specialized medical technology university, the Erba Global Institute of Medical Technology (EGIMT), is set to launch in Vizag's Andhra Pradesh Medtech Zone (AMTZ). It will offer postgraduate and PhD programs in medical technology, bio-engineering, and healthcare innovation, leveraging AMTZ's manufacturing and R&amp;D ecosystem to foster a global med-tech hub.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:26:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8fb9e10c98d0788ea52d_1766756675987.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Revolution in India: 2026 Will Be Year of Accountability, Not Just Hype!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Revolution-in-India-2026-Will-Be-Year-of-Accountability-Not-Just-Hype/694e8ed2e10c98d0788ea366</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Revolution-in-India-2026-Will-Be-Year-of-Accountability-Not-Just-Hype/694e8ed2e10c98d0788ea366</guid><description>India's AI journey is accelerating, moving rapidly from pilot projects to full-scale production. By 2026, Artificial Intelligence is predicted to become foundational infrastructure for Indian companies, transforming operations, security, and business models. Expect AI companions, agentic workflows, and a sharp focus on cost, governance, and engineering discipline over mere novelty.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:24:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8ed2e10c98d0788ea365_1766756369341.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Forex Reserves Skyrocket to Record $693 Billion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Skyrocket-to-Record-693-Billion/694e89b6e10c98d0788e9d27</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Skyrocket-to-Record-693-Billion/694e89b6e10c98d0788e9d27</guid><description>India's foreign exchange reserves saw a significant jump of $4.368 billion, reaching a new high of $693.318 billion in the week ending December 19. This surge was primarily driven by substantial increases in foreign currency assets and gold reserves, as reported by the Reserve Bank of India. The overall kitty also benefited from growth in Special Drawing Rights and India's reserve position with the IMF, signaling robust economic standing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:03:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e89b6e10c98d0788e9d26_1766754892724.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Housing Market Shock: Sales Volume Down 14%, But Luxury Demand Skyrockets Value Past ₹6 Lakh Crore!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Housing-Market-Shock-Sales-Volume-Down-14percent-But-Luxury-Demand-Skyrockets-Value-Past-6-Lakh-Crore/694e8750e10c98d0788e9a80</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Housing-Market-Shock-Sales-Volume-Down-14percent-But-Luxury-Demand-Skyrockets-Value-Past-6-Lakh-Crore/694e8750e10c98d0788e9a80</guid><description>India's residential real estate saw a 14% drop in housing sales volume in 2025 across the top seven cities, selling 3,95,625 units compared to 4,59,645 in 2024. Despite this, the total sales value increased by 6% to over ₹6 lakh crore, driven by strong demand for luxury properties. Chennai was the only city with sales growth, while MMR and Pune saw significant declines. New launches saw a slight increase. Experts attribute the sales dip to economic uncertainties and IT sector layoffs but are optimistic for 2026 if RBI cuts rates and developers manage prices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:54:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8750e10c98d0788e9a7f_1766754351709.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Demat Account Surge: 2026 Outlook Hinges on Smarter Investors Amidst Market Resilience!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Demat-Account-Surge-2026-Outlook-Hinges-on-Smarter-Investors-Amidst-Market-Resilience/694e8745e10c98d0788e9a3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Demat-Account-Surge-2026-Outlook-Hinges-on-Smarter-Investors-Amidst-Market-Resilience/694e8745e10c98d0788e9a3a</guid><description>Indian demat accounts reached 21.28 crore by November 2025, showing resilience despite market volatility and FII outflows. Experts note a shift towards long-term investing, with younger investors under 30 from smaller towns driving new accounts via digital platforms. Growth in 2026 will depend on deeper, intelligent participation rather than just account numbers, influenced by macro fundamentals and household savings shifting to financial assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:53:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8745e10c98d0788e9a39_1766754189932.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock HUGE Gains Monday? Experts Reveal Top Stocks to Buy for Bumper Returns! Don't Miss These Picks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Unlock-HUGE-Gains-Monday-Experts-Reveal-Top-Stocks-to-Buy-for-Bumper-Returns-Dont-Miss-These-Picks/694e8259e10c98d0788e9502</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Unlock-HUGE-Gains-Monday-Experts-Reveal-Top-Stocks-to-Buy-for-Bumper-Returns-Dont-Miss-These-Picks/694e8259e10c98d0788e9502</guid><description>Indian markets (Sensex, Nifty) closed lower on Friday, December 26, amid foreign fund outflows. However, market experts have identified several 'stocks to buy' for the upcoming week starting Monday, December 29, anticipating bumper gains. Top recommendations include NMDC, BEL, Suzlon Energy, Titan, BHEL, MMTC, IRCON International, IRFC, and IRCTC, with specific price targets and stop-loss levels provided by analysts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:31:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8259e10c98d0788e9501_1766753211756.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock 2026 Gains: ICICI Securities Reveals 7 Top Stock Bets with UP TO 32% Upside!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Unlock-2026-Gains-ICICI-Securities-Reveals-7-Top-Stock-Bets-with-UP-TO-32percent-Upside/694e8004e10c98d0788e9285</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Unlock-2026-Gains-ICICI-Securities-Reveals-7-Top-Stock-Bets-with-UP-TO-32percent-Upside/694e8004e10c98d0788e9285</guid><description>ICICI Securities anticipates a robust recovery for Indian equities in 2026, projecting a 15% CAGR in corporate earnings. The brokerage highlights factors like increased retail investor participation and the potential ₹2 lakh crore infusion from the 8th Pay Commission. Based on this optimistic outlook, ICICI Securities has identified seven high-conviction stock ideas, including Bank of Baroda, Bajaj Finance, Bharti Airtel, Dalmia Bharat, NRB Bearings, Phoenix Mills, and KPIT Technologies, with potential upsides ranging up to 32%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:21:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8004e10c98d0788e9284_1766752416040.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>🚨 Stocks Explode: Top Price-Volume Breakouts Revealed for Tomorrow! Don't Miss Out!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Stocks-Explode-Top-Price-Volume-Breakouts-Revealed-for-Tomorrow-Dont-Miss-Out/694e7c04e10c98d0788e8dff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Stocks-Explode-Top-Price-Volume-Breakouts-Revealed-for-Tomorrow-Dont-Miss-Out/694e7c04e10c98d0788e8dff</guid><description>Indian stock markets closed lower for the third consecutive session as investors remained cautious before the Q3 earnings season. Despite overall market fatigue after recent highs, several stocks showed significant price and volume breakouts. Indian Railway Finance Corp Ltd, Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd, and Hindustan Copper Ltd were among the top gainers, displaying strong upward momentum supported by high trading volumes, signalling potential focus for the next trading day.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:03:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7c04e10c98d0788e8dfe_1766751308797.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIFT City Bonds: $68 Billion Institutional Giant — Will Retail Get a Slice?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/GIFT-City-Bonds-68-Billion-Institutional-Giant-Will-Retail-Get-a-Slice/694e7ac6e10c98d0788e8ca8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/GIFT-City-Bonds-68-Billion-Institutional-Giant-Will-Retail-Get-a-Slice/694e7ac6e10c98d0788e8ca8</guid><description>The bond market at India's GIFT City is predominantly institutional, facilitating offshore debt for corporates. With $68 billion outstanding and $7 billion raised in FY24-25, regulators are enhancing investor protection through stricter disclosure and rating norms. While retail access is limited, future avenues like bond fractionalisation and tokenisation are being explored to evolve investor participation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:57:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7ac6e10c98d0788e8ca7_1766750983657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LIC Partners with Sahaj to Revolutionize Rural Insurance Access: HUGE Impact on Bharat's Financial Inclusion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Partners-with-Sahaj-to-Revolutionize-Rural-Insurance-Access-HUGE-Impact-on-Bharats-Financial-Inclusion/694e796fe10c98d0788e8a3c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Partners-with-Sahaj-to-Revolutionize-Rural-Insurance-Access-HUGE-Impact-on-Bharats-Financial-Inclusion/694e796fe10c98d0788e8a3c</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has joined forces with Sahaj Insurance Services, a corporate agent. This strategic alliance aims to distribute LIC's life insurance products across India's rural and semi-urban regions through Sahaj's extensive network of 4.5 lakh digitally enabled centers. The partnership seeks to make insurance simpler, more accessible, and inclusive for all citizens, boosting financial inclusion and social security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:53:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e796fe10c98d0788e8a3b_1766751061708.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Affordable Housing Dream: Can Budget 2026 Make It a Reality?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Affordable-Housing-Dream-Can-Budget-2026-Make-It-a-Reality/694e79c0e10c98d0788e8b55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Affordable-Housing-Dream-Can-Budget-2026-Make-It-a-Reality/694e79c0e10c98d0788e8b55</guid><description>India's housing affordability is improving due to lower interest rates and income growth, but rising costs and supply constraints persist. Real estate developers and housing finance companies are urging the government, in the upcoming Union Budget 2026-27, to revive tax incentives like those under PMAY 1.0 and revise the definition of affordable housing, which currently has a ₹45 lakh cap, to sustain momentum in the sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:50:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e79c0e10c98d0788e8b54_1766752061746.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCI Supercharges Gurugram Cold Chain: Mega New Facility Unlocks Growth for Pharma &amp; Quick Commerce!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TCI-Supercharges-Gurugram-Cold-Chain-Mega-New-Facility-Unlocks-Growth-for-Pharma-and-Quick-Commerce/694e78e6e10c98d0788e8938</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TCI-Supercharges-Gurugram-Cold-Chain-Mega-New-Facility-Unlocks-Growth-for-Pharma-and-Quick-Commerce/694e78e6e10c98d0788e8938</guid><description>Transport Corporation of India (TCI) has significantly expanded its cold chain warehousing business by inaugurating a 1.5 lakh sq ft facility in Taj Nagar, Gurugram. This state-of-the-art facility is designed to cater to high-demand sectors including quick commerce, pharmaceuticals, food and beverages, and dairy. Operated by TCI Cold Chain Solutions Ltd., a joint venture with Mitsui &amp; Co Ltd, the facility offers multi-temperature storage and a flexible pay-as-you-use model, strengthening TCI's logistics capabilities in the NCR region.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:50:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e78e6e10c98d0788e8937_1766750793524.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Clean Energy Secret: Is Grid Power Ready for the Big Switch?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Clean-Energy-Secret-Is-Grid-Power-Ready-for-the-Big-Switch/694e7872e10c98d0788e87e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Clean-Energy-Secret-Is-Grid-Power-Ready-for-the-Big-Switch/694e7872e10c98d0788e87e7</guid><description>India's ambitious clean energy goals are now shifting focus from creating capacity to ensuring grid readiness. N Venu, MD &amp; CEO of Hitachi Energy India, explains that strengthening the grid with high-voltage transmission, energy storage, and digital substations is crucial. This is vital to reliably deliver renewable power to meet rising demand from industry and the booming data center sector, ensuring India's energy transition is successful and sustainable towards its net-zero targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:49:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7872e10c98d0788e87e6_1766750960263.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LIC Seals Deal to Revolutionize Rural Insurance Access Across India!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Seals-Deal-to-Revolutionize-Rural-Insurance-Access-Across-India/694e784ee10c98d0788e8792</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Seals-Deal-to-Revolutionize-Rural-Insurance-Access-Across-India/694e784ee10c98d0788e8792</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has partnered with Sahaj Insurance Services Private Limited to significantly boost insurance access in rural and semi-urban areas. Leveraging Sahaj's extensive network of digitally enabled centers, this collaboration aims to make LIC's life insurance products more understandable and manageable for citizens, especially in regions with low insurance awareness, thereby furthering financial inclusion and social security in India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:49:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e784ee10c98d0788e8791_1766750597708.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tractor Sales Skyrocket: ICRA Predicts Massive 17% Growth Fueled by Tax Cuts &amp; Monsoon Magic!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tractor-Sales-Skyrocket-ICRA-Predicts-Massive-17percent-Growth-Fueled-by-Tax-Cuts-and-Monsoon-Magic/694e774de10c98d0788e860a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tractor-Sales-Skyrocket-ICRA-Predicts-Massive-17percent-Growth-Fueled-by-Tax-Cuts-and-Monsoon-Magic/694e774de10c98d0788e860a</guid><description>Rating agency ICRA has significantly boosted its tractor industry growth forecast for FY26 to 15-17%, a sharp increase from the previous 8-10% estimate and the 7% seen last year. This optimism stems from strong recent performance, including a 30% jump in November wholesale volumes. Key drivers include a reduced GST on tractors making them more affordable, a robust Southwest Monsoon boosting farm income, and anticipated pre-buying due to upcoming stricter emission norms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:46:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e774de10c98d0788e8609_1766750093504.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Tumbles! 📉 Indian Currency Plunges Against US Dollar – What's Driving the Fall &amp; What it Means for Your Wallet!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Tumbles-Indian-Currency-Plunges-Against-US-Dollar-Whats-Driving-the-Fall-and-What-it-Means-for-Your-Wallet/694e767ee10c98d0788e84aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Tumbles-Indian-Currency-Plunges-Against-US-Dollar-Whats-Driving-the-Fall-and-What-it-Means-for-Your-Wallet/694e767ee10c98d0788e84aa</guid><description>The Indian Rupee depreciated by 15 paise to close at 89.86 against the US dollar on Friday. The weakening was driven by a downturn in domestic stock markets, consistent outflows of foreign funds, and rising crude oil prices. The dollar index saw a slight increase, while Brent crude prices edged higher. Foreign institutional investors sold Indian equities worth ₹1,721.26 crore, further pressuring the rupee.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:42:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e767ee10c98d0788e84a9_1766750101516.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DP World's $5 Billion India Push: Deeper Integration and Multimodal Logistics Set to Transform Trade!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DP-Worlds-5-Billion-India-Push-Deeper-Integration-and-Multimodal-Logistics-Set-to-Transform-Trade/694e72f2e10c98d0788e80f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DP-Worlds-5-Billion-India-Push-Deeper-Integration-and-Multimodal-Logistics-Set-to-Transform-Trade/694e72f2e10c98d0788e80f2</guid><description>DP World is significantly expanding its India operations, aiming for deeper integration through higher-value supply chain solutions and multimodal offerings. The multinational logistics firm is bullish on India's trade growth, committing an additional $5 billion to its existing $3 billion investment. This expansion focuses on enhancing predictability and resilience for customers by leveraging its extensive infrastructure, including ports, rail, containers, and warehousing, to create an end-to-end logistics network. This strategic move positions India as a key manufacturing and export hub, anticipating increased contributions to DP World's global business.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:25:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e72f2e10c98d0788e80f1_1766749004011.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver to EXPLODE? Rich Dad Poor Dad Author Robert Kiyosaki Reveals Shocking Price Target!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-to-EXPLODE-Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad-Author-Robert-Kiyosaki-Reveals-Shocking-Price-Target/694e7237e10c98d0788e7f44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-to-EXPLODE-Rich-Dad-Poor-Dad-Author-Robert-Kiyosaki-Reveals-Shocking-Price-Target/694e7237e10c98d0788e7f44</guid><description>Robert Kiyosaki, author of "Rich Dad Poor Dad," believes silver's rally is just beginning, predicting prices could hit $200 per ounce by 2026. He recently purchased silver at $70 per ounce, having first invested in 1965 when prices were under a dollar. Kiyosaki urges investors to conduct their own research, emphasizing learning from mistakes to build wealth. Silver futures recently surged to a record ₹2,32,741 per kg on the MCX, exceeding $75 per ounce globally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:24:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7237e10c98d0788e7f43_1766749105888.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sun Pharma's Bold FY26 Growth Plan: Innovation Bets Meet US Pricing Storm!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sun-Pharmas-Bold-FY26-Growth-Plan-Innovation-Bets-Meet-US-Pricing-Storm/694e72f3e10c98d0788e811d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sun-Pharmas-Bold-FY26-Growth-Plan-Innovation-Bets-Meet-US-Pricing-Storm/694e72f3e10c98d0788e811d</guid><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries targets mid- to high-single digit consolidated revenue growth in FY26, emphasizing investment in its innovative medicines pipeline and R&amp;D. This guidance comes amidst evolving US pharmaceutical pricing policies, including proposed mandatory models aimed at curbing drug costs, which could impact the company's significant revenue from branded pharmaceuticals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:24:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e72f3e10c98d0788e811c_1766749007378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Family Businesses Unlock Growth: Independent Directors Key to Future Success?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Family-Businesses-Unlock-Growth-Independent-Directors-Key-to-Future-Success/694e7257e10c98d0788e7f92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Family-Businesses-Unlock-Growth-Independent-Directors-Key-to-Future-Success/694e7257e10c98d0788e7f92</guid><description>A Deloitte report highlights that Indian family-run businesses need better succession planning and governance to ensure continuity and growth. It suggests that independent directors are crucial for bringing objectivity, transparency, and professional expertise to boards, helping to separate family interests from business decisions, manage risks, and build investor trust for future expansion and generational transitions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:24:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7257e10c98d0788e7f91_1766749387072.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Rewires Russia Ties: Oil Imports Plummeting, Trade Balance Shifts Dramatically!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Rewires-Russia-Ties-Oil-Imports-Plummeting-Trade-Balance-Shifts-Dramatically/694e7027e10c98d0788e7ce3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Rewires-Russia-Ties-Oil-Imports-Plummeting-Trade-Balance-Shifts-Dramatically/694e7027e10c98d0788e7ce3</guid><description>India is enacting a significant shift in its trade strategy with Russia, anticipating a sharp decline in crude oil imports from December 2025. Refiners are diversifying suppliers, increasingly sourcing from the Middle East, Africa, Canada, and the US, which has become a key supplier. While overall bilateral trade is growing robustly, driven by sectors beyond energy, India's trade deficit with Russia has widened substantially. Defence cooperation remains a critical component of the relationship.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:15:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e7027e10c98d0788e7ce2_1766748270977.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kuku FM's Revenue Triples to ₹242 Cr! Massive Ad Spends Fuel Growth, But Losses Swell – IPO Plans Near?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kuku-FMs-Revenue-Triples-to-242-Cr-Massive-Ad-Spends-Fuel-Growth-But-Losses-Swell-IPO-Plans-Near/694e6f97e10c98d0788e7bc9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kuku-FMs-Revenue-Triples-to-242-Cr-Massive-Ad-Spends-Fuel-Growth-But-Losses-Swell-IPO-Plans-Near/694e6f97e10c98d0788e7bc9</guid><description>Audio platform Kuku FM reported a strong financial year, with operating revenue nearly tripling to Rs 242 crore in FY25, a 175% jump. However, aggressive advertising spending led to expenses doubling, causing net losses to widen by 59% to Rs 153 crore. With over 10 million paying subscribers, the company is preparing for a significant Rs 3,000 crore IPO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:11:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6f97e10c98d0788e7bc8_1766748209618.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Creative Exports Soar! Jewellery, Toys Power $12.5B Surge as UAE Becomes Top Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Indias-Creative-Exports-Soar-Jewellery-Toys-Power-125B-Surge-as-UAE-Becomes-Top-Market/694e6ec4e10c98d0788e7a84</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Indias-Creative-Exports-Soar-Jewellery-Toys-Power-125B-Surge-as-UAE-Becomes-Top-Market/694e6ec4e10c98d0788e7a84</guid><description>India's exports of creative goods surged 7.3% to $12.5 billion in the first seven months of FY26, driven by fashion accessories, jewellery, carpets, and toys. The United Arab Emirates has emerged as the largest market, capturing a 31% share, surpassing the US. This growth highlights India's increasing role in global creative goods trade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:09:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6ec4e10c98d0788e7a83_1766747913115.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Parabolic Run Ending in 2026? Nilesh Shah Reveals Surprising Outlook!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Parabolic-Run-Ending-in-2026-Nilesh-Shah-Reveals-Surprising-Outlook/694e6b97e10c98d0788e761c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Parabolic-Run-Ending-in-2026-Nilesh-Shah-Reveals-Surprising-Outlook/694e6b97e10c98d0788e761c</guid><description>Nilesh Shah, Managing Director of Kotak Mahindra AMC, believes the extraordinary parabolic surge in gold and silver prices may not continue into 2026. Despite this, he maintains a positive outlook for both precious metals, citing sustained central bank buying for gold and robust industrial demand, particularly from the electric vehicle sector, for silver. Shah advises investors to adhere to asset allocation principles, diversifying portfolios across real estate, debt, equity, and precious metals. This comes as gold prices recently hit ₹1.39 lakh per 10 grams and silver surged past ₹2.33 lakh per kg on MCX.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:51:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6b97e10c98d0788e761b_1766747136927.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Railway &amp; PSU Stocks Plummet 50%! Spark Private Wealth Sees Hidden Value – Your Buying Guide?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Railway-and-PSU-Stocks-Plummet-50percent-Spark-Private-Wealth-Sees-Hidden-Value-Your-Buying-Guide/694e6ba4e10c98d0788e7663</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Railway-and-PSU-Stocks-Plummet-50percent-Spark-Private-Wealth-Sees-Hidden-Value-Your-Buying-Guide/694e6ba4e10c98d0788e7663</guid><description>Devang Mehta of Spark Private Wealth Management sees significant value opportunities in railway and Public Sector Undertaking (PSU) stocks. These sectors have seen corrections of 30-50%, much deeper than the broader market's median 24% fall. Mehta emphasizes that the investment case has shifted from mere seasonality to strong fundamentals like revenue growth and order books, making them attractive for investors focused on earnings visibility and cash flow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:51:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6ba4e10c98d0788e7662_1766747219849.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Snaps Losing Streak! Defence &amp; Metal Soar, But IT/Auto Stocks Falter - What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Snaps-Losing-Streak-Defence-and-Metal-Soar-But-ITAuto-Stocks-Falter-Whats-Next/694e6b07e10c98d0788e7514</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Snaps-Losing-Streak-Defence-and-Metal-Soar-But-ITAuto-Stocks-Falter-Whats-Next/694e6b07e10c98d0788e7514</guid><description>Indian benchmark indices concluded the week with modest gains, breaking a three-week losing streak. However, Friday saw the market end near day's lows, with the Nifty slipping below 26,050 and Sensex falling 367 points. Defence and metal stocks led sectoral gains, while IT and auto shares dragged the indices down for the third consecutive session. Several midcap stocks showed significant movement, both positive and negative.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:51:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6b07e10c98d0788e7513_1766746964172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FY27 Economic Boom: Economists Reveal Secret Growth Driver &amp; Rupee's Shocking Stability!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-Economic-Boom-Economists-Reveal-Secret-Growth-Driver-and-Rupees-Shocking-Stability/694e6b1de10c98d0788e7555</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-Economic-Boom-Economists-Reveal-Secret-Growth-Driver-and-Rupees-Shocking-Stability/694e6b1de10c98d0788e7555</guid><description>Economists from HDFC Bank and Union Bank of India forecast India's real GDP growth to normalize between 6.5% and 7% in fiscal year 2026-27, driven primarily by consumption. They anticipate nominal GDP growth to rise, supporting earnings and credit. The Indian Rupee is projected to trade in a stable 90-93 range against the US dollar by FY27, supported by a balance of payments surplus.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:51:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6b1de10c98d0788e7554_1766747010758.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manappuram Finance Fuels Growth: Rs 250 Cr Boost for Subsidiary, New CFO Hired!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-Fuels-Growth-Rs-250-Cr-Boost-for-Subsidiary-New-CFO-Hired/694e6a6be10c98d0788e73c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-Fuels-Growth-Rs-250-Cr-Boost-for-Subsidiary-New-CFO-Hired/694e6a6be10c98d0788e73c0</guid><description>Manappuram Finance announced a significant Rs 250 crore investment in its subsidiary, Asirvad Micro Finance, to fuel its expansion. The company also appointed Buvanesh Tharashankar as Group Chief Financial Officer, bringing nearly three decades of banking experience. Additionally, Manappuram Finance's board approved a proposal to hike its borrowing limit up to Rs 75,000 crore, bolstering its capacity for future lending and growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:48:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6a6be10c98d0788e73bf_1766746941789.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SME IPO Frenzy! 78% GMP on E to E Transportation Infra, Dhara Rail &amp; Apollo Techno IPOs - Big Listing Gains Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SME-IPO-Frenzy-78percent-GMP-on-E-to-E-Transportation-Infra-Dhara-Rail-and-Apollo-Techno-IPOs-Big-Listing-Gains-Ahead/694e69f1e10c98d0788e72a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SME-IPO-Frenzy-78percent-GMP-on-E-to-E-Transportation-Infra-Dhara-Rail-and-Apollo-Techno-IPOs-Big-Listing-Gains-Ahead/694e69f1e10c98d0788e72a5</guid><description>Three SME IPOs, E to E Transportation Infrastructure, Dhara Rail Projects, and Apollo Techno Industries, are drawing significant investor interest in India's primary market. E to E Transportation Infrastructure leads with a commanding Grey Market Premium (GMP) of up to 78%, followed by Dhara Rail Projects at 18% and Apollo Techno Industries at over 9%. These strong GMPs suggest potential substantial listing gains for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:47:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e69f1e10c98d0788e72a4_1766746781526.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AC Prices Set for Major Shift: New Rules &amp; Tax Cuts Spark Buyer Dilemma</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-AC-Prices-Set-for-Major-Shift-New-Rules-and-Tax-Cuts-Spark-Buyer-Dilemma/694e6ac9e10c98d0788e74ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-AC-Prices-Set-for-Major-Shift-New-Rules-and-Tax-Cuts-Spark-Buyer-Dilemma/694e6ac9e10c98d0788e74ac</guid><description>India's air conditioner market faces price changes starting January 2026 due to stricter energy efficiency norms from the Bureau of Energy Efficiency (BEE). While these new standards require more expensive components, a recent cut in Goods and Services Tax (GST) to 18% from 28% is expected to largely offset the price increase, potentially keeping new AC prices similar to pre-GST levels. Some manufacturers foresee broader cost pressures, however.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:47:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e6ac9e10c98d0788e74ab_1766747184490.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unveils Massive EV Charging Network: Over 27,000 Stations Installed at Petrol Pumps!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Unveils-Massive-EV-Charging-Network-Over-27000-Stations-Installed-at-Petrol-Pumps/694e69b9e10c98d0788e71d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Unveils-Massive-EV-Charging-Network-Over-27000-Stations-Installed-at-Petrol-Pumps/694e69b9e10c98d0788e71d3</guid><description>India significantly expanded its electric vehicle charging infrastructure in 2025, installing over 27,000 new stations at existing petrol pumps. This initiative, supported by the FAME-II scheme and direct investments from oil marketing companies, aims to boost EV adoption by making charging convenient and accessible. The rollout includes integrated mobility hubs offering various fuel types and facilities, enhancing future transportation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:45:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e69b9e10c98d0788e71d2_1766746641537.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>