<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:20:28 +0000</pubDate><item><title>NSE Unveils 10g Gold Futures: Democratizing Access, Reshaping Discovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NSE-Unveils-10g-Gold-Futures-Democratizing-Access-Reshaping-Discovery/699b0b3eee97f501b0ea3fbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NSE-Unveils-10g-Gold-Futures-Democratizing-Access-Reshaping-Discovery/699b0b3eee97f501b0ea3fbb</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange (NSE) is set to introduce 10-gram gold futures contracts on March 16, 2026, pending final regulatory clearance from SEBI. This strategic move aims to democratize gold investment by offering smaller, more accessible contract sizes, potentially enhancing market liquidity and refining price discovery for retail participants. The launch comes amid stable gold prices and a favorable trading environment following the recent withdrawal of additional margins by major exchanges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:57:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b0b3eee97f501b0ea3fba_1771768834476.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Holi Spurt: ₹80K Cr Sales Fueled by 'Vocal for Local' Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Holi-Spurt-80K-Cr-Sales-Fueled-by-Vocal-for-Local-Shift/699b09cbee97f501b0ea3ec6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Holi-Spurt-80K-Cr-Sales-Fueled-by-Vocal-for-Local-Shift/699b09cbee97f501b0ea3ec6</guid><description>The upcoming Holi festival is projected to generate over ₹80,000 crore in business nationwide, a 25% increase from the previous year. This surge is significantly propelled by the 'Vocal for Local' initiative, which has led to a marked decline in Chinese goods and bolstered demand for domestic products. The Confederation of All India Traders (CAIT) highlights a robust performance expected for MSMEs, traders, and retailers across various sectors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:51:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b09cbee97f501b0ea3ec5_1771768394295.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Serentica Renewables Eyes 5GW by FY27, Bets on India's Demand Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Serentica-Renewables-Eyes-5GW-by-FY27-Bets-on-Indias-Demand-Surge/699b08f8ee97f501b0ea3e1b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Serentica-Renewables-Eyes-5GW-by-FY27-Bets-on-Indias-Demand-Surge/699b08f8ee97f501b0ea3e1b</guid><description>Serentica Renewables, a KKR-backed independent power producer, is set to double its capacity to 5,000 MW by fiscal year 2027 and aims for 50 billion units of clean energy by FY30. The company plans to secure approximately $5 billion in debt and equity by FY27, funding an annual investment of $1.5-2 billion. This strategic expansion targets a significant surge in industrial power demand, driven by government initiatives like 'Make in India' and carbon border adjustment mechanism obligations. Serentica is focused on procuring solar modules and cells, managing recent commodity price volatility which has shown signs of stabilization.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:47:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b08f8ee97f501b0ea3e1a_1771768305541.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EU Trade Deal to Pressure Sula Vineyards' Thin Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/EU-Trade-Deal-to-Pressure-Sula-Vineyards-Thin-Margins/699b06f8ee97f501b0ea3d22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/EU-Trade-Deal-to-Pressure-Sula-Vineyards-Thin-Margins/699b06f8ee97f501b0ea3d22</guid><description>The India-EU Free Trade Agreement (FTA) is set to dramatically alter India's wine market by slashing import duties on European wines. This move threatens Sula Vineyards' core premium segment, where the company is already experiencing significant revenue degrowth and steep profit declines. While Sula's distribution partnerships offer a potential buffer, their thinner margins may not fully offset the intensified competitive pressure and valuation concerns.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:39:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b06f8ee97f501b0ea3d21_1771767680978.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Eyes Green Dominance: CHAKRA Fuels Sunrise Sector Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/SBI-Eyes-Green-Dominance-CHAKRA-Fuels-Sunrise-Sector-Push/699b042fee97f501b0ea3bf9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/SBI-Eyes-Green-Dominance-CHAKRA-Fuels-Sunrise-Sector-Push/699b042fee97f501b0ea3bf9</guid><description>State Bank of India (SBI) has launched CHAKRA, a Centre of Excellence to finance sunrise sectors like renewable energy and electric mobility. The bank aims to grow its green advances portfolio to 7.5-10% by 2030, up from 1.56% in March 2025. This strategic pivot leverages SBI's scale to capture India's green transition demand, supported by international credit lines and a growing regulatory push for sustainable finance.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:27:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b042fee97f501b0ea3bf8_1771766992774.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCDEX Pivots to Equities Amidst Agri-Futures Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NCDEX-Pivots-to-Equities-Amidst-Agri-Futures-Headwinds/699b0285ee97f501b0ea3ae0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NCDEX-Pivots-to-Equities-Amidst-Agri-Futures-Headwinds/699b0285ee97f501b0ea3ae0</guid><description>National Commodity and Derivatives Exchange (NCDEX) is strategically broadening its scope beyond its traditional agri-commodity focus by venturing into equity and equity derivatives segments. This multi-asset platform expansion, supported by a significant Rs 770 crore investment, aims to tap into new investor pools by leveraging its extensive regional network. The move comes as NCDEX grapples with prolonged regulatory bans on key agri-commodity futures trading, which have curtailed volumes and eroded market trust, prompting a search for stable revenue diversification.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:20:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b0285ee97f501b0ea3adf_1771766585878.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IHCL Valuation Under Scrutiny Amid Growth Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/IHCL-Valuation-Under-Scrutiny-Amid-Growth-Surge/699b01d1ee97f501b0ea3a36</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/IHCL-Valuation-Under-Scrutiny-Amid-Growth-Surge/699b01d1ee97f501b0ea3a36</guid><description>Indian Hotels Company (IHCL) showcased robust double-digit revenue growth driven by increased average room rates. However, the company's premium valuation, trading at multiples significantly higher than key competitors like EIH Ltd (Oberoi), alongside flat EBITDA margins in the latest quarter, is sparking debate among analysts. While several brokerages maintain 'Buy' ratings, others advise caution or 'Reduce', citing operational headwinds and valuation concerns. Strategic acquisitions are expected to boost the topline, but their ultimate value creation remains a point of scrutiny against a backdrop of solid domestic travel trends and a recovering tourism sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b01d1ee97f501b0ea3a35_1771766352225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPI Surges Globally: India's Digital Payment Powerhouse Expands</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/UPI-Surges-Globally-Indias-Digital-Payment-Powerhouse-Expands/699afd26ee97f501b0ea3819</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/UPI-Surges-Globally-Indias-Digital-Payment-Powerhouse-Expands/699afd26ee97f501b0ea3819</guid><description>India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) has shattered international transaction volume records in FY26, surpassing one million transactions for the first time. Volume nearly doubled to 1.48 million from 0.75 million in FY25, with value rising to ₹330.43 crore from ₹258.53 crore. This rapid ascent underscores NPCI International's aggressive global expansion strategy, evidenced by over two million international merchants onboarded and strategic market entries planned in Japan and Malaysia. UPI's success positions India as a dominant force in the global fintech landscape, offering a scalable, cost-effective alternative to established payment systems.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:57:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699afd26ee97f501b0ea3818_1771765181626.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>YES Bank Targets 1% ROA Amidst SMBC Stake &amp; Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/YES-Bank-Targets-1percent-ROA-Amidst-SMBC-Stake-and-Recovery/699afd23ee97f501b0ea3802</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/YES-Bank-Targets-1percent-ROA-Amidst-SMBC-Stake-and-Recovery/699afd23ee97f501b0ea3802</guid><description>YES Bank projects ending the fiscal year with a 1% Return on Assets (ROA), a key milestone in its ongoing recovery. CFO Niranjan Banodkar anticipates exceeding this benchmark in the next fiscal year. This target follows a strong December quarter showing a 55% year-on-year net profit surge and improved annualized ROA. The strategic acquisition of a significant stake by Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation (SMBC) is intended to accelerate growth and profitability by rebalancing the bank's asset portfolio and resolving legacy lending shortfalls.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:57:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699afd23ee97f501b0ea3801_1771765179139.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric's 'Structural Reset' Masks Deepening Financial Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-Structural-Reset-Masks-Deepening-Financial-Woes/699afad3ee97f501b0ea36cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-Structural-Reset-Masks-Deepening-Financial-Woes/699afad3ee97f501b0ea36cf</guid><description>Ola Electric is undergoing a drastic 'structural reset' as revenue and deliveries have collapsed by over 70% since early 2025, shrinking its market share to 6%. Auditors have repeatedly flagged concerns about the company's ability to continue as a going concern, relying on management's cash flow projections. Despite these red flags and a significant stock price decline, management continues to reframe setbacks as strategic maneuvers, a pattern now drawing intense scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:47:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699afad3ee97f501b0ea36ce_1771764596762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Macrotech Developers Lands Prime Mumbai Land Via JV</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Macrotech-Developers-Lands-Prime-Mumbai-Land-Via-JV/699af526ee97f501b0ea3497</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Macrotech-Developers-Lands-Prime-Mumbai-Land-Via-JV/699af526ee97f501b0ea3497</guid><description>Macrotech Developers Ltd. has finalized a joint development agreement for 10.26 acres in Mumbai's Parel-Sewri area. The deal, valued at ₹364.80 crore, involves a 63:37 revenue share between the developer and landowners. This partnership structure reduces upfront land acquisition costs, allowing Macrotech to enhance its development pipeline in a prime micro-market known for its transformation into a residential hub. The move aligns with a broader trend of developers favoring such agreements in high-cost urban environments to preserve capital and optimize project viability, especially amidst limited availability of large land parcels.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:23:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699af526ee97f501b0ea3496_1771763150984.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Power Fuels East India Push with ₹40,000 Cr Power Projects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Power-Fuels-East-India-Push-with-40000-Cr-Power-Projects/699af43aee97f501b0ea340e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Power-Fuels-East-India-Push-with-40000-Cr-Power-Projects/699af43aee97f501b0ea340e</guid><description>Adani Group Chairman Gautam Adani reviewed over ₹40,000 crore in power investments across Jharkhand and Bihar, focusing on the 1,600 MW Godda plant exporting power to Bangladesh and a new 2,400 MW project in Bihar. These initiatives cement Adani's infrastructure presence in historically capital-scarce eastern regions, alongside Adani Power's market capitalization of approximately ₹2.75 lakh crore and a P/E ratio around 24x. The move signals continued commitment to thermal power despite a rapidly evolving national energy landscape prioritizing renewables.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:19:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699af43aee97f501b0ea340d_1771763274178.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SCOTUS Ruling: India Gains Trade Respite, But US Tariff Tactics Evolve</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SCOTUS-Ruling-India-Gains-Trade-Respite-But-US-Tariff-Tactics-Evolve/699aef22ee97f501b0ea322e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SCOTUS-Ruling-India-Gains-Trade-Respite-But-US-Tariff-Tactics-Evolve/699aef22ee97f501b0ea322e</guid><description>The US Supreme Court's February 20, 2026, decision invalidating broad executive-imposed tariffs provides India immediate relief from punitive duties. While this eases pressure on key export sectors and strengthens India's negotiating hand, the US administration's rapid pivot to alternative legal mechanisms, like Section 122 tariffs, indicates trade policy remains volatile. This shift from sweeping levies to more targeted, albeit temporary, measures creates a complex and uncertain trade environment, suggesting the US retains significant leverage despite the judicial setback. The market reaction has been positive, anticipating an improvement in export competitiveness and capital inflows, though long-term stability hinges on the legal viability and duration of these new measures.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:57:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699aef22ee97f501b0ea322d_1771761562574.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCR Rapid Rail Expands: New Corridors Planned Amidst TOD Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NCR-Rapid-Rail-Expands-New-Corridors-Planned-Amidst-TOD-Push/699ae6bfee97f501b0ea2f1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NCR-Rapid-Rail-Expands-New-Corridors-Planned-Amidst-TOD-Push/699ae6bfee97f501b0ea2f1f</guid><description>Union Housing and Urban Affairs Minister Manohar Lal Khattar revealed plans for two new rapid rail corridors originating from Sarai Kale Khan, aimed at bolstering the National Capital Region's (NCR) high-speed transit network. This expansion is intrinsically linked to a broader strategy of transit-oriented development (TOD) designed to decentralize economic activity and alleviate pressure on Delhi. The inauguration of the Sarai Kale Khan station on the Delhi-Ghaziabad-Meerut RRTS corridor marks a critical nexus for future regional transport planning, underscoring the government's aggressive push to integrate urban and regional development through infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:21:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ae6bfee97f501b0ea2f1e_1771759401819.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tariffs, AI Fears &amp; Geopolitics Rock Indian Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tariffs-AI-Fears-and-Geopolitics-Rock-Indian-Markets/699ae5bcee97f501b0ea2e05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tariffs-AI-Fears-and-Geopolitics-Rock-Indian-Markets/699ae5bcee97f501b0ea2e05</guid><description>Indian equity markets are braced for continued volatility driven by a confluence of factors. The US Supreme Court's ruling against President Trump's tariffs, coupled with his intent to use alternative measures, injects ongoing trade policy uncertainty. Simultaneously, the Information Technology sector faces significant headwinds from AI-driven disruption, while geopolitical tensions in the Middle East and upcoming domestic economic data, including GDP, will be key market influencers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:17:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ae5bcee97f501b0ea2e04_1771759193497.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sarvam Kaze: India's Sovereign AI Hardware Bet Faces Fierce Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sarvam-Kaze-Indias-Sovereign-AI-Hardware-Bet-Faces-Fierce-Market/699ae5b2ee97f501b0ea2dee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sarvam-Kaze-Indias-Sovereign-AI-Hardware-Bet-Faces-Fierce-Market/699ae5b2ee97f501b0ea2dee</guid><description>Sarvam AI has unveiled Sarvam Kaze, its AI-powered smart glasses, signaling a significant strategic push into capital-intensive hardware. The 'Made-in-India' device aims to bolster India's sovereign AI ambitions, contrasting with software-centric models. While targeting an affordable price point, Kaze enters a market populated by Meta, Reliance Jio, and Lenskart, with crucial details on pricing and specifications still under wraps. This venture represents a high-stakes test for India's capacity to develop competitive domestic AI hardware.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:17:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ae5b2ee97f501b0ea2ded_1771759150456.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Fortifies Financial Backbone with Strategic Odisha Data Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Fortifies-Financial-Backbone-with-Strategic-Odisha-Data-Hub/699ae44bee97f501b0ea2cfc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Fortifies-Financial-Backbone-with-Strategic-Odisha-Data-Hub/699ae44bee97f501b0ea2cfc</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has activated a Tier IV certified, high-security data center in Odisha, a strategic move to insulate critical financial infrastructure from cross-border threats and seismic risks. This initiative aligns with a global trend of central banks prioritizing sovereign control over data, enhancing systemic resilience in an era of escalating geopolitical and cyber uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ae44bee97f501b0ea2cfb_1771758815567.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Eyes M&amp;A Financing Amidst RBI's ECL Shift &amp; AI Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Eyes-MandA-Financing-Amidst-RBIs-ECL-Shift-and-AI-Push/699adf9dee97f501b0ea2b29</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Eyes-MandA-Financing-Amidst-RBIs-ECL-Shift-and-AI-Push/699adf9dee97f501b0ea2b29</guid><description>State Bank of India (SBI) is aggressively positioning itself to capture market share in M&amp;A financing, establishing a dedicated team and exploring international partnerships to leverage its expanded lending capacity under new RBI norms. Concurrently, the bank is embedding Artificial Intelligence across operations, from fraud prevention to personalized customer recommendations, aiming to drive efficiency and deepen customer engagement. Chairman CS Setty expressed confidence that the bank's robust asset quality, proactive strategy, and established practices will ensure a marginal impact from the upcoming RBI Expected Credit Loss (ECL) rules, effective April 2027, even as the competitive banking landscape tightens and PSU banks show renewed growth momentum.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 10:51:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699adf9dee97f501b0ea2b28_1771757697676.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FMCG Sector Shifts to Volume Growth Amid Easing Inflation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Sector-Shifts-to-Volume-Growth-Amid-Easing-Inflation/699ad6b6ee97f501b0ea2809</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Sector-Shifts-to-Volume-Growth-Amid-Easing-Inflation/699ad6b6ee97f501b0ea2809</guid><description>Fast-Moving Consumer Goods (FMCG) companies in India are projecting a pivot towards volume-driven growth in fiscal year 2027. This strategic shift is underpinned by declining inflation and stable commodity prices, which are expected to ease margin pressures and stimulate consumer spending. Key players like Dabur, Marico, and Britannia Industries foresee stronger EBITDA margins, benefiting from macroeconomic tailwinds including GST rationalization. While rural demand remains robust, urban consumption is showing signs of recovery. However, mixed consumer confidence indicators and divergent analyst ratings suggest a nuanced market outlook.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 10:13:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ad6b6ee97f501b0ea2808_1771755384795.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haryana Gov Tightens Banking Rules; IDFC, AU SFB De-Panelled</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Haryana-Gov-Tightens-Banking-Rules-IDFC-AU-SFB-De-Panelled/699ad5c5ee97f501b0ea2737</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Haryana-Gov-Tightens-Banking-Rules-IDFC-AU-SFB-De-Panelled/699ad5c5ee97f501b0ea2737</guid><description>Haryana's finance department has enacted stringent new rules for public fund management and banking relationships, effective February 18, 2026. The directives mandate the use of nationalized banks for government schemes, requiring prior finance department approval for any private or corporate bank accounts. Consequently, IDFC First Bank and AU Small Finance Bank have been removed from the state's approved panel for government business. This move aims to enhance oversight and ensure higher yields on surplus funds, with administrative secretaries held personally accountable for compliance.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 10:09:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ad5c5ee97f501b0ea2736_1771755077750.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariffs: India's Trade Edge Faces Legal Flux</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariffs-Indias-Trade-Edge-Faces-Legal-Flux/699ad0a2ee97f501b0ea2553</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariffs-Indias-Trade-Edge-Faces-Legal-Flux/699ad0a2ee97f501b0ea2553</guid><description>Helios Capital founder Samir Arora suggests India's competitive position remains unchanged by a new 15% US tariff rate, citing broad uniformity. However, a recent Supreme Court ruling has invalidated prior tariff mechanisms, while the US administration pursues alternative legal avenues. This dynamic introduces inherent policy instability, potentially leading to targeted trade pressures and eroding the perceived advantage of uniform rates, especially given prior bilateral trade agreements that set lower tariff expectations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 09:47:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ad0a2ee97f501b0ea2552_1771753798187.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Microsoft Gaming Leadership Shuffle Sparks AI Focus Amidst Controversy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microsoft-Gaming-Leadership-Shuffle-Sparks-AI-Focus-Amidst-Controversy/699acfadee97f501b0ea248e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microsoft-Gaming-Leadership-Shuffle-Sparks-AI-Focus-Amidst-Controversy/699acfadee97f501b0ea248e</guid><description>Microsoft has appointed AI executive Asha Sharma as the new CEO of Microsoft Gaming, replacing retiring Xbox chief Phil Spencer. The move has ignited a firestorm of online criticism, with many gamers questioning Sharma's gaming industry experience. Despite the backlash, Sharma has outlined a vision prioritizing "great games" and a return to "the renegade spirit that built Xbox," emphasizing games as art. This transition signals a strategic pivot for the division, potentially leveraging AI for enhanced creative development rather than mere efficiency, a direction that contrasts with some competitors' approaches.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 09:43:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699acfadee97f501b0ea248d_1771753502621.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Data Hub Ambition Stalls on Power Grid Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Data-Hub-Ambition-Stalls-on-Power-Grid-Hurdles/699acde1ee97f501b0ea2332</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Data-Hub-Ambition-Stalls-on-Power-Grid-Hurdles/699acde1ee97f501b0ea2332</guid><description>India aims to be a major data center hub, fueled by structural cost advantages and government incentives like a tax holiday until 2047. However, the exponential energy demands of AI are straining power generation and grid infrastructure. Inconsistent state policies on renewable energy, coupled with transmission bottlenecks and grid stability issues, create significant execution risks. Addressing these power and grid challenges is paramount for India to realize its digital ambitions and avoid falling behind competitors in the burgeoning Asia-Pacific data center market.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 09:35:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699acde1ee97f501b0ea2331_1771753176718.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Biogas Policy Spark: Rs 1 Lakh Crore Investment Goal Faces Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Biogas-Policy-Spark-Rs-1-Lakh-Crore-Investment-Goal-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/699ac91bee97f501b0ea2188</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Biogas-Policy-Spark-Rs-1-Lakh-Crore-Investment-Goal-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/699ac91bee97f501b0ea2188</guid><description>A Union Budget 2026 excise duty waiver on Compressed Biogas (CBG) blended with Compressed Natural Gas (CNG) is projected by the Indian Biogas Association (IBA) to unlock Rs 1 lakh crore in investment and accelerate India's energy transition. While the policy aims to lower costs for distributors and consumers, and boost revenue for producers, achieving ambitious blending targets hinges on significant infrastructure build-out, consistent feedstock supply, and navigating potential competition from other green energy initiatives. The waiver addresses a key pricing imbalance, making renewable biogas more cost-competitive, which is crucial for project IRR improvements and attracting previously marginal financing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 09:15:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ac91bee97f501b0ea2187_1771751855907.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Growth Race: Mondelez, Reckitt Navigate Complex Execution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Growth-Race-Mondelez-Reckitt-Navigate-Complex-Execution/699ac845ee97f501b0ea20b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Growth-Race-Mondelez-Reckitt-Navigate-Complex-Execution/699ac845ee97f501b0ea20b0</guid><description>Global consumer giants Mondelez International and Reckitt are intensifying their focus on India, a market poised for significant long-term growth driven by a rising middle class and increased disposable incomes. While both companies are leveraging established brands and expanding their reach, the path to sustained success hinges on intricate execution strategies and navigating a highly competitive, evolving retail landscape. Mondelez is pursuing aggressive volume-led growth through extensive store expansion, while Reckitt aims to maintain its high single-digit growth trajectory with innovation and strong brand penetration, even as China emerges as a larger global growth engine.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 09:11:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ac845ee97f501b0ea20af_1771751601828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Builds Secure Odisha Data Hub for Financial Stability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Builds-Secure-Odisha-Data-Hub-for-Financial-Stability/699ac19c73bcaafe2ac133c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Builds-Secure-Odisha-Data-Hub-for-Financial-Stability/699ac19c73bcaafe2ac133c6</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has completed a new, highly secure data centre in Bhubaneswar, Odisha. Strategically located away from borders and seismic zones, this facility is designed to protect critical financial infrastructure from evolving cyber and geopolitical threats. Achieving Tier IV certification, it enhances system resilience and operational continuity for core banking and payment systems, reflecting a global trend among central banks to bolster sovereign data control.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:43:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ac19c73bcaafe2ac133c5_1771749903136.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UGRO Capital: Can Synergies Bridge Cost Gap?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UGRO-Capital-Can-Synergies-Bridge-Cost-Gap/699ac19673bcaafe2ac133af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UGRO-Capital-Can-Synergies-Bridge-Cost-Gap/699ac19673bcaafe2ac133af</guid><description>UGRO Capital aims to slash its 1.25% borrowing cost premium over peers by FY27, leveraging synergies from the Profectus Capital acquisition. While the deal promises cost savings and asset growth, the company's low promoter holding, recent profit plunges, and a challenging NBFC funding environment raise questions about its ability to close the cost gap and improve profitability. Its market valuation remains significantly below larger competitors despite recent capital raises.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:43:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ac19673bcaafe2ac133ae_1771750400063.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Odisha Approves ₹44,200Cr Industrial Projects: A Future Sector Bet</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Odisha-Approves-44200Cr-Industrial-Projects-A-Future-Sector-Bet/699ab9a373bcaafe2ac12fa1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Odisha-Approves-44200Cr-Industrial-Projects-A-Future-Sector-Bet/699ab9a373bcaafe2ac12fa1</guid><description>Odisha's government has greenlit ten industrial projects totaling ₹44,200 crore, focusing on future-oriented sectors like semiconductors, rare earth manufacturing, and renewable energy. These initiatives are projected to create over 8,700 jobs and signal the state's ambition to become a major investment hub. Key approvals include Adani Group's pumped storage hydro, a semiconductor memory chip plant by ASP Semicon, and aerospace component manufacturing by Bharat Forge. The state administration emphasizes timely project execution alongside investment attraction.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:09:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ab9a373bcaafe2ac12fa0_1771750430949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Namo Bharat, Meerut Metro Inaugurated: Integration &amp; Funding Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Namo-Bharat-Meerut-Metro-Inaugurated-Integration-and-Funding-Scrutiny/699ab8d073bcaafe2ac12ed6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Namo-Bharat-Meerut-Metro-Inaugurated-Integration-and-Funding-Scrutiny/699ab8d073bcaafe2ac12ed6</guid><description>The inauguration of the 82 km Delhi-Meerut Namo Bharat RRTS and Meerut Metro marks a significant leap in regional connectivity, boasting speeds up to 180 kmph and integrated infrastructure. This advancement promises to drastically cut travel times, boost economic opportunities, and reduce emissions. However, the project's ambitious scale is shadowed by evolving budget allocations for its operator, NCRTC, and the complex financial engineering required for such large-scale public transport endeavors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:05:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ab8d073bcaafe2ac12ed5_1771750566957.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Navigates Sanctions: Crude Imports Rebalance, Costs Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Navigates-Sanctions-Crude-Imports-Rebalance-Costs-Rise/699aab9873bcaafe2ac1297d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Navigates-Sanctions-Crude-Imports-Rebalance-Costs-Rise/699aab9873bcaafe2ac1297d</guid><description>India's crude import volumes dipped 8% in early February compared to January, signaling a strategic rebalancing away from Russian supplies due to sanctions. Middle Eastern producers, particularly Saudi Arabia, are stepping in to fill the void, marking a shift from Russia's dominant post-Ukraine war position. This transition is projected to increase India's average crude acquisition costs by $2-$3 per barrel, as the nation navigates geopolitical alignment with energy security demands and supply chain complexities. The Vadinar refinery faces particular reliance on Russian crude.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:09:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699aab9873bcaafe2ac1297c_1771744337067.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Grid Accelerator: Unlocking Economic Power for Rural India</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Grid-Accelerator-Unlocking-Economic-Power-for-Rural-India/699aab2373bcaafe2ac128e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Grid-Accelerator-Unlocking-Economic-Power-for-Rural-India/699aab2373bcaafe2ac128e3</guid><description>The Global Energy Alliance for People and Planet's India Grids of the Future Accelerator, backed by a $25 million grant, aims to modernize power distribution and integrate renewables. Focusing on economic competitiveness, it utilizes 'digital twin' technology to optimize grids, unlock latent demand, and foster significant livelihood improvements, particularly for women, thereby bridging the 'two Indias' economic divide. This initiative aligns with India's robust economic growth projections and significant infrastructure investment plans.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:07:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699aab2373bcaafe2ac128e2_1771744188813.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Expands Penicillin-G Output, Boosted by Policy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Expands-Penicillin-G-Output-Boosted-by-Policy/699aab1f73bcaafe2ac128cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Expands-Penicillin-G-Output-Boosted-by-Policy/699aab1f73bcaafe2ac128cc</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma is poised to significantly ramp up its Penicillin-G production to over 10,000 metric tonnes annually within the next 12 months. This strategic move is supported by favorable central government policies relaxing minimum import prices for key antibiotics, which the company views as a crucial catalyst for domestic self-reliance. Concurrently, Aurobindo is progressing with its China and US facility expansions, anticipating EBITDA breakeven in China this quarter and revenue contributions from its US operations starting fiscal year 2027. The company maintains confidence in its growth trajectory, targeting higher end of 20-21% EBITDA margins for FY26.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:07:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699aab1f73bcaafe2ac128cb_1771744151156.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Talks Postponed: A Strategic Pause Amidst Tariff Chaos</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-US-Trade-Talks-Postponed-A-Strategic-Pause-Amidst-Tariff-Chaos/699aa9b873bcaafe2ac127cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-US-Trade-Talks-Postponed-A-Strategic-Pause-Amidst-Tariff-Chaos/699aa9b873bcaafe2ac127cf</guid><description>India and the United States have postponed key trade negotiations meant to finalize an interim bilateral agreement. This deferral signals India's strategic intent to reassess terms amidst evolving U.S. trade policy following a Supreme Court ruling that invalidated broad tariffs. While public statements suggest talks remain on track, the postponement likely reflects India's effort to leverage the new tariff landscape, where a uniform U.S. global tariff replaces previously negotiated rates, potentially diminishing the value of India's concessions and offering leverage for renegotiation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:01:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699aa9b873bcaafe2ac127ce_1771743812412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Talks Stall Amid Tariff Policy Chaos</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Talks-Stall-Amid-Tariff-Policy-Chaos/699aa8c573bcaafe2ac1271d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Talks-Stall-Amid-Tariff-Policy-Chaos/699aa8c573bcaafe2ac1271d</guid><description>The chief negotiators' meeting for the India-US interim trade pact has been rescheduled. This delay follows the US Supreme Court's ruling against former President Trump's emergency tariffs and his subsequent announcement to increase global tariffs. Both nations require time to assess the implications of this volatile trade policy environment before proceeding, casting a shadow over the finalization of the agreement.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:57:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699aa8c573bcaafe2ac1271c_1771743597568.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Parag Parikh Flexi Cap: High Returns, High Risk Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Parag-Parikh-Flexi-Cap-High-Returns-High-Risk-Scrutiny/699aa3a173bcaafe2ac12556</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Parag-Parikh-Flexi-Cap-High-Returns-High-Risk-Scrutiny/699aa3a173bcaafe2ac12556</guid><description>Parag Parikh Flexi Cap Fund (PPFAS) has demonstrated a decade of superior returns, with a 19.24% CAGR outperforming its benchmark and category averages. Its strong risk-adjusted metrics, including a Sharpe ratio of 1.68, underscore its efficiency. However, the fund's 'Very High Risk' classification necessitates a critical review of its concentrated portfolio, key sector allocations in Financials and Technology, and the long-term sustainability of its performance against evolving market dynamics and competitive pressures.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:35:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699aa3a173bcaafe2ac12555_1771742233415.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India's Gevra Mine Surges Amidst Global Coal Decline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-Indias-Gevra-Mine-Surges-Amidst-Global-Coal-Decline/699a9c5881427192210209b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-Indias-Gevra-Mine-Surges-Amidst-Global-Coal-Decline/699a9c5881427192210209b8</guid><description>Coal India's Gevra mine is poised to become the world's largest coal producer, targeting 63 million tonnes annually by FY2026-27, surpassing the US-based Black Thunder Mine. This expansion occurs as global coal trade faces a predicted two-year decline through 2026. Despite Gevra's growing output, Coal India reported a 16% dip in net profit for Q3 FY25 and maintains a 'Neutral' analyst consensus. The company is simultaneously pursuing diversification into solar, gasification, and critical minerals, alongside plans for an IPO of its subsidiary SECL.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:04:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a9c5881427192210209b7_1771740374382.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pernod Ricard India IPO Off Table Amid Global Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pernod-Ricard-India-IPO-Off-Table-Amid-Global-Slump/699a9c5781427192210209a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pernod-Ricard-India-IPO-Off-Table-Amid-Global-Slump/699a9c5781427192210209a1</guid><description>Pernod Ricard's India operations are a bright spot, delivering 4% net sales growth driven by premiumization trends, contributing 12-13% to global revenue. This contrasts sharply with a global sales decline of 5.9% organically in the first half of FY26, dragged by the Americas and China. Despite a deleveraging target to reduce its net debt-to-EBITDA ratio below 3x by FY2029, the company has ruled out an initial public offering of its Indian business, emphasizing its strategic importance as a growth engine.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:04:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a9c5781427192210209a0_1771740378022.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor: CEO Bullish, But High P/E Spurs Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-CEO-Bullish-But-High-PE-Spurs-Valuation-Scrutiny/699a9be181427192210208ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-CEO-Bullish-But-High-PE-Spurs-Valuation-Scrutiny/699a9be181427192210208ec</guid><description>TVS Motor CEO KN Radhakrishnan projects an optimistic long-term growth trajectory for the Indian two-wheeler sector, expecting an 8-9% CAGR fueled by favorable policies and enhanced personal mobility needs. While analysts maintain positive ratings and raise price targets, the company's significantly higher price-to-earnings multiple compared to peers like Hero MotoCorp and Bajaj Auto warrants cautious assessment of its premium valuation. Recent Q4 expectations of over 15% growth and continued momentum into FY27 are noted, but sustainability risks remain under scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:02:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a9be181427192210208eb_1771740301835.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Coal Faces Demand Paradox: Record Output Meets Uncertain Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Coal-Faces-Demand-Paradox-Record-Output-Meets-Uncertain-Future/699a9b698142719221020816</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Coal-Faces-Demand-Paradox-Record-Output-Meets-Uncertain-Future/699a9b698142719221020816</guid><description>India's coal sector is navigating conflicting signals. A strong recovery in power demand during December and January, driven by a harsh winter and economic uptick, offers a short-term reprieve after a period of demand slowdown. However, this comes after the industry hit a record one-billion-tonne production milestone, creating an environment of strategic uncertainty. Industry leaders will convene at the "Coalosseum" conference to address these complex dynamics, balancing immediate demand boosts against evolving global energy landscapes and the sector's substantial production capacity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:00:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a9b698142719221020815_1771740159034.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India GDP Cools; Capex Slump, Exports Drag Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Cools-Capex-Slump-Exports-Drag-Growth/699a9b6781427192210207ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Cools-Capex-Slump-Exports-Drag-Growth/699a9b6781427192210207ff</guid><description>India's economic growth is projected to ease to 7.2% year-on-year in Q3 FY2025-26, down from 8.2% in Q2, according to ICRA. This deceleration stems from a significant 23.4% contraction in government capital expenditure and slower expansion in services and agriculture. While the industrial sector shows resilience with an 8.3% growth projection, it's insufficient to offset broader slowdowns. Weak merchandise exports and moderating services exports also contribute to the headwinds, though robust domestic demand, buoyed by GST rationalization, is expected to maintain growth above the 7% mark.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:00:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699a9b6781427192210207fe_1771740136785.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>