<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:18:34 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's 2025 Leap: Government Unleashes Sweeping Labour Reforms &amp; Social Security Boost – Are You Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-Leap-Government-Unleashes-Sweeping-Labour-Reforms-and-Social-Security-Boost-Are-You-Ready/6953ecba4342f77179e7551a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-Leap-Government-Unleashes-Sweeping-Labour-Reforms-and-Social-Security-Boost-Are-You-Ready/6953ecba4342f77179e7551a</guid><description>India's government is driving major reforms in 2025, implementing four new labour codes to modernize regulations, simplify compliance, and enhance worker welfare. Key initiatives include expanding social security for gig and platform workers, launching EPFO 3.0 for easier fund access, and the Pradhan Mantri Viksit Bharat Rozgar Yojana aimed at creating over 3.5 crore jobs. These reforms seek to boost employment, improve working conditions, and significantly increase social protection coverage across the nation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:07:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ecba4342f77179e75519_1767107848081.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Ministry Awards HUGE ₹1,661 Crore Carbine Contract to Bharat Forge: 'Make in India' Milestone!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Ministry-Awards-HUGE-1661-Crore-Carbine-Contract-to-Bharat-Forge-Make-in-India-Milestone/6953ed1d4342f77179e757df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Ministry-Awards-HUGE-1661-Crore-Carbine-Contract-to-Bharat-Forge-Make-in-India-Milestone/6953ed1d4342f77179e757df</guid><description>Bharat Forge has secured its largest ever small arms contract, valued at ₹1,661.9 crore, from the Defence Ministry. The deal involves supplying 2,55,128 CQB Carbines (5.56×45 mm) to the Indian Army over five years. This indigenously designed and developed weapon underscores the 'Atmanirbhar Bharat' mission, boosting domestic defense manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:07:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Auto Takeover! See How Nearly HALF of South Africa's Cars Now Have an Indian Link!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Takeover-See-How-Nearly-HALF-of-South-Africas-Cars-Now-Have-an-Indian-Link/6953e7444342f77179e6e3b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Takeover-See-How-Nearly-HALF-of-South-Africas-Cars-Now-Have-an-Indian-Link/6953e7444342f77179e6e3b1</guid><description>A report reveals that by 2025, almost half of cars sold in South Africa will be connected to India. This includes vehicles manufactured by Indian giants like Mahindra and Tata, or cars from Japanese and Korean brands assembled using Indian components or from Indian plants, notably Maruti Suzuki. This trend, driven by India's manufacturing cost advantages, sees Indian imports surpassing Chinese brands and causing concern for South Africa's local automotive industry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:46:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e7444342f77179e6e3b0_1767106456275.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airport Blocks Telecom Giants! Govt Intervention Sought in RoW Row</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airport-Blocks-Telecom-Giants-Govt-Intervention-Sought-in-RoW-Row/6953e7bf4342f77179e6e4a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airport-Blocks-Telecom-Giants-Govt-Intervention-Sought-in-RoW-Row/6953e7bf4342f77179e6e4a2</guid><description>The telecom industry body COAI has urged the Department of Telecom (DoT) to intervene against Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIAL). COAI alleges NMIAL is denying essential Right of Way (RoW) permissions for deploying telecom infrastructure and imposing exclusive, costly network usage, impacting major players like Bharti Airtel, Reliance Jio, and Vodafone Idea.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:46:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e7bf4342f77179e6e4a1_1767106652540.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Market Rocket Fuel? CIO Unlocks 2026 Boom Secrets &amp; IPO Valuations!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Market-Rocket-Fuel-CIO-Unlocks-2026-Boom-Secrets-and-IPO-Valuations/6953e62e4342f77179e6e03b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Market-Rocket-Fuel-CIO-Unlocks-2026-Boom-Secrets-and-IPO-Valuations/6953e62e4342f77179e6e03b</guid><description>Sankaran Naren, CIO of ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund, predicts India's equities will outperform globally by 2026, especially if the US market corrects. He notes India is now relatively cheaper than peers. While small-caps have cooled, mid-caps remain elevated due to low floating stock. Naren advises retail investors to maintain asset allocation and a long-term view, and stresses that a healthy IPO market hinges on reasonable pricing to sustain its boom.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:38:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e62e4342f77179e6e03a_1767106341461.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PM Modi's Bold Vision: Reforms for India's Global Economic Dominance Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PM-Modis-Bold-Vision-Reforms-for-Indias-Global-Economic-Dominance-Revealed/6953e6314342f77179e6e071</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PM-Modis-Bold-Vision-Reforms-for-Indias-Global-Economic-Dominance-Revealed/6953e6314342f77179e6e071</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi met with economists to discuss critical reforms needed across sectors for long-term growth and global integration. He emphasized making India a global hub for international markets, aligning with the Viksit Bharat 2047 aspiration. Discussions focused on enhancing productivity, leveraging AI, and scaling Digital Public Infrastructure. Economists shared insights suggesting that ongoing reforms will solidify India's position as one of the world's fastest-growing economies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:37:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e6314342f77179e6e070_1767106270794.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor Strikes Deal: Big Boost for Commercial Vehicle Sales &amp; EV Push!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Strikes-Deal-Big-Boost-for-Commercial-Vehicle-Sales-and-EV-Push/6953e65d4342f77179e6e0e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Strikes-Deal-Big-Boost-for-Commercial-Vehicle-Sales-and-EV-Push/6953e65d4342f77179e6e0e8</guid><description>TVS Motor Company has partnered with Manba Finance, an NBFC, to offer retail finance solutions for its commercial mobility portfolio. This aims to improve vehicle affordability and access to financing for customers across India, focusing on three-wheelers (ICE and EV). The collaboration seeks to strengthen the ecosystem, penetrate rural markets, and support last-mile entrepreneurs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:37:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e65d4342f77179e6e0e7_1767107233505.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shalini Bhupal Buys Taj GVK Stake for ₹592 Cr, IHCL Exits! What Happens Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shalini-Bhupal-Buys-Taj-GVK-Stake-for-592-Cr-IHCL-Exits-What-Happens-Next/6953e1504342f77179e6d5ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shalini-Bhupal-Buys-Taj-GVK-Stake-for-592-Cr-IHCL-Exits-What-Happens-Next/6953e1504342f77179e6d5ce</guid><description>Shalini Bhupal, a promoter shareholder, has acquired a 25.52% stake in Taj GVK Hotels &amp; Resorts Ltd from The Indian Hotels Company Ltd (IHCL) for ₹592 crore. This transaction leads to the termination of agreements between the two companies, resulting in IHCL directors stepping down and Taj GVK Hotels preparing to remove 'Taj' from its corporate name. IHCL will continue operating existing hotels under current agreements.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:15:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e1504342f77179e6d5cd_1767104968220.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PowerGrid Bags Rs 2,000 Crore Battery Storage Project in Andhra Pradesh: What It Means for India's Energy Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/PowerGrid-Bags-Rs-2000-Crore-Battery-Storage-Project-in-Andhra-Pradesh-What-It-Means-for-Indias-Energy-Future/6953e15a4342f77179e6d5fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/PowerGrid-Bags-Rs-2000-Crore-Battery-Storage-Project-in-Andhra-Pradesh-What-It-Means-for-Indias-Energy-Future/6953e15a4342f77179e6d5fb</guid><description>Power Grid Corporation of India Limited (PowerGrid) has been awarded a major bid to set up a 2,000 MWh battery energy storage system in Andhra Pradesh. This project, operating under a build-own-operate model and supported by Viability Gap Funding, aims to enhance grid flexibility, reliability, and renewable energy integration. A specific 150 MW unit will be installed at Kalikiri. The award date was December 29, 2025, though PowerGrid shares saw a slight dip on December 30.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:15:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e15a4342f77179e6d5fa_1767104974452.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RITES Lands $3.6 Million Locomotive Deal in Zimbabwe – Investor Alert!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RITES-Lands-36-Million-Locomotive-Deal-in-Zimbabwe-Investor-Alert/6953e20b4342f77179e6d78f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RITES-Lands-36-Million-Locomotive-Deal-in-Zimbabwe-Investor-Alert/6953e20b4342f77179e6d78f</guid><description>Infrastructure firm RITES Limited has received a Letter of Award from Zimbabwe's Berhard Development Corporation (Private) Ltd for supplying cape gauge diesel electric locomotives. The contract is valued at $3.6 million and is set for completion within three months. This international order highlights RITES' expanding global footprint in the transport sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:15:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e20b4342f77179e6d78e_1767105249804.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Grayscale Forecast: Regulation Set to Dominate Crypto in 2026, Quantum Fears Overstated!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Grayscale-Forecast-Regulation-Set-to-Dominate-Crypto-in-2026-Quantum-Fears-Overstated/6953e0ca4342f77179e6d488</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Grayscale-Forecast-Regulation-Set-to-Dominate-Crypto-in-2026-Quantum-Fears-Overstated/6953e0ca4342f77179e6d488</guid><description>Crypto asset manager Grayscale predicts regulation, not quantum computing, will shape digital asset markets in 2026. The firm anticipates a US bipartisan crypto market structure bill becoming law, bringing traditional financial rules to crypto and encouraging institutional adoption. While quantum computing risks are acknowledged, Grayscale believes they are overstated for the near term and won't significantly impact valuations next year.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:13:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e0ca4342f77179e6d487_1767105185684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unbelievable IPO Frenzy: E to E Transportation Subscribes 490x, Grey Market Soars Over 80%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Unbelievable-IPO-Frenzy-E-to-E-Transportation-Subscribes-490x-Grey-Market-Soars-Over-80percent/6953e0234342f77179e6d2bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Unbelievable-IPO-Frenzy-E-to-E-Transportation-Subscribes-490x-Grey-Market-Soars-Over-80percent/6953e0234342f77179e6d2bd</guid><description>E to E Transportation Infrastructure's IPO has seen an astonishing subscription of nearly 490 times, receiving bids worth Rs 29,492 crore against its Rs 300 crore valuation. The public issue, which closed on December 30, offered 48.4 lakh shares at ₹164-174 per share. Investors, especially non-institutional and retail categories, showed immense interest. Grey market premium (GMP) also remains strong, trading over 80 percent above the issue price, indicating high investor confidence ahead of listing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:13:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953e0234342f77179e6d2bc_1767104712786.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Surge: Google Exec Reveals Why Indian Consumers Are Key to Global Tech Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Surge-Google-Exec-Reveals-Why-Indian-Consumers-Are-Key-to-Global-Tech-Future/6953df704342f77179e6d0da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Surge-Google-Exec-Reveals-Why-Indian-Consumers-Are-Key-to-Global-Tech-Future/6953df704342f77179e6d0da</guid><description>A senior Google executive stated that Indian consumers are highly enthusiastic about adopting new AI features, making India a crucial "leading indicator" for global technology trends. Google observes exceptional usage and unexpected use cases for its AI products in India, from AI Try-Ons to Quick Commerce integration. These insights are vital for developing future AI strategies worldwide.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:06:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953df704342f77179e6d0d9_1767104597922.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Muthoot Finance Unleashes Growth Capital: Massive Equity Injection into Subsidiary Muthoot Money Sparks Investor Excitement!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Unleashes-Growth-Capital-Massive-Equity-Injection-into-Subsidiary-Muthoot-Money-Sparks-Investor-Excitement/6953daeb4342f77179e6c69b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Unleashes-Growth-Capital-Massive-Equity-Injection-into-Subsidiary-Muthoot-Money-Sparks-Investor-Excitement/6953daeb4342f77179e6c69b</guid><description>Muthoot Finance Limited has successfully infused capital into its subsidiary, Muthoot Money Limited, by allotting 3.25 lakh equity shares. This strategic move aims to bolster Muthoot Money's financial foundation, support its aggressive business expansion, improve its capital adequacy ratio, and facilitate the repayment of existing loans. The parent company's ongoing support underscores confidence in Muthoot Money's robust growth, evidenced by its significant turnover increase over recent financial years.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953daeb4342f77179e6c69a_1767103349343.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 SHOCKER: Economist Reveals India's Secret Weapon for Explosive Growth That No One Is Talking About!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-SHOCKER-Economist-Reveals-Indias-Secret-Weapon-for-Explosive-Growth-That-No-One-Is-Talking-About/6953d9dd4342f77179e6c386</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-SHOCKER-Economist-Reveals-Indias-Secret-Weapon-for-Explosive-Growth-That-No-One-Is-Talking-About/6953d9dd4342f77179e6c386</guid><description>CareEdge Group's Chief Economist Rajani Sinha urges the Union Budget 2026 to prioritize research and development (R&amp;D) and harness India's demographic dividend. She highlighted that India's current R&amp;D spending is a mere 0.7% of GDP, far below global innovation hubs, and private sector participation is low. Sinha emphasized the need to create jobs, skill the workforce, and transition them from agriculture to higher-value sectors and diversified services to achieve sustainable, innovation-led growth. Encouraging foreign direct investment through land reforms and easing regulations is also crucial.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:45:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953d9dd4342f77179e6c385_1767103017593.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariffs Shatter India's Diamond Exports: Factories Shut, 1.5 Lakh Jobs LOST!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Tariffs-Shatter-Indias-Diamond-Exports-Factories-Shut-15-Lakh-Jobs-LOST/6953da114342f77179e6c471</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Tariffs-Shatter-Indias-Diamond-Exports-Factories-Shut-15-Lakh-Jobs-LOST/6953da114342f77179e6c471</guid><description>India's diamond industry faces a severe crisis as US tariffs, now at 50%, have slashed exports by nearly 50%. This has led to factory closures and an estimated 1.5 lakh job losses in Surat. The sector is urgently seeking government aid, including eased regulations and worker support, to mitigate the damage and retain skilled labor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:45:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953da114342f77179e6c470_1767103393380.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TRAI's Bold IoT SIM Policy: India Poised for Global Export Boom?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TRAIs-Bold-IoT-SIM-Policy-India-Poised-for-Global-Export-Boom/6953d9214342f77179e6c1e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TRAIs-Bold-IoT-SIM-Policy-India-Poised-for-Global-Export-Boom/6953d9214342f77179e6c1e1</guid><description>The Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI) has proposed a new framework for foreign SIM/eSIM cards in export-focused Internet of Things (IoT) devices. This light-touch authorisation regime, called "International M2M SIM Service Authorisation," aims to streamline operations for Indian manufacturers exporting IoT products. Key features include a fully online application process, zero fees except for a ₹5,000 processing charge, and a 10-year validity. The recommendations also permit foreign SIMs for testing purposes in India for up to six months, supporting the 'Make in India' initiative and enhancing the global competitiveness of Indian IoT and M2M products.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:40:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953d9214342f77179e6c1e0_1767102822369.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBCC Smashes ₹1000 Cr Milestone: 417 Amrapali Homes Find New Owners!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCC-Smashes-1000-Cr-Milestone-417-Amrapali-Homes-Find-New-Owners/6953d9d04342f77179e6c33d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCC-Smashes-1000-Cr-Milestone-417-Amrapali-Homes-Find-New-Owners/6953d9d04342f77179e6c33d</guid><description>State-owned NBCC (India) Ltd has successfully sold 417 Amrapali Group homes in Noida and Greater Noida for ₹1,045.4 crore through an e-auction. This significant sale, conducted as per Supreme Court directives to complete stalled projects, marks a crucial step in reviving the Amrapali developments and generating funds for NBCC's project management and real estate ventures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:39:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953d9d04342f77179e6c33c_1767103265523.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yes Madam Skyrockets: 233% Revenue Surge Fuels Profitability in At-Home Beauty Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Yes-Madam-Skyrockets-233percent-Revenue-Surge-Fuels-Profitability-in-At-Home-Beauty-Boom/6953d7754342f77179e6bdcb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Yes-Madam-Skyrockets-233percent-Revenue-Surge-Fuels-Profitability-in-At-Home-Beauty-Boom/6953d7754342f77179e6bdcb</guid><description>Yes Madam, a home beauty services platform, achieved hypergrowth with revenue tripling from INR 28.33 Cr in FY23 to INR 94.4 Cr in FY25, a 233% increase. Cofounder Akanksha Vishnoi detailed the company's focus on transparency, hygiene with single-use products, and a standardized operating model. Bootstrapped from the start, Yes Madam achieved its first profit in FY24 by building a strong, trained professional network and optimizing unit economics through automation and a tech-first approach, positioning itself for leadership in India's rapidly expanding beauty economy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:34:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953d7754342f77179e6bdca_1767102783542.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks' Bad Debt Recovery Set to Surge! DFS Drives Digitization &amp; Reforms to Supercharge DRTs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Bad-Debt-Recovery-Set-to-Surge-DFS-Drives-Digitization-and-Reforms-to-Supercharge-DRTs/6953d2f44342f77179e6b3b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Bad-Debt-Recovery-Set-to-Surge-DFS-Drives-Digitization-and-Reforms-to-Supercharge-DRTs/6953d2f44342f77179e6b3b3</guid><description>The Department of Financial Services (DFS) is implementing key initiatives like mandatory e-filing, video conferencing, and hybrid hearings to boost digitization in Debts Recovery Tribunals (DRTs). Discussions focused on strengthening recovery mechanisms, prioritizing high-value cases, and enhancing the use of Lok Adalats. Amendments to the Recovery of Debts and Bankruptcy Act, 1993, and the Securitisation and Reconstruction of Financial Assets and Enforcement of Security Interest Act, 2002, are also being considered to improve recovery effectiveness and speed up the resolution of pending cases.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:15:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953d2f44342f77179e6b3b2_1767101392104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jan 2026: 5 Crucial Rules Changing Your Wallet &amp; Daily Life! Don't Get Caught Off Guard!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jan-2026-5-Crucial-Rules-Changing-Your-Wallet-and-Daily-Life-Dont-Get-Caught-Off-Guard/6953d2934342f77179e6b278</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jan-2026-5-Crucial-Rules-Changing-Your-Wallet-and-Daily-Life-Dont-Get-Caught-Off-Guard/6953d2934342f77179e6b278</guid><description>Get ready for significant financial shifts starting January 1, 2026. Key changes include weekly credit score updates for faster loan impact, mandatory PAN-Aadhaar linking for essential services, stricter regulations on digital payments and messaging apps to combat fraud, potential salary revisions for government employees under the 8th Pay Commission, and a new pre-filled income tax return form designed for easier filing but increased scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:15:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953d2934342f77179e6b277_1767101464258.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Foreign Investors Fleeing India? Expert Nilesh Shah Unpacks The Shocking Reasons &amp; What It Means For Your Money!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Foreign-Investors-Fleeing-India-Expert-Nilesh-Shah-Unpacks-The-Shocking-Reasons-and-What-It-Means-For-Your-Money/6953d1b74342f77179e6b010</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Foreign-Investors-Fleeing-India-Expert-Nilesh-Shah-Unpacks-The-Shocking-Reasons-and-What-It-Means-For-Your-Money/6953d1b74342f77179e6b010</guid><description>Nilesh Shah of Kotak Mahindra Asset Management explains the ongoing Foreign Institutional Investor (FII) selloff from India. He attributes it to high valuations, ease of exit, and performance in markets like China and South Korea. Shah advises investors to temper return expectations for FY27, highlighting the need for fiscal prudence, asset monetization, and continued government capex in the upcoming budget. He also touches upon challenges in private capital expenditure and the importance of improving ease of living.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:11:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953d1b74342f77179e6b00f_1767100963222.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Atomberg Slams Door on Losses! FY25 Net Loss Down 41% Amidst Stellar Revenue Growth – $200M IPO Plans Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Atomberg-Slams-Door-on-Losses-FY25-Net-Loss-Down-41percent-Amidst-Stellar-Revenue-Growth-200M-IPO-Plans-Unveiled/6953d02a4342f77179e6ac6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Atomberg-Slams-Door-on-Losses-FY25-Net-Loss-Down-41percent-Amidst-Stellar-Revenue-Growth-200M-IPO-Plans-Unveiled/6953d02a4342f77179e6ac6e</guid><description>Home appliances startup Atomberg significantly improved its financial standing in FY25, narrowing its consolidated net loss by 41% to INR 117.4 Cr. This achievement was driven by a strong operating revenue jump of over 20% to INR 958.4 Cr. The company, known for its energy-efficient BLDC fans and expanding product line, is now aiming for a $200 million IPO in FY27 and is also in talks to raise secondary capital.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:03:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953d02a4342f77179e6ac6d_1767101278384.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EV Charging Boom: VinFast-backed V-GREEN Partners with HPCL to Power Up India's Highways!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/EV-Charging-Boom-VinFast-backed-V-GREEN-Partners-with-HPCL-to-Power-Up-Indias-Highways/6953cf424342f77179e6aa31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/EV-Charging-Boom-VinFast-backed-V-GREEN-Partners-with-HPCL-to-Power-Up-Indias-Highways/6953cf424342f77179e6aa31</guid><description>VinFast-backed V-GREEN is teaming up with Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd (HPCL) to install electric vehicle charging stations at HPCL's widespread fuel outlets across India. This strategic alliance aims to accelerate the adoption of green transportation by leveraging HPCL's extensive network of over 24,400 retail stations. The partnership is set to enhance the EV user experience and build a robust charging infrastructure, supporting India's ambitious electrification goals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:00:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953cf424342f77179e6aa30_1767100775243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Companies Breathe Easy: MCA Extends Filing Deadline to Jan 31, 2026 Amid Portal Woes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Companies-Breathe-Easy-MCA-Extends-Filing-Deadline-to-Jan-31-2026-Amid-Portal-Woes/6953cd7b4342f77179e6a5f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Companies-Breathe-Easy-MCA-Extends-Filing-Deadline-to-Jan-31-2026-Amid-Portal-Woes/6953cd7b4342f77179e6a5f0</guid><description>The Ministry of Corporate Affairs (MCA) has granted a one-month extension for annual financial statement and return filings, pushing the new deadline to January 31, 2026. This move provides relief to companies and professionals grappling with persistent technical issues on the MCA's V3 portal. No late fees will be charged for this extended period, following an earlier extension from December 31, 2025.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:44:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953cd7b4342f77179e6a5ef_1767100524078.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI's Big Strike: Analyst License CANCELLED Amidst Massive Investment Fraud!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-Big-Strike-Analyst-License-CANCELLED-Amidst-Massive-Investment-Fraud/6953ccc54342f77179e6a374</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-Big-Strike-Analyst-License-CANCELLED-Amidst-Massive-Investment-Fraud/6953ccc54342f77179e6a374</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has cancelled the registration of research analyst Purooskhan for his credentials being misused by an unregistered investment advisory firm, Option Research Consultancy (ORC). The firm, operating optionresearch.in, allegedly promised guaranteed returns, causing significant investor losses. SEBI ordered ORC to refund over ₹30.39 lakh, banned them for two years, and fined partners ₹6 lakh each. Purooskhan's license was revoked due to severe negligence in sharing his SEBI registration password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:43:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ccc54342f77179e6a373_1767099718729.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Cement Growth Surge: ICRA Predicts 7% Jump Fueled by Housing &amp; Infra Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Cement-Growth-Surge-ICRA-Predicts-7percent-Jump-Fueled-by-Housing-and-Infra-Boom/6953ccad4342f77179e6a300</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Cement-Growth-Surge-ICRA-Predicts-7percent-Jump-Fueled-by-Housing-and-Infra-Boom/6953ccad4342f77179e6a300</guid><description>ICRA forecasts India's cement industry to grow 6.5-7.5% in FY26 and 6-7% in FY27, driven by steady demand from housing and infrastructure projects. GST reforms and increased government spending are expected to boost momentum. The industry plans to add 85-90 million MTPA capacity by FY2027, with operational EBITDA projected to rise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:43:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ccad4342f77179e6a2ff_1767100630654.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Bold Chip Mandate: Local Equipment Push Set to Reshape Global Tech!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Chinas-Bold-Chip-Mandate-Local-Equipment-Push-Set-to-Reshape-Global-Tech/6953cbbc4342f77179e69f68</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Chinas-Bold-Chip-Mandate-Local-Equipment-Push-Set-to-Reshape-Global-Tech/6953cbbc4342f77179e69f68</guid><description>China is pushing chipmakers to use at least 50% domestic equipment for new capacity expansions. This strategy aims to bolster its local semiconductor industry amid US technology restrictions and achieve greater self-sufficiency. Companies must document their procurement, with potential exceptions for highly advanced chip production. Significant state investment and a national approach are backing this ambitious plan to transform the global semiconductor landscape.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:41:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953cbbc4342f77179e69f67_1767099415920.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Set for Major Surge? Brokerages Reveal Shocking 2026 Targets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Indian-Markets-Set-for-Major-Surge-Brokerages-Reveal-Shocking-2026-Targets/6953cc6d4342f77179e6a226</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Indian-Markets-Set-for-Major-Surge-Brokerages-Reveal-Shocking-2026-Targets/6953cc6d4342f77179e6a226</guid><description>Major global and domestic brokerages are forecasting significant growth for Indian benchmark indices, Nifty and Sensex, by the end of 2026. HSBC and Goldman Sachs have upgraded Indian equities to 'Overweight', citing macro tailwinds, policy easing, and earnings recovery. Projections suggest potential gains of 11-26 percent, with bull case targets reaching as high as 1,07,000 for Sensex and 32,000 for Nifty, indicating a potential strong rebound after recent underperformance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:40:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953cc6d4342f77179e6a225_1767099914742.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Rate Cut Fuels Housing Boom: Home Loans Skyrocket 12% as Young Indians Rush to Buy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Rate-Cut-Fuels-Housing-Boom-Home-Loans-Skyrocket-12percent-as-Young-Indians-Rush-to-Buy/6953cbc84342f77179e69fa0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Rate-Cut-Fuels-Housing-Boom-Home-Loans-Skyrocket-12percent-as-Young-Indians-Rush-to-Buy/6953cbc84342f77179e69fa0</guid><description>Housing loans in India surged by 12% year-on-year, fueled by the Reserve Bank of India's significant 125 basis point repo rate cut to 5.25% in 2025. Notably, borrowers under 30 now account for 16% of new home loans, a sharp rise from 9% in 2022, driven by stable incomes and improved credit access. Average loan sizes also increased, reflecting growing demand and affordability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:40:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953cbc84342f77179e69f9f_1767099568396.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Economists Warn PM Modi: Fiscal Risks Loom, Urge Major Budget Shift!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Economists-Warn-PM-Modi-Fiscal-Risks-Loom-Urge-Major-Budget-Shift/6953cb734342f77179e69e97</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Economists-Warn-PM-Modi-Fiscal-Risks-Loom-Urge-Major-Budget-Shift/6953cb734342f77179e69e97</guid><description>Economists attending a pre-Budget meeting with Prime Minister Narendra Modi have highlighted significant fiscal risks, including rising interest payments and declining household savings. They recommended recalibrating government capital expenditure (capex) to around 3% of GDP to allow more space for private investment and to align with the original Fiscal Responsibility and Budget Management (FRBM) framework. The Prime Minister emphasized addressing the aspirations of citizens lifted out of poverty.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:40:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953cb734342f77179e69e96_1767099797963.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Housing Market Sees 5% Dip in Unit Sales, But Value Surges 11% Across 9 Cities!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Housing-Market-Sees-5percent-Dip-in-Unit-Sales-But-Value-Surges-11percent-Across-9-Cities/6953cae44342f77179e69ccb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Housing-Market-Sees-5percent-Dip-in-Unit-Sales-But-Value-Surges-11percent-Across-9-Cities/6953cae44342f77179e69ccb</guid><description>Residential property registrations in nine major Indian cities dipped 5% to 5.45 lakh units by December 25, 2025, compared to the previous year. However, the total sales value surged 11% to ₹4.46 lakh crore, driven by a strong demand for premium and luxury housing, according to Square Yards.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:37:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953cae44342f77179e69cca_1767099450969.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Motor Insurance Revolution: EVs Fuel 2.5x Growth, Drivers Save Big in 2025!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Motor-Insurance-Revolution-EVs-Fuel-25x-Growth-Drivers-Save-Big-in-2025/6953ca1d4342f77179e69b1d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Motor-Insurance-Revolution-EVs-Fuel-25x-Growth-Drivers-Save-Big-in-2025/6953ca1d4342f77179e69b1d</guid><description>India's motor insurance landscape has fundamentally transformed in 2025. Driven by electric vehicles (EVs) and a desire for data-driven savings, Indian drivers are shifting from compliance to protection. EV motor insurance purchases grew nearly 2.5 times year-on-year, with a striking 200% surge in premiums. Additionally, 96% of new car owners opt for zero depreciation, and the Pay-As-You-Drive model is gaining traction, offering up to 30% savings for 20% of customers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:35:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ca1d4342f77179e69b1c_1767099196808.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Markets Flatline! Metal &amp; Auto Stocks Surge Amid Fourth Straight Nifty Decline - What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Markets-Flatline-Metal-and-Auto-Stocks-Surge-Amid-Fourth-Straight-Nifty-Decline-Whats-Next/6953caeb4342f77179e69d04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Markets-Flatline-Metal-and-Auto-Stocks-Surge-Amid-Fourth-Straight-Nifty-Decline-Whats-Next/6953caeb4342f77179e69d04</guid><description>Indian benchmark indices, Nifty 50 and BSE Sensex, ended nearly flat after a volatile session, marking the Nifty's fourth consecutive decline. However, metal stocks reached an all-time high, led by Hindalco and Tata Steel, while auto stocks like Bajaj Auto and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra also saw significant gains. Broader markets underperformed, and analysts suggest a range-bound trading ahead, awaiting outcomes from US-India trade talks and Q3 results.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953caeb4342f77179e69d03_1767099675265.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mukesh Ambani's Bold AI Vision: Reliance to Become AI-Native, Targeting 10x Productivity and India's Economic Leap!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mukesh-Ambanis-Bold-AI-Vision-Reliance-to-Become-AI-Native-Targeting-10x-Productivity-and-Indias-Economic-Leap/6953c5ef4342f77179e6907a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mukesh-Ambanis-Bold-AI-Vision-Reliance-to-Become-AI-Native-Targeting-10x-Productivity-and-Indias-Economic-Leap/6953c5ef4342f77179e6907a</guid><description>Reliance Industries Chairman Mukesh Ambani has unveiled a draft AI Manifesto, charting a course to transform the conglomerate into an AI-native deep-tech enterprise. The plan aims for a tenfold increase in employee productivity and a significant impact on India's economy and society. AI will be embedded across all businesses, focusing on outcomes, efficiency, and safety, while ensuring 'Affordable AI for Every Indian'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:12:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c5ef4342f77179e69079_1767098703730.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dr Reddy's Srikakulam Plant Faces USFDA Scrutiny: 5 Critical Observations Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Srikakulam-Plant-Faces-USFDA-Scrutiny-5-Critical-Observations-Revealed/6953c5794342f77179e68e98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Srikakulam-Plant-Faces-USFDA-Scrutiny-5-Critical-Observations-Revealed/6953c5794342f77179e68e98</guid><description>Dr. Reddy's Laboratories' Srikakulam facility in Andhra Pradesh received a Form 483 with five observations from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) after a recent inspection. The observations relate to manufacturing practices, quality control, and data integrity. Dr. Reddy's has committed to addressing these findings within the stipulated timeline.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:12:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c5794342f77179e68e97_1767097868886.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Close Flat: Unpacking the Negative Sentiment Dragging Stocks Down!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Close-Flat-Unpacking-the-Negative-Sentiment-Dragging-Stocks-Down/6953c5984342f77179e68ef8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Close-Flat-Unpacking-the-Negative-Sentiment-Dragging-Stocks-Down/6953c5984342f77179e68ef8</guid><description>India's benchmark stock indices, Sensex and Nifty, ended Tuesday flat with minor losses. The BSE Sensex closed down 20.46 points at 84,675.08, and the NSE Nifty50 settled 3.25 points lower at 25,938.85. Market sentiment was influenced by monthly F&amp;O expiry, profit-booking after recent gains, weak global cues, and continued Foreign Institutional Investor (FII) selling. Muted trading volumes due to year-end holidays were also a factor. Despite these headwinds, strong domestic fundamentals and steady local inflows provided some support.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:12:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c5984342f77179e68ef7_1767098591758.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RVNL Analyst's Top Railway Pick: Rs 400 Target Set as Stock Consolidates Ahead of Budget Buzz!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RVNL-Analysts-Top-Railway-Pick-Rs-400-Target-Set-as-Stock-Consolidates-Ahead-of-Budget-Buzz/6953c5004342f77179e68d26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RVNL-Analysts-Top-Railway-Pick-Rs-400-Target-Set-as-Stock-Consolidates-Ahead-of-Budget-Buzz/6953c5004342f77179e68d26</guid><description>Analyst Pradip Halder names Rail Vikas Nigam Limited (RVNL) as a top investment pick in the railway sector, setting a target price of over ₹400. Despite recent rallies leading to profit booking and consolidation around ₹320, investor interest in railway stocks like RVNL remains strong ahead of the Union Budget, which historically causes sector volatility.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:12:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c5004342f77179e68d25_1767097952356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SRF Hit with ₹16 Crore Tax Demand: Company Vows to Fight Back!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/SRF-Hit-with-16-Crore-Tax-Demand-Company-Vows-to-Fight-Back/6953c4ac4342f77179e68ba2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/SRF-Hit-with-16-Crore-Tax-Demand-Company-Vows-to-Fight-Back/6953c4ac4342f77179e68ba2</guid><description>SRF Ltd received a ₹15.76 crore demand from CGST Dehradun for input tax credit reversal concerning a slump sale and supplier compliance issues, plus interest and penalty. The company, confident in its legal standing, plans to contest the demand, expecting no material financial impact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:11:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c4ac4342f77179e68ba1_1767098495859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin's 2025 Rollercoaster: $12,000 Crash Erases Predictions, Wipes $500 Billion! Did ANYONE Get It Right?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoins-2025-Rollercoaster-12000-Crash-Erases-Predictions-Wipes-500-Billion-Did-ANYONE-Get-It-Right/6953c4424342f77179e689b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoins-2025-Rollercoaster-12000-Crash-Erases-Predictions-Wipes-500-Billion-Did-ANYONE-Get-It-Right/6953c4424342f77179e689b0</guid><description>Bitcoin experienced a dramatic 'flash crash' in October 2025, plunging $12,000 in minutes, triggering over $19 billion in liquidations and erasing $500 billion from the total crypto market cap. This event highlighted the spectacular failure of numerous optimistic price predictions made throughout the year by analysts and industry leaders, many of whom had forecast prices reaching $1 million or $500,000. The year is now set to post its first full-year loss since 2022, underscoring the extreme difficulty of forecasting cryptocurrency markets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:09:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c4424342f77179e689af_1767097989133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>