<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:34:27 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Ola Electric Surges! Market Share Skyrockets to 9.3% – Is This the EV Comeback You Waited For?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Surges-Market-Share-Skyrockets-to-93percent-Is-This-the-EV-Comeback-You-Waited-For/695666154342f77179f5d974</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Surges-Market-Share-Skyrockets-to-93percent-Is-This-the-EV-Comeback-You-Waited-For/695666154342f77179f5d974</guid><description>Ola Electric shares rose nearly 4% after reporting a significant month-on-month market share increase to 9.3% in December, up from 7.2% in November. Strong demand for its new S1 Pro+ scooter and government certification for its Roadster X+ motorcycle are key drivers. The company also anticipates scaling its battery energy storage systems business.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:05:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695666154342f77179f5d973_1767270022815.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Krishna Buildspace IPO: Rs 524 Cr Order Book &amp; Rs 15 Cr Profit - Funds to Fuel Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Krishna-Buildspace-IPO-Rs-524-Cr-Order-Book-and-Rs-15-Cr-Profit-Funds-to-Fuel-Growth/695665de4342f77179f5d860</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Krishna-Buildspace-IPO-Rs-524-Cr-Order-Book-and-Rs-15-Cr-Profit-Funds-to-Fuel-Growth/695665de4342f77179f5d860</guid><description>Gujarat-based Krishna Buildspace has filed for an Initial Public Offering (IPO) to raise funds for its capital expenditure and working capital needs. The issue includes a fresh issue of 90 lakh shares and an offer for sale of 9 lakh shares. The company boasts 19 ongoing projects valued at ₹524.1 crore and reported a profit of ₹15.1 crore on revenue of ₹183.3 crore for the year ended March 2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:05:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695665de4342f77179f5d85f_1767269914418.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Meta's Reels EXPLODES: $50 Billion Revenue Machine Built from Scratch!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Metas-Reels-EXPLODES-50-Billion-Revenue-Machine-Built-from-Scratch/6956658a4342f77179f5d6d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Metas-Reels-EXPLODES-50-Billion-Revenue-Machine-Built-from-Scratch/6956658a4342f77179f5d6d0</guid><description>Meta Platforms' Reels, once a TikTok copycat with no revenue, has become a massive success, projected to generate over $50 billion annually. This surge is credited to advanced AI recommendation systems and increased video viewership on Instagram and Facebook. Reels now significantly outperforms competitors like YouTube Shorts in user engagement time and is expanding to new platforms, including Amazon Fire TV.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:04:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956658a4342f77179f5d6cf_1767269993857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India Roars: December Sales Jump 6.6% – See the Astonishing Numbers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Roars-December-Sales-Jump-66percent-See-the-Astonishing-Numbers/6956650f4342f77179f5d496</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Roars-December-Sales-Jump-66percent-See-the-Astonishing-Numbers/6956650f4342f77179f5d496</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India reported a 6.6% year-on-year increase in total sales for December 2025, reaching 58,702 units. This figure comprises 42,416 domestic sales and 16,286 units in exports. Managing Director and CEO Tarun Garg attributed the robust growth to positive momentum from GST 2.0 reforms, highlighting a significant 26.5% surge in export volume for the month.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956650f4342f77179f5d495_1767269839085.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors Surges: Record December Sales &amp; EV Boom Drive 14.1% Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Surges-Record-December-Sales-and-EV-Boom-Drive-141percent-Growth/695664e64342f77179f5d3ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Surges-Record-December-Sales-and-EV-Boom-Drive-141percent-Growth/695664e64342f77179f5d3ce</guid><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles reported a strong 14.1% sales growth in December, reaching 50,519 units. Electric vehicle sales jumped 24.2%. The company achieved its fifth consecutive year of record annual sales in 2025 (587,218 units), including a record 81,125 EVs, signaling robust market momentum and a positive outlook for FY26.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695664e64342f77179f5d3cd_1767269675901.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Market's Shocking 2025 Comeback: How AI, Fed Secrets, and Trump's Tariffs Fueled Record Highs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-Markets-Shocking-2025-Comeback-How-AI-Fed-Secrets-and-Trumps-Tariffs-Fueled-Record-Highs/695664424342f77179f5d084</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-Markets-Shocking-2025-Comeback-How-AI-Fed-Secrets-and-Trumps-Tariffs-Fueled-Record-Highs/695664424342f77179f5d084</guid><description>The US stock market achieved record highs in 2025, overcoming early setbacks caused by former President Donald Trump's tariff announcements. Major indices like the S&amp;P 500, Dow 30, and Nasdaq 100 closed the year positively. Despite initial fears of trade wars and sticky inflation, a powerful AI-driven rally, led by NVIDIA and the 'Magnificent Seven' stocks, alongside three Federal Reserve rate cuts in the latter half of the year, propelled the market upwards. Big Tech's massive AI-related capital expenditure sustained this momentum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:59:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695664424342f77179f5d083_1767269621249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Giants Roar: Skoda Hits Record Year, Kia's December Surge &amp; Maruti Suzuki's New Highs in 2025!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Giants-Roar-Skoda-Hits-Record-Year-Kias-December-Surge-and-Maruti-Suzukis-New-Highs-in-2025/6956637e4342f77179f5ccc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Giants-Roar-Skoda-Hits-Record-Year-Kias-December-Surge-and-Maruti-Suzukis-New-Highs-in-2025/6956637e4342f77179f5ccc3</guid><description>The Indian automotive sector concluded 2025 with strong sales momentum, marked by record performances from key players. Skoda Auto India achieved its best-ever year with 72,665 units sold and 107% growth. Kia India recorded its strongest December ever, with 18,659 units sold (105% YoY growth). Maruti Suzuki also posted record total sales for the year, exceeding 2.35 million units. Mahindra &amp; Mahindra reported 15% annual growth, and MG Motor India saw 19% YoY sales growth, indicating a robust industry.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:59:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956637e4342f77179f5ccc2_1767269325672.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zomato &amp; Blinkit Shatter Records on New Year's Eve, Defying Strike Chaos!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zomato-and-Blinkit-Shatter-Records-on-New-Years-Eve-Defying-Strike-Chaos/6956638e4342f77179f5cd28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zomato-and-Blinkit-Shatter-Records-on-New-Years-Eve-Defying-Strike-Chaos/6956638e4342f77179f5cd28</guid><description>Zomato and Blinkit achieved an all-time high of over 75 lakh orders on New Year's Eve, with 4.5 lakh delivery partners fulfilling the demand. Zomato CEO Deepinder Goyal stated the platforms were unaffected by strike calls, thanks to law enforcement support. He emphasized that no extra incentives beyond typical New Year's Eve bonuses were given and highlighted the gig economy's role in job creation. A workers' union claimed widespread participation in strikes, demanding better wages and conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:58:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956638e4342f77179f5cd27_1767269334953.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Hit by Massive ₹638 Crore GST Demand and Penalty! Will it Survive?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Hit-by-Massive-638-Crore-GST-Demand-and-Penalty-Will-it-Survive/69565f3c4342f77179f5bb85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Hit-by-Massive-638-Crore-GST-Demand-and-Penalty-Will-it-Survive/69565f3c4342f77179f5bb85</guid><description>Telecom operator Vodafone Idea has received a ₹638 crore GST demand and penalty order from CGST Ahmedabad under Section 74, alleging short payment and excess input tax credit. The company stated it disagrees with the order and will pursue legal action, adding to its existing financial pressures despite a narrowed net loss in Q2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:36:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69565f3c4342f77179f5bb84_1767268222897.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NMDC Production EXPLODES 14.7% in December! Sales Surge - Is This Your Next Big Buy?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NMDC-Production-EXPLODES-147percent-in-December-Sales-Surge-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Buy/69565e5b4342f77179f5b7ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/NMDC-Production-EXPLODES-147percent-in-December-Sales-Surge-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Buy/69565e5b4342f77179f5b7ce</guid><description>State-run miner NMDC Ltd reported a significant 14.7% year-on-year jump in December production, reaching 5.4 million tonnes (MT). Sales also saw a robust increase to 4.64 MT from 3.91 MT in the prior year. For the first nine months of the fiscal year, production stood at 36.89 MT and sales at 34.92 MT, both higher than the previous corresponding period. NMDC shares closed positively on the NSE.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:36:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69565e5b4342f77179f5b7cd_1767268007318.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India December Sales MISS Expectations, But Exports SOAR! What This Means for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-December-Sales-MISS-Expectations-But-Exports-SOAR-What-This-Means-for-Investors/69565ef04342f77179f5ba9d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-December-Sales-MISS-Expectations-But-Exports-SOAR-What-This-Means-for-Investors/69565ef04342f77179f5ba9d</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India reported December auto sales of 58,702 units, falling short of estimates. However, total sales saw a 6.6% year-on-year increase, primarily driven by a strong 26.5% surge in exports, reaching 16,286 units. Domestic sales stood at 42,416 units. This export-led growth highlights operational resilience and improving global demand, even as the company navigates a competitive domestic market. Hyundai Motor India shares closed up 0.56% at ₹2,310.00 on January 1, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:36:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69565ef04342f77179f5ba9c_1767268383540.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Set for 2026 Growth Bonanza: GST Reforms, EV Power, and New Models Driving Record Sales!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Set-for-2026-Growth-Bonanza-GST-Reforms-EV-Power-and-New-Models-Driving-Record-Sales/69565e504342f77179f5b773</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Set-for-2026-Growth-Bonanza-GST-Reforms-EV-Power-and-New-Models-Driving-Record-Sales/69565e504342f77179f5b773</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra is poised for significant growth in 2026, driven by strategic factors like GST reforms, exciting new electric vehicle (EV) launches, and ongoing product refreshes, according to automotive division CEO Nalinikanth Gollagunta. The company reported strong December sales, with SUV volumes up 23% and LCV volumes up 34% year-on-year. Plans include a ramp-up in EV production capacity and capitalizing on a commercial vehicle replacement cycle, while managing raw material cost pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:36:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69565e504342f77179f5b772_1767267980948.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Skyrockets Market Share in December! Hyperservice Initiative Drives Massive Surge - Details Inside!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Skyrockets-Market-Share-in-December-Hyperservice-Initiative-Drives-Massive-Surge-Details-Inside/69565c714342f77179f5af2d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Skyrockets-Market-Share-in-December-Hyperservice-Initiative-Drives-Massive-Surge-Details-Inside/69565c714342f77179f5af2d</guid><description>Ola Electric saw its market share climb to 9.3% in December, a significant jump from November's 7.2%. This growth is attributed to the successful rollout of its 'Hyperservice' initiative, which streamlines vehicle servicing via the app and achieved 77% same-day completion for service requests. The company also expanded its workforce by over one thousand personnel, including 250 skilled technicians, and improved its parts supply chain. In the latter half of December, market share neared 12%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:27:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69565c714342f77179f5af2c_1767267508719.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking Tax Hike! ITC Plummets 9.69% on Day 1 of 2026, Indian Markets End Flat</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shocking-Tax-Hike-ITC-Plummets-969percent-on-Day-1-of-2026-Indian-Markets-End-Flat/69565ba34342f77179f5abab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shocking-Tax-Hike-ITC-Plummets-969percent-on-Day-1-of-2026-Indian-Markets-End-Flat/69565ba34342f77179f5abab</guid><description>Indian equity markets closed flat on the first trading session of 2026, marred by a significant sell-off in ITC shares. The company's stock tanked 9.69% after the government notified an increase in excise duty and health cess on tobacco products, effective February 1. This news overshadowed initial market enthusiasm, leading to foreign fund outflows, despite domestic investors showing buying interest. While major indices Sensex and Nifty ended marginally changed, the sharp decline in ITC and Godfrey Phillips India dominated trading.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69565ba34342f77179f5abaa_1767267306203.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Buyers Flock to Penny Stocks! Rs 100 Shares Surge in Upper Circuit Frenzy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Buyers-Flock-to-Penny-Stocks-Rs-100-Shares-Surge-in-Upper-Circuit-Frenzy/695658634342f77179f59dfb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Buyers-Flock-to-Penny-Stocks-Rs-100-Shares-Surge-in-Upper-Circuit-Frenzy/695658634342f77179f59dfb</guid><description>Indian stock markets saw a mixed trading session with BSE Sensex and NSE Nifty-50 in the red. However, numerous low-priced stocks, trading below Rs 100, locked in the upper circuit, indicating strong buying interest. Companies like Sovereign Diamonds Ltd, Vision Cinemas Ltd, and Filatex Fashions Ltd experienced significant price jumps, with some up by 20%. The broader market indices showed mixed performance, while specific sectors like Oil &amp; Gas and Energy gained, Healthcare and FMCG lagged.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:07:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695658634342f77179f59dfa_1767266639644.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stock Market Shockwaves: Top Gainers &amp; Losers Revealed! See Which Giants Soared and Which Fell Today!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Stock-Market-Shockwaves-Top-Gainers-and-Losers-Revealed-See-Which-Giants-Soared-and-Which-Fell-Today/6956580b4342f77179f59c07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Stock-Market-Shockwaves-Top-Gainers-and-Losers-Revealed-See-Which-Giants-Soared-and-Which-Fell-Today/6956580b4342f77179f59c07</guid><description>On January 1, 2026, the Indian stock market saw mixed movements. Shriram Finance Ltd and Bajaj Auto Ltd led the gainers with robust performances. Conversely, ITC Ltd and Dr Reddys Laboratories Ltd were among the top losers, experiencing significant declines. The Sensex saw a minor dip of 0.04%, while the Nifty 50 and Nifty Bank indices closed slightly higher, indicating a mixed trading session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:03:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956580b4342f77179f59c06_1767266386980.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quant MF's Bold 2026 Call: Pharma is 'No-Brainer', Warns on Hype Stocks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Quant-MFs-Bold-2026-Call-Pharma-is-No-Brainer-Warns-on-Hype-Stocks/695657774342f77179f598b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Quant-MFs-Bold-2026-Call-Pharma-is-No-Brainer-Warns-on-Hype-Stocks/695657774342f77179f598b8</guid><description>Sandeep Tandon of Quant Mutual Fund advises Indian investors to shun hype-driven rallies for 2026, focusing instead on valuation comfort and downside protection. He sees a better macro environment and selective recovery in mid/small caps. Tandon identifies pharmaceuticals as a 'no-brainer' decadal opportunity, while favoring NBFCs and insurance. He cautions against expensive new-age IPOs and overvalued defense stocks, advocating a disciplined, data-driven approach.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:03:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695657774342f77179f598b7_1767266348735.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Gold Rush: Analyst Rohit Srivastava Predicts Massive Equity Surge, Reveals Undervalued PSU Stock Picks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-Gold-Rush-Analyst-Rohit-Srivastava-Predicts-Massive-Equity-Surge-Reveals-Undervalued-PSU-Stock-Picks/695658034342f77179f59ba9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-Gold-Rush-Analyst-Rohit-Srivastava-Predicts-Massive-Equity-Surge-Reveals-Undervalued-PSU-Stock-Picks/695658034342f77179f59ba9</guid><description>Rohit Srivastava, Founder of Indiacharts, predicts Indian equities will lead the 2026 market cycle, outperforming gold and silver. He advocates a strategic asset rotation from overbought precious metals to equities linked to an emerging commodity cycle. Srivastava forecasts significant upside for Indian markets, highlighting key Nifty levels and identifying opportunities in undervalued PSU stocks like REC, Power Finance Corporation, NTPC, and GAIL, suggesting accumulation before the Union Budget. He also sees attractive entry points in mid- and small-cap stocks following recent corrections.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:03:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695658034342f77179f59ba8_1767266422691.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Giant Bharat Electronics Lands ₹569 Crore Orders, Q2 Profits Soar Past Estimates!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Giant-Bharat-Electronics-Lands-569-Crore-Orders-Q2-Profits-Soar-Past-Estimates/6956565b4342f77179f593b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Giant-Bharat-Electronics-Lands-569-Crore-Orders-Q2-Profits-Soar-Past-Estimates/6956565b4342f77179f593b6</guid><description>Bharat Electronics Limited (BEL), a leading defence PSU, announced it has secured new orders worth ₹569 crore since December 29, 2025. These orders include communication equipment, medical electronics, and fire suppression systems. The company also reported strong second-quarter results, with net profit rising 18% to ₹1,286 crore, exceeding market expectations. Revenue for the quarter grew 26% year-on-year to ₹5,764 crore.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:02:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956565b4342f77179f593b5_1767265949250.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Kicks Off with Market Rollercoaster! Sensex Dips, Nifty Inches Up - See Who Won &amp; Who Lost!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-Kicks-Off-with-Market-Rollercoaster-Sensex-Dips-Nifty-Inches-Up-See-Who-Won-and-Who-Lost/695654f14342f77179f58d96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-Kicks-Off-with-Market-Rollercoaster-Sensex-Dips-Nifty-Inches-Up-See-Who-Won-and-Who-Lost/695654f14342f77179f58d96</guid><description>Indian equity markets started 2026 with significant volatility. After an initial rise, profit booking led to a flat close for major indices. The Sensex fell 32 points, while the Nifty gained 17 points. Sectors like FMCG and pharma declined, but auto, IT, metals, and PSU banks showed gains. Over 130 stocks hit 52-week highs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:58:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695654f14342f77179f58d95_1767265891042.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Aviation Nightmare: Deadly Crash &amp; Mass Cancellations Rock Sector – What Happens Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Aviation-Nightmare-Deadly-Crash-and-Mass-Cancellations-Rock-Sector-What-Happens-Next/6956541c4342f77179f588b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Aviation-Nightmare-Deadly-Crash-and-Mass-Cancellations-Rock-Sector-What-Happens-Next/6956541c4342f77179f588b5</guid><description>India's aviation sector faced its toughest year in over a decade during 2025. Key events included a deadly Air India crash in June, claiming 260 lives and prompting investigations, followed by IndiGo's massive flight cancellations in December due to new crew duty rules, disrupting travel for thousands. These disruptions, alongside other headwinds, have led to a downgraded forecast for domestic passenger traffic growth and a significant increase in the industry's net loss projection for FY2026, now estimated between ₹17,000 crore and ₹18,000 crore.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956541c4342f77179f588b4_1767265388891.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nayara Energy's Russia Reliance Under Fire: Sanctions Squeeze, But Operations Rebound!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Nayara-Energys-Russia-Reliance-Under-Fire-Sanctions-Squeeze-But-Operations-Rebound/6956542c4342f77179f58939</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Nayara-Energys-Russia-Reliance-Under-Fire-Sanctions-Squeeze-But-Operations-Rebound/6956542c4342f77179f58939</guid><description>Nayara Energy, heavily dependent on Russian crude for its Vadinar refinery, faced significant operational hurdles and international scrutiny due to the Ukraine-Russia conflict and sanctions. Despite a dip in refinery run rates, the company has successfully diversified its crude supplies and is now operating at over 85%. Nayara is also aggressively expanding its retail network, with potential for further operational normalization by 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:52:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956542c4342f77179f58938_1767265591145.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prabhudas Lilladher Group Eyes Mutual Fund Launch: Amisha Vora Reveals Ambitious Expansion Amidst Market Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Prabhudas-Lilladher-Group-Eyes-Mutual-Fund-Launch-Amisha-Vora-Reveals-Ambitious-Expansion-Amidst-Market-Surge/695653ca4342f77179f58750</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Prabhudas-Lilladher-Group-Eyes-Mutual-Fund-Launch-Amisha-Vora-Reveals-Ambitious-Expansion-Amidst-Market-Surge/695653ca4342f77179f58750</guid><description>Prabhudas Lilladher Group, under Chairperson Amisha Vora, is actively progressing towards entering the mutual fund business. Building on its legacy and recent success in corporate finance and investment banking (which grew 5x), the firm plans to leverage its expertise in quantitative strategies and AI to offer differentiated mutual fund products. This strategic move aims to strengthen its position as a comprehensive financial services platform amidst rising retail participation and evolving SEBI regulations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:52:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695653ca4342f77179f5874f_1767265513211.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Hiring Surge! India's Top Firms to Add Millions of Jobs – What's Driving This Boom?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-Hiring-Surge-Indias-Top-Firms-to-Add-Millions-of-Jobs-Whats-Driving-This-Boom/695652694342f77179f581bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-Hiring-Surge-Indias-Top-Firms-to-Add-Millions-of-Jobs-Whats-Driving-This-Boom/695652694342f77179f581bf</guid><description>Indian companies are projecting a significant hiring increase in 2026, with estimates suggesting 10-12 million jobs will be created, up from 8-10 million in 2025. Major firms like EY, Tata Motors, Godrej Consumer Products, and Motilal Oswal Financial Services are expanding their recruitment efforts. This surge is driven by digital transformation, growth in financial services, healthcare, and infrastructure, alongside multinational companies establishing global capability centers and increasing consumer demand. Companies are also prioritizing new skills and diversity goals, with plans for upskilling existing employees.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:48:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695652694342f77179f581be_1767264941325.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hazoor Multi Projects Stock Surges 8% Amidst FII Buying &amp; Mega NHAI Contract Wins – Is Your Portfolio Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hazoor-Multi-Projects-Stock-Surges-8percent-Amidst-FII-Buying-and-Mega-NHAI-Contract-Wins-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/695650c44342f77179f57aaa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hazoor-Multi-Projects-Stock-Surges-8percent-Amidst-FII-Buying-and-Mega-NHAI-Contract-Wins-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/695650c44342f77179f57aaa</guid><description>Hazoor Multi Projects Ltd. (HMPL) stock jumped 8% to Rs 37.50. Foreign Institutional Investors (FIIs) increased their stake to 23.84% by Sep 2025. The company secured two NHAI contracts worth ₹277.40 crore for toll collection and maintenance. HMPL also raised over ₹42.55 crore via warrant conversions following a stock split, strengthening its capital base for diversified infrastructure, engineering, and oil &amp; gas operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:33:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695650c44342f77179f57aa9_1767264544133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chalet Hotels Skyrockets: Elara Capital Upgrades to 'Buy' with Huge Upside Target!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Luxury-Products/Chalet-Hotels-Skyrockets-Elara-Capital-Upgrades-to-Buy-with-Huge-Upside-Target/69564f7e4342f77179f574ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Luxury-Products/Chalet-Hotels-Skyrockets-Elara-Capital-Upgrades-to-Buy-with-Huge-Upside-Target/69564f7e4342f77179f574ce</guid><description>Chalet Hotels shares surged over 3.6% to ₹920.5 after Elara Capital upgraded its rating to 'Buy' and maintained a ₹1,086 target price, signaling a potential 24.74% upside. The brokerage provided a positive Q3 FY26 preview, expecting a 13.5% rise in adjusted net profit to ₹109.5 crore and a 19% jump in Ebitda to ₹243 crore. Elara maintains a structurally bullish view due to planned room additions until FY30 and healthy cash generation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:29:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69564f7e4342f77179f574cd_1767264328321.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Reports Stellar Q3: Business Soars 14% on Strong Deposit and Advance Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tamilnad-Mercantile-Bank-Reports-Stellar-Q3-Business-Soars-14percent-on-Strong-Deposit-and-Advance-Growth/69564fda4342f77179f57680</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tamilnad-Mercantile-Bank-Reports-Stellar-Q3-Business-Soars-14percent-on-Strong-Deposit-and-Advance-Growth/69564fda4342f77179f57680</guid><description>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd. announced impressive third-quarter results, with total business growing 14.28% year-on-year to ₹107,470 crore. Deposits saw a significant 12.53% increase to ₹56,707 crore, and advances rose 16.30% to ₹50,763 crore, indicating robust operational expansion. Current Account Savings Account (CASA) deposits also saw a healthy 14.93% year-on-year jump.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:28:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69564fda4342f77179f5767f_1767264306699.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Retirement Revolution: Senior Living Market Poised for $8 Billion Surge by 2030!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Retirement-Revolution-Senior-Living-Market-Poised-for-8-Billion-Surge-by-2030/69564f7f4342f77179f574fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Retirement-Revolution-Senior-Living-Market-Poised-for-8-Billion-Surge-by-2030/69564f7f4342f77179f574fb</guid><description>India's organized senior living market is projected to reach nearly $8 billion by 2030, according to a JLL–ASLI report. This growth is driven by retirees seeking enhanced safety features, accessible healthcare, and predictable living expenses, moving away from traditional reliance on family care. The market is experiencing a significant demand-supply gap, signaling strong interest from both residents and investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:28:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69564f7f4342f77179f574fa_1767264320057.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GST Revenue Surges 6.1% in December 2025: What It Means for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GST-Revenue-Surges-61percent-in-December-2025-What-It-Means-for-Your-Investments/69564e6c4342f77179f56fa2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GST-Revenue-Surges-61percent-in-December-2025-What-It-Means-for-Your-Investments/69564e6c4342f77179f56fa2</guid><description>India's Goods and Services Tax (GST) collections for December 2025 reached ₹1,74,550 crore, marking a significant 6.1% year-on-year increase. Net GST revenue also saw a rise of 2.2% to ₹1,45,570 crore. Collections from imports surged by 19.7%, while domestic collections grew 1.2%. Cumulative figures for April-December 2025 show an 8.6% rise in gross GST revenue to ₹16,50,039 crore, indicating robust economic activity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:28:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69564e6c4342f77179f56fa1_1767263934763.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kiri Industries Eyes ₹5,200 Cr Bonanza: Fertilizers &amp; Metals Beckon After DyStar Deal Victory!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Kiri-Industries-Eyes-5200-Cr-Bonanza-Fertilizers-and-Metals-Beckon-After-DyStar-Deal-Victory/69564e5c4342f77179f56f3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Kiri-Industries-Eyes-5200-Cr-Bonanza-Fertilizers-and-Metals-Beckon-After-DyStar-Deal-Victory/69564e5c4342f77179f56f3b</guid><description>Kiri Industries is set to invest over ₹5,200 crore from its DyStar stake sale into new Indian ventures, focusing on fertilizers and metals. This strategic pivot, pending board approval, aims for high returns exceeding 30% IRR within a 3-4 year payback period, marking a significant diversification from its traditional chemical business.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:28:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69564e5c4342f77179f56f3a_1767263898330.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Stocks Stage Comeback! Wipro, HCL Tech Lead Surge After 6-Day Slump - What's Driving the Rebound?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-Stage-Comeback-Wipro-HCL-Tech-Lead-Surge-After-6-Day-Slump-Whats-Driving-the-Rebound/69564e714342f77179f56fdd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-Stage-Comeback-Wipro-HCL-Tech-Lead-Surge-After-6-Day-Slump-Whats-Driving-the-Rebound/69564e714342f77179f56fdd</guid><description>Indian IT shares surged today, with the Nifty IT index rising nearly 1 percent after a six-day losing streak. Wipro, HCL Technologies, and Mphasis were among the top gainers. This recovery is attributed to value buying by investors attracted to beaten-down stocks and renewed hopes for US interest rate cuts. Market participants are also anticipating better Q3 performance results as the earnings season approaches.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:24:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69564e714342f77179f56fdc_1767263942553.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Wellness Stock Surges 10% After Brokerage Slaps 'Buy' Rating, Targets 35% Jump!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zydus-Wellness-Stock-Surges-10percent-After-Brokerage-Slaps-Buy-Rating-Targets-35percent-Jump/69564def4342f77179f56d5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zydus-Wellness-Stock-Surges-10percent-After-Brokerage-Slaps-Buy-Rating-Targets-35percent-Jump/69564def4342f77179f56d5c</guid><description>Zydus Wellness shares surged nearly 10% over two days after Motilal Oswal initiated coverage with a 'Buy' rating and a target price of ₹575, suggesting up to 35% upside. The brokerage highlighted the company's diversified health and nutrition portfolio, including brands like Glucon-D and Complan, and its expansion into high-protein and wellness trends through recent acquisitions. Motilal Oswal believes Zydus Wellness offers a strong risk-reward profile, especially given its potential for superior earnings growth compared to its past performance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:24:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69564def4342f77179f56d5b_1767263795781.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India 2026: Will Markets Soar or Stumble? Key Questions for Investors Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-2026-Will-Markets-Soar-or-Stumble-Key-Questions-for-Investors-Revealed/69564d894342f77179f56b6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-2026-Will-Markets-Soar-or-Stumble-Key-Questions-for-Investors-Revealed/69564d894342f77179f56b6b</guid><description>India enters 2026 with robust industrial and manufacturing growth. Key events like the Union Budget and RBI's monetary policy in February will be crucial. While GDP growth is strong, investors watch consumption demand durability and capital goods. Fiscal implications from GST cuts and foreign investment sentiment are also key factors shaping the potentially exciting equity market year ahead.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:23:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69564d894342f77179f56b6a_1767263685969.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric's HUGE Comeback: 9,000+ Vehicles Registered, Market Share Soars to 9.3%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-HUGE-Comeback-9000-Vehicles-Registered-Market-Share-Soars-to-93percent/69564c944342f77179f566da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electrics-HUGE-Comeback-9000-Vehicles-Registered-Market-Share-Soars-to-93percent/69564c944342f77179f566da</guid><description>Ola Electric registered 9,020 vehicles in December, boosting its market share to 9.3% from 7.2% in November. The company credits its 'Hyperservice' program for improved customer experience and increased demand, with market share reaching nearly 12% in late December. Ola Electric is also advancing its technology roadmap with new 4680-cell vehicles and upcoming energy storage system deliveries.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:22:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69564c944342f77179f566d9_1767263451440.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's First Bullet Train: Get Ready to Ride by August 15, 2027! Full Launch Plan Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-First-Bullet-Train-Get-Ready-to-Ride-by-August-15-2027-Full-Launch-Plan-Revealed/69564ca54342f77179f5674d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-First-Bullet-Train-Get-Ready-to-Ride-by-August-15-2027-Full-Launch-Plan-Revealed/69564ca54342f77179f5674d</guid><description>India's inaugural bullet train is set to commence operations on August 15, 2027, according to Railways Minister Ashwini Vaishnaw. The 508 km Mumbai-Ahmedabad High-Speed Rail corridor will launch in phases, starting with the Surat to Bilimora section. This milestone project aims to transform inter-city travel with world-class high-speed rail standards, inspired by the success of the Vande Bharat Express.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:21:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69564ca54342f77179f5674c_1767263468414.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Power Demand Skyrockets 7% in December: Chilling Cold Fuels Electricity Surge - What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Demand-Skyrockets-7percent-in-December-Chilling-Cold-Fuels-Electricity-Surge-Whats-Next/69564ae54342f77179f55fac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Demand-Skyrockets-7percent-in-December-Chilling-Cold-Fuels-Electricity-Surge-Whats-Next/69564ae54342f77179f55fac</guid><description>India's power consumption rose nearly 7% to 138.39 billion units in December, fueled by severe cold in North India increasing use of heating appliances like geysers and blowers. Peak power demand also climbed to 241.20 GW. Experts predict consumption will remain steady in January as cold conditions persist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 10:14:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69564ae54342f77179f55fab_1767263016536.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock 2026 Wealth: Experts Reveal Which Asset Will Skyrocket – Gold, Stocks, or Real Estate?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Unlock-2026-Wealth-Experts-Reveal-Which-Asset-Will-Skyrocket-Gold-Stocks-or-Real-Estate/695645d14342f77179f54a46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Unlock-2026-Wealth-Experts-Reveal-Which-Asset-Will-Skyrocket-Gold-Stocks-or-Real-Estate/695645d14342f77179f54a46</guid><description>Indian households are set to have more disposable income in 2026 due to government tax relief and GST changes. Experts are comparing the investment potential of gold, silver, equities, and real estate for the upcoming year. While equities offer long-term growth, gold provides stability, silver presents a high-beta opportunity with volatility, and real estate promises steady appreciation and rental income. A diversified approach is recommended.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:51:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695645d14342f77179f54a45_1767261755481.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSNL's Bold Move: Crystal Clear Calls Anywhere in India! Nationwide Wi-Fi Calling Service Launched!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/BSNLs-Bold-Move-Crystal-Clear-Calls-Anywhere-in-India-Nationwide-Wi-Fi-Calling-Service-Launched/695645194342f77179f54727</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/BSNLs-Bold-Move-Crystal-Clear-Calls-Anywhere-in-India-Nationwide-Wi-Fi-Calling-Service-Launched/695645194342f77179f54727</guid><description>Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited (BSNL) has launched its Voice over WiFi (VoWiFi) or Wi-Fi Calling service nationwide. Available to all customers across every telecom circle, this service allows users to make and receive calls and messages over a Wi-Fi network. It is particularly beneficial in areas with weak mobile signals, such as homes and remote locations, offering clear connectivity without needing third-party apps. BSNL states the service is free of charge and represents a key step in its network modernization efforts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:47:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695645194342f77179f54726_1767261536935.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor SMASHES Sales Records in December! 33% Jump You Won't Believe!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Toyota-Kirloskar-Motor-SMASHES-Sales-Records-in-December-33percent-Jump-You-Wont-Believe/695643ee4342f77179f54197</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Toyota-Kirloskar-Motor-SMASHES-Sales-Records-in-December-33percent-Jump-You-Wont-Believe/695643ee4342f77179f54197</guid><description>Toyota Kirloskar Motor announced a significant 33% surge in sales for December, reaching 39,333 units compared to 29,529 units in the previous year. Domestic sales saw a 37% rise, while exports grew 12%. For the full calendar year 2025, total sales increased by 19% to 3,88,801 units.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:44:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695643ee4342f77179f54196_1767261244049.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Startup Engine Sputters: Unicorn Creation Plummets 17% in 2025 Amid Funding Crunch!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Engine-Sputters-Unicorn-Creation-Plummets-17percent-in-2025-Amid-Funding-Crunch/695643d34342f77179f540f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Engine-Sputters-Unicorn-Creation-Plummets-17percent-in-2025-Amid-Funding-Crunch/695643d34342f77179f540f0</guid><description>India saw a sharp 17% decline in new unicorns in 2025, creating only 5. Total tech funding fell 13% year-on-year to $11.1 billion, with funding rounds down 35%. Mega rounds also decreased significantly. Despite the challenging global environment, experts note investor interest shifting towards AI and disruptive technologies for future growth, while IPOs and acquisitions saw robust increases.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:43:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695643d34342f77179f540ef_1767261381641.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>