<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:40:28 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Nifty Bank Sinks Below Key Support Amid Geopolitical Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nifty-Bank-Sinks-Below-Key-Support-Amid-Geopolitical-Fears/6996d7efd25eafd9cd007ae0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nifty-Bank-Sinks-Below-Key-Support-Amid-Geopolitical-Fears/6996d7efd25eafd9cd007ae0</guid><description>The Nifty Bank index experienced a significant downturn, losing over 560 points and breaking below crucial support levels, effectively ending its recent three-day rally. Widespread selling pressure across major banking stocks, led by Kotak Mahindra Bank, contributed to this decline. This sharp reversal signals increased investor anxiety, potentially amplified by escalating geopolitical tensions and broader market fragility, despite earlier signs of positive momentum in the financial sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:29:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996d7efd25eafd9cd007adf_1771493526416.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brazil Seeks API Localization From India, Eyes Pharma Self-Reliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Brazil-Seeks-API-Localization-From-India-Eyes-Pharma-Self-Reliance/6996d6f8d25eafd9cd007a07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Brazil-Seeks-API-Localization-From-India-Eyes-Pharma-Self-Reliance/6996d6f8d25eafd9cd007a07</guid><description>Brazil is aggressively pursuing a strategic shift from a buyer-seller dynamic to a production partnership with India for pharmaceuticals, with a specific focus on localizing Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient (API) manufacturing. This initiative aims to significantly reduce the nation's over-reliance on imported APIs, bolster health security, and foster domestic industrial capabilities. India, recognized as the 'pharmacy of the world', is positioned as a key partner in this endeavor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:25:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996d6f8d25eafd9cd007a06_1771493278064.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pivots to Open-Source AI, Challenging Global Tech Hegemony</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Pivots-to-Open-Source-AI-Challenging-Global-Tech-Hegemony/6996d609d25eafd9cd00795b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Pivots-to-Open-Source-AI-Challenging-Global-Tech-Hegemony/6996d609d25eafd9cd00795b</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi has called for artificial intelligence to be treated as a "global common good," advocating for open-source development over proprietary, confidential systems. Speaking at the India AI Impact Summit, Modi directly challenged the prevailing Western approach, emphasizing democratized access, affordability, and shared innovation. This stance positions India against the U.S. strategy of promoting its own AI stack among allies, signaling a potential geopolitical and economic realignment in the rapidly expanding global AI market, projected to reach $2.5 trillion in 2026. India's vision aims to leverage open-source technologies to foster indigenous capabilities and digital sovereignty, a move that could reshape the competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:21:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996d609d25eafd9cd00795a_1771492994327.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Greaves Ampere Scooter to Challenge Petrol Bikes in India</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Greaves-Ampere-Scooter-to-Challenge-Petrol-Bikes-in-India/6996d241d25eafd9cd0077f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Greaves-Ampere-Scooter-to-Challenge-Petrol-Bikes-in-India/6996d241d25eafd9cd0077f8</guid><description>Greaves Electric Mobility is launching its Ampere 6th Gen electric scooter in FY27, targeting India's high-volume sub-₹1 lakh market. The new model aims to directly compete with petrol scooters by offering better performance, lower running costs, and advanced software features, making EVs more accessible to mass-market consumers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:05:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996d241d25eafd9cd0077f7_1771492011850.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Lending Curbs Spark Broker Plea for Pause Amid Liquidity Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Lending-Curbs-Spark-Broker-Plea-for-Pause-Amid-Liquidity-Fears/6996d1d3d25eafd9cd00775e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Lending-Curbs-Spark-Broker-Plea-for-Pause-Amid-Liquidity-Fears/6996d1d3d25eafd9cd00775e</guid><description>The Association of NSE Members of India (ANMI) has formally requested a six-month deferral of new Reserve Bank of India (RBI) regulations set to impact bank lending to capital market intermediaries from April 1, 2026. The stringent rules mandate full collateralization for credit facilities and prohibit bank financing for proprietary trading. ANMI warns these measures will reduce market liquidity, increase trading costs, and potentially disadvantage domestic firms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:03:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996d1d3d25eafd9cd00775d_1771491920833.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Star: Climate Risk vs. Data Center Boom; Valuation Scrutiny Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Blue-Star-Climate-Risk-vs-Data-Center-Boom-Valuation-Scrutiny-Mounts/6996d157d25eafd9cd0076f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Blue-Star-Climate-Risk-vs-Data-Center-Boom-Valuation-Scrutiny-Mounts/6996d157d25eafd9cd0076f0</guid><description>Blue Star's Managing Director flags climate change and excess production capacity as critical risks for the upcoming summer season in the air-conditioning sector. While inventory levels are easing, demand hinges on sustained heat. Simultaneously, the company is poised to benefit from the booming data center market. However, recent quarterly results, a flat yearly stock performance, and high valuation multiples have led to analyst downgrades, shifting sentiment to a cautious 'Hold' amidst a complex outlook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:01:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996d157d25eafd9cd0076ef.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Liquidity Flood Drains Out, Yields Surge Despite Easing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Liquidity-Flood-Drains-Out-Yields-Surge-Despite-Easing/6996d069d25eafd9cd00758f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Liquidity-Flood-Drains-Out-Yields-Surge-Despite-Easing/6996d069d25eafd9cd00758f</guid><description>Despite the Reserve Bank of India's aggressive liquidity injections totaling Rs 17.7 trillion since late 2024, system liquidity remains constricted, forcing money market rates higher. This paradox stems from significant currency demand, substantial dollar sales by the RBI to manage capital outflows, and the government's large cash balances. While policy aims to stimulate growth, these opposing forces are neutralizing the intended effects, creating a challenging environment for credit expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996d069d25eafd9cd00758e_1771491653507.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unveils Critical Minerals Strategy Amidst Private Capital Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Unveils-Critical-Minerals-Strategy-Amidst-Private-Capital-Push/6996d060d25eafd9cd007578</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Unveils-Critical-Minerals-Strategy-Amidst-Private-Capital-Push/6996d060d25eafd9cd007578</guid><description>India is deploying a confidential fast-track framework to streamline approvals and attract private capital for critical minerals development. This initiative complements increased government-funded exploration and strategic talks with partners like Canada, which offers significant sovereign fund matching for investments. Despite a surge in global demand for minerals essential to clean energy and technology, structural hurdles like high capital intensity and financing risks persist, prompting a dual approach of domestic resource development and international collaboration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:57:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996d060d25eafd9cd007577.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Democratization Call Sparks Market Scrutiny Amid Superintelligence Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Democratization-Call-Sparks-Market-Scrutiny-Amid-Superintelligence-Race/6996cf82d25eafd9cd00744a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Democratization-Call-Sparks-Market-Scrutiny-Amid-Superintelligence-Race/6996cf82d25eafd9cd00744a</guid><description>OpenAI CEO Sam Altman championed AI democratization and shared control at the India AI Impact Summit, warning against centralization. He predicted profound economic shifts, including cost reductions and job disruption, while hinting at superintelligence within years. This vision presents a complex market dynamic, balancing rapid innovation and economic growth against increasing regulatory oversight and the existential questions posed by advanced AI. Major tech firms are heavily investing, yet the industry faces valuation concerns and a fragmented regulatory environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:53:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996cf82d25eafd9cd007449_1771491354345.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Housing Boom: Bigger Homes Fuel Affordability Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Housing-Boom-Bigger-Homes-Fuel-Affordability-Gap/6996cf73d25eafd9cd007430</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Housing-Boom-Bigger-Homes-Fuel-Affordability-Gap/6996cf73d25eafd9cd007430</guid><description>India's top cities are experiencing a structural shift towards larger homes, with average apartment sizes increasing by 17% in two years. This trend, predominantly fueled by a surge in luxury housing launches and evolving buyer preferences for premium living, is significantly inflating property ticket prices. While the luxury segment thrives, this expansion is exacerbating affordability challenges for the broader middle-income demographic, leading to increasing market segmentation and potential economic strain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:53:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996cf73d25eafd9cd00742f_1771491356165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Travel Food Services Sees Sales Surge 18%, Eyes Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Travel-Food-Services-Sees-Sales-Surge-18percent-Eyes-Global-Expansion/6996ce08d25eafd9cd007358</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Travel-Food-Services-Sees-Sales-Surge-18percent-Eyes-Global-Expansion/6996ce08d25eafd9cd007358</guid><description>Travel Food Services (TFS) reported a strong Q3 FY2026 with consolidated sales soaring 18.3% year-on-year to ₹456 crore and adjusted profit after tax (PAT) jumping 35.3% to ₹137 crore. The company highlighted robust system-wide sales growth, expansion into new airports like Navi Mumbai, and strategic brand additions. TFS maintains a healthy financial position with zero debt and ₹800 crore in cash, fueling its aggressive growth strategy in travel retail and the highway segment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:47:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996ce08d25eafd9cd007357_1771490937358.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Embraer, Mahindra Plan India Jet MRO Hub If IAF Buys C-390</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Embraer-Mahindra-Plan-India-Jet-MRO-Hub-If-IAF-Buys-C-390/6996cd93d25eafd9cd0072f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Embraer-Mahindra-Plan-India-Jet-MRO-Hub-If-IAF-Buys-C-390/6996cd93d25eafd9cd0072f1</guid><description>Embraer and Mahindra Group are planning to set up a Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul (MRO) facility in India for the C-390 Millennium aircraft. This significant move is dependent on the Indian Air Force (IAF) selecting the C-390 for its Medium Transport Aircraft (MTA) program. The collaboration aims to bolster India's aerospace capabilities, support 'Make in India' initiatives, and potentially position the country as a regional MRO hub.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:45:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996cd93d25eafd9cd0072f0_1771490815672.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hemant Surgical Lands ₹264 Crore Government Order, Boosting Medical Supply Stock</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Hemant-Surgical-Lands-264-Crore-Government-Order-Boosting-Medical-Supply-Stock/6996cc9fd25eafd9cd00725d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Hemant-Surgical-Lands-264-Crore-Government-Order-Boosting-Medical-Supply-Stock/6996cc9fd25eafd9cd00725d</guid><description>Hemant Surgical Industries Limited has received a major purchase order worth ₹264.33 crore from the Central Medical Service Society (CMSS), a government body under the Ministry of Health and Family Welfare. The order is for medical equipment including a Flat Panel Detector, batteries, router, and an X-ray Generator. This significant win, expected to be executed in tranches by September 2026, is poised to substantially boost the company's revenue and market position in the vital Indian healthcare sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:41:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996cc9fd25eafd9cd00725c_1771490603276.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fractal Analytics Surges on AI Healthcare Model; Analyst Predicts 40% Upside</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-Surges-on-AI-Healthcare-Model-Analyst-Predicts-40percent-Upside/6996ca4dd25eafd9cd0070d9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-Surges-on-AI-Healthcare-Model-Analyst-Predicts-40percent-Upside/6996ca4dd25eafd9cd0070d9</guid><description>Fractal Analytics shares experienced a notable rise after unveiling its advanced healthcare AI model, Vaidya 2.0, which claims to outperform leading frontier models on OpenAI's HealthBench (hard) benchmark. This development has helped the stock recover from its recent weak market debut. Brokerage firm PL Capital initiated coverage with a 'Buy' rating and a target price of ₹1,260, implying approximately 40% upside, citing strong AI positioning and client retention strategies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:31:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996ca4dd25eafd9cd0070d8_1771490011790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eric Trump's $1M Bitcoin Forecast Meets Market Realities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Eric-Trumps-1M-Bitcoin-Forecast-Meets-Market-Realities/6996ca4bd25eafd9cd0070c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Eric-Trumps-1M-Bitcoin-Forecast-Meets-Market-Realities/6996ca4bd25eafd9cd0070c2</guid><description>Despite a significant crypto market downturn, Eric Trump remains an ardent proponent of Bitcoin, predicting a $1 million price target and calling it the 'asset class of this generation'. His optimism centers on historical performance and increasing institutional adoption by major financial players. However, this perspective contrasts with Bitcoin's inherent volatility, the cautious pace of institutional allocation, and evolving regulatory scrutiny, alongside specific challenges faced by associated ventures like World Liberty Financial.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:31:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996ca4bd25eafd9cd0070c1_1771490024147.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Dual Threat: Infosys Navigates Disruption vs. Growth Promises</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Dual-Threat-Infosys-Navigates-Disruption-vs-Growth-Promises/6996c964d25eafd9cd006fd0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Dual-Threat-Infosys-Navigates-Disruption-vs-Growth-Promises/6996c964d25eafd9cd006fd0</guid><description>Infosys co-founder Nandan Nilekani's warning about AI's 'race to the bottom' outpacing positive development underscores a critical market inflection point. For IT service giants like Infosys, this translates into a complex balancing act: leveraging AI for future growth while mitigating the immediate deflationary impact on existing revenue streams. The company's strategy hinges on aggressive AI integration, but investor apprehension over execution and market acceptance persists, evidenced by recent stock declines.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:27:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996c964d25eafd9cd006fcf.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rare Earth Gambit: Tapping Reserves Amidst China's Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rare-Earth-Gambit-Tapping-Reserves-Amidst-Chinas-Dominance/6996c8e9d25eafd9cd006f69</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rare-Earth-Gambit-Tapping-Reserves-Amidst-Chinas-Dominance/6996c8e9d25eafd9cd006f69</guid><description>India is launching domestic production of rare earth permanent magnets with a ₹73 billion program, seeking to curb import dependence and capitalize on its substantial rare earth reserves. This strategic push targets high-demand sectors like electric vehicles and defense. However, the initiative faces formidable obstacles, including underdeveloped midstream processing capabilities, technological gaps, complex regulatory environments, and the pervasive dominance of China, which controls over 90% of global processing and magnet production capacity. While India possesses the world's third-largest reserves, its current output remains minuscule, highlighting the critical need to overcome significant execution hurdles to achieve its self-reliance goals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:25:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c8e9d25eafd9cd006f68_1771489674434.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Sarvam's Launch, But Global Race Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Sarvams-Launch-But-Global-Race-Looms/6996c7fbd25eafd9cd006e5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Sarvams-Launch-But-Global-Race-Looms/6996c7fbd25eafd9cd006e5f</guid><description>India's push for AI sovereignty is gaining momentum, exemplified by the launch of the Sarvam foundation AI model and significant government backing via the IndiaAI Mission. While Sarvam showcases impressive performance against global benchmarks in specific tasks, the sector confronts the immense scale of international AI development and the critical need for sustainable monetization beyond subsidies. Prominent figures like Paytm's CEO Vijay Shekhar Sharma champion domestic capabilities, yet the landscape is fraught with challenges including fierce competition, evolving regulations, and the practical hurdles of translating technological prowess into lasting market dominance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:21:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c7fbd25eafd9cd006e5e_1771489407087.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>INOXGFL Acquires Bankrupt Wind World India Assets Amid Sector Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/INOXGFL-Acquires-Bankrupt-Wind-World-India-Assets-Amid-Sector-Headwinds/6996c7f8d25eafd9cd006e48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/INOXGFL-Acquires-Bankrupt-Wind-World-India-Assets-Amid-Sector-Headwinds/6996c7f8d25eafd9cd006e48</guid><description>INOXGFL Group, through Inox Green Energy Services and Inox Clean Energy, has secured the bankruptcy-acquired IPP (600 MW) and O&amp;M (4.5 GW) businesses of Wind World India. This strategic expansion aims to bolster the group's renewable energy targets, particularly Inox Clean's 10 GW IPP goal by FY28 and Inox Green's O&amp;M portfolio, now managing over 17 GW. Announced on February 19, 2026, the deal, pending NCLT approval, injects distressed assets into INOXGFL's operations. Inox Green's stock saw a modest uptick following the announcement, trading around ₹171.04. However, the acquisition emerges against a backdrop of significant sector challenges, including DISCOM financial distress, transmission bottlenecks, and high valuations for renewable entities, casting a shadow on the long-term viability and integration success.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:21:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c7f8d25eafd9cd006e47_1771489422026.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ENIL Promoter Group Reorganisation Update: THPL to Become New Parent</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/ENIL-Promoter-Group-Reorganisation-Update-THPL-to-Become-New-Parent/6996c51ed25eafd9cd006ce4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/ENIL-Promoter-Group-Reorganisation-Update-THPL-to-Become-New-Parent/6996c51ed25eafd9cd006ce4</guid><description>Entertainment Network (India) Limited (ENIL) has announced a further update on its promoter group reorganisation. Bennett Coleman and Company Limited (BCCL) is transferring its non-publishing businesses, including media and entertainment, to its subsidiary Times Horizon Private Limited (THPL) via a scheme of arrangement. Following approvals from NCLT and CCI, THPL will become ENIL's new parent and promoter, changing the ownership structure. This move is part of broader industry consolidation trends.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:09:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c51ed25eafd9cd006ce3_1771488683315.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ansal Housing Assets Worth ₹83 Crore Attached by ED</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ansal-Housing-Assets-Worth-83-Crore-Attached-by-ED/6996c304d25eafd9cd006b40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ansal-Housing-Assets-Worth-83-Crore-Attached-by-ED/6996c304d25eafd9cd006b40</guid><description>The Directorate of Enforcement (ED) has provisionally attached assets worth ₹82.79 crore belonging to Ansal Housing Limited. The order, related to alleged money laundering violations, impacts land and construction costs. This means unsold units on the attached property cannot be sold, potentially hitting future revenue streams. The company is exploring legal options.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:00:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996c304d25eafd9cd006b3f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fears Trigger IT Selloff: Opportunity or Overreaction?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fears-Trigger-IT-Selloff-Opportunity-or-Overreaction/6996c2d2d25eafd9cd006af7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fears-Trigger-IT-Selloff-Opportunity-or-Overreaction/6996c2d2d25eafd9cd006af7</guid><description>Foreign portfolio investors divested ₹10,956 crore from Indian IT stocks in early February, fueling a 14% slide in the Nifty IT index, its worst monthly performance since March 2020. Fears that AI could disrupt traditional business models and cannibalize demand drove the selloff, impacting heavyweights like Infosys, LTIMindtree, and Coforge. However, industry experts point to AI's potential for new revenue streams and the sector's history of adapting to technological shifts. Current valuations are under scrutiny as the market weighs disruption risks against long-term growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:59:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c2d2d25eafd9cd006af6_1771488079404.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Tax Scrutiny: Clarified Powers, Unforeseen Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Digital-Tax-Scrutiny-Clarified-Powers-Unforeseen-Risks/6996c2d0d25eafd9cd006ae0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Digital-Tax-Scrutiny-Clarified-Powers-Unforeseen-Risks/6996c2d0d25eafd9cd006ae0</guid><description>India's Finance Ministry has clarified that Section 247 of the Income-tax Act, 2025, effective April 1, does not grant new or unlimited digital search powers. The provision mirrors existing search and seizure authorities under the 1961 Act, applying only to formal investigations and not routine scrutiny. Despite reassurances, concerns linger regarding the "technology-neutral" language, which could potentially encompass AI-based tools and create future compliance complexities for businesses navigating an increasingly digital fiscal landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:59:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c2d0d25eafd9cd006adf_1771488111421.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Rebounds 6% on USFDA Clarification; Market Watchers Eye Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Rebounds-6percent-on-USFDA-Clarification-Market-Watchers-Eye-Margins/6996c2cfd25eafd9cd006ac6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Rebounds-6percent-on-USFDA-Clarification-Market-Watchers-Eye-Margins/6996c2cfd25eafd9cd006ac6</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma shares climbed 3% on Thursday, rebounding 6% from Wednesday's lows. The surge followed the company's clarification regarding a USFDA inspection at its Unit VII facility, which had previously sparked a 5% stock decline due to reported deficiencies in manufacturing and quality control. The company assured timely responses to regulatory observations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:59:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c2cfd25eafd9cd006ac5_1771488109971.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Snap Rally: Mid/Small Caps Face Sell-off Amid Geopolitical Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Snap-Rally-MidSmall-Caps-Face-Sell-off-Amid-Geopolitical-Fears/6996c1fbd25eafd9cd006984</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Snap-Rally-MidSmall-Caps-Face-Sell-off-Amid-Geopolitical-Fears/6996c1fbd25eafd9cd006984</guid><description>Indian equity markets reversed course on February 19, 2026, breaking a three-day rally. The Nifty Midcap 100 fell 0.9% and the Nifty Smallcap 100 dropped 0.5%, signaling a potential shift towards risk aversion. Persistent Systems shares declined approximately 4%, while Paytm saw a more than 3% drop. The sell-off was attributed to renewed geopolitical uncertainties and profit-booking sentiment, overriding recent positive trends in some large-cap IT peers. Analysts urge caution, advising selective stock picking and waiting for clearer market direction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:55:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c1fbd25eafd9cd006983_1771487849905.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Retirement Planning: Decade-Based Rules Evolve Amidst Longevity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Retirement-Planning-Decade-Based-Rules-Evolve-Amidst-Longevity/6996c1ecd25eafd9cd00696b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Retirement-Planning-Decade-Based-Rules-Evolve-Amidst-Longevity/6996c1ecd25eafd9cd00696b</guid><description>Retirement planning is evolving beyond static decade-based accumulation goals towards dynamic, personalized strategies. The 20s focus on habit formation, aiming for one year's income saved by 30. The 30s and 40s are acceleration and calculation phases, targeting 4-5 times income by 40 and precise projections thereafter. By the 50s, the emphasis shifts to wealth preservation and debt reduction, aiming for 12-15 times annual income, recognizing increased longevity and market uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:55:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996c1ecd25eafd9cd00696a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Launches Eye Biosimilar, Faces Crowded Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Launches-Eye-Biosimilar-Faces-Crowded-Market/6996c110d25eafd9cd006813</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Launches-Eye-Biosimilar-Faces-Crowded-Market/6996c110d25eafd9cd006813</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences launched Anyra, its first indigenously developed biosimilar of Aflibercept, targeting visual impairments like diabetic retinopathy. This move aims to enhance access to affordable biologics in India, a nation grappling with a high diabetes prevalence. Despite strategic partnerships with Regeneron and Bayer, the company enters a competitive ophthalmic biologics arena where established players and emerging biosimilars are vying for market share. The launch signals Zydus's intent to address significant unmet needs, though investor reaction remains cautiously optimistic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:51:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c110d25eafd9cd006812_1771487705869.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JioHotstar &amp; OpenAI Pioneer Conversational Streaming</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/JioHotstar-and-OpenAI-Pioneer-Conversational-Streaming/6996c0f6d25eafd9cd00678b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/JioHotstar-and-OpenAI-Pioneer-Conversational-Streaming/6996c0f6d25eafd9cd00678b</guid><description>JioHotstar has partnered with OpenAI to integrate ChatGPT, launching a first-of-its-kind conversational AI interface in India. This move replaces traditional keyword searches with multilingual, natural-language interactions, aiming to solve the "what to watch" dilemma. The AI-powered assistant will offer context-aware recommendations and extend to live sports, transforming passive content consumption into a dynamic, deeply personal two-way engagement. This strategic innovation positions JioHotstar to redefine user experience in the competitive Indian streaming market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:51:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c0f6d25eafd9cd00678a_1771487736378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Consumer Eyes ₹1 Lakh Crore Revenue Amidst Aggressive Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Consumer-Eyes-1-Lakh-Crore-Revenue-Amidst-Aggressive-Expansion/6996c08ad25eafd9cd006665</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Consumer-Eyes-1-Lakh-Crore-Revenue-Amidst-Aggressive-Expansion/6996c08ad25eafd9cd006665</guid><description>Reliance Consumer Products Ltd. (RCPL) has outlined an aggressive five-year plan aiming for ₹1 lakh crore in revenue, driven by strategic acquisitions and a vast distribution network expansion. Director T Krishnakumar emphasized a portfolio-centric acquisition strategy and a national rollout across its diverse product categories. The company has already seen four brands surpass ₹1,000 crore in sales, with plans to scale further and expand into non-food segments. Significant investment in integrated food parks supports this ambitious growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:49:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c08ad25eafd9cd006664_1771487535931.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AGI Race Fuels AI Investment Frenzy, But Risks Mount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AGI-Race-Fuels-AI-Investment-Frenzy-But-Risks-Mount/6996c084d25eafd9cd006631</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AGI-Race-Fuels-AI-Investment-Frenzy-But-Risks-Mount/6996c084d25eafd9cd006631</guid><description>Global AI leaders signal an imminent AGI era, but the race is creating immense valuation pressures and competitive strain. Giants like Alphabet and Anthropic are investing billions, yet tightening VC funding, supply chain bottlenecks, and intensifying regulatory scrutiny cast a shadow over the sector's future sustainability. The pursuit of Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) is accelerating, driving unprecedented capital deployment, but also raising significant financial and operational risks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:49:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c084d25eafd9cd006630_1771487486006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ePlane's NVIDIA Partnership: Digital Twin Accelerates India's eVTOL Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/ePlanes-NVIDIA-Partnership-Digital-Twin-Accelerates-Indias-eVTOL-Ambitions/6996c07ed25eafd9cd006615</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/ePlanes-NVIDIA-Partnership-Digital-Twin-Accelerates-Indias-eVTOL-Ambitions/6996c07ed25eafd9cd006615</guid><description>The ePlane Company is pushing India's electric air taxi development forward by creating a high-fidelity digital twin of its e200x aircraft using NVIDIA Omniverse and NVIDIA IGX platforms. This collaboration enables extensive virtual testing, significantly de-risking the validation process. While this deep-tech approach accelerates design and simulation, the broader eVTOL sector in India faces considerable challenges related to regulatory certification, infrastructure development, and market adoption, suggesting a long road to widespread commercial operation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:49:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c07ed25eafd9cd006614_1771487489372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Dive on Valuation Fears; Institutions Selectively Buy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Dive-on-Valuation-Fears-Institutions-Selectively-Buy/6996c079d25eafd9cd0065f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Dive-on-Valuation-Fears-Institutions-Selectively-Buy/6996c079d25eafd9cd0065f5</guid><description>Indian equities faced a widespread decline, with benchmarks falling significantly and investor wealth eroding. This sell-off was driven by high valuations in mid and small-cap segments compared to large caps, prompting a stock-picker's market. Despite the downturn, foreign and domestic institutions continued net buying, while defensive sectors like pharmaceuticals demonstrated resilience.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:49:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c079d25eafd9cd0065f4_1771487477166.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's RE Boom Faces Storage Bottleneck: Capacity Soars, Grid Stability Lags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-RE-Boom-Faces-Storage-Bottleneck-Capacity-Soars-Grid-Stability-Lags/6996c05cd25eafd9cd0065aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-RE-Boom-Faces-Storage-Bottleneck-Capacity-Soars-Grid-Stability-Lags/6996c05cd25eafd9cd0065aa</guid><description>India's renewable energy capacity surged to over 52 GW in the first ten months of FY26, predominantly from solar and wind, pushing total installed capacity past 520 GW. This rapid expansion, however, is outpacing the development of essential energy storage infrastructure. While policy targets are ambitious for Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) and Pumped Storage Projects (PSP), significant implementation hurdles, high costs, and PPA delays create a looming bottleneck that could hinder India's clean energy transition and impact sector valuations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:48:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996c05cd25eafd9cd0065a9_1771487419355.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tega Industries Q3 Profit Drops 41% on Acquisition Costs; Molycop Deal Nears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tega-Industries-Q3-Profit-Drops-41percent-on-Acquisition-Costs-Molycop-Deal-Nears/6996be19d25eafd9cd006473</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tega-Industries-Q3-Profit-Drops-41percent-on-Acquisition-Costs-Molycop-Deal-Nears/6996be19d25eafd9cd006473</guid><description>Tega Industries Limited saw its third-quarter EBITDA plunge by 41.6% to ₹60.0 Cr, largely due to one-off costs related to the Molycop acquisition. Despite this, revenue remained stable. The company is on track to complete the Molycop acquisition by March 31, 2026, and maintains a positive outlook for full-year FY26, expecting double-digit growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:39:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996be19d25eafd9cd006472_1771486854582.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks Crash: Oil Shock Triggers Deep Profit-Taking</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Stocks-Crash-Oil-Shock-Triggers-Deep-Profit-Taking/6996bc14d25eafd9cd00639a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Stocks-Crash-Oil-Shock-Triggers-Deep-Profit-Taking/6996bc14d25eafd9cd00639a</guid><description>Indian stock markets experienced a sharp decline, breaking a three-day rally as surging crude oil prices, fueled by US-Iran geopolitical tensions, combined with domestic profit-taking. The BSE Sensex fell significantly, with broader market indices also showing weakness. This sell-off highlights India's economic sensitivity to external energy price shocks and potential inflationary pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:30:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996bc14d25eafd9cd006399_1771486339882.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Plunge: Beyond Profit-Taking to Structural Weakness?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Plunge-Beyond-Profit-Taking-to-Structural-Weakness/6996bb5dd25eafd9cd006242</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Plunge-Beyond-Profit-Taking-to-Structural-Weakness/6996bb5dd25eafd9cd006242</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks, the Sensex and Nifty50, experienced a sharp downturn on Thursday, characterized by broad-based selling across banking, financial services, and large-cap stocks. This decline, exceeding 700 points for the Sensex and 200 points for the Nifty50, signals a confluence of profit-taking after recent rallies and heightened global uncertainties, prompting a strategic reassessment of market valuations and risk appetite.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:27:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996bb5dd25eafd9cd006241_1771486168664.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HSBC Multi Cap Fund Defies Volatility with Disciplined Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/HSBC-Multi-Cap-Fund-Defies-Volatility-with-Disciplined-Strategy/6996bb4ed25eafd9cd00620b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/HSBC-Multi-Cap-Fund-Defies-Volatility-with-Disciplined-Strategy/6996bb4ed25eafd9cd00620b</guid><description>The HSBC Multi Cap Fund has delivered robust returns since its January 2023 inception, with a ₹10,000 monthly SIP growing to ₹4.39 lakh by January 2026, yielding an XIRR of 13.41%. This performance notably surpasses its benchmark, the NIFTY 500 Multicap 50:25:25 TRI, which returned 11.32% over the same period. The fund's success is attributed to its disciplined multi-cap strategy, mandated allocation across market capitalizations, and a Growth at a Reasonable Price (GARP) investment philosophy, even as it carries a 'very high risk' classification.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:27:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996bb4ed25eafd9cd00620a_1771486156238.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Fund Outperforms Amidst Rising Valuations, Evolving Landscape</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Mid-Cap-Fund-Outperforms-Amidst-Rising-Valuations-Evolving-Landscape/6996bb4cd25eafd9cd0061f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Mid-Cap-Fund-Outperforms-Amidst-Rising-Valuations-Evolving-Landscape/6996bb4cd25eafd9cd0061f4</guid><description>Mahindra Manulife Mid Cap Fund has delivered robust XIRR and benchmark-beating returns over eight years, showcasing strong risk-adjusted performance. However, the fund operates within a mid-cap segment characterized by surging investor interest, intensified competition, and historically high valuations. While its strategy emphasizes diversified holdings in sectors like financial services and auto, a higher expense ratio for its regular plan and the inherent volatility of mid-caps warrant investor scrutiny regarding the sustainability of its premium performance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:27:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996bb4cd25eafd9cd0061f3_1771486165059.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India IPO Market Cools: Valuations, Exits Fuel Investor Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/India-IPO-Market-Cools-Valuations-Exits-Fuel-Investor-Caution/6996bb26d25eafd9cd0061b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/India-IPO-Market-Cools-Valuations-Exits-Fuel-Investor-Caution/6996bb26d25eafd9cd0061b8</guid><description>India's primary market has begun 2026 on a subdued note, with IPO activity significantly slowing after record-breaking prior years. Only nine issues have launched as of early 2026, a stark contrast to the robust activity in 2025. Poor listing performance, aggressive past pricing, and concerns over stretched valuations have dampened investor confidence, leading to a more selective approach. While a substantial IPO pipeline remains, market participants are prioritizing valuation discipline and quality execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:26:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996bb26d25eafd9cd0061b7_1771486095328.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KNR Constructions Wins Big: Tax Demand Slashed by ₹91.55 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-Wins-Big-Tax-Demand-Slashed-by-9155-Cr/6996ba1dd25eafd9cd0060bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-Wins-Big-Tax-Demand-Slashed-by-9155-Cr/6996ba1dd25eafd9cd0060bc</guid><description>KNR Constructions Limited has received a crucial 'consequential order' from the Income Tax Department for Assessment Year 2019-20. This significantly revises a prior tax demand, slashing it by over ₹91 crore from ₹100.44 crore down to ₹8.89 crore. The company confirmed this outcome, following a successful appeal, has no impact on its financial or operational activities, removing a potential overhang for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:22:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996ba1dd25eafd9cd0060bb_1771485834388.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>