<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:34 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Kesar Terminals Posts Q3 Profit Amidst Legal Cloud; Dividend Declared</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kesar-Terminals-Posts-Q3-Profit-Amidst-Legal-Cloud-Dividend-Declared/698b29ff757d40c7818673e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kesar-Terminals-Posts-Q3-Profit-Amidst-Legal-Cloud-Dividend-Declared/698b29ff757d40c7818673e1</guid><description>Kesar Terminals &amp; Infrastructure Limited reported a Q3 FY26 net profit of ₹136.23 Lakhs, reversing a year-ago loss. However, a significant ₹3,500.72 Lakhs net loss for the nine months ended December 2025, driven by the sale of a subsidiary, remains. Auditors issued a qualified conclusion citing ongoing litigation with Deendayal Port Trust, impacting future valuations. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹0.50 per share.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dhampure Sugars Soars on Q3 Profit Jump, Sales Surge 43% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Dhampure-Sugars-Soars-on-Q3-Profit-Jump-Sales-Surge-43percent-YoY/698b290a757d40c781867238</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Dhampure-Sugars-Soars-on-Q3-Profit-Jump-Sales-Surge-43percent-YoY/698b290a757d40c781867238</guid><description>Dhampure Speciality Sugars posted strong Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated net profit leaping 178.5% YoY to ₹204.36 Lakh on a 43.14% surge in net sales to ₹1635.15 Lakh. PBT margin expanded significantly to 16.26%. Nine-month consolidated profit also doubled, up 107.60%. Standalone numbers mirrored this strong performance with substantial revenue and profit growth. The company noted the seasonal nature of the sugar industry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:48:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b290a757d40c781867237.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HLE Glascoat Revenue Soars 41%, But Q3 Profit Plunges 55% On One-Offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HLE-Glascoat-Revenue-Soars-41percent-But-Q3-Profit-Plunges-55percent-On-One-Offs/698b28a8757d40c78186702d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HLE-Glascoat-Revenue-Soars-41percent-But-Q3-Profit-Plunges-55percent-On-One-Offs/698b28a8757d40c78186702d</guid><description>HLE Glascoat Limited reported a significant 41.35% year-on-year revenue jump to ₹326.57 crore for Q3 FY26. However, consolidated net profit after tax (PAT) plummeted 55.26% to ₹4.60 crore, primarily due to ₹3.18 crore in exceptional items including acquisition costs and a provision for new labour codes. The Glass Lined Products segment posted a PBIT loss in the quarter. For the nine-month period, revenue grew 38.53% and PAT rose 20.91%. No forward guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trade Deal Hopes Face Earnings Reality, Sectoral Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Deal-Hopes-Face-Earnings-Reality-Sectoral-Divergence/698b289d757d40c781866fd9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Deal-Hopes-Face-Earnings-Reality-Sectoral-Divergence/698b289d757d40c781866fd9</guid><description>Indian equity markets climbed for a third day, fueled by India-US trade deal optimism, with the Sensex and Nifty ending higher. However, profit-taking limited gains. The optimism masks sector-specific pressures, as seen in textiles due to a US-Bangladesh agreement. Q3 FY26 earnings presented a mixed financial picture, with profit surges offset by revenue concerns, suggesting a cautious outlook dependent on execution and fundamental strength.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Landmark Cars Surges on Strong Consolidated Sales, But Standalone Metrics Wobble</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Landmark-Cars-Surges-on-Strong-Consolidated-Sales-But-Standalone-Metrics-Wobble/698b2835757d40c781866e65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Landmark-Cars-Surges-on-Strong-Consolidated-Sales-But-Standalone-Metrics-Wobble/698b2835757d40c781866e65</guid><description>Landmark Cars posted robust consolidated results for Q3 FY26, with revenue up 12.55% YoY to ₹13,450.76 Cr and PAT climbing 20.09% to ₹141.80 Cr. Nine-month PAT surged 47.90%. However, standalone revenue grew modestly by 3.12%, and PAT declined 0.43% for the quarter and a significant 19.13% for nine months. Key events include the Mercedes-Benz agency model conversion and strategic acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:44:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b2835757d40c781866e64.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Glycols Posts 21% Q3 Profit Jump; Eyes Demerger &amp; Fundraise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Glycols-Posts-21percent-Q3-Profit-Jump-Eyes-Demerger-and-Fundraise/698b281a757d40c781866d48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Glycols-Posts-21percent-Q3-Profit-Jump-Eyes-Demerger-and-Fundraise/698b281a757d40c781866d48</guid><description>India Glycols Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26, with standalone PAT rising 21.04% YoY to ₹65.07 crore on 5.25% revenue growth. Consolidated EBITDA soared 36.09%, and margins expanded to 6.91%. The company also advanced its demerger plan, focusing on Bio Pharma and Spirits &amp; Biofuel, completed a ₹467 crore preferential allotment, and executed a 10:5 stock split. No forward-looking guidance was issued.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Foods Surges with 25% PAT Growth; Acquires New Facilities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Hindustan-Foods-Surges-with-25percent-PAT-Growth-Acquires-New-Facilities/698b27b8757d40c781866b86</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Hindustan-Foods-Surges-with-25percent-PAT-Growth-Acquires-New-Facilities/698b27b8757d40c781866b86</guid><description>Hindustan Foods Limited reported a strong Q3 FY26 with consolidated PAT rising 25.85% year-on-year to ₹36.12 Crores, driven by a 13.45% increase in revenue to ₹998.11 Crores. The company also expanded its manufacturing footprint by acquiring two facilities and a stake in a new entity. For the nine months, PAT grew over 30%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Pesticides Q3 Revenue Surges 30.7% on Strong Volume Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Pesticides-Q3-Revenue-Surges-307percent-on-Strong-Volume-Growth/698b27a1757d40c781866aa4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Pesticides-Q3-Revenue-Surges-307percent-on-Strong-Volume-Growth/698b27a1757d40c781866aa4</guid><description>India Pesticides Limited (IPL) reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue soaring 30.7% YoY to ₹229 crore, driven by a 32% volume increase. EBITDA and Net Profit climbed over 40%, bolstered by strong export and domestic sales. Management expressed confidence in sustained growth, citing capacity expansions and operational efficiencies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Maharashtra Corp Plummets 97% Revenue, Posts Net Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Maharashtra-Corp-Plummets-97percent-Revenue-Posts-Net-Loss/698b273d757d40c7818668e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Maharashtra-Corp-Plummets-97percent-Revenue-Posts-Net-Loss/698b273d757d40c7818668e6</guid><description>Maharashtra Corporation Limited has announced a dire financial update, reporting a 97.1% year-on-year plunge in revenue for Q3 FY26 to ₹4.50 Lakhs, from ₹155.00 Lakhs in the prior year. The company swung to a net loss of ₹1.20 Lakhs, a stark contrast to a profit in the previous year. The nine-month period mirrored this trend, with revenue severely hit and a substantial net loss incurred. Earnings Per Share for the quarter were negligible. No management guidance or outlook was provided.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SEBI Probes Goyal Aluminiums Business Deal; Company Summons Issued</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Probes-Goyal-Aluminiums-Business-Deal-Company-Summons-Issued/698b272b757d40c7818667ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Probes-Goyal-Aluminiums-Business-Deal-Company-Summons-Issued/698b272b757d40c7818667ff</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has appointed an Investigating Officer to probe a business transaction involving Goyal Aluminiums Limited. The company confirmed receiving a summon on February 10, 2026, requiring document submission by February 13. Goyal Aluminiums stated that the specific nature of alleged violations and the financial or operational impact are currently unquantifiable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Future Market Networks Plunges on Profit Drop, ₹1845 Cr Legal Threat Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Future-Market-Networks-Plunges-on-Profit-Drop-1845-Cr-Legal-Threat-Looms/698b26b1757d40c78186667b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Future-Market-Networks-Plunges-on-Profit-Drop-1845-Cr-Legal-Threat-Looms/698b26b1757d40c78186667b</guid><description>Future Market Networks reported a 11.9% year-on-year dip in Q3 consolidated net profit to ₹18.08 Cr. The nine-month consolidated profit saw a drastic 88.4% fall to ₹40.02 Cr. The company faces a severe overhang from an ₹18,448.96 lakh (approx. ₹1845 Cr) demand notice from JC Flower (formerly Yes Bank), alongside other significant legal disputes and contingent liabilities. Standalone Q3 profit also declined 66.9%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:38:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b26b1757d40c78186667a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wakefit IPO Fuels Record Profit Surge Post-Listing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Wakefit-IPO-Fuels-Record-Profit-Surge-Post-Listing/698b25db757d40c7818663f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Wakefit-IPO-Fuels-Record-Profit-Surge-Post-Listing/698b25db757d40c7818663f9</guid><description>Wakefit Innovations reported its strongest-ever Q3 FY26 and nine-month performance following its successful IPO in December 2025. Revenue rose 9.4% YoY to INR 4,213.4 Mn in Q3, while Operating EBITDA surged 422.7% YoY to INR 416.4 Mn, turning PAT positive at INR 318.6 Mn. The company holds INR 8,891.8 Mn in cash post-IPO and aims for mid-to-high teen revenue growth in FY26.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:34:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b25db757d40c7818663f8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Krishival Foods Posts Stellar Q3 PAT Growth, Approves ESOPs &amp; Guarantee</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Krishival-Foods-Posts-Stellar-Q3-PAT-Growth-Approves-ESOPs-and-Guarantee/698b25c1757d40c781866347</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Krishival-Foods-Posts-Stellar-Q3-PAT-Growth-Approves-ESOPs-and-Guarantee/698b25c1757d40c781866347</guid><description>Krishival Foods Limited reported a massive financial uplift in Q3 FY26, with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) skyrocketing by 11,700% year-on-year to ₹641.24 Lakhs. Revenue also saw robust growth of 35.9% to ₹7,441.20 Lakhs. The company's board approved granting 6,35,000 ESOPs and a corporate guarantee of up to ₹4.5 Crores for its subsidiary, Melt ‘N’ Mellow Foods Private Limited. A factory building acquisition from a wholly-owned subsidiary was also greenlit, pending shareholder approval.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Power Surges on 30% Profit Jump, Interim Dividend &amp; Japan LNG Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Surges-on-30percent-Profit-Jump-Interim-Dividend-and-Japan-LNG-Deal/698b2576757d40c7818661b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Surges-on-30percent-Profit-Jump-Interim-Dividend-and-Japan-LNG-Deal/698b2576757d40c7818661b3</guid><description>Torrent Power's Q3 FY26 Total Comprehensive Income (TCI) soared 30% year-on-year to ₹637 Crore, driven by a 15% EBITDA growth to ₹1,472 Crore and 4% revenue increase to ₹6,778 Crore. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹15 per share. A significant development was the signing of a 10-year LNG supply agreement with Japan's JERA, bolstering fuel security for its gas-based power plants and supporting future capacity additions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishival Foods Skyrockets Profit 11,739% on Strong Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Krishival-Foods-Skyrockets-Profit-11739percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Surge/698b255d757d40c7818660a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Krishival-Foods-Skyrockets-Profit-11739percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Surge/698b255d757d40c7818660a1</guid><description>Krishival Foods reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated PAT surging 11,739.98% YoY to ₹641.24 Lakhs and revenue climbing 36.03% to ₹7,441.20 Lakhs. Standalone PAT also jumped 145.33%. The company also approved an ESOP grant, a corporate guarantee for its subsidiary, and an asset purchase. No forward guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>E To E Rail Wins Rs 12 Cr Contract Amidst Low Promoter Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/E-To-E-Rail-Wins-Rs-12-Cr-Contract-Amidst-Low-Promoter-Stake/698b254b757d40c781865fe4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/E-To-E-Rail-Wins-Rs-12-Cr-Contract-Amidst-Low-Promoter-Stake/698b254b757d40c781865fe4</guid><description>E To E Transportation Infrastructure has secured a ₹12.44 crore contract from Central Railway for axle counters, adding to its robust order book which now totals over ₹215 crore (including GST) for the period October 2025 to February 2026. This follows a ₹20.60 crore award from Southern Railway. Despite strong revenue growth of 47% in FY25, the company reported a loss in H1-FY26. With a market capitalization of ₹370 crore, the promoter stake at 32.51% draws attention amid significant government investment in the railway sector and increasing competition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NGL Fine-Chem Surges on 43% Revenue Growth &amp; Stellar Profit Jump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/NGL-Fine-Chem-Surges-on-43percent-Revenue-Growth-and-Stellar-Profit-Jump/698b24d3757d40c781865e4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/NGL-Fine-Chem-Surges-on-43percent-Revenue-Growth-and-Stellar-Profit-Jump/698b24d3757d40c781865e4c</guid><description>NGL Fine-Chem reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with revenue up 43.11% YoY to ₹127.51 crore and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 1129.12% to ₹15.69 crore. This performance was driven by higher volumes and operational efficiencies, boosting EBITDA margins by 1178 basis points to 17.50%. The company is progressing with a ₹210 crore expansion project, targeting commissioning in Q1FY27 and commercial production from H2 FY27, aiming for an asset turnover exceeding two times. Significant strides in regulatory filings for controlled markets were also noted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Eicher Motors Bets Big on Capacity Hike Amid Strong Q3</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Bets-Big-on-Capacity-Hike-Amid-Strong-Q3/698b245a757d40c781865cae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Bets-Big-on-Capacity-Hike-Amid-Strong-Q3/698b245a757d40c781865cae</guid><description>Eicher Motors posted robust Q3 FY26 results, exceeding estimates with revenue up 23% and net profit climbing 21.3%. Aided by strong volume growth and operating leverage, the company also announced a substantial ₹958 crore investment to expand its motorcycle manufacturing capacity at the Cheyyar plant. This expansion aims to boost annual production from 14.6 lakh to 20 lakh units by FY28, signaling confidence in future market demand and reinforcing its position in the mid-size motorcycle segment. The company's stock traded near record highs, reflecting investor optimism.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Glycols Posts Strong Q3 Growth, Eyes Strategic Demerger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Glycols-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Eyes-Strategic-Demerger/698b23fb757d40c781865b73</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Glycols-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Eyes-Strategic-Demerger/698b23fb757d40c781865b73</guid><description>India Glycols Limited (IGL) posted a solid Q3 FY26 with standalone revenue up 5.25% YoY to ₹2,551 Cr and PAT surging 21.05% to ₹65 Cr. Nine-month figures also show robust growth. The company is proceeding with a demerger of its Bio Pharma and Spirits &amp; Biofuel undertakings, setting April 1, 2026, as the appointed date, following stock exchange and NCLT approvals. This strategic move aims to unlock value and create focused entities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:26:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b23fb757d40c781865b72.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Phoenix Int'l Q3 Profit Plummets 89% Amidst Segment Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Phoenix-Intl-Q3-Profit-Plummets-89percent-Amidst-Segment-Woes/698b23e1757d40c781865a5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Phoenix-Intl-Q3-Profit-Plummets-89percent-Amidst-Segment-Woes/698b23e1757d40c781865a5d</guid><description>Phoenix International Ltd reported a steep 89.5% YoY decline in standalone net profit to ₹21.24 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, with consolidated profit down 89.8% to ₹20.76 Lakhs. This sharp quarterly drop contrasts with a robust 12.7% YoY revenue growth for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, which saw standalone net profit jump 47.6%. The profitable Rent segment masked losses in the Manufacturing segment during Q3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Windlas Biotech Halts Codeine Syrup Output Post Regulatory Notice</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Windlas-Biotech-Halts-Codeine-Syrup-Output-Post-Regulatory-Notice/698b236a757d40c7818658ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Windlas-Biotech-Halts-Codeine-Syrup-Output-Post-Regulatory-Notice/698b236a757d40c7818658ea</guid><description>Windlas Biotech faces a temporary halt in manufacturing Codeine-containing cough syrups following a Show Cause Notice from Uttarakhand's Food Safety &amp; Drug Administration. This product line contributed ₹55.21 crore to the company's revenue in the current financial year. The company is actively preparing a detailed response, assuring that operations for other products continue unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:24:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b236a757d40c7818658e9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCP Plastene Surges: Standalone Profit Jumps 433% on Strong Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HCP-Plastene-Surges-Standalone-Profit-Jumps-433percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/698b2306757d40c78186577d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HCP-Plastene-Surges-Standalone-Profit-Jumps-433percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/698b2306757d40c78186577d</guid><description>HCP Plastene Bulkpack reported robust Q3FY26 standalone results with a 110.95% YoY revenue increase to ₹7,390.12 Lakhs and a staggering 433.15% surge in PAT to ₹563.00 Lakhs. Consolidated PAT also jumped 279% to ₹833.36 Lakhs, driven by strong profit growth despite modest revenue increase. The company also announced the appointment of Mr. Rishabh Kumar Jain as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer and declared an interim dividend.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Astron Paper Assets Auctioned by Union Bank Over ₹83 Cr Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astron-Paper-Assets-Auctioned-by-Union-Bank-Over-83-Cr-Debt/698b22be757d40c781865611</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astron-Paper-Assets-Auctioned-by-Union-Bank-Over-83-Cr-Debt/698b22be757d40c781865611</guid><description>Union Bank of India has initiated an e-auction for Astron Paper and Board Mill Ltd.'s immovable secured assets, including land, plant, and machinery, scheduled for March 13, 2026. This action, taken under the SARFAESI Act, 2002, aims to recover ₹83.07 crore in secured debt plus interest and costs as of December 31, 2025, signalling severe financial distress for the company.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Landmark Cars Reports Strong Consolidated Growth, Standalone PAT Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Landmark-Cars-Reports-Strong-Consolidated-Growth-Standalone-PAT-Dips/698b2289757d40c7818654c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Landmark-Cars-Reports-Strong-Consolidated-Growth-Standalone-PAT-Dips/698b2289757d40c7818654c9</guid><description>Landmark Cars Limited posted robust consolidated financial results for Q3 FY26, with revenue climbing 12.55% YoY to ₹1,345.08 Cr and consolidated PAT surging 20.10% YoY to ₹14.18 Cr. Quarter-on-quarter, PAT saw an impressive 844.14% jump. However, standalone PAT experienced a marginal dip of 0.42% YoY. The company also highlighted its transition to an agency model for Mercedes-Benz sales and strategic subsidiary acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Captain Polyplast Sees Profit Surge on Solar Deals, Growth Faces Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Captain-Polyplast-Sees-Profit-Surge-on-Solar-Deals-Growth-Faces-Scrutiny/698b2249757d40c78186537a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Captain-Polyplast-Sees-Profit-Surge-on-Solar-Deals-Growth-Faces-Scrutiny/698b2249757d40c78186537a</guid><description>Captain Polyplast Ltd. posted a 41% net profit increase to ₹9.47 crore and 40% revenue jump to ₹127.22 crore in Q3 2025-26, fueled by significant solar pump orders and expansion in micro-irrigation and solar EPC segments. This performance highlights strategic execution in growing renewable energy and agricultural markets, though it enters a landscape of mixed sector sentiment and competitive pressures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:19:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b2249757d40c781865379_1770726059775.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dev IT Reports Q3 Net Loss, Reverses Profit Trend; Acquires Scaleax Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Dev-IT-Reports-Q3-Net-Loss-Reverses-Profit-Trend-Acquires-Scaleax-Stake/698b221a757d40c781865213</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Dev-IT-Reports-Q3-Net-Loss-Reverses-Profit-Trend-Acquires-Scaleax-Stake/698b221a757d40c781865213</guid><description>Dev Information Technology Limited (Dev IT) reported a stark financial downturn for Q3 FY26, swinging to a consolidated net loss of ₹(741.91) Lakhs from a profit of ₹181.66 Lakhs in the prior year. Standalone revenue declined 14.65% YoY to ₹3603.21 Lakhs. For nine months ended Dec 31, 2025, net loss stood at ₹(222.27) Lakhs consolidated, versus a profit last year. Amidst this, Dev IT approved acquiring a 19% stake in Scaleax Advisory for ₹1.90 Lakhs to boost GCC solutions and extended preference share maturity by five years.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:18:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashapuri Gold Declines 10% Revenue in Q3, Profit Edges Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ashapuri-Gold-Declines-10percent-Revenue-in-Q3-Profit-Edges-Up/698b2200757d40c781865132</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ashapuri-Gold-Declines-10percent-Revenue-in-Q3-Profit-Edges-Up/698b2200757d40c781865132</guid><description>Ashapuri Gold Ornament Limited posted its Q3 FY26 results, revealing a 10.05% year-on-year decline in revenue to ₹9,124.48 Lakhs. Despite the top-line dip, net profit rose by 7.76% to ₹557.07 Lakhs. For the nine months, revenue grew 6.04% to ₹24,660.18 Lakhs, while net profit surged 53.19% to ₹1,721.09 Lakhs. Diluted EPS for the quarter improved to ₹0.17. The company provided no forward-looking guidance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sam Industries Q3 Profit Plunges 81% QoQ Amidst Other Income Reliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Sam-Industries-Q3-Profit-Plunges-81percent-QoQ-Amidst-Other-Income-Reliance/698b218b757d40c781864f93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Sam-Industries-Q3-Profit-Plunges-81percent-QoQ-Amidst-Other-Income-Reliance/698b218b757d40c781864f93</guid><description>Sam Industries reported a significant 48.2% YoY revenue jump to ₹422.07 Lakhs for Q3 FY26. However, profitability saw a sharp decline, with PAT falling 80.9% QoQ to ₹41.83 Lakhs and PBT down 83.0% QoQ. The company's reliance on 'Other Income', which includes significant dividend and investment gains, appears substantial. A Whole-Time Director has also resigned.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Boosts Cooperative Sector via NCDC Lending Route</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Boosts-Cooperative-Sector-via-NCDC-Lending-Route/698b213d757d40c781864de7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Boosts-Cooperative-Sector-via-NCDC-Lending-Route/698b213d757d40c781864de7</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India will recognize loans made to the National Cooperative Development Corporation (NCDC) as priority sector lending (PSL) effective January 19, 2026. This strategic move aims to channel increased institutional credit towards cooperative societies across India, bolstering their financial capacity. The initiative is part of a larger, coordinated effort by the government and RBI to strengthen the cooperative banking sector through comprehensive governance, digital, and financial health reforms, creating a more robust ecosystem for rural credit delivery and development.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:14:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b213d757d40c781864de6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Launches Rare Earth Magnet Push for EV Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Launches-Rare-Earth-Magnet-Push-for-EV-Dominance/698b2117757d40c781864d00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Launches-Rare-Earth-Magnet-Push-for-EV-Dominance/698b2117757d40c781864d00</guid><description>India has greenlit a ₹7,280 crore initiative to establish domestic manufacturing of sintered rare earth permanent magnets (REPMs), crucial for electric vehicles and defense systems. This strategic move, aiming to create 6,000 metric tonnes per annum capacity, directly targets reducing import dependence, particularly from China's dominant global supply chain, and aligns with India's broader ambitions in electric mobility and critical mineral self-reliance. The program is a key component of India's larger strategy to bolster its manufacturing ecosystem and secure essential materials for its rapidly expanding green technology sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jefferies Turns Cautious on BSE, MGL, Ramco Cements</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Jefferies-Turns-Cautious-on-BSE-MGL-Ramco-Cements/698b20a4757d40c781864b96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Jefferies-Turns-Cautious-on-BSE-MGL-Ramco-Cements/698b20a4757d40c781864b96</guid><description>Global brokerage Jefferies has adopted a more reserved stance on BSE, Mahanagar Gas, and Ramco Cements, issuing 'Hold' or 'Underperform' ratings. The firm cites persistent cost pressures and long-term growth uncertainties for BSE, while Mahanagar Gas faces declining return on capital employed and margin compression. Ramco Cements contends with weakening volumes and pricing power in its core southern markets, leading to limited earnings visibility and execution risks on expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SAIL Targets 20 MT Sales Amid Profit Surge, But Margin Pressures Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SAIL-Targets-20-MT-Sales-Amid-Profit-Surge-But-Margin-Pressures-Loom/698b1faf757d40c781864996</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SAIL-Targets-20-MT-Sales-Amid-Profit-Surge-But-Margin-Pressures-Loom/698b1faf757d40c781864996</guid><description>Steel Authority of India Limited (SAIL) is targeting 20 million tonnes in sales for FY26, a 12% increase over FY25, fueled by proactive marketing and operational efficiency. The company reported a 2.6-fold surge in net profit for Q3 FY26 to ₹374 crore, driven by substantial debt reduction. However, the broader steel sector faces margin compression due to global pricing pressures and increased supply, which could temper SAIL's growth prospects despite its focus on sustainability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HCP Plastene Profit Soars 432%, Consolidated Revenue Stalls</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HCP-Plastene-Profit-Soars-432percent-Consolidated-Revenue-Stalls/698b1f4d757d40c78186481b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HCP-Plastene-Profit-Soars-432percent-Consolidated-Revenue-Stalls/698b1f4d757d40c78186481b</guid><description>HCP Plastene Bulkpack Limited announced robust Q3 FY26 financial results, showcasing a remarkable 432% year-on-year surge in standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹563.00 Lakhs. Standalone revenue grew an impressive 111% YoY to ₹7,390.12 Lakhs, with PAT margins expanding significantly to 7.6%. On a consolidated level, PAT jumped 279% YoY to ₹833.36 Lakhs, though revenue saw only a modest 1.6% increase YoY, declining quarter-on-quarter. The company also declared an interim dividend of ₹1 per share.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:06:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SG Finserve seeks shareholder nod to hike borrowing limit to ₹5,000 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SG-Finserve-seeks-shareholder-nod-to-hike-borrowing-limit-to-5000-Cr/698b1f34757d40c781864715</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SG-Finserve-seeks-shareholder-nod-to-hike-borrowing-limit-to-5000-Cr/698b1f34757d40c781864715</guid><description>SG Finserve Limited is seeking shareholder approval through a postal ballot for significant financial proposals. The company plans to increase its borrowing limit to ₹5,000 crores, up from ₹3,000 crores, and empower the board to pledge assets up to the same amount. Additionally, corporate guarantees from promoter entity S Gupta Holding Private Limited will be raised to ₹5,000 crores. The proposals also include introducing an Employee Stock Option Scheme (ESOP) for up to 20 lakh options and diversifying into factoring and other financial services following an RBI registration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:06:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698b1f34757d40c781864714_1770725232327.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titan Surges 40% Revenue in Q3 on Festive Demand, Jewellery Leads Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Surges-40percent-Revenue-in-Q3-on-Festive-Demand-Jewellery-Leads-Growth/698b1ef3757d40c781864594</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Surges-40percent-Revenue-in-Q3-on-Festive-Demand-Jewellery-Leads-Growth/698b1ef3757d40c781864594</guid><description>Titan Company reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue jumping 40% YoY to ₹24,592 Cr, propelled by robust festive demand. The Jewellery segment led the charge with 42% growth. Profit Before Tax (PBT) surged 70% YoY to ₹2,375 Cr, and consolidated PAT climbed 61% to ₹1,684 Cr, reflecting strong margin expansion across key businesses. The company also expanded into lab-grown jewellery and acquired a majority stake in Damas Jewellery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:05:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Eicher Motors Hits Record Q3; Royal Enfield Plans Major ₹958 Cr Capacity Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Hits-Record-Q3-Royal-Enfield-Plans-Major-958-Cr-Capacity-Boost/698b1eda757d40c78186446a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Hits-Record-Q3-Royal-Enfield-Plans-Major-958-Cr-Capacity-Boost/698b1eda757d40c78186446a</guid><description>Eicher Motors (EML) announced its strongest-ever third quarter (Q3 FY26), with consolidated revenue jumping 23% year-on-year to ₹6,114 crores. EBITDA surged 30% to a record ₹1,557 crores, and Profit After Tax (PAT) grew 21% to ₹1,421 crores. Royal Enfield sales rose 21% to 325,773 motorcycles, while VE Commercial Vehicles (VECV) saw sales increase 24% to 26,086 vehicles. The company also greenlit a significant ₹958 crore expansion for Royal Enfield's Cheyyar plant, boosting annual capacity by over 5 lakh units.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:04:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698b1eda757d40c781864469.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Repco Home Finance: Disbursement Surge 40%, But Profit Faces Margin Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Repco-Home-Finance-Disbursement-Surge-40percent-But-Profit-Faces-Margin-Pressure/698b1ebc757d40c781864384</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Repco-Home-Finance-Disbursement-Surge-40percent-But-Profit-Faces-Margin-Pressure/698b1ebc757d40c781864384</guid><description>Repco Home Finance announced a robust Q3 FY2026 with disbursements leaping 40% year-on-year to ₹1064 Crores and Assets Under Management (AUM) crossing ₹15,394 Crores. The company improved asset quality, reducing gross NPAs and Stage 2 assets. Despite strong operational momentum and a positive outlook for FY27 disbursements, recent financial data suggests a sequential and year-on-year decline in net profit and margin compression, attributed partly to increased operating expenses from one-off events.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:04:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Power Declares ₹15 Dividend, Plans ₹7000 Cr NCD Fundraising</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Declares-15-Dividend-Plans-7000-Cr-NCD-Fundraising/698b1e5a757d40c7818641c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Declares-15-Dividend-Plans-7000-Cr-NCD-Fundraising/698b1e5a757d40c7818641c6</guid><description>Torrent Power Limited's Board approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹15 per equity share for FY 2025-26, payable by March 12, 2026. Additionally, Torrent Power plans to raise up to ₹7,000 Crore through the issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) via private placement, signaling significant future capital expenditure or refinancing plans.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kansai Nerolac Revenue Edges Up, Profitability Faces Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kansai-Nerolac-Revenue-Edges-Up-Profitability-Faces-Pressure/698b1e45757d40c781864117</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kansai-Nerolac-Revenue-Edges-Up-Profitability-Faces-Pressure/698b1e45757d40c781864117</guid><description>Kansai Nerolac Paints reported a modest 3.1% YoY rise in consolidated net revenue for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹[revenue_consol_q3_figure] billion. However, profits faced headwinds, with PBT before exceptional items declining 3.7% YoY to ₹[pbt_consol_q3_figure] billion. The industrial segment posted strong double-digit growth, contrasting with the flat to marginally negative performance in the decorative segment. Management reiterated its EBITDA margin guidance of 13-14%, amidst concerns over commodity price volatility and intense competition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hexaware Launches 'Zero License' to Cut SaaS Costs with AI Agents</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexaware-Launches-Zero-License-to-Cut-SaaS-Costs-with-AI-Agents/698b1d82757d40c781863f65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexaware-Launches-Zero-License-to-Cut-SaaS-Costs-with-AI-Agents/698b1d82757d40c781863f65</guid><description>Hexaware Technologies has launched 'Zero License', an innovative enterprise offering that leverages agentic AI to replace complex SaaS workflows. The solution aims to significantly reduce software license costs, minimize manual effort, and streamline application stacks by positioning AI agents as the primary execution layer. This strategic move targets workflow-heavy industries like healthcare, insurance, and banking, promising faster execution and simpler technology landscapes within months.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>