<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:50:40 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Geopolitical Shockwaves Trigger Market Sell-off, Oil Surges to $100 Fear</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitical-Shockwaves-Trigger-Market-Sell-off-Oil-Surges-to-100-Fear/69a3ba7fedbd0c0ef0194c26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitical-Shockwaves-Trigger-Market-Sell-off-Oil-Surges-to-100-Fear/69a3ba7fedbd0c0ef0194c26</guid><description>Indian markets experienced a sharp decline on Friday, mirroring global sentiment as geopolitical tensions escalated over the weekend. The Nifty 50 fell below its 200-day moving average, signaling bearish momentum. Crude oil prices surged, with Barclays predicting a potential rise to $100 per barrel, creating significant headwinds for downstream refiners but benefiting upstream players like ONGC and Oil India. Companies with substantial Middle East exposure, including L&amp;T, Kalyan Jewellers, Welspun Corp, and KEC International, face heightened risks from regional retaliation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:03:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3ba7fedbd0c0ef0194c25_1772337945169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Risk Premium Hits Indian Aviation Hard</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Geopolitical-Risk-Premium-Hits-Indian-Aviation-Hard/69a3b734edbd0c0ef0194ac8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Geopolitical-Risk-Premium-Hits-Indian-Aviation-Hard/69a3b734edbd0c0ef0194ac8</guid><description>Escalating Middle East tensions and airspace closures have led to significant flight cancellations by Indian carriers, including IndiGo and Air India. Beyond immediate disruptions, the geopolitical conflict is exacerbating already thin airline margins through increased operational costs like fuel and rerouting. While government agencies monitor the situation, the aviation sector faces a sustained "geopolitical risk premium" affecting profitability and market valuations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 03:49:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3b734edbd0c0ef0194ac7_1772337069671.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPFO Poised to Hold 8.25% Interest Rate Amidst Market Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFO-Poised-to-Hold-825percent-Interest-Rate-Amidst-Market-Headwinds/69a3af38edbd0c0ef019487e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFO-Poised-to-Hold-825percent-Interest-Rate-Amidst-Market-Headwinds/69a3af38edbd0c0ef019487e</guid><description>The Employees' Provident Fund Organisation (EPFO) is anticipated to recommend maintaining its interest rate at 8.25% for the fiscal year 2026. This decision, expected from the Central Board of Trustees (CBT) meeting on March 2, comes despite muted government bond yields and a year where Indian equities underperformed global markets. EPFO's substantial corpus, coupled with an adequate surplus and strategic initiatives to diversify investments, underpins the confidence in sustaining this rate for a third consecutive year. The move is also influenced by the need to maintain employee sentiment ahead of upcoming state elections.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3af38edbd0c0ef019487d_1772335030890.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dividend Surge Signals Shareholder Focus Amidst Valuation Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dividend-Surge-Signals-Shareholder-Focus-Amidst-Valuation-Divergence/69a3a99dedbd0c0ef01946b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dividend-Surge-Signals-Shareholder-Focus-Amidst-Valuation-Divergence/69a3a99dedbd0c0ef01946b8</guid><description>As the financial year concludes, a wave of dividend declarations is set to reward shareholders across various Indian sectors. Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs) like Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL) and Bharat Electronics (BEL) are leading payouts, alongside entities in insurance and infrastructure. However, the scale of these payouts, coupled with significant valuation disparities among these companies, is prompting a closer look at the sustainability of such shareholder returns, especially for those trading at premium multiples.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:51:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3a99dedbd0c0ef01946b7_1772333633360.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerage Surge: 7 Indian Stocks Eye Double-Digit Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerage-Surge-7-Indian-Stocks-Eye-Double-Digit-Gains/69a3a1a7edbd0c0ef0192da6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerage-Surge-7-Indian-Stocks-Eye-Double-Digit-Gains/69a3a1a7edbd0c0ef0192da6</guid><description>A wave of positive analyst sentiment is driving significant upside targets for seven prominent Indian stocks. Brokerages like Jefferies, Motilal Oswal, and JM Financial have issued 'Buy' ratings, citing improving earnings visibility, market share gains, margin expansion, and technology-driven efficiencies. The chosen companies span critical sectors including banking, telecom, consumer durables, financial services, and hospitality, indicating broad confidence in the economic outlook.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:17:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3a1a7edbd0c0ef0192da5_1772331551635.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hormuz Flashpoint: India's Energy Reserves Tested Amid Asian Security Divide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Hormuz-Flashpoint-Indias-Energy-Reserves-Tested-Amid-Asian-Security-Divide/69a3984aedbd0c0ef0192b56</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Hormuz-Flashpoint-Indias-Energy-Reserves-Tested-Amid-Asian-Security-Divide/69a3984aedbd0c0ef0192b56</guid><description>Military actions near the Strait of Hormuz are heightening global energy market anxieties. While India activates contingency plans, bolstering reserves and exploring alternative routes, the event starkly reveals the varied energy security postures of Asian nations. Japan and South Korea remain highly vulnerable, contrasting with China's diversified approach and India's proactive measures, even as oil prices react to the escalating geopolitical premium.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:37:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3984aedbd0c0ef0192b55_1772329152992.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fear Overdrive: Market Dips Ignore Economic Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fear-Overdrive-Market-Dips-Ignore-Economic-Fundamentals/69a3922dedbd0c0ef019292b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fear-Overdrive-Market-Dips-Ignore-Economic-Fundamentals/69a3922dedbd0c0ef019292b</guid><description>A sensationalist report predicting AI-induced economic collapse due to job losses has spooked markets. However, economic analysis, supported by historical precedent, indicates AI's role as a productivity enhancer will ultimately increase aggregate income and consumption, not trigger a crisis. This disconnect between fear-driven narratives and economic reality may present buying opportunities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:11:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3922dedbd0c0ef019292a_1772327667589.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>March Market Volatility: Geopolitics &amp; Inflation Trump Seasonality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/March-Market-Volatility-Geopolitics-and-Inflation-Trump-Seasonality/69a3922aedbd0c0ef0192914</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/March-Market-Volatility-Geopolitics-and-Inflation-Trump-Seasonality/69a3922aedbd0c0ef0192914</guid><description>February's market turbulence extends into March 2026, fueled by escalating Middle East conflict and stubborn US inflation data, which diminishes hopes for immediate interest rate cuts. While historical seasonal patterns offer a statistical edge for Pidilite Industries, Cummins India, and AIA Engineering, the current macro-economic climate introduces significant, unpredictable risks. A stock-specific strategy is essential, but investors must navigate this volatile environment with heightened caution as external shocks may override established trends.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:11:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3922aedbd0c0ef0192913_1772327698039.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>