<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:31 +0000</pubDate><item><title>SpaceX Eyes Record IPO: Valuation Soars Amidst Visionary Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SpaceX-Eyes-Record-IPO-Valuation-Soars-Amidst-Visionary-Ambitions/69a2681efa7d0695d1aff067</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SpaceX-Eyes-Record-IPO-Valuation-Soars-Amidst-Visionary-Ambitions/69a2681efa7d0695d1aff067</guid><description>SpaceX is on track for a confidential IPO filing in March 2026, targeting a June listing with a valuation north of $1.75 trillion, potentially raising $50 billion. This would shatter existing records, with funds earmarked for Starship development, orbital AI data centers, and lunar base construction. Major financial institutions are slated to manage the offering, while a dual-class share structure is under consideration to maintain insider control. This move signals a significant shift in the space industry's public market presence, though questions linger regarding the sustainability of its lofty valuation against developmental risks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 03:59:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a2681efa7d0695d1aff066_1772251275628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GDP Surge: New Math, Sectoral Splits, and Investor Realities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Surge-New-Math-Sectoral-Splits-and-Investor-Realities/69a263b2fa7d0695d1afeec5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Surge-New-Math-Sectoral-Splits-and-Investor-Realities/69a263b2fa7d0695d1afeec5</guid><description>India's economy grew 7.8% in Q3 FY26, bolstered by a revised GDP calculation framework with a 2022-23 base year. Manufacturing output surged 13.3%, with services expanding 9.5%, underscoring the economy's resilience. However, agriculture growth slowed to 1.4%, highlighting a widening sectoral divergence. This methodological overhaul, incorporating GST and administrative data, enhances accuracy but requires reassessment of historical performance, with FY24 growth now revised down to 7.2%. Consumer spending (8.7%) remains a key driver, while investment eased, indicating a recalibration of growth engines.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 03:40:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a263b2fa7d0695d1afeec4_1772250127907.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Lombard Rating Outlook Revised to Positive by AM Best</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/ICICI-Lombard-Rating-Outlook-Revised-to-Positive-by-AM-Best/69a261effa7d0695d1afeddb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/ICICI-Lombard-Rating-Outlook-Revised-to-Positive-by-AM-Best/69a261effa7d0695d1afeddb</guid><description>AM Best has upgraded the outlook on ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company's Financial Strength Rating (FSR) and Long-Term Issuer Credit Rating (ICR) to Positive from Stable. The company's ratings remain affirmed at B++ (Good) and "bbb+" (Good) respectively, with the India National Scale Rating (NSR) holding at aaa.IN (Exceptional). This move reflects AM Best's confidence in ICICI Lombard's robust capital generation and prudent capital management, which are expected to further strengthen its balance sheet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 03:33:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a261effa7d0695d1afedda_1772249690309.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Recalibrates GDP Metrics, Enhancing Economic Clarity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Recalibrates-GDP-Metrics-Enhancing-Economic-Clarity/69a25898fa7d0695d1afea9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Recalibrates-GDP-Metrics-Enhancing-Economic-Clarity/69a25898fa7d0695d1afea9b</guid><description>India's national accounts have been significantly revised, moving the Gross Domestic Product (GDP) base year from 2011-12 to 2022-23. This recalibration incorporates advanced data sources like GST and adopts methodologies such as double deflation to achieve greater accuracy. The updated framework promises a more representative reflection of the economy's structure, including the burgeoning digital and gig sectors, while also influencing growth projections and fiscal calculations. This significant overhaul aims to enhance India's economic measurement credibility on the global stage.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 02:53:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a25898fa7d0695d1afea9a_1772247317000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Growth Push: Infrastructure Ambition vs. Execution Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Push-Infrastructure-Ambition-vs-Execution-Gap/69a25029fa7d0695d1afce5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Push-Infrastructure-Ambition-vs-Execution-Gap/69a25029fa7d0695d1afce5d</guid><description>Prime Minister Modi's call for innovation and investment in infrastructure and financial markets signals India's ambition for developed nation status. While capital expenditure has surged and foreign investment flows into debt markets are robust, driven by index inclusions, structural challenges persist. The private sector's hesitant participation in infrastructure projects and persistent illiquidity, transparency, and access issues in the corporate bond market highlight a critical execution gap. The integration of AI and blockchain aims to bolster governance, but translating policy intent into tangible ground-level impact remains paramount for sustained economic growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 02:17:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a25029fa7d0695d1afce5c_1772245148816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>QSRs Pivot Dine-In: Margin Grab or Digital Bet Against Convenience?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/QSRs-Pivot-Dine-In-Margin-Grab-or-Digital-Bet-Against-Convenience/69a23c8efa7d0695d1afc7f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/QSRs-Pivot-Dine-In-Margin-Grab-or-Digital-Bet-Against-Convenience/69a23c8efa7d0695d1afc7f0</guid><description>Major Indian Quick Service Restaurant (QSR) chains are strategically re-emphasizing dine-in experiences, introducing exclusive menu items and targeted promotions to counter declining delivery profitability. This pivot aims to capture higher dine-in gross margins, estimated at 15-20% above delivery, driven by savings on aggregator commissions and reduced discounting. However, this shift occurs amidst intense competition from dominant delivery platforms, rising operational costs, and a consumer base increasingly swayed by digital convenience. Jubilant FoodWorks, Devyani International, Restaurant Brands Asia, and Speciality Restaurants are recalibrating their models, though the long-term success of recapturing footfall against ingrained delivery habits remains a significant question.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:53:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23c8efa7d0695d1afc7ef_1772240148880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Sneaker Boom: Premium Valuations Mask Rising Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Sneaker-Boom-Premium-Valuations-Mask-Rising-Risks/69a23c82fa7d0695d1afc7d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Sneaker-Boom-Premium-Valuations-Mask-Rising-Risks/69a23c82fa7d0695d1afc7d6</guid><description>India's sneaker market is expanding rapidly, shifting focus to premiumization and aspirational consumption, projected to reach US$4.5 billion by 2030. While Metro Brands, Campus Activewear, and Bata India are executing diverse strategies to capture growth, elevated valuations and sensitivity to macroeconomic shifts pose significant risks. Investors must weigh sustained premium pricing against the potential for demand compression in a discretionary spending environment, alongside intense competitive pressures from global players.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:53:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23c82fa7d0695d1afc7d5_1772240152000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Stocks Surge Amid Market Pressure on AI, ESG Catalysts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Indian-Stocks-Surge-Amid-Market-Pressure-on-AI-ESG-Catalysts/69a23b9efa7d0695d1afc61a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Indian-Stocks-Surge-Amid-Market-Pressure-on-AI-ESG-Catalysts/69a23b9efa7d0695d1afc61a</guid><description>Amidst a challenging week for Indian equity markets, marked by declines in the Sensex and Nifty, several leading brokerage firms have identified select stocks with substantial upside potential. These recommendations are anchored by companies leveraging advanced manufacturing capabilities, artificial intelligence integration, and strong sector-specific growth drivers. Key themes include robust electronics manufacturing expansion, burgeoning EdTech sector evolution, and the strategic adoption of AI in IT services, aiming to create value against a backdrop of global economic uncertainty and geopolitical concerns.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:49:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23b9efa7d0695d1afc619_1772240050727.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>City Gas Expansion: High-Stakes Growth or Valuation Traps?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/City-Gas-Expansion-High-Stakes-Growth-or-Valuation-Traps/69a23b82fa7d0695d1afc5f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/City-Gas-Expansion-High-Stakes-Growth-or-Valuation-Traps/69a23b82fa7d0695d1afc5f2</guid><description>The Indian city gas distribution sector is aggressively expanding into smaller cities and industrial areas, shifting focus from saturated metros. This strategic pivot, driven by cleaner fuel demand and policy support, has led to significant valuation differences among key players. Adani Total Gas commands a premium for its aggressive expansion, while Indraprastha Gas and Gujarat Gas offer stability. IRM Energy remains an early-stage play facing execution hurdles and lower returns. Investors face a choice between high-growth bets with execution risks and established, steadier performers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:49:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23b82fa7d0695d1afc5f1_1772240173876.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Agri-Finance Gap: Public Dominance Risks Private Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Agri-Finance-Gap-Public-Dominance-Risks-Private-Capital/69a23b6efa7d0695d1afc5ab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Agri-Finance-Gap-Public-Dominance-Risks-Private-Capital/69a23b6efa7d0695d1afc5ab</guid><description>India's agricultural sector is critically underfunded for climate adaptation, facing an annual gap estimated between $310-$365 billion by 2035. The agri-food system receives only 20% of required adaptation funds, with public finance dominating domestic efforts (98-99%). Private sector participation is minimal due to high investment risks, long gestation periods, and fragmented landholdings. Despite COP30 agreements to enhance domestic climate finance ecosystems through platforms like the Green Climate Fund, unlocking private capital remains a challenge.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:48:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23b6efa7d0695d1afc5aa_1772239985680.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Capital Account Strain: Valuations, Outflows Cloud Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Capital-Account-Strain-Valuations-Outflows-Cloud-Outlook/69a23b18fa7d0695d1afc51b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Capital-Account-Strain-Valuations-Outflows-Cloud-Outlook/69a23b18fa7d0695d1afc51b</guid><description>India's capital account is under significant strain, characterized by substantial Foreign Portfolio Investor (FPI) outflows and declining net Foreign Direct Investment (FDI). Despite recent RBI liberalization of External Commercial Borrowings (ECBs), the currency faces ongoing depreciation pressure. Elevated domestic market valuations, coupled with a competitive global investment landscape favoring developed economies, are key factors contributing to investor caution. Analysts anticipate continued volatility throughout 2026.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:47:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23b18fa7d0695d1afc51a_1772239966915.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India EV 2W: Powering Livelihoods &amp; Indigenous Industry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-EV-2W-Powering-Livelihoods-and-Indigenous-Industry/69a23b0dfa7d0695d1afc4ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-EV-2W-Powering-Livelihoods-and-Indigenous-Industry/69a23b0dfa7d0695d1afc4ff</guid><description>The Indian electric two-wheeler market is rapidly evolving from basic transport to critical economic assets. These vehicles are electrifying livelihoods, creating employment, and addressing urban challenges while simultaneously driving domestic industrialization. Despite past safety concerns and import reliance, the sector's growth is underpinned by strong government policy, innovation in battery technology, and a growing demand for sustainable, affordable mobility solutions. In 2025, approximately 1.28 million units were sold, marking an 11% year-on-year increase, though market leadership shifted from Ola Electric to TVS Motor.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:47:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23b0dfa7d0695d1afc4fe_1772239941168.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Solar Tariffs Hit India: Trade Deal Ambiguity Amid Duty Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Solar-Tariffs-Hit-India-Trade-Deal-Ambiguity-Amid-Duty-Surge/69a23392fa7d0695d1afc270</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Solar-Tariffs-Hit-India-Trade-Deal-Ambiguity-Amid-Duty-Surge/69a23392fa7d0695d1afc270</guid><description>The U.S. Department of Commerce has imposed preliminary countervailing duties (CVD) of 126% on solar imports from India, citing unfair government subsidies. This move significantly impacts Indian solar exporters, with key companies like Waaree Energies and Premier Energies experiencing sharp stock declines. While Union Commerce Minister Piyush Goyal stated the duties are outside the India-US trade deal and the situation is fluid, the action raises questions about bilateral trade relations and India's strategic export ambitions. The duties are expected to make US market access economically unviable for Indian manufacturers, potentially leading to domestic oversupply and necessitating a recalibration of export strategies. Despite these headwinds, India's long-term solar sector outlook remains robust, supported by strong domestic demand and government policies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:15:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23392fa7d0695d1afc26f_1772237835249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>R Systems Board Meeting March 6 to Consider Interim Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/R-Systems-Board-Meeting-March-6-to-Consider-Interim-Dividend/69a23133fa7d0695d1afc13a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/R-Systems-Board-Meeting-March-6-to-Consider-Interim-Dividend/69a23133fa7d0695d1afc13a</guid><description>R Systems International Limited has scheduled a Board Meeting for March 6, 2026, to deliberate on declaring an interim dividend. This move underscores the company's focus on shareholder returns, with the final decision pending board approval and assessment of financial performance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:05:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a23133fa7d0695d1afc139_1772237210371.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>