<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:47 +0000</pubDate><item><title>RBI Curbs Spark Bank Fee Income Rethink, Insurance Models Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/RBI-Curbs-Spark-Bank-Fee-Income-Rethink-Insurance-Models-Shift/698e2c9aa47bab470ac54bba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/RBI-Curbs-Spark-Bank-Fee-Income-Rethink-Insurance-Models-Shift/698e2c9aa47bab470ac54bba</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's draft regulations targeting bundled third-party product sales by banks are poised to disrupt the rapid expansion of credit life insurance. This move aims to enhance consumer protection and curb mis-selling, potentially impacting a segment generating approximately ₹30,000 crore in annual premiums. Banks may face reduced fee-based income, necessitating a recalibration of their distribution strategies and product partnerships.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:40:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e2c9aa47bab470ac54bb9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Telecom Sees Slower Growth, Focus Shifts to Value</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Telecom-Sees-Slower-Growth-Focus-Shifts-to-Value/698e2c1f47d2f8db4b7da35a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Telecom-Sees-Slower-Growth-Focus-Shifts-to-Value/698e2c1f47d2f8db4b7da35a</guid><description>India's telecom industry experienced a single-digit revenue growth in Q4 2025, a marked slowdown after five quarters of double-digit gains as tariff hike benefits subsided. Despite this, subscriber additions and data consumption per user accelerated, with 5G adoption driving a significant portion of the surge. Analysts anticipate a shift towards subscriber premiumization and bundled offerings for future Average Revenue Per User (ARPU) growth, with potential for further tariff increases in the latter half of the fiscal year. Bharti Airtel maintains leadership in ARPU, while Reliance Jio and Bharti Airtel continue to gain subscribers, contrasting with Vodafone Idea's ongoing subscriber attrition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:38:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e2c1f47d2f8db4b7da359.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Govt CPSE Assets to REITs: Unlocking ₹10 Lakh Crore for Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Govt-CPSE-Assets-to-REITs-Unlocking-10-Lakh-Crore-for-Investors/698e2b6d47d2f8db4b7da2b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Govt-CPSE-Assets-to-REITs-Unlocking-10-Lakh-Crore-for-Investors/698e2b6d47d2f8db4b7da2b1</guid><description>The Indian government plans to monetize state-owned real estate assets via Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs). This strategic shift aims to unlock an estimated ₹10 lakh crore in idle government property, bolstering public sector balance sheets and expanding the yield-oriented investment market. Experts anticipate it will deepen capital markets and create a new income-generating pipeline for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:35:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e2b6d47d2f8db4b7da2b0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's DoT Shield Saves ₹1,400 Crore from Financial Fraud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-DoT-Shield-Saves-1400-Crore-from-Financial-Fraud/698e2b2e47d2f8db4b7da291</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-DoT-Shield-Saves-1400-Crore-from-Financial-Fraud/698e2b2e47d2f8db4b7da291</guid><description>India's Department of Telecommunications (DoT) has blocked an estimated ₹1,400 crore in potential financial fraud since launching its Financial Fraud Risk Indicator (FRI). Minister Jyotiraditya Scindia revealed the system flags high-risk mobile numbers, enabling banks and UPI providers to implement safeguards. The initiative, part of the Digital Intelligence Platform, leverages AI and stakeholder collaboration to combat increasingly sophisticated scams.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:34:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e2b2e47d2f8db4b7da290.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sadbhav Infra Auditors Doubt Survival, Warn of 'Going Concern' Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sadbhav-Infra-Auditors-Doubt-Survival-Warn-of-Going-Concern-Risk/698e2b2b47d2f8db4b7da288</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sadbhav-Infra-Auditors-Doubt-Survival-Warn-of-Going-Concern-Risk/698e2b2b47d2f8db4b7da288</guid><description>Sadbhav Infrastructure Project Ltd. reported significant net losses for Q3 FY26, both standalone and consolidated. Crucially, statutory auditors issued a qualified opinion on standalone results and a modified conclusion on consolidated results, explicitly stating a "material uncertainty" about the company's ability to continue as a going concern. This raises serious questions about the company's financial health, driven by subsidiary issues and substantial exceptional items.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:34:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e2b2b47d2f8db4b7da287_1770926193482.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tax Overhaul: Simplification Masks Regime Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Tax-Overhaul-Simplification-Masks-Regime-Shift/698e2aeb47d2f8db4b7da234</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Tax-Overhaul-Simplification-Masks-Regime-Shift/698e2aeb47d2f8db4b7da234</guid><description>India's upcoming Income-tax Rules, 2026, effective April 1, introduce significant hikes in allowances and streamline compliance. However, these changes subtly reinforce the government's push towards the new tax regime by incrementally diminishing the advantages of the older, deduction-rich framework. While ostensibly offering relief, the updated rules may reshape investment incentives and financial planning strategies, particularly for sectors dependent on the old regime's benefits. Stakeholder feedback is open until February 22.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:32:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e2aeb47d2f8db4b7da233.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VC Bets Big on Subway India Amid Fierce QSR Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VC-Bets-Big-on-Subway-India-Amid-Fierce-QSR-Race/698e2ab547d2f8db4b7da228</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VC-Bets-Big-on-Subway-India-Amid-Fierce-QSR-Race/698e2ab547d2f8db4b7da228</guid><description>Growth-stage VC firm Playbook Partners has injected approximately ₹130 crore for a 5% stake in Subway India, valuing the quick-service restaurant chain at ₹2,600-2,800 crore. This investment, spearheaded by former Reliance Jio executive Vikas Choudhury, signals continued venture capital confidence in India's burgeoning food service sector. The deal comes as Subway India, operated by Everstone Group's Culinary Brands, eyes a potential public listing, joining a crowded IPO pipeline of established global QSR players. The move highlights Everstone's strategy to scale its F&amp;B portfolio, while Playbook Partners deploys capital from its India Fund II, targeting significant returns in a dynamic market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:32:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e2ab547d2f8db4b7da227.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BPCL Pivots to Petrochemicals, Eyes Value Chain Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BPCL-Pivots-to-Petrochemicals-Eyes-Value-Chain-Dominance/698e2a3f47d2f8db4b7da1d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BPCL-Pivots-to-Petrochemicals-Eyes-Value-Chain-Dominance/698e2a3f47d2f8db4b7da1d0</guid><description>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd. (BPCL) is significantly advancing its integrated energy strategy with the development of a major petrochemical park alongside its Bina refinery in Madhya Pradesh. This ₹49,000 crore expansion includes a new 1.2 mmtpa ethylene cracker to produce polymers and aims to capture value addition beyond fuel refining. Scheduled for commissioning around fiscal year 2027-28, the project signifies BPCL's intent to become a more comprehensive player in India's booming petrochemical market, mirroring similar strategic pushes by competitors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:30:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e2a3f47d2f8db4b7da1cf_1770926182730.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel Surges on Record India Volumes, Europe Turnaround Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Surges-on-Record-India-Volumes-Europe-Turnaround-Looms/698e29cd90cee40befe063bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Surges-on-Record-India-Volumes-Europe-Turnaround-Looms/698e29cd90cee40befe063bd</guid><description>Tata Steel delivered robust 3QFY2026 results, spearheaded by India's record 6.34 million tons crude steel production and best-ever quarterly volumes in its Automotive &amp; Special Products segment. Significant cost savings of over Rs. 3,000 crores in the quarter lifted consolidated EBITDA margins to 15%. The company also generated strong operating cash flows, reducing net debt by Rs. 5,200 crores to Rs. 81,834 crores, while UK losses narrowed and Netherlands EBITDA turned positive. The outlook is cautiously optimistic, with plans for further capacity expansion in India.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:28:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e29cd90cee40befe063bc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zensar Technologies Secures $210 Million Deal for AI Transformation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zensar-Technologies-Secures-210-Million-Deal-for-AI-Transformation/698e294b90cee40befe06361</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zensar-Technologies-Secures-210-Million-Deal-for-AI-Transformation/698e294b90cee40befe06361</guid><description>Zensar Technologies has landed a significant $210 million framework deal over 5.5 years with a major financial industry player. The contract focuses on transforming client operations through AI-led automation, aiming to create an 'AI-native enterprise'. This partnership marks a strategic push for Zensar into advanced AI solutions within the critical financial services sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SoftBank Banks $7.4B From India Bets As IPOs Surge Portfolio Value</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/SoftBank-Banks-74B-From-India-Bets-As-IPOs-Surge-Portfolio-Value/698e294b90cee40befe0635a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/SoftBank-Banks-74B-From-India-Bets-As-IPOs-Surge-Portfolio-Value/698e294b90cee40befe0635a</guid><description>SoftBank has realized $7.4 billion from its India investments, bolstering its portfolio value to $13.7 billion as of December 31, 2025. Strong market debuts from Lenskart and Meesho, coupled with gains from OpenAI, have propelled the Vision Fund back into profitability. India continues to be a critical growth engine for the Japanese conglomerate's strategy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Inox &amp; RJ Corp Ink Africa JV, Targeting 2.5 GW Solar</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Inox-and-RJ-Corp-Ink-Africa-JV-Targeting-25-GW-Solar/698e28d590cee40befe062e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Inox-and-RJ-Corp-Ink-Africa-JV-Targeting-25-GW-Solar/698e28d590cee40befe062e8</guid><description>Inox Clean Energy and RJ Corp have established a 50:50 joint venture to invest an initial Rs 1,700 crore in African renewable energy projects, acquiring Skypower Services MENA Ltd. The partnership aims to commission 570 MW in its first phase and scale to 2.5 GW by FY29, leveraging RJ Corp's existing African footprint for operational synergies and Inox Clean's energy expertise. The venture targets sovereign-backed power purchase agreements, mitigating payment risks, though challenges in execution and financing persist across diverse African markets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:24:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e28d590cee40befe062e7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Sector Dues Fall, But Current Arrears Signal Lingering Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Power-Sector-Dues-Fall-But-Current-Arrears-Signal-Lingering-Risk/698e286490cee40befe06291</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Power-Sector-Dues-Fall-But-Current-Arrears-Signal-Lingering-Risk/698e286490cee40befe06291</guid><description>The Indian power sector has dramatically reduced legacy dues, from Rs 1.40 lakh crore in June 2022 to Rs 4,109 crore by February 2026, thanks to the Electricity (Late Payment Surcharge and Related Matters) Rules, 2022. However, total overdues, including current amounts, remain substantial at Rs 25,287 crore. While distribution companies posted a collective profit in FY24-25, the sector continues to contend with significant accumulated losses and high debt levels, pointing to persistent structural challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:22:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>VIP Clothing Q3 Revenue Dips 19%, But 9-Month Profit Soars 77% Amidst Credit Upgrade</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/VIP-Clothing-Q3-Revenue-Dips-19percent-But-9-Month-Profit-Soars-77percent-Amidst-Credit-Upgrade/698e27e690cee40befe06240</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/VIP-Clothing-Q3-Revenue-Dips-19percent-But-9-Month-Profit-Soars-77percent-Amidst-Credit-Upgrade/698e27e690cee40befe06240</guid><description>VIP Clothing reported a mixed Q3 FY26 with revenue down 18.9% YoY to ₹507.76 Mn, impacted by billing shifts, and PAT dropping 53.5% to ₹9.27 Mn. However, the nine-month period showed strong recovery, with revenue up 6% to ₹1,822.92 Mn and PAT soaring 77.3% to ₹53.87 Mn. The company also saw its credit rating upgraded and set an ambitious FY27 revenue target of ₹420 Cr, driven by premiumization and new product launches.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fratelli Vineyards Slips Deeper Into Loss, Standalone Revenue Vanishes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Fratelli-Vineyards-Slips-Deeper-Into-Loss-Standalone-Revenue-Vanishes/698e27e590cee40befe06239</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Fratelli-Vineyards-Slips-Deeper-Into-Loss-Standalone-Revenue-Vanishes/698e27e590cee40befe06239</guid><description>Fratelli Vineyards (formerly Tinna Trade) reported a sharp deterioration in its financial health. Standalone net loss ballooned to ₹877.06 lakhs in Q3 FY26 from ₹52.96 lakhs a year ago, with revenue from operations absent for the quarter. Consolidated losses also widened significantly, despite a 10% revenue jump in Q3. For the nine months, consolidated revenue plummeted 46%. The appointment of an experienced director offers a glimmer of hope amidst financial gloom.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fitch Affirms HUDCO Ratings at 'BBB-'; Stable Outlook Supported by Govt.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fitch-Affirms-HUDCO-Ratings-at-BBB-Stable-Outlook-Supported-by-Govt/698e27ae90cee40befe061ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fitch-Affirms-HUDCO-Ratings-at-BBB-Stable-Outlook-Supported-by-Govt/698e27ae90cee40befe061ef</guid><description>Fitch Ratings has affirmed Housing and Urban Development Corporation Limited's (HUDCO) Long-Term Issuer Default Ratings at 'BBB-' with a Stable Outlook. The agency highlighted HUDCO's critical policy role, strong government backing due to 75% ownership, and robust operating performance with rapid loan book expansion. However, Fitch noted rising leverage and moderated capital ratios, alongside strong asset quality metrics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Excelsoft Revenue Soars 29% on EdTech Demand, But Margins Take a Hit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Excelsoft-Revenue-Soars-29percent-on-EdTech-Demand-But-Margins-Take-a-Hit/698e276d90cee40befe061df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Excelsoft-Revenue-Soars-29percent-on-EdTech-Demand-But-Margins-Take-a-Hit/698e276d90cee40befe061df</guid><description>Excelsoft Technologies reported a strong 29.5% year-on-year revenue growth to Rs. 710 million in Q3 FY26, propelled by its education technology services vertical. Despite the top-line surge, EBITDA margins compressed to 27.7% from 32.8% due to higher operational expenses. The company is sharpening its focus on an AI-native, platform-led recurring revenue model, securing significant international deals and actively pursuing acquisitions to fuel future expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Synthiko Foils Posts Quarterly Loss Amidst ₹1047 Crore Mega Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Synthiko-Foils-Posts-Quarterly-Loss-Amidst-1047-Crore-Mega-Acquisition/698e276b90cee40befe061d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Synthiko-Foils-Posts-Quarterly-Loss-Amidst-1047-Crore-Mega-Acquisition/698e276b90cee40befe061d7</guid><description>Synthiko Foils Limited reported a consolidated net loss of ₹121.78 lakhs for Q3 FY26, a sharp decline from profit in the previous year, with revenue remaining flat. However, the company announced two significant acquisitions, including a ₹1,046.73 crore deal for DC&amp;T Global Private Limited via share swap. The nine-month period showed revenue growth and profit, but was impacted by an exceptional item. The company has a history of SEBI penalties for price manipulation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nurture Well Industries Posts 95% Profit Surge on Acquisition Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nurture-Well-Industries-Posts-95percent-Profit-Surge-on-Acquisition-Boost/698e268d90cee40befe06143</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nurture-Well-Industries-Posts-95percent-Profit-Surge-on-Acquisition-Boost/698e268d90cee40befe06143</guid><description>Nurture Well Industries Limited reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with net profit soaring 95% year-on-year to ₹34.60 Crore. Revenue grew a robust 46% to ₹289.77 Crore, fueled by the successful acquisition and integration of a biscuit manufacturing facility. Margins also saw significant improvement, underscoring the company's strategic operational expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepak Nitrite Q3 Profit Climbs 2% Amid Wider 9-Month Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Deepak-Nitrite-Q3-Profit-Climbs-2percent-Amid-Wider-9-Month-Dip/698e267a90cee40befe06135</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Deepak-Nitrite-Q3-Profit-Climbs-2percent-Amid-Wider-9-Month-Dip/698e267a90cee40befe06135</guid><description>Deepak Nitrite reported a resilient Q3 FY26 with revenue up 3% YoY to ₹1,983 Cr and EBITDA rising 16% to ₹219 Cr, improving margins. However, 9M FY26 figures show a dip in revenue, EBITDA, and profit. The company anticipates a stronger Q4 FY26, driven by new product launches, capacity expansion, and the significant removal of US duties on Sodium Nitrite.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Defends Tax Growth Amid Middle-Class Squeeze Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Defends-Tax-Growth-Amid-Middle-Class-Squeeze-Fears/698e264890cee40befe060ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Defends-Tax-Growth-Amid-Middle-Class-Squeeze-Fears/698e264890cee40befe060ef</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman rejected claims of middle-class economic suppression, highlighting robust personal income tax collections as evidence of economic expansion and a widening formal economy. She pointed to a significant increase in the taxpayer base and updated tax exemptions, asserting that rising real incomes and record-low inflation negate claims of distress. Despite these assurances, concerns persist regarding wealth concentration and the distributional impact of economic growth. Projections indicate continued strong GDP growth for India, though external risks and domestic inequality remain under scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nurture Well Industries Posts Huge Profit Growth With New Products, Factory</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nurture-Well-Industries-Posts-Huge-Profit-Growth-With-New-Products-Factory/698e260690cee40befe060d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nurture-Well-Industries-Posts-Huge-Profit-Growth-With-New-Products-Factory/698e260690cee40befe060d8</guid><description>Nurture Well Industries reported stellar Q3 results with Net Profit soaring 95.04% YoY to ₹34.60 Cr and revenue up 45.80% to ₹289.77 Cr. The company credits this growth to its expanding product line, including new biscuit variants and entry into the fresh bakery segment, alongside the strategic acquisition of a manufacturing plant in Neemrana, Rajasthan.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Debt Swap: Proactive Play Against FY27 Redemption Storm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Debt-Swap-Proactive-Play-Against-FY27-Redemption-Storm/698e259b90cee40befe0608b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Debt-Swap-Proactive-Play-Against-FY27-Redemption-Storm/698e259b90cee40befe0608b</guid><description>The Indian government executed a significant debt management operation on February 12, 2026, repurchasing ₹75,504.43 crore of maturing government securities from the Reserve Bank of India. This strategic move involved issuing new ₹69,436.15 crore of 8.30% GS 2040 bonds. The operation aims to smooth the government's debt maturity profile and mitigate redemption pressures expected in Fiscal Year 2027, when ₹5.47 lakh crore in bond maturities are due. This action occurs against a backdrop of increased market borrowing targets for FY27 and a complex global interest rate environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Silicon Valley Infotech Eyes Survival via Share Capital Reduction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Silicon-Valley-Infotech-Eyes-Survival-via-Share-Capital-Reduction/698e249d90cee40befe05e94</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Silicon-Valley-Infotech-Eyes-Survival-via-Share-Capital-Reduction/698e249d90cee40befe05e94</guid><description>Silicon Valley Infotech Ltd. will hold an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EOGM) on March 9, 2026, to seek shareholder approval for a significant share capital reduction. The move aims to cancel ₹12.70 crore of paid-up equity share capital to write off accumulated losses of ₹13.45 crore as of September 30, 2025. This strategic action is vital for the company, which reported a negative net worth of ₹48.43 lakh on the same date, and is crucial for its financial stability and future viability, pending National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) confirmation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:06:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Revenue Up 10%, But Margins Squeeze Amid Expansion Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Revenue-Up-10percent-But-Margins-Squeeze-Amid-Expansion-Costs/698e242a19b91b06434079c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Revenue-Up-10percent-But-Margins-Squeeze-Amid-Expansion-Costs/698e242a19b91b06434079c6</guid><description>Max Healthcare Institute Limited posted a 10% year-on-year increase in Q3 FY26 gross revenue, reaching ₹2,608 crore, driven by higher occupied bed days. However, operating EBITDA grew by a slower 4% to ₹648 crore, and EBITDA margins compressed by 1.2 percentage points to 26.1%. Profit after tax rose 9% YoY to ₹344 crore. The company is actively pursuing significant capacity expansion across multiple locations, including a new hospital in Pune by 2030.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e242a19b91b06434079c5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nykaa Seals Exclusive Kiehl's Deal, Deepening Luxury Bets Amidst Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nykaa-Seals-Exclusive-Kiehls-Deal-Deepening-Luxury-Bets-Amidst-Competition/698e23ae19b91b064340793c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nykaa-Seals-Exclusive-Kiehls-Deal-Deepening-Luxury-Bets-Amidst-Competition/698e23ae19b91b064340793c</guid><description>Nykaa has secured an exclusive distribution agreement for L'Oréal's luxury skincare brand Kiehl's in India, marking a significant expansion of its decade-long partnership with the beauty giant. This move grants Kiehl's access to Nykaa's vast customer base and nationwide retail network, aiming to capitalize on India's projected $40-45 billion beauty market by 2030. The alliance positions Nykaa to further entrench itself in the high-growth premium segment amidst a crowded competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:02:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e07b2687d8214b2f5fa78_1770918026201.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sarda Energy Targets ₹2,000 Cr EBITDA Amidst Ambitious Energy &amp; Mining Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Sarda-Energy-Targets-2000-Cr-EBITDA-Amidst-Ambitious-Energy-and-Mining-Expansion/698e23ad19b91b064340792e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Sarda-Energy-Targets-2000-Cr-EBITDA-Amidst-Ambitious-Energy-and-Mining-Expansion/698e23ad19b91b064340792e</guid><description>Sarda Energy &amp; Minerals (SEML) is targeting an EBITDA of ₹2,000 crore for the fiscal year ending March 2026, fueled by strategic growth in its energy and mining operations. The company's EBITDA has seen substantial growth, rising from ₹350 crore in FY20 to ₹1,250 crore in FY25, significantly boosted by the acquisition of SKS Power Generation via the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC). Approximately two-thirds of the FY26 EBITDA target is expected to come from the energy sector, supported by new hydropower and solar projects, while plans to double mining capacity aim to enhance earnings stability. The company is also advancing multiple coal mine development projects, projecting a significant increase in overall coal production capacity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:02:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e23ad19b91b064340792d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hazoor Multi Projects Posts Mixed Results Amid Subsidiary Exit &amp; Debt Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hazoor-Multi-Projects-Posts-Mixed-Results-Amid-Subsidiary-Exit-and-Debt-Rise/698e1fea19b91b0643401a23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hazoor-Multi-Projects-Posts-Mixed-Results-Amid-Subsidiary-Exit-and-Debt-Rise/698e1fea19b91b0643401a23</guid><description>Hazoor Multi Projects Limited (HMPL) reported a mixed financial performance for Q3 FY26. Standalone revenue surged 33.84% YoY to ₹7,597 lakhs, but standalone PAT dipped 13.42%. Consolidated revenue fell 15.67%, though PAT rose 138.09% driven by a tax credit. However, consolidated PAT margins contracted significantly, and debt-to-equity climbed to 0.73, with Interest Service Coverage Ratio turning negative (-0.87) in Q3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:46:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e1fea19b91b0643401a22.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ducon Infratech Posts Steep Profit Drop, Auditor Flags Investment Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ducon-Infratech-Posts-Steep-Profit-Drop-Auditor-Flags-Investment-Valuation/698e1f7219b91b064340024a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ducon-Infratech-Posts-Steep-Profit-Drop-Auditor-Flags-Investment-Valuation/698e1f7219b91b064340024a</guid><description>Ducon Infratechnologies Limited reported a sharp decline in third-quarter earnings, with standalone net profit falling 65.64% year-on-year to ₹39.86 Lakhs. Consolidated net profit dropped 32.15% to ₹231.24 Lakhs. Revenue also saw declines across standalone and consolidated figures. The company's auditor flagged an 'Emphasis of Matters' concerning investments valued at cost rather than fair value, totaling ₹500 Lakhs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:44:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e1f7219b91b0643400249_1770927681346.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ONGC Surges on Record Dividend, Profit Jump; Revenue Edges Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Surges-on-Record-Dividend-Profit-Jump-Revenue-Edges-Up/698e1efc19b91b06434001ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Surges-on-Record-Dividend-Profit-Jump-Revenue-Edges-Up/698e1efc19b91b06434001ce</guid><description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) reported a robust 22.56% year-on-year surge in consolidated net profit to ₹11,946 crore for Q3 FY'26. The company also declared its highest-ever cumulative interim dividend for FY'26 at 245%. However, consolidated gross revenue saw a marginal 0.13% rise YoY, with standalone revenues declining. Lower crude oil and gas price realisations impacted performance despite operational progress and new gas monetization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e1efc19b91b06434001cd_1770927692126.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jiya Eco-Products Reports Nil Revenue Amidst Corporate Insolvency Proceedings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Jiya-Eco-Products-Reports-Nil-Revenue-Amidst-Corporate-Insolvency-Proceedings/698e1eb319b91b0643400140</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Jiya-Eco-Products-Reports-Nil-Revenue-Amidst-Corporate-Insolvency-Proceedings/698e1eb319b91b0643400140</guid><description>Jiya Eco-Products Limited disclosed its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, revealing a stark zero revenue from operations. The company remains under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) since May 2023, with its Board of Directors' powers suspended. The Resolution Professional reported a net loss of ₹1.13 Lakhs for the quarter on nil income, against a profit in the previous quarter. No future outlook is provided due to the ongoing insolvency proceedings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:40:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e1eb319b91b064340013f_1770927694828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jyoti Resins Posts Flat Q3 Revenue, Margin Dip Amidst Brand Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Jyoti-Resins-Posts-Flat-Q3-Revenue-Margin-Dip-Amidst-Brand-Push/698e1e8419b91b0643400127</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Jyoti-Resins-Posts-Flat-Q3-Revenue-Margin-Dip-Amidst-Brand-Push/698e1e8419b91b0643400127</guid><description>Jyoti Resins &amp; Adhesives reported a subdued Q3 FY26 with flattish revenue and volume growth year-on-year. While unit economics were deemed good, investors expressed significant disappointment over stagnant revenue and earnings per share since FY24. The company's EBITDA margins compressed from 32-34% to 25-26% due to increased ATL and BTL marketing expenditures, a strategic move management believes is necessary for long-term market share and brand building towards a ₹500 crore revenue target. A debt-free company with ₹170 crore in cash, Jyoti Resins is undertaking brownfield expansion to boost capacity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e1e8419b91b0643400126_1770926022282.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CMS Info Systems: Revenue Climbs 6.3% Amid Profit Dip; Secures ₹1000 Cr SBI Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CMS-Info-Systems-Revenue-Climbs-63percent-Amid-Profit-Dip-Secures-1000-Cr-SBI-Order/698e1e8219b91b064340011f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CMS-Info-Systems-Revenue-Climbs-63percent-Amid-Profit-Dip-Secures-1000-Cr-SBI-Order/698e1e8219b91b064340011f</guid><description>CMS Info Systems reported a 6.3% YoY revenue growth to ₹618.22 Cr in Q3 FY26, but consolidated PAT declined 38.3% to ₹57.40 Cr, impacted by ₹11.11 Cr in exceptional wage code costs and industry pressures. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹2.75 per share and secured a significant ₹1,000 Cr, 10-year contract with SBI for ATM cash solutions. Management sees Q3 FY26 as a financial bottom, anticipating sequential gains and a FY27 revenue goal of ₹2,800 Cr.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:40:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e1e8219b91b064340011e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Autoriders International Sees 113% Profit Jump, Announces 5:1 Bonus Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Autoriders-International-Sees-113percent-Profit-Jump-Announces-51-Bonus-Issue/698e1e0b19b91b06433fed0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Autoriders-International-Sees-113percent-Profit-Jump-Announces-51-Bonus-Issue/698e1e0b19b91b06433fed0b</guid><description>Autoriders International reported a robust Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit soaring 113.33% YoY to ₹235.01 lacs on 18.92% revenue growth. Nine-month PAT rose 26.15%. The company also approved a 5:1 bonus issue and extended a ₹5 crore loan to its subsidiary, Solareco Energy Private Limited. Standalone results mirrored consolidated figures. No forward-looking guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:38:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e1e0b19b91b06433fed0a_1770926006531.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ONGC Payouts ₹7,863 Cr Dividend; Profit Surge Masking Deep Liabilities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Payouts-7863-Cr-Dividend-Profit-Surge-Masking-Deep-Liabilities/698e1d1d19b91b06433fa749</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Payouts-7863-Cr-Dividend-Profit-Surge-Masking-Deep-Liabilities/698e1d1d19b91b06433fa749</guid><description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) announced a second interim dividend of ₹6.25 per share, totaling ₹7,863 Crore. While consolidated net profit surged 22.57% YoY to ₹11,946 Crore for Q3 FY26, standalone revenue slipped 6.45% and PAT saw a marginal 1.57% rise. Investors should note significant contingent liabilities of ₹14,600 Crore for arbitration and ₹8,613 Crore for tax disputes, alongside operational complexities in subsidiaries and a stalled JV block.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:34:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e1d1d19b91b06433fa748.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GAIL Appoints New CMD Amid Profit Pressure: Will Projects Focus Drive Turnaround?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GAIL-Appoints-New-CMD-Amid-Profit-Pressure-Will-Projects-Focus-Drive-Turnaround/698e1d1a19b91b06433fa72f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GAIL-Appoints-New-CMD-Amid-Profit-Pressure-Will-Projects-Focus-Drive-Turnaround/698e1d1a19b91b06433fa72f</guid><description>Deepak Gupta assumes leadership of GAIL (India) Limited as Chairman and Managing Director from March 1, 2026, succeeding Sandeep Kumar Gupta. This appointment by the Ministry of Petroleum and Natural Gas aims to ensure leadership continuity. However, the transition coincides with GAIL's Q3 results revealing a decline in gas marketing EBIT and a widening loss in petrochemicals, presenting a critical challenge for the new CMD. Gupta, previously Director (Projects), brings extensive experience in large-scale project execution to navigate these financial headwinds in India's expanding natural gas sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:34:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e1d1a19b91b06433fa72e_1770926086105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shivam Autotech Raises ₹45 Cr Via Debentures from Alpha Alternatives Fund</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shivam-Autotech-Raises-45-Cr-Via-Debentures-from-Alpha-Alternatives-Fund/698e1ca219b91b06433f8dbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shivam-Autotech-Raises-45-Cr-Via-Debentures-from-Alpha-Alternatives-Fund/698e1ca219b91b06433f8dbb</guid><description>Shivam Autotech Limited has approved the private placement of 4,500 unlisted, secured, redeemable, optionally convertible debentures (OCDs) worth ₹45 crore. The issuance, allotted to Alpha Alternatives Structured Credit Opportunities Fund, carries a 10% annual interest rate and a tenure of up to 18 months, with a 12-month lock-in. This move aims to bolster the company's capital structure and liquidity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:32:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698e1ca219b91b06433f8dba_1770925891334.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ONGC Posts Mixed Q3 Results, Declares ₹6.25 Dividend Amid Revenue Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Results-Declares-625-Dividend-Amid-Revenue-Dip/698e1c2f19b91b06433e4689</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Results-Declares-625-Dividend-Amid-Revenue-Dip/698e1c2f19b91b06433e4689</guid><description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) reported its unaudited financial results for Q3 FY26. Standalone revenue dipped 6.46% YoY to ₹31,546.51 Crore, though PAT saw a marginal 1.59% rise to ₹8,371.85 Crore with improved operating margins. Consolidated PAT surged 22.57% to ₹11,946.42 Crore on slightly higher revenue. The board declared a second interim dividend of ₹6.25 per share for FY25-26, amounting to a ₹7,863 Crore payout.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:30:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e1c2f19b91b06433e4688.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's KCC Overhaul: Digital Push Meets Banking Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-KCC-Overhaul-Digital-Push-Meets-Banking-Risks/698e1bf419b91b06433e40e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-KCC-Overhaul-Digital-Push-Meets-Banking-Risks/698e1bf419b91b06433e40e5</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has proposed significant revisions to the Kisan Credit Card (KCC) scheme, aiming to enhance credit access for marginal farmers. The draft framework introduces flexible credit limits between ₹10,000 to ₹50,000, standardizes crop seasons, and extends the KCC tenure to six years. A key focus is the integration of technological expenses and an increased emphasis on digital channels for credit drawdown, aligning with a broader national strategy for financial inclusion in agriculture. However, the move raises potential concerns for the banking sector regarding increased credit risk and operational complexities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:29:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e1bf419b91b06433e40e4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Risk-Based Deposit Premiums to Reshape Indian Banking</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Risk-Based-Deposit-Premiums-to-Reshape-Indian-Banking/698e1bb519b91b06433e38cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Risk-Based-Deposit-Premiums-to-Reshape-Indian-Banking/698e1bb519b91b06433e38cb</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is introducing a risk-based deposit insurance premium structure, effective April 2026, replacing the long-standing flat rate. This significant reform, championed by expert committees for years, aims to curb moral hazard by aligning premiums with bank risk profiles. Scheduled Commercial Banks will face tiered assessments, potentially lowering costs for safer institutions. Co-operative and Regional Rural Banks will also be categorized, though with a more quantitative risk focus. The move is expected to foster greater financial discipline across the banking sector, albeit with potential implications for competitive dynamics and transparency.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:28:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698dfb60b357b56a644dd4f0_1770917703724.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>