<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:17:10 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Dairy Export Dream: Can It Go From Milk Giant To Global Trader by 2026?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Dairy-Export-Dream-Can-It-Go-From-Milk-Giant-To-Global-Trader-by-2026/694ddf5be10c98d0788d83fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Dairy-Export-Dream-Can-It-Go-From-Milk-Giant-To-Global-Trader-by-2026/694ddf5be10c98d0788d83fd</guid><description>India, the world's largest milk producer, is poised to significantly boost its dairy exports, targeting $490 million in FY25 with plans to capture a larger global market share by 2026. While production is abundant, the nation faces hurdles in quality, compliance, and cold chain logistics to fully leverage its potential in value-added products like cheese and skimmed milk powder.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:53:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddf5be10c98d0788d83fc_1766711198679.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pet Care Wars: Giants &amp; Startups Brace for 2026 Indian Market Explosion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pet-Care-Wars-Giants-and-Startups-Brace-for-2026-Indian-Market-Explosion/694ddfc8e10c98d0788d848a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pet-Care-Wars-Giants-and-Startups-Brace-for-2026-Indian-Market-Explosion/694ddfc8e10c98d0788d848a</guid><description>India's pet care market is rapidly expanding and becoming fiercely competitive. Major FMCG players like Reliance Retail, Nestlé SA, Godrej Consumer Products, and Wipro Consumer Care are increasing investments and launching new brands for 2026. The market is projected to grow significantly, reaching an estimated ₹35,000 crore, driven by indulgent pet owners seeking premium nutrition. Startups are also attracting funding, intensifying the competition in this burgeoning sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:53:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddfc8e10c98d0788d8489_1766711309040.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's EV Boom: Massive ₹857 Crore Electric 3-Wheeler Subsidy Fund EXHAUSTED 3 Months Early!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Boom-Massive-857-Crore-Electric-3-Wheeler-Subsidy-Fund-EXHAUSTED-3-Months-Early/694ddeebe10c98d0788d82e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Boom-Massive-857-Crore-Electric-3-Wheeler-Subsidy-Fund-EXHAUSTED-3-Months-Early/694ddeebe10c98d0788d82e9</guid><description>India's government is set to exhaust its ₹857 crore subsidy fund for electric three-wheelers (L5 category) under the PM E-Drive scheme three months ahead of the March 2026 deadline. This rapid depletion is driven by unexpectedly high consumer adoption of electric three-wheelers. The Ministry of Heavy Industries will cease issuing incentives once the allocated funds are disbursed or the target of 288,809 vehicles is met, whichever comes first, as per a letter to manufacturers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:53:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddeebe10c98d0788d82e8_1766711084423.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Investor Alert! Analyst Raja Venkatraman Reveals 3 Must-Buy Stocks for December 26th Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Investor-Alert-Analyst-Raja-Venkatraman-Reveals-3-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-December-26th-Surge/694ddea9e10c98d0788d825c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Investor-Alert-Analyst-Raja-Venkatraman-Reveals-3-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-December-26th-Surge/694ddea9e10c98d0788d825c</guid><description>Top analyst Raja Venkatraman of NeoTrader has identified three promising stocks for investors to consider on December 26th. Amidst market uncertainty and FII selling, Venkatraman recommends Gravita India, Laurus Labs, and PNB Housing Finance, providing specific buy levels, stop losses, and target prices. The Indian market closed lower on December 24th, with the Sensex and Nifty experiencing modest declines.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:53:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddea9e10c98d0788d825b_1766711227786.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Defence Stocks Dip 15%: Rally Over or Just a Pause? Investors Must Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Defence-Stocks-Dip-15percent-Rally-Over-or-Just-a-Pause-Investors-Must-Know/694dde9ee10c98d0788d822d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Defence-Stocks-Dip-15percent-Rally-Over-or-Just-a-Pause-Investors-Must-Know/694dde9ee10c98d0788d822d</guid><description>India's defence stocks have corrected by approximately 15% over the last six months, underperforming the Nifty50. Many leading companies are significantly below their 52-week highs. Despite institutional confidence, including HDFC Mutual Fund resuming SIPs and Tonbo Imaging filing its draft prospectus, experts warn of rich valuations, lumpy growth, and cash-flow risks. Outperformance is expected to be limited, with consistent delivery being key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:53:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694dde9ee10c98d0788d822c_1766711014074.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Gold Rush Soars 50% But Sebi Warning Sparks Caution: What Investors Must Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Digital-Gold-Rush-Soars-50percent-But-Sebi-Warning-Sparks-Caution-What-Investors-Must-Know/694ddde9e10c98d0788d816a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Digital-Gold-Rush-Soars-50percent-But-Sebi-Warning-Sparks-Caution-What-Investors-Must-Know/694ddde9e10c98d0788d816a</guid><description>Indian investors, especially young buyers, purchased approximately 12 tonnes of digital gold, valued at ₹16,670 crore, between January and November. This represents a significant surge, but demand has slowed following a warning from the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) highlighting the product's unregulated status. Industry players are now advocating for a regulatory framework, with the India Bullion &amp; Jewellers Association forming a self-regulatory organization to ensure customer protection and backed holdings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:50:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddde9e10c98d0788d8169_1766710855544.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 35-Year Economic Model Broken? Shocking Crisis Demands a NEW Path!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-35-Year-Economic-Model-Broken-Shocking-Crisis-Demands-a-NEW-Path/694ddd4ae10c98d0788d808a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-35-Year-Economic-Model-Broken-Shocking-Crisis-Demands-a-NEW-Path/694ddd4ae10c98d0788d808a</guid><description>India's 35-year-old economic model, credited with GDP growth, is now facing a severe socio-economic crisis. Key failures include a critical shortage of well-paying jobs, a surge in food subsidies affecting over 800 million people, and distress in the agricultural sector, especially for the 60% rural population. Urban centers grapple with pollution and congestion, while India lags in crucial emerging technologies. Experts argue the current model is unsustainable and advocate for a comprehensive overhaul, not just piecemeal fixes, to address these deep-rooted issues and build a better future by 2047.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:47:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddd4ae10c98d0788d8089_1766710703127.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026: India Inc's Big Shift! Gig Work Booms, AI Disrupts, &amp; Talent Hunts Beyond Metros!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-India-Incs-Big-Shift-Gig-Work-Booms-AI-Disrupts-and-Talent-Hunts-Beyond-Metros/694dd876e10c98d0788d7de2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-India-Incs-Big-Shift-Gig-Work-Booms-AI-Disrupts-and-Talent-Hunts-Beyond-Metros/694dd876e10c98d0788d7de2</guid><description>Experts predict India Inc will see major shifts in 2026. Companies will increasingly hire from smaller cities, reducing reliance on metros. The gig workforce is set to significantly grow, boosted by new labor codes offering social security. Artificial intelligence will continue to disrupt workplaces, prompting a focus on upskilling and restructuring roles, with fewer people potentially doing more AI-assisted work.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:26:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694dd876e10c98d0788d7de1_1766709561385.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Green Energy Puzzle: Why Are States Ditching Cheap Renewables for Costly Coal Power?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Energy-Puzzle-Why-Are-States-Ditching-Cheap-Renewables-for-Costly-Coal-Power/694dd7d1e10c98d0788d7c8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Energy-Puzzle-Why-Are-States-Ditching-Cheap-Renewables-for-Costly-Coal-Power/694dd7d1e10c98d0788d7c8d</guid><description>Indian power utilities are signing Power Purchase Agreements (PPAs) for thermal coal power at rates as high as ₹6.64 per unit, despite cheaper solar and wind power being available for ₹2.5-4 per unit. This preference for coal is driven by concerns over the intermittent nature of renewables, battery storage supply chain issues, and the need for reliable baseload power. The trend raises significant questions about India's commitment to its energy transition goals and leaves substantial renewable energy capacity without buyers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:26:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694dd7d1e10c98d0788d7c8c_1766709268507.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Giants SHOCKED: ₹10,900 Crore E-Bus Tender Goes to Newcomers! What Went Wrong?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Giants-SHOCKED-10900-Crore-E-Bus-Tender-Goes-to-Newcomers-What-Went-Wrong/694dd7fee10c98d0788d7cdf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Giants-SHOCKED-10900-Crore-E-Bus-Tender-Goes-to-Newcomers-What-Went-Wrong/694dd7fee10c98d0788d7cdf</guid><description>India's ₹10,900 crore PM E-Drive tender for 10,900 electric buses has seen new-age manufacturers PMI Electro Mobility and Eka Mobility win nearly 80% of the contracts. Legacy players, including Tata Motors and VE Commercial Vehicles, surprisingly secured no orders. Ashok Leyland missed due to a technical glitch and is pursuing legal action. Aggressive, lower-than-expected pricing by newer companies was a key factor in their success, leaving established players blindsided.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:26:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694dd7fee10c98d0788d7cde_1766709433113.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>