<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news from Whalesbook</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:24:54 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Shockwaves in Indian Markets: Retail Investors Flee Stocks, Highest Outflows Since 2019!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694addc1edf7500b4774a993</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694addc1edf7500b4774a993</guid><description>Indian stock markets witnessed significant activity in 2025, with retail investors pulling out ₹8,461 crore, the highest since 2019. Foreign Portfolio Investors (FPIs) recorded their largest ever outflows at ₹1.58 lakh crore. In contrast, Domestic Institutional Investors (DIIs) made record investments, infusing ₹7.61 lakh crore. While the overall investor base grew, the pace of new registrations slowed, influenced by global headwinds. The market capitalization of NSE-listed companies increased, with the Nifty 50 showing gains, though small-cap indices declined.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:13:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694addc1edf7500b4774a992_1766514187597.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Income Tax Nudge: 15 Lakh Taxpayers Revise Returns Amidst Bogus Donation Probe!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694adb9eedf7500b47740f9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694adb9eedf7500b47740f9e</guid><description>India's Income Tax Department has reported over 15 lakh taxpayers have revised their returns for Assessment Year 2025-26. This follows a 'NUDGE' campaign targeting incorrect deductions, especially concerning donations to unrecognized political parties and charitable institutions. Additionally, over 21 lakh taxpayers updated their returns this fiscal, contributing ₹2,500 crore in taxes. The deadline for revisions is December 31, 2025, after which updated ITRs will be necessary.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:06:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694adb9eedf7500b47740f9d_1766513666432.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC Bank Q3 Earnings Date Revealed! Investors Brace for Jan 17 Announcement – What to Watch For!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ad92fedf7500b47736d6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ad92fedf7500b47736d6d</guid><description>HDFC Bank has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on Saturday, January 17, 2026, to approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ending December 31, 2025. Investors await the Q3 FY26 earnings report, with the trading window for bank securities closing from December 25, 2025, to January 19, 2026. This announcement sets expectations for the earnings season.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ad92fedf7500b47736d6c_1766513054862.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NTPC Launches Massive Green Hydrogen Project! 🚀 What Investors MUST Know NOW!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ad8baedf7500b47736d01</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ad8baedf7500b47736d01</guid><description>NTPC, India's power giant, announced plans to establish a 1 tonne per day green hydrogen plant at Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh. The project, spearheaded by NTPC's R&amp;D wing NETRA, will utilize advanced plasma gasification technology to convert waste into hydrogen. This initiative aligns with NTPC's ambitious expansion goals for renewable energy capacity by 2032 and 2037, signalling a significant step towards cleaner energy solutions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:52:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ad8baedf7500b47736d00_1766513056294.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Telecom Duopoly: Jio &amp; Airtel Eye Price Hikes &amp; Premium Growth by 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ad7dbedf7500b47736beb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ad7dbedf7500b47736beb</guid><description>India's telecom sector is set to remain a duopoly dominated by Reliance Jio and Bharti Airtel through 2026, with Vodafone Idea facing challenges. Analysts predict a tariff hike of 10-12% in early 2025, as companies shift focus from subscriber growth to premiumization, higher Average Revenue Per User (ARPU), and enterprise 5G solutions driven by AI workloads. Success will hinge on executing pricing strategies and expanding high-value offerings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:44:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ad7dbedf7500b47736bea_1766512884251.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Talks Intensify: Will Exporters Finally Secure Deeper Market Access?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ad0dcedf7500b4771cbfc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ad0dcedf7500b4771cbfc</guid><description>India is actively engaged in high-level trade discussions with the United States, aiming to secure deeper market access for its exporters and resolve existing tariff challenges. Commerce Secretary Rajesh Agrawal expressed optimism about concluding these talks soon, which are crucial for restoring substantial bilateral trade. The negotiations are part of efforts to finalize a comprehensive Bilateral Trade Agreement (BTA) with the goal of significantly increasing trade volume between the two nations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:14:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ad0dcedf7500b4771cbfb_1766511576287.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma's Bold China Play: Boosting Stake for Global Dominance!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acffdedf7500b4771cad4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acffdedf7500b4771cad4</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma's Dutch subsidiary, Helix Healthcare BV, is increasing its stake in its Chinese joint venture, Luoxin Aurovitas Pharma, by 20% for over $5 million. This move is set to raise Aurobindo's stake to 50% by Q1 2026, with plans to acquire full 100% ownership by December 2029 for an additional $18.9 million. The expansion aims to boost manufacturing capacity for inhalation products and cater to growing market demand.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:12:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acffdedf7500b4771cad3_1766510858795.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Unleashes ₹2 Lakh Crore Liquidity Lifeline: Banking System Set for Major Support!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acf2cedf7500b4771c735</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acf2cedf7500b4771c735</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India announced a significant liquidity infusion, planning to purchase ₹2 lakh crore of government securities and conduct a $10 billion dollar-rupee swap auction. These measures, scheduled between December 29, 2025, and January 22, 2026, aim to ease conditions and ensure orderly liquidity in the banking system amidst evolving market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:12:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acf2cedf7500b4771c734_1766510735349.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Chaos Prompts Govt Action: New Airlines Get Green Light to Fly!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ace4bedf7500b477173da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ace4bedf7500b477173da</guid><description>The Indian government has issued No Objection Certificates (NOCs) to two new airlines, Al Hind Air and FlyExpress, this week, with Shankh Air having already received one. This move aims to boost competition and provide more choices for Indian flyers, following disruptions caused by IndiGo's schedule issues. The Aviation Ministry is encouraging new players in the rapidly growing Indian aviation market, despite industry concerns about high operating costs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:10:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ace4bedf7500b477173d9_1766510234717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metropolis Healthcare's Ameera Shah Reveals Secret to Margin Recovery &amp; Explosive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acd19edf7500b47717291</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acd19edf7500b47717291</guid><description>Metropolis Healthcare is outperforming rivals in India's organized diagnostics sector, driven by strong demand for preventive health packages and specialized tests. Promoter Ameera Shah expects continued revenue growth and margin recovery, despite a temporary drag from a past acquisition. The company plans strategic expansion through new collection centers and acquisitions to fuel its medium-term growth strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:54:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acd19edf7500b47717290_1766509965510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Exports to Sri Lanka SOAR 17%! Vehicles &amp; Ships Lead Massive Surge - Are You Invested?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acbcbedf7500b477171a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acbcbedf7500b477171a7</guid><description>India's exports to Sri Lanka surged by 17% year-on-year, reaching $3,364.49 million from April to November 2025. This significant growth was predominantly fueled by a remarkable 318% increase in vehicle exports and a 115% rise in ship exports. Other sectors like machinery, pharmaceuticals, and chemicals also contributed to this strong trade performance, highlighting India's expanding export footprint and robust economic ties with Sri Lanka.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acbcbedf7500b477171a6_1766509786237.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Next Tech Frontier: BYT Capital Launches ₹180 Crore Deep-Tech Fund Targeting Hardware Powerhouses!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acb05edf7500b477170e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acb05edf7500b477170e2</guid><description>BYT Capital has launched a ₹180-crore early-stage fund to invest in India's deep-tech sector, with a strong emphasis on hardware and foundational technologies. The fund, primarily backed by ultra-high-net-worth individuals and family offices, will support 18-20 startups over four years, focusing on areas like space-tech, robotics, life sciences, and clean energy. With 55% reserved for follow-on investments, BYT Capital aims to foster long-term growth, addressing a gap in growth-stage capital while signalling strong investor confidence in India's deep-tech future.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:53:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acb05edf7500b477170e1_1766509392387.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shyam Dhani IPO Crushes Expectations: 241x Subscribed on Day 2, GMP Rockets to 88%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acab5edf7500b47717041</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694acab5edf7500b47717041</guid><description>Rajasthan-based Shyam Dhani Industries' IPO is generating huge investor excitement, receiving an overwhelming 241 times subscription on its second day of bidding. The company aims to raise ₹38.48 crore through fresh issue of shares priced at ₹65-70. Grey market investors are equally bullish, with the grey market premium (GMP) surging to an impressive 88 percent, reflecting strong demand across retail, non-institutional, and institutional categories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:51:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694acab5edf7500b47717040_1766509342990.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto's Motorcycle Dominance Erodes as TVS and Hero Surge Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694aca11edf7500b47716f07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694aca11edf7500b47716f07</guid><description>Bajaj Auto is losing significant market share in its key motorcycle segments, particularly the 125cc and 150-250cc categories. Data shows Bajaj's overall motorcycle market share dropped from 18.5% in FY20 to 16.6% in FY25, further to 16% year-to-date FY26. Meanwhile, TVS Motor Company has seen its market share climb from 15.5% to nearly 19% in the same period, while Hero MotoCorp maintains its leading position. The 125cc segment, crucial for new buyers, sees TVS Motor significantly expanding its lead.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:45:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aca11edf7500b47716f06_1766509171550.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Poised for Manufacturing Boom? Samsung India Boss Reveals Major Shift Away From China!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac9ededf7500b47716ec3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac9ededf7500b47716ec3</guid><description>Samsung India's chief, JB Park, believes global brands are actively de-coupling from China for manufacturing, with India emerging as a prime destination. He cited India's Production Linked Incentive (PLI) schemes and its growing consumer market as key attractors. Park also highlighted India's strong engineering talent pool, crucial for global innovations in areas like semiconductors and AI, and noted Samsung India contributes significantly to global revenues, expecting this to grow. He also touched upon competition and the need to develop manpower proficient in automation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:41:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac9ededf7500b47716ec2_1766509239107.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Leap: Samsung Invests Billions, Joins PLI Scheme for Component Manufacturing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac40bedf7500b47716895</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac40bedf7500b47716895</guid><description>Samsung is significantly investing in India's Artificial Intelligence (AI) ecosystem and participating in the government's Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme for display modules. The company sees immense potential in India, aiming to transition its mass market offerings to premium. Samsung India has no immediate plans for an Initial Public Offering (IPO) on local stock exchanges. This strategic shift, particularly the focus on AI transformation over the next 30 years, leverages India's talent pool for global R&amp;D efforts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:16:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac40bedf7500b47716894_1766507829731.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JK Tyre's Bold Move: Cavendish Merger Unlocks Massive Growth Potential! See How!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac3c7edf7500b477167da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac3c7edf7500b477167da</guid><description>JK Tyre &amp; Industries has successfully completed the merger of its subsidiary, Cavendish Industries Ltd. This strategic integration aims to unlock significant value through enhanced operational synergies, economies of scale, a diversified product portfolio, and an expanded distribution network. Cavendish, acquired in 2016, manufactured truck/bus radial, truck/bus bias, and two/three-wheeler tires. Its capacity utilization has dramatically increased from 30% to 95% post-acquisition, contributing substantially to JK Tyre's overall operations. This merger reinforces JK Tyre's strategy of sustainable growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:16:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac3c7edf7500b477167d9_1766507662356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emerging Markets Shock: Are They Outperforming Due to Smart Policies or Just Pure Luck?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac40eedf7500b477168c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac40eedf7500b477168c0</guid><description>A recent IMF analysis revisits a 1993 paper, questioning the remarkable growth of emerging market economies (EMDEs), particularly in Asia. Despite global uncertainties like geopolitical tensions and trade wars, these regions show resilient and higher GDP growth compared to advanced economies. The IMF points to improved monetary and fiscal policy frameworks, including central bank independence and inflation targeting, as key drivers. However, the analysis prompts a deeper look, suggesting factors like global value chains and trade might also play significant roles beyond conventional economic policies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:13:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac40eedf7500b477168bf_1766507814446.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver ETFs Outshine Gold in 2025: Massive 137% Returns Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac2b2edf7500b47716657</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac2b2edf7500b47716657</guid><description>In 2025, Indian Silver ETFs delivered an astonishing 137% year-to-date return, nearly doubling the 73% gain from Gold ETFs. This surge was fueled by robust industrial demand, growing adoption in renewable energy, significant investor inflows, and supply constraints. The total Assets Under Management (AUM) for silver ETFs expanded sharply to ₹49,075 crore by November 2025, with trading volumes soaring by 560% due to increased participation from corporates and High Net Worth Individuals (HNIs). Nippon India Silver ETF led the market in liquidity and AUM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:13:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac2b2edf7500b47716656_1766507415677.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Unlocks Massive Value: Two Giants Set for Stock Market Debut!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac1bfedf7500b477164a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac1bfedf7500b477164a3</guid><description>Coal India's board has approved the in-principle listing of its two largest coal-producing subsidiaries, Mahanadi Coalfields and South Eastern Coalfields, following a directive from the Ministry of Coal. This strategic move aims to unlock value and provide investors with direct access to these key mining operations, building on previous IPO plans for other subsidiaries like CMPDI and BCCL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:13:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac1bfedf7500b477164a2_1766507405382.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sky's the Limit: Salesforce Partners Indian Drone Pioneer Garuda Aerospace for Global Expansion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac136edf7500b47716423</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ac136edf7500b47716423</guid><description>US tech giant Salesforce has partnered with Chennai-based Garuda Aerospace, an Indian drone manufacturer. The collaboration aims to revolutionize Garuda's customer lifecycle, streamline operations, and fuel its expansion into Southeast Asia and Africa using Salesforce's unified intelligent platform. This digital transformation will enhance customer relationships and drive business growth across agriculture, defense, and infrastructure sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:12:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ac136edf7500b47716422_1766507070652.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India's Bold Move: Board Approves Listing of Key Subsidiaries MCL &amp; SECL - What Investors Must Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694abed4edf7500b47716144</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694abed4edf7500b47716144</guid><description>Coal India Limited's Board of Directors has granted in-principle approval for the listing of its two major subsidiaries, Mahanadi Coalfields Limited (MCL) and South Eastern Coalfields Limited (SECL). This decision, following a directive from the Ministry of Coal, targets listing in the upcoming financial year 2027 and is contingent upon securing all necessary regulatory approvals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:53:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694abed4edf7500b47716143_1766506996395.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCS Q3 Earnings &amp; Dividend Alert! Key Dates for Investors Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694abe11edf7500b47715fde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694abe11edf7500b47715fde</guid><description>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) has announced its board meeting schedule for January 12, 2026, to approve its Q3 FY26 financial results. Investors will also be watching for the potential declaration of a third interim dividend, with a record date set for January 17, 2026. The company last reported a 1.4% profit rise in Q2 FY26.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:53:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694abe11edf7500b47715fdd_1766506579442.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Lands Big US Deal: Eye Drug NUFYMCO Set for US Launch! See What It Means for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694abeb4edf7500b477160e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694abeb4edf7500b477160e1</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences has partnered with Swiss company Bioeq AG to market NUFYMCO, an interchangeable biosimilar for macular degeneration treatment, in the United States. Zydus Lifesciences Global FZE will handle US commercialization, while Bioeq manages development and manufacturing. The drug, NUFYMCO, received US FDA approval on December 18, 2025, for treating conditions like wet age-related macular degeneration and diabetic macular edema. This collaboration expands Zydus's US biosimilar portfolio.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:53:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694abeb4edf7500b477160e0_1766506276768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump's Tariff Triumph? 4.3% US GDP Soars, But Inflation Fears Linger!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694abe33edf7500b4771600e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694abe33edf7500b4771600e</guid><description>US President Donald Trump attributed the nation's stronger-than-expected 4.3% third-quarter GDP growth to his administration's tariff policies, dismissing inflation concerns. While Trump hailed the economic figures as "GREAT USA Economic Numbers," economists expressed caution, pointing to a "K-shaped" economy where benefits are unevenly distributed and consumer spending shows signs of slowing. Analysts warn that rising import duties contribute to higher living costs for many, and potential government shutdowns add further economic uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:53:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694abe33edf7500b4771600d_1766506661716.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal Auction Frenzy: Ministry Opens 14th Round, 49 Bids Pour In for 24 Blocks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694abb4eedf7500b47715c2e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694abb4eedf7500b47715c2e</guid><description>The Ministry of Coal has initiated the 14th round of commercial coal block auctions, receiving a robust 49 bids for 24 out of the 41 blocks offered. Eleven companies, including five new entrants, participated, signaling strong industry confidence in India's coal mining framework and energy security initiatives. Bids will now undergo technical evaluation before an electronic auction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:46:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694abb4eedf7500b47715c2d_1766505433670.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIFT City Shocker: IFSCA Unlocks Huge Opportunities for Fund Managers &amp; Global Firms - New Rules Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab7662a8fb21531f30663</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab7662a8fb21531f30663</guid><description>The International Financial Services Centres Authority (IFSCA) has significantly eased norms for fund management entities in India's GIFT City. Key changes include relaxed eligibility for key personnel and more flexible fundraising timelines. IFSCA also unveiled new, more accommodating regulations for Global In-House Centres (GICs), aiming to bolster GIFT City's position as a global financial hub and attract more international business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:23:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ab7662a8fb21531f30662_1766506430176.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metropolis Healthcare CEO Ameera Shah's Masterplan: Margin Recovery &amp; Expansion Secrets REVEALED!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab65e2a8fb21531f304ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab65e2a8fb21531f304ce</guid><description>Metropolis Healthcare CEO Ameera Shah detailed the company's growth strategy, focusing on margin recovery through expansion, cross-selling, and disciplined pricing. Organized diagnostic players are outperforming unorganized ones due to improving profitability and demand for bundled health tests. Metropolis aims to increase revenue from health packages to 25% in 18 months and plans to open around 300 new collection centers, expecting gradual maturation over four years. The company is also turning around its acquired Core Diagnostics business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:22:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ab65e2a8fb21531f304cd_1766505969284.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric's Secret Weapon: ₹100 Crore Boost for Battery Tech!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab5432a8fb21531f303a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab5432a8fb21531f303a5</guid><description>Ola Electric's subsidiary, Ola Electric Technologies Private Limited, has approved a ₹100 crore investment through Optionally Convertible Redeemable Preference Shares. This is the third tranche of funding from IPO proceeds, earmarked for developing its battery technology. The infusion is into Ola Cell Technologies Private Limited, another wholly owned subsidiary.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:22:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ab5432a8fb21531f303a4_1766505827195.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance &amp; Axis Energy Battle for India's Future Energy: Coal Block Bids Heat Up!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab4dd2a8fb21531f3027d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab4dd2a8fb21531f3027d</guid><description>Reliance Industries and Axis Energy Ventures India are leading bidders in the central government's coal block auctions, aimed at boosting domestic coal gasification and cleaner energy production. Both companies jointly bid for multiple coal blocks across states like Odisha, Chhattisgarh, and Andhra Pradesh, demonstrating strong strategic interest in gasification and downstream applications. This participation highlights growing private sector confidence in India's coal gasification policy and the nation's energy demand outlook.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:16:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ab4dd2a8fb21531f3027c_1766503867817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Finance Set to Double Value: Rs 40,000 Crore MUFG Deal Sparks Growth Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab4682a8fb21531f30190</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab4682a8fb21531f30190</guid><description>Shriram Finance is poised to more than double its valuation in three-and-a-half years following a strategic partnership with Japan's Mitsubishi UFJ Financial Group (MUFG). The deal involves a nearly Rs 40,000 crore ($4.4 billion) infusion aimed at strengthening capital, reducing borrowing costs, and accelerating expansion. With MUFG's backing, Shriram Finance has raised its annual growth target to 18-20%, projecting substantial growth in Assets Under Management (AUM). The partnership is expected to finalize before March FY2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:14:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ab4682a8fb21531f3018f_1766505612816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE Bans Brokers from Distributing Loans: Investor Alert Issued!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab3822a8fb21531f2ff7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab3822a8fb21531f2ff7b</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange of India has prohibited stock brokers, including those registered as research analysts, from distributing third-party banking loan products. This measure aims to ensure brokers focus on SEBI-regulated activities and reduce market leverage risks. Industry leaders have welcomed the clarification as a positive step for market integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:12:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ab3822a8fb21531f2ff7a_1766503383133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samsung India Eyes Double-Digit Growth by 2026 Fueled by GST Cuts, Defying Economic Headwinds!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab4332a8fb21531f30134</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab4332a8fb21531f30134</guid><description>Samsung India experienced a significant boost in sales during the festive season, largely attributed to government GST rate reductions making air conditioners and large LED TVs more accessible. The company is targeting double-digit growth in 2026, despite facing challenges from a weakening rupee and inflationary pressures that are expected to dampen the broader consumer electronics industry. Samsung India confirmed it is not pursuing an IPO and highlighted the nation's increasing importance in global innovation through its R&amp;D centers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:12:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ab4332a8fb21531f30133_1766505459589.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Unleashes Rs 2.9 Lakh Crore Liquidity Boost: What it Means for Your Money!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab31b2a8fb21531f2ff05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab31b2a8fb21531f2ff05</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is set to inject a massive Rs 290,000 crore ($32 billion) into the banking system over the next month. This will be achieved through open market operation (OMO) purchase auctions of government securities and a US dollar-rupee buy-sell swap auction. The move aims to manage liquidity, potentially lower interest rates, and encourage credit offtake, supporting economic activity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:11:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ab31b2a8fb21531f2ff04_1766503318807.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FirstCry's Parent Company Acquires Hygiene Business in Rs 58 Crore Deal! Deeper Dive into New Segment?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab3852a8fb21531f2ffaa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab3852a8fb21531f2ffaa</guid><description>Brainbees Solutions, the parent company of popular online retailer FirstCry, is expanding its hygiene product offerings by acquiring KA Hygiene for Rs 57.74 crore. The deal, structured as a share swap, will make KA Hygiene a wholly owned subsidiary. This strategic move aims to strengthen Brainbees' presence in the growing hygiene market, complementing its core baby care business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rupee Pressure Eases? RBI Pumps ₹3 Trillion into Banks Amid Forex Woes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab1892a8fb21531f2fc5e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab1892a8fb21531f2fc5e</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is injecting nearly ₹3 trillion into the banking system via open market operations (OMOs) and a $10 billion USD/INR buy-sell swap. This significant liquidity boost aims to counter funds drained by recent foreign exchange interventions to support the rupee and address seasonal demands like advance tax payments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:53:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ab1892a8fb21531f2fc5d_1766502876040.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Study: Gold Remains Fortress of Stability Amidst Global Chaos, Oil Faces Whiplash!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab08d2a8fb21531f2faaa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab08d2a8fb21531f2faaa</guid><description>A Reserve Bank of India staff study reveals gold is the most stable asset during geopolitical crises, offering a safe haven. Crude oil, however, is the most sensitive to regional conflicts and sanctions, experiencing significant volatility. Silver and U.S. Treasury securities show intermediate reactions, providing a nuanced view for investors navigating global uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:52:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ab08d2a8fb21531f2faa9_1766503058802.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Tomorrow: Expert Forecast Reveals Key Support &amp; Resistance Levels - Will the Rally Continue?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab0352a8fb21531f2f9dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694ab0352a8fb21531f2f9dc</guid><description>Indian stock market indices, Nifty and Sensex, closed flat on December 23rd with profit-taking in IT and pharma sectors. Nifty gained 4.75 points to 26,177.15, while Sensex dipped slightly. The India VIX fell over 3%. Experts predict consolidation after a recent rally, with Nifty finding support around 25,950-26,050 and resistance near 26,300, suggesting a potential continuation of the uptrend with a buy-on-dips strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:52:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ab0352a8fb21531f2f9db_1766502838533.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel Secures Full Control of Tata BlueScope: CCI Approves Landmark Acquisition!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694aafc22a8fb21531f2f947</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694aafc22a8fb21531f2f947</guid><description>The Competition Commission of India (CCI) has approved Tata Steel Limited's proposal to acquire full ownership of Tata BlueScope Steel Private Ltd. This acquisition ends the 50:50 joint venture with BlueScope Steel Asia Holdings and grants Tata Steel sole control, significantly strengthening its position in the value-added and downstream steel products market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:52:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aafc22a8fb21531f2f946_1766505335605.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emcure Pharma's Gujarat Plant Gets US FDA 'Clean Chit': Major Boost for Exports?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694aae542a8fb21531f2f667</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/694aae542a8fb21531f2f667</guid><description>Emcure Pharmaceuticals announced its Gujarat manufacturing facility received a 'No Action Indicated' report from the US FDA after a recent inspection. This signifies the plant meets stringent regulatory standards, bolstering confidence in its export capabilities and compliance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:52:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aae542a8fb21531f2f666_1766502046652.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>