<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:53:34 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Jalans Launch Takeover Bid for Shah Foods Amidst Deep Financial Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Jalans-Launch-Takeover-Bid-for-Shah-Foods-Amidst-Deep-Financial-Woes/69940df6cffb93b3e927bc5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Jalans-Launch-Takeover-Bid-for-Shah-Foods-Amidst-Deep-Financial-Woes/69940df6cffb93b3e927bc5a</guid><description>Mr. Ankit Jalan and Mr. Anuj Jalan are launching an open offer to acquire up to 26% of Shah Foods Limited at ₹62.50 per share, aiming for management control. The company faces severe financial distress, with a persistent negative net worth and highly erratic revenue figures, including zero revenue reported for two fiscal years and the recent nine-month period. This move follows a preferential allotment and share purchase agreement by the acquirers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:43:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940df6cffb93b3e927bc59_1771310698148.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>N R Agarwal Promoters Pledge 73% Shares for Loans</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/N-R-Agarwal-Promoters-Pledge-73percent-Shares-for-Loans/69940d7ecffb93b3e927bbee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/N-R-Agarwal-Promoters-Pledge-73percent-Shares-for-Loans/69940d7ecffb93b3e927bbee</guid><description>Promoters of N R Agarwal Industries Limited have disclosed encumbrancing a significant 73.55% of their shareholding, which amounts to 1,25,16,998 shares. This pledge, primarily in favour of SBICAP Trustee Company Limited and Axis Bank Limited, is to secure term loans for the company. Such a high percentage of pledged shares raises governance concerns and increases financial risk for investors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:41:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940d7ecffb93b3e927bbed_1771310569062.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Supply Chain Turns Profitable, Boosts Margins Amid Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/TVS-Supply-Chain-Turns-Profitable-Boosts-Margins-Amid-Acquisition/69940c93cffb93b3e927bb38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/TVS-Supply-Chain-Turns-Profitable-Boosts-Margins-Amid-Acquisition/69940c93cffb93b3e927bb38</guid><description>TVS Supply Chain Solutions has reported a strong turnaround in its third quarter results, swinging to profitability and achieving significant margin expansion. The company also announced a strategic acquisition, enhancing its capabilities in the FMCG sector. The results reflect improved operational execution and strategic initiatives aimed at profitable growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:37:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940c93cffb93b3e927bb37_1771310327326.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Senores Pharma Promoter Group Pledges Shares, Investor Alert Issued</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Senores-Pharma-Promoter-Group-Pledges-Shares-Investor-Alert-Issued/69940c16cffb93b3e927baa8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Senores-Pharma-Promoter-Group-Pledges-Shares-Investor-Alert-Issued/69940c16cffb93b3e927baa8</guid><description>Senores Pharmaceuticals Limited announced that its promoter group, Espee Therapeutics LLP, has pledged 4,00,000 equity shares. This move raises concerns among investors, especially given the company's history of related-party transactions and past regulatory issues. The pledge signifies promoters using their shares as collateral for loans, potentially impacting shareholding structure and market sentiment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:35:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940c16cffb93b3e927baa7_1771310212190.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Patels Launch ₹34 Cr Open Offer for Western Ministil at ₹10 Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Patels-Launch-34-Cr-Open-Offer-for-Western-Ministil-at-10-Share/69940c16cffb93b3e927ba92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Patels-Launch-34-Cr-Open-Offer-for-Western-Ministil-at-10-Share/69940c16cffb93b3e927ba92</guid><description>Mr. Kalpesh Patel and Mrs. Vandana Patel have officially launched an open offer to acquire up to 26% of Western Ministil Limited's expanded equity capital at ₹10.00 per share. This move, backed by a ₹34 crore escrow deposit, follows their appointment to the company's board and aims to revitalize the dormant, loss-making entity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:35:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940c16cffb93b3e927ba91_1771310272670.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Polyplex Q3 Revenue Surges 27%, But Profit Pressure Mounts Amid Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Polyplex-Q3-Revenue-Surges-27percent-But-Profit-Pressure-Mounts-Amid-Global-Headwinds/69940b28cffb93b3e927b9bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Polyplex-Q3-Revenue-Surges-27percent-But-Profit-Pressure-Mounts-Amid-Global-Headwinds/69940b28cffb93b3e927b9bb</guid><description>Polyplex Corporation Limited reported a strong 27% year-on-year revenue growth in Q3 FY26, reaching ₹1,680 Crores. However, the company's year-to-date (YTD) profit before minority interest saw a drastic fall of 99% to ₹3 Crores, down from ₹363 Crores in the prior year. This performance was impacted by softer demand in industrial films, global overcapacity leading to pricing pressure, and higher operational costs, alongside foreign exchange losses.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940b28cffb93b3e927b9ba_1771309971184.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindustan Foods Delivers Record Profit, Sets Ambitious FY27 Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindustan-Foods-Delivers-Record-Profit-Sets-Ambitious-FY27-Target/69940ab2cffb93b3e927b908</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindustan-Foods-Delivers-Record-Profit-Sets-Ambitious-FY27-Target/69940ab2cffb93b3e927b908</guid><description>Hindustan Foods Limited (HFL) reported its best-ever quarterly EBITDA and PAT for Q3 FY26, with total income rising 13% year-on-year to ₹1,000 Cr and PAT growing 26% to ₹36 Cr. The company has guided for FY27 PAT between ₹200-220 Cr, signaling aggressive growth plans driven by diversification, M&amp;A, and significant capital expenditure. While growth is strong, investors note past regulatory compliance issues and potential GST impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:29:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69940ab2cffb93b3e927b907.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Rebound: AI Fears Spark Undervaluation, Analysts See Value</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Rebound-AI-Fears-Spark-Undervaluation-Analysts-See-Value/69940a44cffb93b3e927b838</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Rebound-AI-Fears-Spark-Undervaluation-Analysts-See-Value/69940a44cffb93b3e927b838</guid><description>The Indian IT sector, after shedding nearly ₹5 trillion in market value due to AI-driven investor fears, is showing signs of a technical rebound and potential undervaluation. While concerns persist about AI's disruptive potential, a strategic shift towards AI-centric services and new deal pipelines is creating opportunities. Key players like Infosys and TCS are trading at lower P/E multiples than historical averages, presenting an attractive entry point for value investors, though a forensic look reveals persistent risks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:27:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940a44cffb93b3e927b837_1771309754314.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Equities: Earnings Jitters Amidst Rich Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Earnings-Jitters-Amidst-Rich-Valuations/69940a3dcffb93b3e927b821</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Earnings-Jitters-Amidst-Rich-Valuations/69940a3dcffb93b3e927b821</guid><description>Despite a strong Q3FY26 earnings season for the Nifty50, which saw net income rise 9.8%, analysts are flagging a growing disconnect. Forward earnings estimates are being revised downwards across numerous sectors, juxtaposed against elevated market valuations. The Nifty 50 trades at a Price-to-Earnings (P/E) ratio of approximately 22-23.5x, a premium compared to emerging market peers and historical averages. This suggests that retail investor enthusiasm and expectations of an earnings rebound may be outstripping a more cautious outlook for future profitability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:27:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940a3dcffb93b3e927b820_1771309758348.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Newgen Software Rebounds Sharply from 52-Week Low</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Newgen-Software-Rebounds-Sharply-from-52-Week-Low/69940a38cffb93b3e927b7fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Newgen-Software-Rebounds-Sharply-from-52-Week-Low/69940a38cffb93b3e927b7fa</guid><description>Newgen Software Technologies surged 12.9% on February 17, 2026, on heavy volume, recovering from a 52-week low. This rebound occurred despite recent disappointing Q3 FY26 earnings, which saw net profit decline 29.4% YoY due to operational costs and a one-time charge. Analysts maintain optimism with a consensus 'Buy' rating and substantial upside targets, viewing the current valuation as attractive relative to historical performance, even as the broader Indian IT sector grapples with AI-driven disruptions and valuation resets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:27:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940a38cffb93b3e927b7f9_1771309785952.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supreme Court Judicial Scrutiny Signals Governance Risk for Yadav Case</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Supreme-Court-Judicial-Scrutiny-Signals-Governance-Risk-for-Yadav-Case/69940949cffb93b3e927b71d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Supreme-Court-Judicial-Scrutiny-Signals-Governance-Risk-for-Yadav-Case/69940949cffb93b3e927b71d</guid><description>The Supreme Court's review of Lalu Prasad Yadav's bail in the Deoghar fodder scam case has escalated into a broader judicial examination of sentence suspension legality for convicted individuals. Justices noted the advanced age of accused and remarked on the questionable basis for release, indicating a potential shift towards stricter oversight. This, coupled with systemic judicial delays, underscores significant governance risks and prolonged legal uncertainty, impacting investor confidence in sectors prone to corruption. The case, involving embezzlement totaling hundreds of millions, highlights the persistent challenges of corruption and judicial efficiency in India.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:23:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69940949cffb93b3e927b71c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHIT Acquires ₹6,220 Cr Highway Assets, Bolstering Infrastructure Portfolio</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NHIT-Acquires-6220-Cr-Highway-Assets-Bolstering-Infrastructure-Portfolio/69940846cffb93b3e927b5ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NHIT-Acquires-6220-Cr-Highway-Assets-Bolstering-Infrastructure-Portfolio/69940846cffb93b3e927b5ca</guid><description>National Highways Infra Trust (NHIT) has acquired two significant highway sections totaling 310 kilometers in Maharashtra and Andhra Pradesh for ₹6,220.90 crore. This move increases NHIT's total monetized asset value to ₹49,858 crore. The transaction underscores NHIT's role as a key vehicle for asset monetization within India's burgeoning infrastructure sector, channeling capital from marquee investors into essential road networks. NHIT's current market capitalization hovers around ₹29,000 crore, with units trading near ₹152.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:18:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69940846cffb93b3e927b5c9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Divide Sparks Market Divergence: Infrastructure Surges, Software Sinks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Divide-Sparks-Market-Divergence-Infrastructure-Surges-Software-Sinks/699407e7cffb93b3e927b541</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Divide-Sparks-Market-Divergence-Infrastructure-Surges-Software-Sinks/699407e7cffb93b3e927b541</guid><description>U.S. equity futures dipped as markets reopened, mirroring global weakness driven by geopolitical tensions and cautious anticipation of Federal Reserve signals. The dominant market force remains the accelerating "AI scare trade," which is creating a pronounced bifurcation. Companies developing AI infrastructure are experiencing strong demand and investment, while software and service providers facing direct automation threats are under intense pressure. This dynamic is reshaping sector valuations and driving distinct institutional strategies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:17:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699407e7cffb93b3e927b540.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pyramid Technoplast Posts Lower Profit Despite Revenue Growth, Focus on New Plants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pyramid-Technoplast-Posts-Lower-Profit-Despite-Revenue-Growth-Focus-on-New-Plants/699407e1cffb93b3e927b528</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pyramid-Technoplast-Posts-Lower-Profit-Despite-Revenue-Growth-Focus-on-New-Plants/699407e1cffb93b3e927b528</guid><description>Pyramid Technoplast reported flat revenue of ₹162.16 Cr for Q3 FY26, with net profit declining 29% YoY to ₹4.8 Cr due to higher expenses and one-offs. However, the company sees growth drivers in its new solar, recycling, and WADA plants, aiming for improved margins and ₹800 Cr revenue by FY27.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699407e1cffb93b3e927b527_1771309127724.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dharani Sugars Profit Tanks 43% Amidst Revenue Fall</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Dharani-Sugars-Profit-Tanks-43percent-Amidst-Revenue-Fall/699406f4cffb93b3e927b3ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Dharani-Sugars-Profit-Tanks-43percent-Amidst-Revenue-Fall/699406f4cffb93b3e927b3ba</guid><description>Dharani Sugars and Chemicals Limited reported a steep fall in its financial performance for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Quarterly revenue dropped 24.03% year-on-year to ₹265.85 Cr, while profit after tax (PAT) tumbled 43.45% to ₹160.33 Cr. The nine-month period also saw a decline in revenue by 13.34% and PAT by 4.68%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:13:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699406f4cffb93b3e927b3b9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cybele Industries Posts Huge Profit Turnaround, Fueled by 'Other Income'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cybele-Industries-Posts-Huge-Profit-Turnaround-Fueled-by-Other-Income/699406f1cffb93b3e927b3a4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cybele-Industries-Posts-Huge-Profit-Turnaround-Fueled-by-Other-Income/699406f1cffb93b3e927b3a4</guid><description>Cybele Industries Limited announced a spectacular turnaround in its Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated net profit soaring to ₹6.16 Cr from a loss of ₹2.02 Cr a year ago. Revenue also jumped by over 143% YoY. A substantial rise in 'Other Income' was the primary driver, while its Real Estate segment turned profitable, offsetting losses in the Cables business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:13:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699406f1cffb93b3e927b3a3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godawari Power Rating Upgraded to Positive Outlook by CRISIL</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Rating-Upgraded-to-Positive-Outlook-by-CRISIL/699406efcffb93b3e927b38e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Rating-Upgraded-to-Positive-Outlook-by-CRISIL/699406efcffb93b3e927b38e</guid><description>CRISIL Ratings has upgraded Godawari Power &amp; Ispat Limited's credit outlook to 'Positive' from 'Stable', while reaffirming its 'CRISIL AA-' rating for long-term facilities and 'CRISIL A1+' for short-term ones. This favourable revision signals confidence in the company's future financial strength, supported by its robust performance and strategic expansion initiatives.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:13:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699406efcffb93b3e927b38d_1771308894385.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DhanSafal Finserve Q3 Profit Soars 185% on Loan Growth Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/DhanSafal-Finserve-Q3-Profit-Soars-185percent-on-Loan-Growth-Surge/69940691cffb93b3e927b2f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/DhanSafal-Finserve-Q3-Profit-Soars-185percent-on-Loan-Growth-Surge/69940691cffb93b3e927b2f0</guid><description>DhanSafal Finserve Limited, formerly Luharuka Media &amp; Infra, posted a strong third quarter with Assets Under Management (AUM) soaring 141% year-on-year to ₹80.46 crore and revenue from operations jumping 185% to ₹8.59 crore. The NBFC is actively expanding its presence across four states and focusing on secured MSME and retail loans.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:11:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940691cffb93b3e927b2ef_1771308793469.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Navigates Geopolitics Amidst ETF Surge and Inventory Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Navigates-Geopolitics-Amidst-ETF-Surge-and-Inventory-Squeeze/69940687cffb93b3e927b2da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Navigates-Geopolitics-Amidst-ETF-Surge-and-Inventory-Squeeze/69940687cffb93b3e927b2da</guid><description>Gold prices remain volatile, caught between escalating geopolitical tensions and mixed economic indicators. Investors are closely watching a divergence between increasing gold ETF holdings and critically low COMEX registered inventories. Simultaneously, regulatory crackdowns in China on dubious gold trading schemes add complexity to the precious metal's near-term outlook, potentially influencing physical market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:11:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940687cffb93b3e927b2d9_1771308804762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India: Dividends &amp; Diversification Mask Operational Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Dividends-and-Diversification-Mask-Operational-Slump/69940514cffb93b3e927b1f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Dividends-and-Diversification-Mask-Operational-Slump/69940514cffb93b3e927b1f3</guid><description>Coal India Limited reported a 16% net profit drop in Q3 FY26, driven by lower volumes and realizations, compounded by a one-time provision. Despite operational pressures and falling EBITDA margins, the company's strategic push into renewables and critical minerals, alongside a robust dividend yield approaching 7%, offers a complex valuation narrative. The stock trades at approximately 7.2 times FY28 estimated earnings, reflecting a discount compared to peers, as analysts remain cautiously divided on its near-term outlook amidst a challenging energy transition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:05:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940514cffb93b3e927b1f2_1771308455682.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys Taps Anthropic Amid China AI Surge &amp; IT Sector AI Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Taps-Anthropic-Amid-China-AI-Surge-and-IT-Sector-AI-Fears/699403bdcffb93b3e927b06f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Taps-Anthropic-Amid-China-AI-Surge-and-IT-Sector-AI-Fears/699403bdcffb93b3e927b06f</guid><description>Infosys shares saw a modest 3% gain following a strategic collaboration with AI firm Anthropic to develop advanced enterprise AI solutions, leveraging Claude models. This move occurs as China's AI advancements are increasingly seen as a challenge to US tech dominance, potentially creating a global 'tech shock.' Meanwhile, the broader Indian IT sector experienced significant volatility, losing an estimated $56 billion in market value due to investor concerns about AI-driven automation disrupting traditional service models and compressing margins. Analysts remain divided on the sector's prospects, with some seeing long-term opportunities in AI integration, while others highlight immediate risks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:59:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699403bdcffb93b3e927b06e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NRI Capital Shifts: Beyond Deposits to Riskier Alphas</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NRI-Capital-Shifts-Beyond-Deposits-to-Riskier-Alphas/699403a1cffb93b3e927b013</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NRI-Capital-Shifts-Beyond-Deposits-to-Riskier-Alphas/699403a1cffb93b3e927b013</guid><description>Non-resident Indians (NRIs) are reallocating substantial capital away from traditional deposit schemes, favoring investments in real estate and alternative investment funds (AIFs), particularly Category III funds. This strategic pivot, facilitated by enhanced access through GIFT City, signals a growing appetite for yield and alpha, despite increased risk exposure. While overall remittances remain strong, the pronounced decline in deposit inflows underscores a maturing NRI investor base actively seeking growth opportunities beyond fixed incomes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:58:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699403a1cffb93b3e927b012_1771308123949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T Nears ₹6 Trillion Market Cap on Divestment, Order Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-Nears-6-Trillion-Market-Cap-on-Divestment-Order-Surge/69940369cffb93b3e927afca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-Nears-6-Trillion-Market-Cap-on-Divestment-Order-Surge/69940369cffb93b3e927afca</guid><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T) is nearing a ₹6 trillion market capitalization, propelled by a 10% stock rally over the past month and the strategic divestment of Nabha Power Ltd. for ₹3,660.87 crore. This move aligns with L&amp;T's strategy to exit non-core assets and redeploy capital into higher-return EPC and engineering segments. The company boasts a record order backlog of ₹7.33 trillion and a robust near-term pipeline of ₹5.9 trillion, positioning it to benefit from India's infrastructure boom.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:58:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940369cffb93b3e927afc9_1771308084948.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks: Capex Bulls, EV Hype, and Regulatory Winds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Stocks-Capex-Bulls-EV-Hype-and-Regulatory-Winds/69940352cffb93b3e927af89</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Stocks-Capex-Bulls-EV-Hype-and-Regulatory-Winds/69940352cffb93b3e927af89</guid><description>Marketsmith India, through its Director of Research Mayuresh Joshi, is strategically underweighting emerging ventures like Ola Electric, preferring established infrastructure giant Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T) and asset manager HDFC AMC, which are poised to benefit from India's capital expenditure cycle and rising market participation, respectively. Concurrently, the firm maintains a watchful eye on ITC's expansion strategies and acknowledges the disruptive potential of AI in the IT sector. This is against a backdrop of heightened regulatory scrutiny on market speculation, exemplified by the RBI's new stringent lending norms for capital market intermediaries, which could reshape trading dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:57:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940352cffb93b3e927af88_1771307994475.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Subex Limited Posts Steady Q3 Recovery, Boosted by AI Focus and Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Subex-Limited-Posts-Steady-Q3-Recovery-Boosted-by-AI-Focus-and-Revenue-Growth/699402b8cffb93b3e927ae6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Subex-Limited-Posts-Steady-Q3-Recovery-Boosted-by-AI-Focus-and-Revenue-Growth/699402b8cffb93b3e927ae6d</guid><description>Subex Limited has reported a positive Q3 FY26, showcasing a steady recovery with revenue growth of 2.7% QoQ to ₹70.79 Crores. The company saw a significant jump in normalized PAT to ₹7.68 Crores. Management highlighted strong focus on AI, including its FraudZap product, and expressed confidence in achieving double-digit revenue growth in the upcoming fiscal year, marking a strategic shift towards an AI-native operating model.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:55:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699402b8cffb93b3e927ae6c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys Unveils AI Dominance Strategy with Topaz, Eyes $400 Billion Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Unveils-AI-Dominance-Strategy-with-Topaz-Eyes-400-Billion-Market/69940260cffb93b3e927ad58</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Unveils-AI-Dominance-Strategy-with-Topaz-Eyes-400-Billion-Market/69940260cffb93b3e927ad58</guid><description>Infosys held its AI Day on February 17, 2026, detailing its aggressive "AI First" strategy centered around its Infosys Topaz Fabric platform. The tech giant aims to capture a significant share of the projected $300-$400 billion AI services market by 2030, focusing on driving client value through AI-led innovation and efficiency. The company highlighted its progress with over 500 AI agents deployed and engagements with 90% of its top clients, positioning itself as a leader in the rapidly evolving AI landscape.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:53:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940260cffb93b3e927ad57_1771307785518.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VIP Industries: Discounting Woes Mask Asset Sale Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VIP-Industries-Discounting-Woes-Mask-Asset-Sale-Gains/6994024acffb93b3e927ad26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VIP-Industries-Discounting-Woes-Mask-Asset-Sale-Gains/6994024acffb93b3e927ad26</guid><description>VIP Industries posted a 9.4% revenue decline in Q3 FY26, driven by aggressive discounting and heightened competition. While the company booked an exceptional gain from asset sales and aims to strengthen its balance sheet, persistent losses and negative returns highlight ongoing operational headwinds. Despite a 'BUY' recommendation and a target price of INR 475 from Motilal Oswal, a nuanced view is warranted given the challenging competitive environment and historical profitability concerns.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:53:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994024acffb93b3e927ad25.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Neysa Secures $1.2B for AI GPUs Amidst Intense Indian Data Center Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Neysa-Secures-12B-for-AI-GPUs-Amidst-Intense-Indian-Data-Center-Race/69940245cffb93b3e927ad0f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Neysa-Secures-12B-for-AI-GPUs-Amidst-Intense-Indian-Data-Center-Race/69940245cffb93b3e927ad0f</guid><description>AI cloud startup Neysa has secured $1.2 billion in funding, led by Blackstone, to aggressively expand its GPU infrastructure, targeting 20,000 units within 18 months. This capital infusion aims to capitalize on India's burgeoning AI demand and leverage significant government incentives, including a tax holiday until 2047. However, Neysa enters a hyper-competitive landscape where global hyperscalers and established Indian players are undertaking massive capacity expansions, raising critical questions about market saturation and execution risk.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:53:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940245cffb93b3e927ad0e_1771307723430.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Astra Microwave: Margin Boost Masks Rising Debt, Stretched Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Astra-Microwave-Margin-Boost-Masks-Rising-Debt-Stretched-Valuation/69940245cffb93b3e927acf8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Astra-Microwave-Margin-Boost-Masks-Rising-Debt-Stretched-Valuation/69940245cffb93b3e927acf8</guid><description>Astra Microwave Products (ASTRA) reported strong 3QFY26 results, driven by better-than-expected margins and robust order inflows totaling INR 4.7 billion. The company anticipates further bolstering its order book by INR 5-6 billion in 4QFY26. Despite positive projections for the defense sector, ASTRA faces increased consolidated borrowings, now at INR 423 Cr, and its Price-to-Earnings (P/E) ratio of approximately 54x places it at a premium compared to some key industry players. While analysts maintain a 'BUY' consensus, the sustainability of margin expansion amidst rising debt and the execution of large, lumpy defense contracts warrants close scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:53:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69940245cffb93b3e927acf7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Uniparts India Surges on 35% Revenue Growth and Strong Profitability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Uniparts-India-Surges-on-35percent-Revenue-Growth-and-Strong-Profitability/6994023fcffb93b3e927ace1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Uniparts-India-Surges-on-35percent-Revenue-Growth-and-Strong-Profitability/6994023fcffb93b3e927ace1</guid><description>Uniparts India reported a strong Q3 FY26, with revenue soaring 35% year-on-year to ₹281 crore and net profit leaping 74% to ₹33 crore. The company achieved an EBITDA margin of 21.5% and maintains a net cash position, signaling robust financial health. Management is optimistic, guiding for mid-teens growth in FY26 and FY27 and confidence in sustaining 20% EBITDA margins.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:53:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994023fcffb93b3e927ace0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Court: PSU Financial Woes Can't Block Resignations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Court-PSU-Financial-Woes-Cant-Block-Resignations/699401c9cffb93b3e927abca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Court-PSU-Financial-Woes-Cant-Block-Resignations/699401c9cffb93b3e927abca</guid><description>The Kerala High Court has ruled that an employer, including a State Public Sector Undertaking, cannot deny an employee's resignation based on financial hardship. The court equated forcing an employee to continue service against their will to 'bonded labour,' a violation of Article 23 of the Indian Constitution. This decision, stemming from a Company Secretary's dispute with Traco Cable Company Limited over rejected resignation and unpaid salaries, sets a critical precedent for employee autonomy even amidst corporate financial distress.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699401c9cffb93b3e927abc9_1771307610696.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kellton Tech Sees Q3 Profit Rise, Bets Big on AI For Future Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kellton-Tech-Sees-Q3-Profit-Rise-Bets-Big-on-AI-For-Future-Growth/699401c7cffb93b3e927abaa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kellton-Tech-Sees-Q3-Profit-Rise-Bets-Big-on-AI-For-Future-Growth/699401c7cffb93b3e927abaa</guid><description>Kellton Tech reported a strong Q3 FY26 with revenue up 2.7% QoQ and PAT up 5.8%. For the nine months, revenue grew 11.4% YoY. The company is heavily investing in AI for operational efficiencies, expecting significant gains, and also boosted its ServiceNow capabilities via the Kumori Technologies acquisition, positioning for future growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:51:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699401c7cffb93b3e927aba9_1771307576745.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI in India's Grid: Opportunity Meets Implementation Hurdle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/AI-in-Indias-Grid-Opportunity-Meets-Implementation-Hurdle/69940155cffb93b3e927aa92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/AI-in-Indias-Grid-Opportunity-Meets-Implementation-Hurdle/69940155cffb93b3e927aa92</guid><description>An International Energy Agency (IEA) expert highlighted AI's potential to manage the escalating complexity in India's power sector, driven by rising electrification and variable renewables. However, the practical implementation of AI solutions faces substantial hurdles in India. These include critical gaps in data infrastructure, the need for significant investment in grid modernization, challenges in cybersecurity, and a pronounced shortage of skilled AI talent. While AI promises enhanced forecasting and automation, its efficacy is contingent upon addressing these foundational issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:49:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69940155cffb93b3e927aa91_1771307475558.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Batliboi Surges on Strong Q3 Profit Turnaround, Eyes FY27 Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Batliboi-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-Turnaround-Eyes-FY27-Boom/6994014ecffb93b3e927aa7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Batliboi-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-Turnaround-Eyes-FY27-Boom/6994014ecffb93b3e927aa7b</guid><description>Batliboi Limited reported a robust third quarter for FY26, with revenue jumping 30% year-on-year to ₹124 Crores and EBITDA nearly tripling. Profit Before Tax (PBT) before exceptional items showed a significant turnaround, rising to ₹5 Crores from ₹0.85 Crores in the prior year. The company expressed optimism for the capital goods sector, highlighting completed Capex and the launch of a new subsidiary focused on zero liquid discharge solutions, projecting a strong FY27.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:49:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994014ecffb93b3e927aa7a_1771307459420.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IHCL's Profit Surge Masked by Margin Concerns and Valuation Divide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/IHCLs-Profit-Surge-Masked-by-Margin-Concerns-and-Valuation-Divide/699400dbcffb93b3e927a9d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/IHCLs-Profit-Surge-Masked-by-Margin-Concerns-and-Valuation-Divide/699400dbcffb93b3e927a9d6</guid><description>The Indian Hotels Company (IHCL) reported a 50.86% year-over-year net profit increase to ₹954.24 crore for Q3 FY26, heavily influenced by a ₹327 crore gain from a joint venture stake sale. While revenue rose 12.19% to ₹2,841.96 crore, flat EBITDA margins and concerns over falling management fees per key have led to a divergence in analyst sentiment. Nomura and Motilal Oswal maintain 'Buy' ratings with targets suggesting significant upside, while Nuvama reiterates a 'Reduce' call due to operational headwinds and a premium valuation, which is notably higher than peers like EIH Ltd. The stock's recent underperformance underscores market scrutiny beyond headline profit figures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:47:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699400dbcffb93b3e927a9d5_1771307487208.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EMS Limited Faces Q3 Slump, Investor Concerns Rise Over Promoter Pledge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EMS-Limited-Faces-Q3-Slump-Investor-Concerns-Rise-Over-Promoter-Pledge/699400d7cffb93b3e927a9bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EMS-Limited-Faces-Q3-Slump-Investor-Concerns-Rise-Over-Promoter-Pledge/699400d7cffb93b3e927a9bf</guid><description>EMS Limited reported Q3 FY26 results below expectations, citing adverse weather and project design delays impacting revenue. Margins have compressed significantly compared to historical performance. Management addressed investor concerns regarding a sharp increase in promoter pledging for personal investments and revised debt repayment timelines, promising a recovery in Q4 FY26 and strong growth in FY27. The company aims to expand its order book by 40-50%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:47:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699400d7cffb93b3e927a9be_1771307332678.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Gig Economy Tax Chaos: Revenue Goals Clash with Innovation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Gig-Economy-Tax-Chaos-Revenue-Goals-Clash-with-Innovation/6993fc78cffb93b3e927a6ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Gig-Economy-Tax-Chaos-Revenue-Goals-Clash-with-Innovation/6993fc78cffb93b3e927a6ec</guid><description>India's burgeoning gig economy is ensnared in a web of complex Goods and Services Tax (GST) regulations. Despite efforts to formalize the sector via Section 9(5) of the CGST Act, disparate tax rates, coverage gaps, and conflicting advance rulings are creating significant regulatory friction. This environment challenges platform business models, increases costs for gig workers, and deviates from international best practices advocating for simplicity and fairness, potentially stifling the very innovation the sector represents. Platforms like Uber, Zomato, and Swiggy are navigating this uncertainty, with direct consequences for their operations and millions of independent workers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:28:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993fc78cffb93b3e927a6eb_1771306288114.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supriya Lifescience Sees 11% Revenue Rise, Profit Growth Lags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Supriya-Lifescience-Sees-11percent-Revenue-Rise-Profit-Growth-Lags/6993fc4ccffb93b3e927a67a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Supriya-Lifescience-Sees-11percent-Revenue-Rise-Profit-Growth-Lags/6993fc4ccffb93b3e927a67a</guid><description>Supriya Lifescience reported an 11% year-on-year increase in revenue to INR 206 crore for the third quarter of FY26. However, profit after tax (PAT) grew at a slower pace of 6.4% to INR 50 crore. The company reiterated its guidance for approximately 20% revenue growth in FY26 and aims for INR 1000 crore revenue in FY27, banking on new product launches and capacity expansions like the Ambernath facility.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:27:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993fc4ccffb93b3e927a679_1771306161110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FMCG Stocks: Technical Rallies vs. Sector Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Stocks-Technical-Rallies-vs-Sector-Headwinds/6993fc47cffb93b3e927a663</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FMCG-Stocks-Technical-Rallies-vs-Sector-Headwinds/6993fc47cffb93b3e927a663</guid><description>The Indian FMCG sector grapples with broad weakness, amplified by ITC's significant decline, yet Nifty FMCG has seen a modest recovery. Analysts are selectively bullish, anticipating improved rural and semi-urban demand. Technical strength is noted in Marico and Britannia, with Varun Beverages showing recent volatility. Investors face a decision between individual stock momentum and pervasive sector challenges, including elevated valuations and competition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:27:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993fc47cffb93b3e927a662.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aye Finance Surges Post-IPO, Analyst Caution Amid Profit Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aye-Finance-Surges-Post-IPO-Analyst-Caution-Amid-Profit-Dip/6993fc39cffb93b3e927a611</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aye-Finance-Surges-Post-IPO-Analyst-Caution-Amid-Profit-Dip/6993fc39cffb93b3e927a611</guid><description>Aye Finance shares experienced a significant post-IPO surge, reaching an all-time high of ₹140.80 on February 17, 2026, despite a subdued market. This performance, however, is juxtaposed with analyst concerns regarding a sharp 40% year-on-year decline in net profit and increasing non-performing assets. While revenue growth remains robust, market participants are carefully weighing these fundamental risks against the company's expansion prospects in the MSME lending sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 05:27:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993fc39cffb93b3e927a610_1771306217975.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>