<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 02:00:27 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Q3 FY26: Europe Fuels 8.4% Revenue Growth, API Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Q3-FY26-Europe-Fuels-84percent-Revenue-Growth-API-Dips/698a8c77757d40c781847a05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Q3-FY26-Europe-Fuels-84percent-Revenue-Growth-API-Dips/698a8c77757d40c781847a05</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma reported Q3FY26 revenue of ₹8,646 Cr, up 8.4% YoY, propelled by strong European sales and ARV segment growth. EBITDA rose 9.0% to ₹1,773 Cr with margins at 20.5%. The US market remained stable, though the API business saw a 4.3% decline. The company highlighted progress in its biosimilars pipeline and US product approvals, eyeing future growth despite API challenges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:40:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a8c77757d40c781847a04_1770687803023.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Surges on Iran Tensions; Supply Surplus Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-Surges-on-Iran-Tensions-Supply-Surplus-Looms/698a8c22757d40c781847882</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-Surges-on-Iran-Tensions-Supply-Surplus-Looms/698a8c22757d40c781847882</guid><description>Oil prices ascended on heightened geopolitical tensions involving Iran and the Strait of Hormuz, pushing WTI above $64 and Brent near $69. However, global oil demand growth forecasts for 2026 remain subdued, with the IEA predicting a substantial market surplus that may cap upward price momentum. Major energy firms' valuations present a mixed picture, and the broader energy sector ETF indicates overbought conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:38:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698a8c22757d40c781847881.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ramco Cements: Asset Sales Mask Margin Squeeze Amid Cost Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ramco-Cements-Asset-Sales-Mask-Margin-Squeeze-Amid-Cost-Headwinds/698a8c07757d40c781847770</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ramco-Cements-Asset-Sales-Mask-Margin-Squeeze-Amid-Cost-Headwinds/698a8c07757d40c781847770</guid><description>Ramco Cements reported a significant Q3 FY26 profit jump, largely driven by ₹506 crore from non-core asset sales. However, this masks underlying operational pressures: cement prices fell 6% QoQ, steeper than anticipated, impacting revenue growth to a modest 6.2% YoY. EBITDA remained flat, and operating margins compressed to 13.3% from 14% year-on-year. Elevated fuel costs and a new ₹160/tonne limestone tax in Tamil Nadu further pressured raw material expenses, contributing to an 11% EBITDA miss against analyst estimates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:38:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a8c07757d40c78184776f_1770687633930.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Giant's Capex vs. Chemical's Soaring P/E: A Tale of Two Industries</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Steel-Giants-Capex-vs-Chemicals-Soaring-PE-A-Tale-of-Two-Industries/698a8765757d40c78184745d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Steel-Giants-Capex-vs-Chemicals-Soaring-PE-A-Tale-of-Two-Industries/698a8765757d40c78184745d</guid><description>JSW Steel's Q3 FY26 saw revenue climb and volumes increase, yet EBITDA margins faced sequential pressure. Aggressive capacity expansion plans requiring significant capital expenditure are underway, financed partly by stake monetization. Meanwhile, Acutaas Chemicals reported robust revenue and profit growth driven by its Contract Development and Manufacturing Organization (CDMO) segment, raising forward guidance. However, the company's valuation multiples stand exceptionally high compared to industry peers, and its nascent specialty chemical ventures carry inherent risks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:18:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698a8765757d40c78184745c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asia Hits Record Highs as Alphabet Eyes 100-Year Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Asia-Hits-Record-Highs-as-Alphabet-Eyes-100-Year-Debt/698a8752757d40c7818473a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Asia-Hits-Record-Highs-as-Alphabet-Eyes-100-Year-Debt/698a8752757d40c7818473a2</guid><description>Asian markets achieved record highs Tuesday, propelled by a U.S. tech stock recovery and easing AI trade concerns. Japan's Nikkei 225 index reached an all-time high, mirroring global optimism. Alphabet Inc. is making a significant move into long-dated debt with plans for a rare 100-year bond to finance its substantial AI infrastructure investments. Investors await crucial U.S. jobs and inflation data, which will heavily influence Federal Reserve rate policy expectations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:18:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a8752757d40c7818473a1_1770686407314.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Miners Pivot to AI: High Stakes, High Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Miners-Pivot-to-AI-High-Stakes-High-Risk/698a86dc757d40c781847236</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Miners-Pivot-to-AI-High-Stakes-High-Risk/698a86dc757d40c781847236</guid><description>Morgan Stanley has highlighted Cipher Mining (CIFR) and TeraWulf (WULF) for potential share growth exceeding 150% as they transition from Bitcoin mining to AI data center operations. This strategic shift leverages existing power infrastructure for a burgeoning AI compute market. However, both companies operate with negative profit margins and face substantial capital expenditure, operational complexity, and intense competition from established data center providers. While contracts offer long-term revenue potential, success hinges on complex execution and navigating a financially challenging landscape. TeraWulf, in particular, shows signs of high leverage, raising concerns about its financial resilience.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:16:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a86dc757d40c781847235_1770686292185.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Gig Economy Faces Reckoning: Speed vs. Sustainability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Gig-Economy-Faces-Reckoning-Speed-vs-Sustainability/698a840b757d40c781846ffd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Gig-Economy-Faces-Reckoning-Speed-vs-Sustainability/698a840b757d40c781846ffd</guid><description>Indian quick commerce platforms are under intense scrutiny following government intervention to curb '10-minute delivery' promises due to worker safety concerns. This regulatory pressure, coupled with inherent operational inefficiencies and rising labor costs, signals a critical juncture for the sector's business model. The focus is shifting from hyper-growth fueled by speed to sustainable operations, transparency, and worker welfare, potentially reshaping platform strategies and market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:04:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a840b757d40c781846ffc_1770685573598.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Market Hits Record Highs Amid Tech Rally, AI Drives Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-Market-Hits-Record-Highs-Amid-Tech-Rally-AI-Drives-Growth/698a823c757d40c781846dd4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-Market-Hits-Record-Highs-Amid-Tech-Rally-AI-Drives-Growth/698a823c757d40c781846dd4</guid><description>US stocks concluded Monday, February 9, 2026, on a strong note, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average reaching a new record high above 50,000. Technology shares led the advance, with Nvidia and Broadcom posting significant gains. Oracle experienced a notable surge following a positive analyst upgrade tied to AI-linked demand. Investors are now shifting focus to a critical week of economic data, including the US jobs report and CPI inflation figures, which are expected to influence Federal Reserve policy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:56:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a823c757d40c781846dd3_1770685198527.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty 50 Eyes 26,000 Amid Expiry; Valuation, FPI Flows in Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-50-Eyes-26000-Amid-Expiry-Valuation-FPI-Flows-in-Focus/698a8228757d40c781846cf9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-50-Eyes-26000-Amid-Expiry-Valuation-FPI-Flows-in-Focus/698a8228757d40c781846cf9</guid><description>The Nifty 50 index is nearing the 26,000 mark ahead of its monthly expiry, fueled by renewed foreign investor inflows and positive sentiment from the India-US trade deal. While the index exhibits strength, a P/E ratio of 22.8 suggests fair valuation, and sector-specific dynamics, particularly weakness in IT, contrast with gains in financials and PSU banks, indicating a bifurcated market. The Reserve Bank of India's recent decision to hold rates steady at 5.25% underscores a growth-supportive stance amidst controlled inflation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:56:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a8228757d40c781846cf8_1770685093773.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Banks: Chart Patterns Mask Divergent Fortunes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Chart-Patterns-Mask-Divergent-Fortunes/698a813c757d40c781846b21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Chart-Patterns-Mask-Divergent-Fortunes/698a813c757d40c781846b21</guid><description>India's leading private banks, HDFC Bank, ICICI Bank, and Axis Bank, exhibit constructive chart patterns suggesting potential upside. HDFC Bank is in a re-accumulation phase, ICICI Bank is executing a breakout-retest-resumption strategy, and Axis Bank is at all-time highs. However, beneath these technical signals lie differing operational stages and potential headwinds. Investors must look beyond charts to understand comparative strengths, competitive positioning, and sector-wide vulnerabilities to navigate this complex market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:52:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a813c757d40c781846b20_1770684952603.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Capex Boom: Indian Data Center Plays Face Valuation Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AI-Capex-Boom-Indian-Data-Center-Plays-Face-Valuation-Hurdles/698a80c6757d40c7818469bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AI-Capex-Boom-Indian-Data-Center-Plays-Face-Valuation-Hurdles/698a80c6757d40c7818469bd</guid><description>Global hyperscalers are committing $650 billion to AI infrastructure in 2026, a spending spree expected to supercharge data center demand. This creates opportunities for Indian enablers like Sterlite Technologies, HFCL, and Black Box. However, beneath the surface of immense capital expenditure, these companies exhibit divergent valuation metrics, varying profitability, and distinct execution challenges that warrant investor scrutiny beyond the sector's bullish narrative. Each player navigates the AI data center boom with unique risk-reward profiles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:50:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a80c6757d40c7818469bc_1770684800272.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Waaree's Solar Subsidiaries Soar on Budget Boost; Two Small-Caps Shine</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Waarees-Solar-Subsidiaries-Soar-on-Budget-Boost-Two-Small-Caps-Shine/698a804b757d40c781846836</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Waarees-Solar-Subsidiaries-Soar-on-Budget-Boost-Two-Small-Caps-Shine/698a804b757d40c781846836</guid><description>India's solar sector receives a significant boost with over Rs 30,000 crore allocated in Budget 2026, driving a manufacturing renaissance. Investors are eyeing two under-the-radar small-cap companies, subsidiaries of Waaree Energies, that are quietly consolidating market positions and showing impressive capital efficiency and profit growth, presenting potential entry points amid market discounts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:48:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a804b757d40c781846835_1770684648034.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Chip Gear Ambition Faces High-Stakes Reality Check</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Chip-Gear-Ambition-Faces-High-Stakes-Reality-Check/698a7fd4757d40c7818466c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Chip-Gear-Ambition-Faces-High-Stakes-Reality-Check/698a7fd4757d40c7818466c3</guid><description>India's strategic aim to build indigenous semiconductor manufacturing equipment faces an uphill battle against established global titans. While government incentives and a growing domestic demand provide a foundation, the colossal R&amp;D investment, intense competition, and technological complexity present significant financial and execution risks. This ambitious venture demands a long-term, patient capital approach, far beyond mere import substitution, to navigate the steep learning curve and challenging market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:46:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a7fd4757d40c7818466c2_1770684524451.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Actis Eyeing Sprng Energy Buyback Amidst Shell's Renewables Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Actis-Eyeing-Sprng-Energy-Buyback-Amidst-Shells-Renewables-Pivot/698a7d07757d40c781846449</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Actis-Eyeing-Sprng-Energy-Buyback-Amidst-Shells-Renewables-Pivot/698a7d07757d40c781846449</guid><description>Actis LLP has unexpectedly re-entered the race to acquire Shell's Sprng Energy platform, a clean energy asset Actis itself developed before selling it to the oil major in 2022. Shortlisted alongside rivals like KKR and NIIF, Actis is initiating due diligence with final bids anticipated by March-end. The potential deal, valued at $1.8-$2 billion, represents a premium over Shell's $1.55 billion acquisition, yet industry observers question the valuation hike due to slow greenfield development under Shell, a move indicative of Shell's broader strategic withdrawal from capital-intensive renewable generation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:34:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a7d07757d40c781846448_1770683778283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hillhouse Bets $4.5B on Quest Global India IPO Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hillhouse-Bets-45B-on-Quest-Global-India-IPO-Ambitions/698a7b98757d40c7818462b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hillhouse-Bets-45B-on-Quest-Global-India-IPO-Ambitions/698a7b98757d40c7818462b5</guid><description>Hillhouse Investment Management is acquiring a ~5% stake in Quest Global for $4.5 billion, fueling the engineering services firm's pre-IPO fundraising. This aggressive move by Hillhouse signals strong conviction in Quest Global's strategy to list on Indian stock exchanges via a reverse flip. The deal underscores Quest Global's impressive growth, having achieved $1 billion in revenue in FY25, and highlights Hillhouse's significant expansion into India's technology outsourcing arena. The investment's structure includes primary capital and secondary share sales, positioning Quest Global for its next growth phase.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:28:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a7b98757d40c7818462b4_1770683431817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises Surges on Strong Q3 Growth, Expansion Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Growth-Expansion-Drive/698a7855757d40c781846094</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Growth-Expansion-Drive/698a7855757d40c781846094</guid><description>Amber Enterprises India posted a strong Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue up 38% YoY to ₹2,943 Cr and EBITDA soaring 53% to ₹247 Cr. Margins improved to 8.4%. Despite a 9MFY26 PAT dip due to a ₹94 Cr investment impairment, the company detailed aggressive expansion plans, including acquisitions and new facilities, driving optimistic guidance for its Consumer Durables, Electronics, and Railway divisions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:14:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a7855757d40c781846093_1770682570080.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises Posts Strong Growth, But Auditor's Qualified Report Raises Red Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-Posts-Strong-Growth-But-Auditors-Qualified-Report-Raises-Red-Flags/698a77d9757d40c781845f34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-Posts-Strong-Growth-But-Auditors-Qualified-Report-Raises-Red-Flags/698a77d9757d40c781845f34</guid><description>Amber Enterprises India Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 results with standalone revenue up 60.3% and PAT up 85.8%. Consolidated revenue grew 38.2%, with PAT turning profitable after a prior year loss. However, a qualified auditor's report from S.R. Batliboi &amp; Co. LLP casts a shadow, citing unreviewed financials of subsidiaries and joint ventures. A significant ₹93.77 crore impairment charge also impacted profitability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:12:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a77d9757d40c781845f33_1770682424523.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises Q3 Profit Surges 128% on Revenue Growth, Acquisitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amber-Enterprises-Q3-Profit-Surges-128percent-on-Revenue-Growth-Acquisitions/698a7769757d40c781845dae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amber-Enterprises-Q3-Profit-Surges-128percent-on-Revenue-Growth-Acquisitions/698a7769757d40c781845dae</guid><description>Amber Enterprises India reported a strong Q3 FY26, with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 128% year-on-year to ₹84 Cr on a 38% revenue jump to ₹2,943 Cr. The nine-month period saw 29% revenue growth. Strategic moves bolstering future prospects include acquiring an 80% stake in Shogini Technoarts and securing 100 acres at YEIDA for new manufacturing facilities, driving growth across its diversified divisions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:10:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a7769757d40c781845dad_1770682419543.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MPS Limited Acquires US Firm Unbound Medicine, Plans Investor Call</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/MPS-Limited-Acquires-US-Firm-Unbound-Medicine-Plans-Investor-Call/698a775e757d40c781845cd1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/MPS-Limited-Acquires-US-Firm-Unbound-Medicine-Plans-Investor-Call/698a775e757d40c781845cd1</guid><description>MPS Limited announced the acquisition of US-based Unbound Medicine, Inc. The company will host a conference call on February 18, 2026, at 7:00 PM IST, led by Chairman and CEO Rahul Arora. The call aims to detail the acquisition's rationale, potential synergies, financial implications, and growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:10:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698a775e757d40c781845cd0_1770682313707.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>