<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:49:54 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Ambuja Cements Misses Q3; Motilal Oswal Reiterates BUY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ambuja-Cements-Misses-Q3-Motilal-Oswal-Reiterates-BUY/698099c847db7081af692bea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ambuja-Cements-Misses-Q3-Motilal-Oswal-Reiterates-BUY/698099c847db7081af692bea</guid><description>Ambuja Cements (ACEM) reported a third fiscal quarter consolidated EBITDA of INR13.5 billion, a 53% year-on-year increase that fell 24% short of analyst estimates. EBITDA per tonne reached INR716, up 33% but missing forecasts of INR953, impacted by elevated operating expenses. Adjusted profit after tax saw a significant 76% decline to INR1.1 billion. Despite these headwinds, Motilal Oswal maintains a BUY recommendation and a target price of INR600, projecting future EBITDA per tonne growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:38:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698099c847db7081af692be9_1770035901458.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABREL Misses Targets, Faces Sector Slump Despite Analyst Optimism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/ABREL-Misses-Targets-Faces-Sector-Slump-Despite-Analyst-Optimism/6980997c47db7081af692a99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/ABREL-Misses-Targets-Faces-Sector-Slump-Despite-Analyst-Optimism/6980997c47db7081af692a99</guid><description>Aditya Birla Real Estate (ABREL) reported third-quarter FY26 presales of INR25.4 billion, a significant year-on-year increase but 29% below analyst expectations. The company also slashed its full-year FY26 launch guidance from INR139 billion to INR88 billion, deferring key projects to FY27. Despite these headwinds, brokerage Motilal Oswal reiterated a BUY rating with a revised target price of INR1,988. The Indian real estate sector, including ABREL, is contending with a broad market correction and declining stock performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:36:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980997c47db7081af692a98_1770035770118.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRB Infra Seals ₹513 Cr Deal, Slashes Debt by ₹700 Cr Via Project Transfer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRB-Infra-Seals-513-Cr-Deal-Slashes-Debt-by-700-Cr-Via-Project-Transfer/6980916747db7081af690a31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRB-Infra-Seals-513-Cr-Deal-Slashes-Debt-by-700-Cr-Via-Project-Transfer/6980916747db7081af690a31</guid><description>IRB Infrastructure Developers has finalized the transfer of its Gandeva Ena HAM project subsidiary, VM7 Expressway Private Limited, to IRB InvIT Fund for ₹513 crore. This strategic move is expected to reduce the company's consolidated debt by approximately ₹700 crore, enhancing liquidity and enabling pursuit of future growth opportunities. The transaction validates IRB Infra's capital recycling model.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:35:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980916747db7081af690a30_1770035732867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal Flags ACME Solar, Sets Rs 350 Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Motilal-Oswal-Flags-ACME-Solar-Sets-Rs-350-Target/6980996147db7081af69297e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Motilal-Oswal-Flags-ACME-Solar-Sets-Rs-350-Target/6980996147db7081af69297e</guid><description>Motilal Oswal initiated a 'Buy' recommendation for ACME Solar Holdings, setting a Rs 350 price target. The brokerage highlighted robust year-over-year revenue growth of 42% and strong EBITDA margins. Investors can anticipate an interim dividend of ₹0.2 per share for FY26. The target valuation was adjusted to 9.5x FY28E EBITDA, aligning with industry peers like NTPC Green.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:35:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980996147db7081af69297d_1770035712988.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Utkarsh SFB Posts Steep Q3 Loss, Pivots to Secured Lending</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Utkarsh-SFB-Posts-Steep-Q3-Loss-Pivots-to-Secured-Lending/698098d347db7081af6927de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Utkarsh-SFB-Posts-Steep-Q3-Loss-Pivots-to-Secured-Lending/698098d347db7081af6927de</guid><description>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank reported a significant loss of ₹375 crore in Q3 FY26, a stark reversal from last year's profit. The bank saw a 74% surge in provisions and an alarming rise in Gross NPAs to 11.0%, forcing a strategic pivot. Management plans to focus on secured lending (MSME, Housing, Gold) and retail deposits to navigate market disruptions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698098d347db7081af6927dd_1770035601884.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Craftsman Automation Eyes ₹1,000 Cr Capex, Targets Debt Reduction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Craftsman-Automation-Eyes-1000-Cr-Capex-Targets-Debt-Reduction/698097b547db7081af692325</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Craftsman-Automation-Eyes-1000-Cr-Capex-Targets-Debt-Reduction/698097b547db7081af692325</guid><description>Craftsman Automation plans ₹1,000 crore capex and targets reducing debt-to-EBITDA to 1.5. The company detailed segmental performance, with Aluminium facing startup losses but expected recovery, Alloy Wheels needing utilization boost, and strong outlook for Industrial/Engineering and Powertrain. Management sees EV shift benefits and continued ICE investment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:31:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698097b547db7081af692324_1770035483662.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Awfis Space Solutions Reports Robust Q3 Revenue Growth, Margins Expand Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Awfis-Space-Solutions-Reports-Robust-Q3-Revenue-Growth-Margins-Expand-Sharply/698097ec47db7081af6924c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Awfis-Space-Solutions-Reports-Robust-Q3-Revenue-Growth-Margins-Expand-Sharply/698097ec47db7081af6924c0</guid><description>Awfis Space Solutions posted impressive Q3 FY26 results, with standalone revenue jumping 31.42% YoY to ₹3,196.76 crore and consolidated revenue up 19.03% to ₹3,817.76 crore. Profitability soared, driven by substantial margin expansion in EBITDA. For the nine months, consolidated PBT declined YoY due to an exceptional gain in the previous year. The company also enhanced its term loan facility for capital expenditure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:28:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698097ec47db7081af6924bf_1770035332462.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Tourism, Mobility Pillars Boost VFS Global Ecosystem</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/India-Budget-2026-Tourism-Mobility-Pillars-Boost-VFS-Global-Ecosystem/6980980347db7081af692570</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/India-Budget-2026-Tourism-Mobility-Pillars-Boost-VFS-Global-Ecosystem/6980980347db7081af692570</guid><description>The Indian government's Budget 2026-27 strategically positions tourism, mobility, and human capital as central drivers for long-term economic expansion. Policy measures are designed to invigorate travel demand and foster a globally connected workforce. VFS Global, a key player in visa and passport services, operates within this evolving ecosystem. The budget's focus on making international travel more accessible, coupled with initiatives supporting outbound student and medical remittances, is expected to influence the volume and nature of applications processed by VFS Global. Analysts maintain a 'Buy' rating on VFS Global, anticipating growth from these policy shifts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:28:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980980347db7081af69256f_1770035322714.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Equities Rebound Post-Budget; Power Grid Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Rebound-Post-Budget-Power-Grid-Soars/6980977847db7081af692183</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Rebound-Post-Budget-Power-Grid-Soars/6980977847db7081af692183</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks staged a significant recovery on Monday, February 2, 2026, reversing the sharp declines from the previous day's budget announcement. The Nifty 50 closed 1.06% higher at 25,088.40, and the BSE Sensex gained 1.17% to 81,666. Power Grid Corporation of India was a top performer, climbing over 7%. The recovery followed a volatile session attributed to the Union Budget's fiscal prudence, policy continuity, and a decline in global crude oil prices. However, analysts suggest near-term caution due to earnings and ongoing geopolitical uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:27:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980977847db7081af692182_1770035249881.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aanchal Ispat Promoter Set for Offer For Sale on BSE</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aanchal-Ispat-Promoter-Set-for-Offer-For-Sale-on-BSE/698093ac47db7081af6916b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aanchal-Ispat-Promoter-Set-for-Offer-For-Sale-on-BSE/698093ac47db7081af6916b1</guid><description>Aanchal Ispat Limited announces an Offer For Sale (OFS) by promoter Mukesh Goel, scheduled for February 3-4, 2026. The transaction will occur on the BSE, designated as the stock exchange. This OFS allows both Non-Retail and Retail investors to participate, with specific timelines and bidding procedures outlined per SEBI guidelines.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:26:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698093ac47db7081af6916b0_1770035191408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Auto Market Kicks Off 2026 with Record Sales Amidst Cost Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Market-Kicks-Off-2026-with-Record-Sales-Amidst-Cost-Pressures/698097a747db7081af69228a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Market-Kicks-Off-2026-with-Record-Sales-Amidst-Cost-Pressures/698097a747db7081af69228a</guid><description>India's passenger vehicle market achieved its highest-ever January sales in 2026, surpassing 456,000 units. Strong demand for SUVs and post-GST benefits fueled growth across major manufacturers like Maruti Suzuki, Tata Motors, and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra. However, the sector grapples with increasing input costs and persistent supply chain constraints. Government incentives, particularly for EVs, aim to bolster future manufacturing, while companies like Maruti Suzuki review potential price hikes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>City Union Bank Posts 12.2% Profit Rise, Asset Quality Improves</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/City-Union-Bank-Posts-122percent-Profit-Rise-Asset-Quality-Improves/6980910647db7081af6907bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/City-Union-Bank-Posts-122percent-Profit-Rise-Asset-Quality-Improves/6980910647db7081af6907bd</guid><description>City Union Bank reported a 12.2% year-on-year increase in net profit to ₹332.16 Cr for Q3 FY2026, driven by a 17.2% total income growth to ₹2001.03 Cr. The bank saw significant improvement in asset quality, with Gross NPAs declining to 2.17% and Net NPAs to 0.78%. However, operating expenses surged 28.7% YoY, and provisions rose 28% YoY, while Capital Adequacy Ratio (CAR) fell to 20.13%.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:24:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980910647db7081af6907bc_1770035082428.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ather Energy Zooms 53% Revenue, Narrows Loss; EBITDA Still Negative</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ather-Energy-Zooms-53percent-Revenue-Narrows-Loss-EBITDA-Still-Negative/698093be47db7081af6917bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ather-Energy-Zooms-53percent-Revenue-Narrows-Loss-EBITDA-Still-Negative/698093be47db7081af6917bd</guid><description>Ather Energy reported a robust 53% YoY revenue jump to ₹9,957 million in Q3 FY26, driven by 50% unit sales growth. The company narrowed its net loss significantly for 9M FY26 and improved margins, though EBITDA remained negative at -3%. Expansion efforts and product success bolster its market position.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:21:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698093be47db7081af6917bc_1770034893394.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CIAL Launches India's First Airport Hydrogen Buses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/CIAL-Launches-Indias-First-Airport-Hydrogen-Buses/6980958d47db7081af691f3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/CIAL-Launches-Indias-First-Airport-Hydrogen-Buses/6980958d47db7081af691f3f</guid><description>Cochin International Airport Ltd (CIAL) is poised to deploy India's first hydrogen-powered buses for passenger transit, following an agreement with the Kerala Hydrogen Valley Innovation Cluster (K-HVIC) Foundation. The ₹8.7 crore initiative, financially supported by K-HVIC, will see three buses procured within 12 months, with CIAL managing operations. This strategic move aligns with the National Green Hydrogen Mission and aims to enhance passenger experience while curbing transport emissions, supported by an imminent green hydrogen plant.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:19:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980958d47db7081af691f3e_1770034739572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ananda Dairy Aims for ₹10,000 Cr Turnover by 2030</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ananda-Dairy-Aims-for-10000-Cr-Turnover-by-2030/6980954247db7081af691dba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ananda-Dairy-Aims-for-10000-Cr-Turnover-by-2030/6980954247db7081af691dba</guid><description>Ananda Dairy has set an ambitious target to achieve ₹10,000 crore in turnover by 2030, a substantial leap from its FY'24 turnover of approximately ₹1,700 crore. This aggressive growth plan hinges on a broad diversification strategy extending beyond core dairy products into value-added dairy and adjacent food categories. The company is leveraging its established operational infrastructure, including a wide farmer network, significant processing capacity, and an extensive distribution reach across India.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:17:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980954247db7081af691db9_1770034657710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Utkarsh SFB Posts Widening Losses, Revenue Dip; Gross NPAs Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Utkarsh-SFB-Posts-Widening-Losses-Revenue-Dip-Gross-NPAs-Surge/6980949b47db7081af691c06</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Utkarsh-SFB-Posts-Widening-Losses-Revenue-Dip-Gross-NPAs-Surge/6980949b47db7081af691c06</guid><description>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank reported a challenging third quarter with revenue falling 13% YoY to ₹901.71 Cr and net losses widening to ₹375.02 Cr. For nine months, revenue dipped 10.7% and losses increased to ₹1,101.59 Cr. Gross NPAs surged to 4.48%, Debt/Equity rose to 0.89, and CAR fell. The bank is progressing on its amalgamation with Utkarsh CoreInvest.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:16:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980949b47db7081af691c05_1770034579412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nexus Select Trust's Record Q3 Distribution Fuels Portfolio Doubling Plans</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nexus-Select-Trusts-Record-Q3-Distribution-Fuels-Portfolio-Doubling-Plans/6980942447db7081af691a5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nexus-Select-Trusts-Record-Q3-Distribution-Fuels-Portfolio-Doubling-Plans/6980942447db7081af691a5a</guid><description>Nexus Select Trust reported its highest quarterly distribution of INR 3,586 million in Q3 FY26, driven by a 16% YoY surge in tenant sales to INR 41 billion. Retail Net Operating Income climbed 15% YoY to INR 5,033 million. Proactive debt management included issuing a INR 7 billion sustainability-linked bond, reducing debt cost by 30 bps to 7.2% and saving INR 60 million annually. The REIT is on track for FY26 guidance and eyes doubling its portfolio by 2030 with a strong acquisition pipeline.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:14:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980942447db7081af691a59_1770034406192.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nexus Select Trust Q3 Results Show 31% Standalone Revenue Surge, ₹358 Cr Distribution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nexus-Select-Trust-Q3-Results-Show-31percent-Standalone-Revenue-Surge-358-Cr-Distribution/698093d347db7081af6918e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nexus-Select-Trust-Q3-Results-Show-31percent-Standalone-Revenue-Surge-358-Cr-Distribution/698093d347db7081af6918e5</guid><description>Nexus Select Trust reported a strong Q3 FY26, with standalone revenue jumping 31.83% YoY to ₹505.56 Cr and profit rising 27.47% to ₹296.65 Cr. Consolidated revenue grew 12.91% to ₹671.16 Cr, while profit climbed 17.41% to ₹139.40 Cr. The Trust declared a ₹358.60 Cr distribution. Consolidated net borrowings increased to ₹6,063.30 Cr.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:11:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698093d347db7081af6918e4_1770034284674.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Innova Captab Posts 42% Revenue Surge, Driven by Generics Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Innova-Captab-Posts-42percent-Revenue-Surge-Driven-by-Generics-Growth/6980933547db7081af69152e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Innova-Captab-Posts-42percent-Revenue-Surge-Driven-by-Generics-Growth/6980933547db7081af69152e</guid><description>Innova Captab reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue soaring 42.3% YoY to ₹450.3 Cr, fueled by a stellar 79% growth in branded generics. EBITDA rose 39.6% YoY to ₹71.1 Cr with stable margins. The company expressed confidence in sustaining over 20% growth in FY27, with its Jammu facility set to contribute positively from FY27. Key GMP certifications were also secured.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980933547db7081af69152d_1770034124347.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ather Energy Hits Record Q3 Revenue, Profitability Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ather-Energy-Hits-Record-Q3-Revenue-Profitability-Soars/6980924847db7081af690f5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ather-Energy-Hits-Record-Q3-Revenue-Profitability-Soars/6980924847db7081af690f5d</guid><description>Ather Energy reported its strongest-ever Q3 FY26, with total income jumping 53% YoY to ₹995.7 crore, driven by record sales volumes of 67,851 units. The company significantly improved its financial health, narrowing EBITDA loss by 45% QoQ and expanding EBITDA margins by 1600 bps YoY to -3%. Adjusted Gross Margin (AGM) surged 111% YoY. Ather also bolstered its market share to 18.8% nationally, expanding its physical and charging networks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980924847db7081af690f5c_1770034067907.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GPT Healthcare Posts 17.5% Revenue Growth, But Profits Tumble 23.5%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/GPT-Healthcare-Posts-175percent-Revenue-Growth-But-Profits-Tumble-235percent/6980927a47db7081af6912f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/GPT-Healthcare-Posts-175percent-Revenue-Growth-But-Profits-Tumble-235percent/6980927a47db7081af6912f3</guid><description>GPT Healthcare reported a 17.56% year-on-year increase in revenue from operations for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹120.16 Cr. However, profitability took a hit, with Profit After Tax (PAT) declining by 23.50% to ₹9.37 Cr from ₹12.25 Cr in Q3 FY25. EBITDA margins also compressed to 16.56% from 22.24% YoY, signaling rising costs or pricing pressures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:06:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980927a47db7081af6912f2_1770033969927.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aeroflex Industries Shatters Records with Record Revenue, Profit; Eyes Data Center Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aeroflex-Industries-Shatters-Records-with-Record-Revenue-Profit-Eyes-Data-Center-Boom/698091eb47db7081af690d7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aeroflex-Industries-Shatters-Records-with-Record-Revenue-Profit-Eyes-Data-Center-Boom/698091eb47db7081af690d7d</guid><description>Aeroflex Industries Limited announced record Q3 FY26 results, with revenue up 21% YoY to INR 121 Cr, EBITDA up 28% to INR 28.5 Cr, and PAT up 8% to INR 16.5 Cr. The company is expanding capacity for data center cooling solutions and targets sustained 23-25% EBITDA margins, leveraging strong export demand, particularly from the EU.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:06:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698091eb47db7081af690d7c_1770033868680.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nexome Capital Markets Plans ₹25 Cr Rights Issue Amidst Sharp Revenue &amp; Profit Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nexome-Capital-Markets-Plans-25-Cr-Rights-Issue-Amidst-Sharp-Revenue-and-Profit-Plunge/698091d047db7081af690cd2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nexome-Capital-Markets-Plans-25-Cr-Rights-Issue-Amidst-Sharp-Revenue-and-Profit-Plunge/698091d047db7081af690cd2</guid><description>Nexome Capital Markets Limited (formerly SMIFS Capital) plans to raise ₹25 Crores through a Rights Issue. This comes as the company reported a drastic YoY decline in consolidated revenue to ₹44.41 Crores in FY25 from ₹239.86 Crores in FY24, with Profit After Tax (PAT) falling 52% to ₹1.17 Crores. Basic EPS slipped to ₹2.04 from ₹4.31, and RoNW fell to 1.07%. Total borrowings surged significantly to ₹30.02 Crores.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:03:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698091d047db7081af690cd1_1770033809955.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nexome Capital Markets Plans ₹25Cr Rights Issue Amidst Steep Financial Downturn</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nexome-Capital-Markets-Plans-25Cr-Rights-Issue-Amidst-Steep-Financial-Downturn/6980915647db7081af690963</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nexome-Capital-Markets-Plans-25Cr-Rights-Issue-Amidst-Steep-Financial-Downturn/6980915647db7081af690963</guid><description>Nexome Capital Markets Limited plans to raise up to ₹25 crore via a rights issue, intended for investments and general corporate needs. However, the move comes as the company reported a severe year-on-year decline in FY2025, with revenue plunging 81.5% and PAT falling 51.6%. Borrowings have also surged dramatically. Investors face significant dilution and questions about the company's financial health.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980915647db7081af690962_1770033635115.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRB InvIT Fund Acquires Gandeva Ena Asset for Rs 1,200 Cr, Expands Portfolio</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRB-InvIT-Fund-Acquires-Gandeva-Ena-Asset-for-Rs-1200-Cr-Expands-Portfolio/6980918647db7081af690b5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRB-InvIT-Fund-Acquires-Gandeva-Ena-Asset-for-Rs-1200-Cr-Expands-Portfolio/6980918647db7081af690b5f</guid><description>IRB InvIT Fund has successfully acquired the Gandeva Ena HAM Asset (VM7 Expressway Private Limited) from its sponsor, IRB Infrastructure Developers Limited, for an enterprise value of approximately Rs. 1,200 Crores. This strategic move increases IRB InvIT's operational highway asset count to 10, with a total portfolio value nearing Rs. 17,600 Crores. The acquisition, funded by debt, is expected to boost distributable cash flow and dividend payouts for unitholders by enhancing the Trust's asset base and long-term revenue visibility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:01:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980918647db7081af690b5e_1770033706436.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India Crash Probe: Financial Scrutiny Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Crash-Probe-Financial-Scrutiny-Mounts/698090f547db7081af6906c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Crash-Probe-Financial-Scrutiny-Mounts/698090f547db7081af6906c4</guid><description>The investigation into the fatal Air India flight AI171 crash on June 12, 2025, is intensifying scrutiny on the airline's operational integrity and financial standing. Emerging claims from a US safety organization highlight recurring technical issues and data non-disclosure with the Boeing 787-8. Regulatory bodies are meticulously examining all probable causes, navigating complexities amid past controversies surrounding preliminary report leaks and calls for formal government inquiries.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698090f547db7081af6906c3_1770033563351.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Sparks Sector Shift: Manufacturing &amp; EVs Lead</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-2026-Sparks-Sector-Shift-Manufacturing-and-EVs-Lead/69808d6147db7081af68fbed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-2026-Sparks-Sector-Shift-Manufacturing-and-EVs-Lead/69808d6147db7081af68fbed</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 initiatives are poised to reshape India's industrial future, focusing on scaling manufacturing, securing critical mineral value chains, and advancing semiconductor capabilities. Proposed measures, including dedicated mineral corridors and enhanced capital expenditure, aim to bolster electric vehicle (EV), electronics, and next-generation mobility sectors. Despite an initial market dip attributed to tax adjustments, industry leaders view the budget as a strategic blueprint for 'Make in India,' potentially driving long-term growth and global competitiveness. The ₹40,000 crore allocation for India Semiconductor Mission 2.0 underscores a commitment to technological sovereignty.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69808d6147db7081af68fbec_1770033479692.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Advent Eyes $300M Stake in Aditya Birla Housing Finance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Advent-Eyes-300M-Stake-in-Aditya-Birla-Housing-Finance/6980880d47db7081af68e74d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Advent-Eyes-300M-Stake-in-Aditya-Birla-Housing-Finance/6980880d47db7081af68e74d</guid><description>Private equity major Advent International is reportedly in advanced discussions to infuse approximately $300 million into Aditya Birla Housing Finance (ABHF). This substantial capital injection aims to strengthen ABHF's financial foundation, enhance its capital adequacy, and fuel loan book expansion. The move aligns with Aditya Birla Capital's strategic focus on retail lending and the broader HFC sector's need for capital resilience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980880d47db7081af68e74c_1770033410136.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nexus Select Trust Posts PAT Growth Despite Revenue Dip; Acquires New Assets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nexus-Select-Trust-Posts-PAT-Growth-Despite-Revenue-Dip-Acquires-New-Assets/698090dd47db7081af6905bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nexus-Select-Trust-Posts-PAT-Growth-Despite-Revenue-Dip-Acquires-New-Assets/698090dd47db7081af6905bc</guid><description>Nexus Select Trust announced Q3 FY26 results with a standalone revenue dip of 28%, yet PAT grew 5.7%. Consolidated revenue increased 6.4%, and PAT rose 5.3%. The trust declared substantial distributions and noted acquisition impacts on comparability, maintaining a strong financial position with a low Net Borrowing Ratio.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Market Disconnect: Budget Fuels AI Hopes Amid STT Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Market-Disconnect-Budget-Fuels-AI-Hopes-Amid-STT-Sell-Off/69808ff147db7081af690431</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Market-Disconnect-Budget-Fuels-AI-Hopes-Amid-STT-Sell-Off/69808ff147db7081af690431</guid><description>India's equity market is exhibiting a striking divergence between robust macroeconomic fundamentals and prevailing investor pessimism, according to Morgan Stanley strategist Ridham Desai. Despite positive economic indicators, markets have priced in significant issues, pushing valuations to multi-year lows. The Union Budget 2026 introduced strategic initiatives, notably a strong push for an AI ecosystem and infrastructure development, but an unexpected increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives led to a sharp market sell-off, erasing substantial market capitalization on February 1st.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:56:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69808ff147db7081af690430_1770033330874.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quess Corp: Q3 Results In Line, Neutral View Maintained</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Quess-Corp-Q3-Results-In-Line-Neutral-View-Maintained/69808eff47db7081af69014f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Quess-Corp-Q3-Results-In-Line-Neutral-View-Maintained/69808eff47db7081af69014f</guid><description>Quess Corp posted third-quarter fiscal year 2026 results, featuring a 3% quarter-on-quarter revenue increase and a 2.2% year-on-year dip, performance that aligned with analyst forecasts. The company's EBITDA margin saw a 40 basis points improvement year-on-year, reaching 2%. Adjusted Profit After Tax (PAT) surged by 29% year-on-year to INR 620 million, excluding one-time labor code adjustments. For the first nine months of FY26, revenue, EBITDA, and adjusted PAT increased by 1%, 16%, and 12.5% respectively.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:53:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69808eff47db7081af69014e_1770033226688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta Earnings Beat; Stock Drops Amid Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Vedanta-Earnings-Beat-Stock-Drops-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/69808f1c47db7081af6901bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Vedanta-Earnings-Beat-Stock-Drops-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/69808f1c47db7081af6901bf</guid><description>Vedanta Limited exceeded expectations in its third quarter of fiscal year 2026, posting consolidated revenue of INR 45,899 crore and EBITDA of INR 15,171 crore, driven by higher LME prices and improved volumes. Despite this operational strength, the company's stock experienced a significant drop on January 30, 2026, reflecting investor concerns over current valuations and a divided analyst consensus. Motilal Oswal reiterated a 'Neutral' stance, highlighting the stock's trading multiples, while other brokerages maintained 'Buy' ratings with revised price targets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:52:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69808f1c47db7081af6901be_1770033145188.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks Surge Post-Budget, Digesting STT Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Stocks-Surge-Post-Budget-Digesting-STT-Hike/6980888e47db7081af68ea7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Stocks-Surge-Post-Budget-Digesting-STT-Hike/6980888e47db7081af68ea7d</guid><description>Indian stock indices Sensex and Nifty surged on February 2, 2026, defying initial sell-off pressures after the Union Budget 2026 was presented. The BSE Sensex reclaimed over 1,300 points from its intraday low, while the NSE Nifty50 surpassed the 25,000 mark. This market recovery was driven by investor digestion of Budget proposals, a significant drop in global commodity prices, and optimism surrounding India-US trade negotiations, with analysts downplaying the immediate impact of increased Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives trading volumes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980888e47db7081af68ea7c_1770032906906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors: Profit Miss, Margin Squeeze, Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Profit-Miss-Margin-Squeeze-Valuation-Concerns/69808e8747db7081af68ffe9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Profit-Miss-Margin-Squeeze-Valuation-Concerns/69808e8747db7081af68ffe9</guid><description>Tata Motors (TMCV) reported a Q3 FY26 profit after tax (PAT) of INR15.9 billion, falling short of estimates, primarily due to a lower-than-expected margin of 12.8% caused by increased input costs. Analysts highlight concerns over market share erosion and potential de-rating from the Iveco acquisition due to global macro uncertainties. Despite these issues, Motilal Oswal maintains a 'Neutral' rating with a target price of INR431, deeming the stock fairly valued at current multiples.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:49:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69808e8747db7081af68ffe8_1770032968863.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's IBC Reforms: Faster Insolvency Aims for Global Edge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-IBC-Reforms-Faster-Insolvency-Aims-for-Global-Edge/69808e1147db7081af68fe7e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-IBC-Reforms-Faster-Insolvency-Aims-for-Global-Edge/69808e1147db7081af68fe7e</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced plans to introduce the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (Amendment) Bill, 2025, in the latter half of the Budget session starting March 9. This move, the seventh amendment since 2016, aims to accelerate resolution timelines, enhance the effectiveness of insolvency proceedings, and bring India's framework closer to international best practices. The legislation seeks to bolster investor confidence and streamline corporate debt resolution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:46:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69808e1147db7081af68fe7d_1770032789403.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Premium Surge Lifts Apple to Record Market Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Premium-Surge-Lifts-Apple-to-Record-Market-Share/69808d4247db7081af68fb2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Premium-Surge-Lifts-Apple-to-Record-Market-Share/69808d4247db7081af68fb2c</guid><description>The Indian smartphone market's pivot to high-end devices propelled Apple to a record 28% value share in 2025. While overall volume growth remained modest at 1%, the market's total value expanded by 8%, driven by a significant 11% surge in the premium segment (&gt;₹30,000). This trend, supported by extensive financing options, saw Apple's iPhone 16 emerge as the top-shipped model. Competitors like Samsung maintained strong positions in specific niches, while Motorola and CMF showed rapid volume growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:44:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69808d4247db7081af68fb2b_1770032642146.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Rally: Power Grid Capex, Auto Sales Drive Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Markets-Rally-Power-Grid-Capex-Auto-Sales-Drive-Gains/6980886c47db7081af68e9c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Markets-Rally-Power-Grid-Capex-Auto-Sales-Drive-Gains/6980886c47db7081af68e9c3</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks concluded Monday's session near their peak, with the BSE Sensex climbing 944 points to 81,667 and the NSE Nifty rising 263 points to 25,088. Power Grid Corporation's increased FY26 capex forecast and Tata Motors' significant January sales jump were primary catalysts for the broad-based rally, which saw most sectors advance barring IT.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:42:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980886c47db7081af68e9c2_1770032484631.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Tax Overhaul Fuels Investment &amp; Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Tax-Overhaul-Fuels-Investment-and-Growth/69808c3247db7081af68f8d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Tax-Overhaul-Fuels-Investment-and-Growth/69808c3247db7081af68f8d2</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 marks a strategic pivot toward tax simplification and enhanced business predictability. Key announcements include extended tax holidays for foreign cloud service providers until 2047 and for IFSC units to 20 years, alongside rationalized tax frameworks for IT services. These measures, coupled with administrative reforms aimed at reducing litigation and decriminalizing minor defaults, signal India's intent to become a global investment hub.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69808c3247db7081af68f8d1_1770032373755.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Digitide Solutions Posts 6.5% Revenue Growth, Eyes $1B by 2031</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Digitide-Solutions-Posts-65percent-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-1B-by-2031/69808ad847db7081af68f403</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Digitide-Solutions-Posts-65percent-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-1B-by-2031/69808ad847db7081af68f403</guid><description>Digitide Solutions reported a 6.5% YoY revenue increase to INR 780 crores in Q3 FY26, fueled by its tech segment's 19% surge. The company secured a record Total Contract Value (TCV) of INR 662 crores, signaling robust future growth. Management reaffirmed its ambitious goal to triple revenues to USD1 billion by FY'31, driven by AI integration, expanded hyperscaler partnerships, and operational efficiencies aimed at boosting EBITDA margins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:37:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69808ad847db7081af68f402_1770032233436.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Go Fashion Announces ₹65 Cr Share Buyback at ₹460, Promoters Opt Out</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Go-Fashion-Announces-65-Cr-Share-Buyback-at-460-Promoters-Opt-Out/69808b3d47db7081af68f6a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Go-Fashion-Announces-65-Cr-Share-Buyback-at-460-Promoters-Opt-Out/69808b3d47db7081af68f6a9</guid><description>Go Fashion (India) Limited has unveiled a ₹64.99 crore share buyback plan, offering to repurchase 14.13 lakh shares at ₹460 each. This tender offer, representing 2.62% of equity, aims to boost ROE and EPS. Promoters will not participate, utilizing free reserves for funding. Record date is Feb 9, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69808b3d47db7081af68f6a8_1770032105196.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>