<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:17:38 +0000</pubDate><item><title>IndiGo Soars Ahead: Operations Stabilised, Ready for Holiday Rush &amp; New Long-Haul Flights!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Soars-Ahead-Operations-Stabilised-Ready-for-Holiday-Rush-and-New-Long-Haul-Flights/694c0216e10c98d0787b6084</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Soars-Ahead-Operations-Stabilised-Ready-for-Holiday-Rush-and-New-Long-Haul-Flights/694c0216e10c98d0787b6084</guid><description>IndiGo announced on December 24, 2025, that its operations are fully stabilised and ready for the upcoming holiday travel season. The airline is operating 2,100 to 2,200 flights daily, serving over a million customers every three days across 138 destinations. It successfully managed recent industry-wide disruptions, including dense fog, and is preparing to introduce its first Airbus A321XLR aircraft for longer routes, with plans to fly to Athens from Delhi and Mumbai starting January 23, 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:55:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c0216e10c98d0787b6083_1766589044571.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UltraTech Cement Unleashes Mega Expansion: India's Production Powerhouse Just Got Bigger! 🚀</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UltraTech-Cement-Unleashes-Mega-Expansion-Indias-Production-Powerhouse-Just-Got-Bigger/694c0126e10c98d0787b5ee9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UltraTech-Cement-Unleashes-Mega-Expansion-Indias-Production-Powerhouse-Just-Got-Bigger/694c0126e10c98d0787b5ee9</guid><description>UltraTech Cement, part of the Aditya Birla Group, has significantly boosted its production capabilities by commissioning an additional 1.8 million tonnes per annum (mtpa) of cement capacity. This expansion, split between its Dhule unit in Maharashtra (0.6 mtpa) and Nathdwara unit in Rajasthan (1.2 mtpa), raises the company's total domestic grey cement manufacturing capacity to an impressive 188.66 mtpa. With global capacity now at 194.06 mtpa, this move solidifies UltraTech's market leadership and its commitment to meeting India's growing infrastructure demands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:55:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c0126e10c98d0787b5ee8_1766589247787.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EU's Crypto Tax Law Kicks In: Reporting Mandatory From January 1st, Threatens Asset Seizure!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EUs-Crypto-Tax-Law-Kicks-In-Reporting-Mandatory-From-January-1st-Threatens-Asset-Seizure/694c015ce10c98d0787b5f34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EUs-Crypto-Tax-Law-Kicks-In-Reporting-Mandatory-From-January-1st-Threatens-Asset-Seizure/694c015ce10c98d0787b5f34</guid><description>The European Union's new crypto tax transparency law, DAC8, begins January 1st. Crypto service providers must report user data and transactions to tax authorities, who will share it across member states. This closes a reporting gap, offering authorities visibility similar to bank accounts, and non-compliance by users could lead to asset embargoes or seizure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:53:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c015ce10c98d0787b5f33_1766589307327.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fuel Demand Slows Sharply: Imports Rise as Gas Use Declines!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Fuel-Demand-Slows-Sharply-Imports-Rise-as-Gas-Use-Declines/694bfff2e10c98d0787b5d51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Fuel-Demand-Slows-Sharply-Imports-Rise-as-Gas-Use-Declines/694bfff2e10c98d0787b5d51</guid><description>India's petroleum product consumption growth has decelerated significantly to 1.4% in FY26, falling short of the historical 4% average. This slowdown, driven by fuel-efficient vehicles, CNG expansion, and electric mobility, has led to a rise in crude oil import dependence to 91%. Natural gas consumption also saw a 4.5% de-growth. However, lower crude oil prices have boosted marketing margins for Oil Marketing Companies (OMCs), supported by stable retail prices and government compensation for LPG under-recoveries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:45:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bfff2e10c98d0787b5d50_1766588549126.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fuel Network Shatters 1 Lakh Milestone: IOCL &amp; Nayara Fuel Rural Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Fuel-Network-Shatters-1-Lakh-Milestone-IOCL-and-Nayara-Fuel-Rural-Surge/694bff41e10c98d0787b5c5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Fuel-Network-Shatters-1-Lakh-Milestone-IOCL-and-Nayara-Fuel-Rural-Surge/694bff41e10c98d0787b5c5b</guid><description>India's fuel station network has surpassed 1 lakh outlets, with state-run Indian Oil Corporation (IOCL) and Rosneft-backed Nayara Energy leading a significant rural expansion. These companies account for over a third of their networks in villages. While IOCL has nearly 33% of its 41,000+ stations rural, Nayara Energy boasts about 31% of its 6,921 stations serving smaller towns. This expansion signals robust demand growth in India's automotive fuel sector, projected to increase by 5.37% annually until 2030.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:44:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bff41e10c98d0787b5c5a_1766588584256.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Prediction Dec 26: Bullish Bias Holds? Experts Reveal Crucial Support &amp; Resistance Levels!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Nifty-Prediction-Dec-26-Bullish-Bias-Holds-Experts-Reveal-Crucial-Support-and-Resistance-Levels/694bf9d4e10c98d0787b556d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Nifty-Prediction-Dec-26-Bullish-Bias-Holds-Experts-Reveal-Crucial-Support-and-Resistance-Levels/694bf9d4e10c98d0787b556d</guid><description>Indian stock markets, Sensex and Nifty, closed lower on Wednesday, December 24, ending a three-day rally amid volatile trade and subdued volumes. Analysts maintain a bullish outlook for Nifty's prediction on Friday, December 26, identifying support near 26,000 and resistance around 26,240-26,325. A stock-specific approach is recommended as the market anticipates consolidation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:24:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf9d4e10c98d0787b556c_1766587397037.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Panacea Biotech Scores Big: UNICEF Boosts Vaccine Orders by $8.9 Million!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Panacea-Biotech-Scores-Big-UNICEF-Boosts-Vaccine-Orders-by-89-Million/694bf949e10c98d0787b543f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Panacea-Biotech-Scores-Big-UNICEF-Boosts-Vaccine-Orders-by-89-Million/694bf949e10c98d0787b543f</guid><description>Panacea Biotec has received significant updates to its UNICEF contract for the WHO-pre-qualified Easyfive-TT pentavalent vaccine. Contract values for 2026 and 2027 have increased by a combined $5.25 million, and a new award for 2027 adds $3.68 million, totaling approximately $8.9 million in additional orders. This follows a substantial previous order for polio vaccines, strengthening the company's partnership with the UN agency. Panacea Biotec shares closed up 0.93%.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:24:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf949e10c98d0787b543e_1766586789087.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPF Claim Rejections Haunt Employees! Avoid These Costly Mistakes &amp; Secure Your Savings Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/EPF-Claim-Rejections-Haunt-Employees-Avoid-These-Costly-Mistakes-and-Secure-Your-Savings-Now/694bf992e10c98d0787b54c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/EPF-Claim-Rejections-Haunt-Employees-Avoid-These-Costly-Mistakes-and-Secure-Your-Savings-Now/694bf992e10c98d0787b54c8</guid><description>Many salaried employees face EPF claim rejections due to common, avoidable errors. Issues like incomplete KYC, name or bank details not matching EPFO records, inactive UAN, or incorrect withdrawal reasons are frequent culprits. Mismatched spellings between Aadhaar and PF portal, or invalid bank account details, can also lead to rejection. Employees are advised to meticulously check all personal and bank information, ensure their UAN is active and linked, and select correct withdrawal reasons. Submitting joint declaration forms for discrepancies and seeking guidance from employers or EPFO offices can help prevent these rejections and ensure timely access to PF savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:21:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf992e10c98d0787b54c7_1766587297852.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Novo Nordisk's Miracle Pill Approved: Stock Surges 9% – Is This the Future of Weight Loss?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisks-Miracle-Pill-Approved-Stock-Surges-9percent-Is-This-the-Future-of-Weight-Loss/694bf93be10c98d0787b540d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisks-Miracle-Pill-Approved-Stock-Surges-9percent-Is-This-the-Future-of-Weight-Loss/694bf93be10c98d0787b540d</guid><description>Novo Nordisk has received FDA approval for its new Wegovy weight-loss pill, a potential game-changer for the global obesity drug market. Clinical trials show the pill leads to an average 16.6% body weight loss over 64 weeks, surpassing competitor Eli Lilly's experimental pill. This convenient pill format may unlock the market for millions who avoid injections, positioning Novo Nordisk for a strong comeback.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:15:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf93be10c98d0787b540c_1766587016871.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Strikes Deal: Russian Crude Flows Back to Jamnagar Refinery Amid Sanctions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Reliance-Strikes-Deal-Russian-Crude-Flows-Back-to-Jamnagar-Refinery-Amid-Sanctions/694bf6d9e10c98d0787b50ab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Reliance-Strikes-Deal-Russian-Crude-Flows-Back-to-Jamnagar-Refinery-Amid-Sanctions/694bf6d9e10c98d0787b50ab</guid><description>Reliance Industries has resumed buying discounted Russian crude oil for its Jamnagar refinery in Gujarat. The company is sourcing barrels from non-sanctioned suppliers, a move expected to help stabilize India's overall purchases of Russian oil after a temporary halt due to international sanctions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:06:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf6d9e10c98d0787b50aa_1766586436122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Star's Sales Comeback: Early Wins Signal Hope, But What's Next for 2026?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Blue-Stars-Sales-Comeback-Early-Wins-Signal-Hope-But-Whats-Next-for-2026/694bf6b6e10c98d0787b507b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Blue-Stars-Sales-Comeback-Early-Wins-Signal-Hope-But-Whats-Next-for-2026/694bf6b6e10c98d0787b507b</guid><description>Blue Star Managing Director B Thiagarajan reports early signs of a pickup in air-conditioner sales after a difficult year for the industry. While the second half is expected to be better than the first, it won't fully compensate for the summer slowdown. Thiagarajan notes improved sales traction from the festive period through December and expresses optimism for the upcoming quarter and calendar year 2026, citing strong fundamentals. Challenges remain, including slower project finalisation and the upcoming energy label transition impacting costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:06:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf6b6e10c98d0787b507a_1766586675095.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Rs 1,000 Crore NCD Plan: Board Greenlights Draft Prospectus!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Adani-Enterprises-Rs-1000-Crore-NCD-Plan-Board-Greenlights-Draft-Prospectus/694bf177e10c98d0787b4ad3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Adani-Enterprises-Rs-1000-Crore-NCD-Plan-Board-Greenlights-Draft-Prospectus/694bf177e10c98d0787b4ad3</guid><description>Adani Enterprises Limited has approved the draft prospectus for its upcoming Non-Convertible Debenture (NCD) issuance, aiming to raise up to ₹1,000 crore. The fundraising plan includes a base issue of ₹500 crore with an option to retain an over-subscription of another ₹500 crore. The draft prospectus has been filed with the BSE, the National Stock Exchange of India, and the Securities and Exchange Board of India.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:49:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf177e10c98d0787b4ad2_1766584874144.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto Dealmaking Explodes: Record $8.6 Billion in M&amp;A Fueled by Landmark US Policy Shift!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-Dealmaking-Explodes-Record-86-Billion-in-MandA-Fueled-by-Landmark-US-Policy-Shift/694bf102e10c98d0787b49ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-Dealmaking-Explodes-Record-86-Billion-in-MandA-Fueled-by-Landmark-US-Policy-Shift/694bf102e10c98d0787b49ed</guid><description>Cryptocurrency mergers and acquisitions hit an all-time high of $8.6 billion in 2025, a significant jump from $2.17 billion the previous year. This surge is largely attributed to supportive regulatory developments from the Trump administration, which established a federal framework for stablecoins and tokenized assets. The favorable policy environment fueled 267 deals, an 18% increase, with major transactions including Deribit, Kraken's acquisition of NinjaTrader, and Ripple's significant purchase. Experts also cite a rush for licenses as financial institutions acquire firms to enter crypto markets amidst evolving global compliance rules like the EU's MiCA framework. Despite structural advancements and increased Total Value Locked (TVL) across ecosystems, 2025 saw stagnant large-cap token prices, highlighting a decoupling of network usage from market performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:46:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf102e10c98d0787b49ec_1766584759717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Logistics Giant Yatayat Corporation Eyes Stock Market Debut: IPO Filing Sparks Investor Buzz!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Logistics-Giant-Yatayat-Corporation-Eyes-Stock-Market-Debut-IPO-Filing-Sparks-Investor-Buzz/694bf0ade10c98d0787b48df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Logistics-Giant-Yatayat-Corporation-Eyes-Stock-Market-Debut-IPO-Filing-Sparks-Investor-Buzz/694bf0ade10c98d0787b48df</guid><description>Gujarat-based Yatayat Corporation India has filed preliminary IPO papers with SEBI to raise capital. The offering includes a fresh issue of 77 lakh shares and an offer-for-sale of 56 lakh shares by promoter Meena Praveen Aggarwal. Proceeds will primarily fund working capital needs and general corporate purposes. Yatayat Corporation reported significant profit growth in fiscal year 2025, with revenue increasing by 28.6 percent.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:46:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf0ade10c98d0787b48de_1766584659223.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IBBI's New Mandate: Beneficial Ownership Disclosure Now Key in Company Resolution Plans!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IBBIs-New-Mandate-Beneficial-Ownership-Disclosure-Now-Key-in-Company-Resolution-Plans/694bf05ce10c98d0787b47b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IBBIs-New-Mandate-Beneficial-Ownership-Disclosure-Now-Key-in-Company-Resolution-Plans/694bf05ce10c98d0787b47b5</guid><description>The Insolvency and Bankruptcy Board of India (IBBI) has made it mandatory to disclose beneficial ownership in resolution plans. This new rule requires identifying ultimate owners and their shareholding structures, aiming to curb opaque bids and prevent ineligible promoters from acquiring distressed companies. It enhances transparency and reduces post-resolution disputes, alongside requiring an affidavit for Section 32A eligibility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:39:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf05ce10c98d0787b47b4_1766584523122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Oil Tensions Rock Energy Flows: How India Is Masterfully Securing Cheaper Fuel!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Global-Oil-Tensions-Rock-Energy-Flows-How-India-Is-Masterfully-Securing-Cheaper-Fuel/694bf067e10c98d0787b4827</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Global-Oil-Tensions-Rock-Energy-Flows-How-India-Is-Masterfully-Securing-Cheaper-Fuel/694bf067e10c98d0787b4827</guid><description>India's oil refiners are skillfully navigating 2025's geopolitical and trade challenges, including US sanctions on Russian oil. By diversifying suppliers to the UAE, Saudi Arabia, the US, Brazil, and African nations, India is ensuring energy security and affordable fuel prices for its citizens, maintaining strategic autonomy amidst global volatility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bf067e10c98d0787b4826_1766584662893.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Two-Wheeler Exports Surge 24%! Latin America &amp; Africa Fueling Massive Global Demand!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Two-Wheeler-Exports-Surge-24percent-Latin-America-and-Africa-Fueling-Massive-Global-Demand/694befbbe10c98d0787b46ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Two-Wheeler-Exports-Surge-24percent-Latin-America-and-Africa-Fueling-Massive-Global-Demand/694befbbe10c98d0787b46ea</guid><description>Indian two-wheeler exports have seen a remarkable 24% year-on-year growth from April to November 2025, driven by strong demand in key markets like Latin America and Africa. A total of 42,43,330 units were exported. Motorcycles accounted for 87% of these exports, showing a 27% increase, while scooters grew by 8%. Bajaj Auto Limited, TVS Motor Company, and Hero MotoCorp Limited are leading this export momentum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:38:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694befbbe10c98d0787b46e9_1766584527273.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NTPC Green Energy Ignites India's Power Grid: 69 MW Solar Capacity Comes Online!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/NTPC-Green-Energy-Ignites-Indias-Power-Grid-69-MW-Solar-Capacity-Comes-Online/694bea5ce10c98d0787b4228</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/NTPC-Green-Energy-Ignites-Indias-Power-Grid-69-MW-Solar-Capacity-Comes-Online/694bea5ce10c98d0787b4228</guid><description>NTPC Green Energy Limited has successfully commissioned an additional 69.04 MW of solar power capacity at its Khavda-I project in Gujarat. This expansion brings the total commercial operational capacity of the NTPC Green Energy Group to 7,996.30 MW, reinforcing its significant role in India's renewable energy landscape. The Khavda project is situated in a region known for its high solar potential and robust energy infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:16:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bea5ce10c98d0787b4227_1766582999976.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Castrol India Jumps as Big Players Launch 26% Stake Buyout Offer After BP Exits!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Castrol-India-Jumps-as-Big-Players-Launch-26percent-Stake-Buyout-Offer-After-BP-Exits/694bea1ee10c98d0787b41b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Castrol-India-Jumps-as-Big-Players-Launch-26percent-Stake-Buyout-Offer-After-BP-Exits/694bea1ee10c98d0787b41b0</guid><description>Motion JVCo, Stonepeak, and Canada Pension Plan Investment Board are launching an open offer to buy up to 26% of Castrol India for ₹194.04 per share. This follows British Petroleum's deal to sell a 65% stake in the global Castrol business to Stonepeak. Castrol India shares rose 1.81% to ₹189.30 on the NSE before the open offer announcement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:16:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bea1ee10c98d0787b41af_1766583304805.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 125 Crore South Delhi Bungalow: Select Group's Luxury Real Estate Power Play Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Rs-125-Crore-South-Delhi-Bungalow-Select-Groups-Luxury-Real-Estate-Power-Play-Revealed/694be973e10c98d0787b40bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Rs-125-Crore-South-Delhi-Bungalow-Select-Groups-Luxury-Real-Estate-Power-Play-Revealed/694be973e10c98d0787b40bc</guid><description>Select Group, through its subsidiary Select World Tours India Private Limited, has acquired a bungalow in South Delhi's Westend Colony for Rs 125 crore. The property spans 668.90 square meters and represents a significant investment in one of Delhi's most exclusive residential areas. The deal, registered on October 14, 2025, highlights continued interest in premium real estate assets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:13:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be973e10c98d0787b40bb_1766583188071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Urban Company IPO Buzz Fizzles? Stock Plunges 25% After Record Debut! What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Urban-Company-IPO-Buzz-Fizzles-Stock-Plunges-25percent-After-Record-Debut-Whats-Next/694be6a7e10c98d0787b3df8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Urban-Company-IPO-Buzz-Fizzles-Stock-Plunges-25percent-After-Record-Debut-Whats-Next/694be6a7e10c98d0787b3df8</guid><description>Urban Company, a leading service provider, expanded into products like air conditioners under its 'Native' brand and launched quick services 'InstaHelp' in 2025. After a stellar IPO, oversubscribed nearly 104X and listing at a 57% premium, the company returned to losses in Q2 FY26 due to heavy investment in new verticals. Facing competition and operational challenges, the stock has dropped 25.16% since its debut.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:05:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be6a7e10c98d0787b3df7_1766582624853.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Robot Masters: Local Code Drives World-Class Humanoids &amp; Robodogs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Robot-Masters-Local-Code-Drives-World-Class-Humanoids-and-Robodogs/694be389e10c98d0787b3a91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Robot-Masters-Local-Code-Drives-World-Class-Humanoids-and-Robodogs/694be389e10c98d0787b3a91</guid><description>Indian robotics startups are showcasing advanced humanoid and quadruped robots, often nicknamed 'robodogs,' at events like IIT Bombay's Techfest. While these companies excel at complex local programming and software development, they heavily rely on sourcing critical hardware components such as motors, actuators, and sensors from international markets, primarily China and Switzerland. Despite these supply chain challenges, the deployment of industrial robots in India has seen significant growth over the last decade, though humanoids remain a niche category primarily in the research and development phase.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:46:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be389e10c98d0787b3a90_1766582122690.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supreme Industries Bags ₹54 Crore BPCL LPG Cylinder Order: What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Supreme-Industries-Bags-54-Crore-BPCL-LPG-Cylinder-Order-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694be330e10c98d0787b39ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Supreme-Industries-Bags-54-Crore-BPCL-LPG-Cylinder-Order-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694be330e10c98d0787b39ed</guid><description>Supreme Industries Limited has received a significant repeat order from Bharat Petroleum Corporation Limited (BPCL) for supplying approximately 2 lakh 10-kg composite LPG cylinders. The Letter of Acceptance is valued at an estimated ₹54 crore. This contract is valid for six months and may be extended, bolstering the company's order book amid positive volume growth expectations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:45:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be330e10c98d0787b39ec_1766581108579.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal Predicts 2026 Market Boom: Unveils Top Sectors Poised for Explosive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Motilal-Oswal-Predicts-2026-Market-Boom-Unveils-Top-Sectors-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/694be2a1e10c98d0787b38e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Motilal-Oswal-Predicts-2026-Market-Boom-Unveils-Top-Sectors-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/694be2a1e10c98d0787b38e4</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services forecasts steady growth for Indian equity markets in 2026, following a year of consolidation in 2025. Key drivers include recovering corporate earnings, revived private investments, and supportive government policies. The brokerage prefers large-cap stocks, highlighting sectors like Financials, Consumer Discretionary, Automobiles, Industrials, Capital Goods, and IT Services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:42:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be2a1e10c98d0787b38e3_1766581762870.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GST SHOCKER! Auto Dealers' Profits SINGED, Investor Interest DIES as Court Fight LOOMS!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/GST-SHOCKER-Auto-Dealers-Profits-SINGED-Investor-Interest-DIES-as-Court-Fight-LOOMS/694be2c8e10c98d0787b3927</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/GST-SHOCKER-Auto-Dealers-Profits-SINGED-Investor-Interest-DIES-as-Court-Fight-LOOMS/694be2c8e10c98d0787b3927</guid><description>Auto dealers are suffering significant profit margin erosion and declining investor interest following the government's discontinuation of the compensation cess from GST on September 22. Listed dealers like Landmark Cars, Popular Vehicles, and Competent Automobiles have seen share prices fall as they incurred losses clearing old stock. The Federation of Automobile Dealers Associations has taken the issue to the Supreme Court seeking resolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:41:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be2c8e10c98d0787b3926_1766582225539.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Noida Airport: India's Mega Hub to Open Jan 2026! UP CM Confirms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airport-Indias-Mega-Hub-to-Open-Jan-2026-UP-CM-Confirms/694be1cae10c98d0787b3755</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airport-Indias-Mega-Hub-to-Open-Jan-2026-UP-CM-Confirms/694be1cae10c98d0787b3755</guid><description>Uttar Pradesh Chief Minister Yogi Adityanath announced that the Noida International Airport at Jewar will be inaugurated in January 2026. This facility will become Uttar Pradesh's fifth international airport and is set to be India's largest. Developed under a public-private partnership, the greenfield project in Gautam Buddh Nagar district has faced previous delays, with its first phase initially planned for September 2024. Adityanath highlighted the state's rapid infrastructure growth since 2017, with functional airports increasing from four to sixteen.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:39:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be1cae10c98d0787b3754_1766581906920.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBCC's Bold Dubai Move: $4 Million Land Buy Signals Global Real Estate Ambitions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCCs-Bold-Dubai-Move-4-Million-Land-Buy-Signals-Global-Real-Estate-Ambitions/694be1bfe10c98d0787b3721</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCCs-Bold-Dubai-Move-4-Million-Land-Buy-Signals-Global-Real-Estate-Ambitions/694be1bfe10c98d0787b3721</guid><description>State-owned NBCC (India) Ltd has officially stepped into the international real estate market by acquiring nearly 15,000 sq ft of land in Dubai for AED 15 million (approx. ₹37 crore). This strategic purchase, made through its subsidiary NBCC Overseas Real Estate LLC, is earmarked for a mixed-use development, marking a significant expansion of its business overseas.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:38:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be1bfe10c98d0787b3720_1766581044266.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Export Shock: SUVs Surge Past Cars for First Time, Reshaping Global Image!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Export-Shock-SUVs-Surge-Past-Cars-for-First-Time-Reshaping-Global-Image/694be0e9e10c98d0787b35c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Export-Shock-SUVs-Surge-Past-Cars-for-First-Time-Reshaping-Global-Image/694be0e9e10c98d0787b35c1</guid><description>India's automotive export landscape has shifted significantly, with utility vehicles (UVs) now surpassing traditional passenger cars in overseas shipments for the first time in November. This trend mirrors domestic demand, positioning India as a manufacturing hub for higher-value vehicles. Compact SUVs, particularly those under four meters, dominate these exports, reinforcing India's role in supplying fuel-efficient, higher-value compact vehicles globally. Maruti Suzuki leads both car and UV exports, signaling a new era for Indian automotive manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:36:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694be0e9e10c98d0787b35c0_1766581389153.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Europe Air Travel Set for HUGE Boost! Air India Resumes Rome Flights, IndiGo Launches London Service – Is Your Next Trip Easier?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Europe-Air-Travel-Set-for-HUGE-Boost-Air-India-Resumes-Rome-Flights-IndiGo-Launches-London-Service-Is-Your-Next-Trip-Easier/694bdc6ee10c98d0787b30aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Europe-Air-Travel-Set-for-HUGE-Boost-Air-India-Resumes-Rome-Flights-IndiGo-Launches-London-Service-Is-Your-Next-Trip-Easier/694bdc6ee10c98d0787b30aa</guid><description>Air India will resume flights to Rome from Delhi four times weekly starting March 25, 2026, using Boeing 787-8 aircraft. Simultaneously, IndiGo will launch direct flights from Delhi to London Heathrow five times a week from February 2, 2026, using leased Boeing 787s. These expansions aim to enhance India-Europe connectivity for business and leisure travellers, bolstering both airlines' international networks and reflecting growing demand.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:13:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdc6ee10c98d0787b30a9_1766579402698.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Stocks Hit Brakes, Metals Rally: Expert Rohit Srivastava's Crucial Market Forecast!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/IT-Stocks-Hit-Brakes-Metals-Rally-Expert-Rohit-Srivastavas-Crucial-Market-Forecast/694bdbb8e10c98d0787b2f1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/IT-Stocks-Hit-Brakes-Metals-Rally-Expert-Rohit-Srivastavas-Crucial-Market-Forecast/694bdbb8e10c98d0787b2f1e</guid><description>Market expert Rohit Srivastava, founder of Strike Money Analytics and Indiacharts, forecasts the Nifty may reach 26,500 before December expiry. He expresses long-term caution on the IT sector despite short-term trading potential, while advocating for metals like Hindalco and National Aluminium as top picks for the Santa Rally, driven by a weakening dollar and rising commodity prices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:13:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdbb8e10c98d0787b2f1d_1766579582094.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Premier Energies Strikes Major Deal: Acquires Significant Stake in Transcon Ind for ₹250 Crore!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premier-Energies-Strikes-Major-Deal-Acquires-Significant-Stake-in-Transcon-Ind-for-250-Crore/694bdb3ae10c98d0787b2e30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premier-Energies-Strikes-Major-Deal-Acquires-Significant-Stake-in-Transcon-Ind-for-250-Crore/694bdb3ae10c98d0787b2e30</guid><description>Premier Energies Limited has successfully acquired a 34.21% equity stake in Transcon Ind Ltd for ₹250 crore. This marks the first phase of their planned acquisition, aiming for a total 51% stake. The deal, structured in tranches linked to Transcon Ind's capital expenditure, is expected to see its remaining stages completed by February 20, 2026. This strategic move positions Premier Energies to increase its control over Transcon Ind.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:13:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdb3ae10c98d0787b2e2f_1766579252588.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CESC Subsidiary Lands Massive 180 MW Renewable Deal! 25-Year Contract Ignites Investor Interest</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/CESC-Subsidiary-Lands-Massive-180-MW-Renewable-Deal-25-Year-Contract-Ignites-Investor-Interest/694bdbfee10c98d0787b2fed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/CESC-Subsidiary-Lands-Massive-180-MW-Renewable-Deal-25-Year-Contract-Ignites-Investor-Interest/694bdbfee10c98d0787b2fed</guid><description>CESC Limited's subsidiary, Purvah Green Power Private Limited, has been awarded a significant 180 MW round-the-clock (RTC) renewable energy project by REMC Limited. This 25-year contract, secured through competitive bidding, marks a substantial step for CESC in the expanding renewable energy sector, complementing its recent strong financial performance which saw a 20.4% rise in net profit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdbfee10c98d0787b2fec_1766580110378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manba Finance Powers TVS Electric 3-Wheelers: New Pan-India Funding Deal to Accelerate EV Adoption!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manba-Finance-Powers-TVS-Electric-3-Wheelers-New-Pan-India-Funding-Deal-to-Accelerate-EV-Adoption/694bdb62e10c98d0787b2e8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manba-Finance-Powers-TVS-Electric-3-Wheelers-New-Pan-India-Funding-Deal-to-Accelerate-EV-Adoption/694bdb62e10c98d0787b2e8f</guid><description>Manba Finance Limited has partnered with TVS Motor Company Limited through a new Memorandum of Understanding. This collaboration designates Manba Finance as the preferred financier for all TVS three-wheelers across India, with a strategic emphasis on electric models. The phased, pan-India rollout aims to boost EV financing and reduce ownership barriers for entrepreneurs and fleet operators, supporting India's sustainable mobility goals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:12:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdb62e10c98d0787b2e8e_1766579727547.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SFIO Launches Shock Probe into IndusInd Bank: Accounting Red Flags Uncovered!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SFIO-Launches-Shock-Probe-into-IndusInd-Bank-Accounting-Red-Flags-Uncovered/694bdaa7e10c98d0787b2da7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SFIO-Launches-Shock-Probe-into-IndusInd-Bank-Accounting-Red-Flags-Uncovered/694bdaa7e10c98d0787b2da7</guid><description>The Serious Fraud Investigation Office (SFIO) has started a formal investigation into IndusInd Bank's accounting practices under Section 212 of the Companies Act, 2013. This probe follows concerns raised by auditors regarding derivative trades, unsubstantiated balances, and microfinance interest income. IndusInd Bank has stated it is cooperating fully with the authorities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:12:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bdaa7e10c98d0787b2da6_1766579139147.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2025 Travel Surge: Faith, Festivals &amp; Spontaneous Trips Dominate Bookings!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-2025-Travel-Surge-Faith-Festivals-and-Spontaneous-Trips-Dominate-Bookings/694bd967e10c98d0787b2c1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-2025-Travel-Surge-Faith-Festivals-and-Spontaneous-Trips-Dominate-Bookings/694bd967e10c98d0787b2c1c</guid><description>Paytm Travel's 2025 recap reveals faith-based journeys, particularly the Kumbh Mela in Prayagraj, drove significant growth, with bookings tripling. Festival travel, like Chhath Puja flights to Patna, also saw spikes. Decisions increasingly align with salary cycles, favoring spontaneous short breaks. Entertainment events are spurring travel, while leisure spots like Srinagar and Goa remain popular. Tier-2 cities like Indore and Kochi are showing steady inbound growth, reflecting evolving Indian travel preferences.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:03:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bd967e10c98d0787b2c1b_1766578640709.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Premji Invest's ₹754 Crore Infrastructure Power Play: Big Bet on India's Highways!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premji-Invests-754-Crore-Infrastructure-Power-Play-Big-Bet-on-Indias-Highways/694bd8cce10c98d0787b2ac9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premji-Invests-754-Crore-Infrastructure-Power-Play-Big-Bet-on-Indias-Highways/694bd8cce10c98d0787b2ac9</guid><description>Premji Invest, the family office of Azim Premji, has invested ₹754 crore to acquire a 2.61% stake in National Highways Infra Trust (NHIT). This strategic move through Prazim Trading signals strong investor confidence in India's infrastructure development and the government's asset monetization initiatives. NHIT, sponsored by NHAI, offers exposure to operational highway assets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:03:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bd8cce10c98d0787b2ac8_1766578620968.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Wedding Season Fuels Jewellery Boom: Diamonds Steal the Show as Spending Soars!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Wedding-Season-Fuels-Jewellery-Boom-Diamonds-Steal-the-Show-as-Spending-Soars/694bd34ae10c98d0787b25ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Wedding-Season-Fuels-Jewellery-Boom-Diamonds-Steal-the-Show-as-Spending-Soars/694bd34ae10c98d0787b25ba</guid><description>Jewellery demand is strong this wedding season, driven by higher spending and a noticeable shift towards diamond products, according to C Krishniah Chetty Group. India's overall wedding spending is nearing ₹6.5 lakh crore, with jewellery capturing a significant share. Consumers are increasingly opting for premium diamond bridal sets and solitaires, influenced by moderating diamond prices and a desire for contemporary designs. Traditional gold items and coins also see steady demand for wealth preservation, though gold price volatility prompts flexible buying strategies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:39:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bd34ae10c98d0787b25b9_1766577096045.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's REIT Market Set to Explode: Experts Reveal Massive Growth Potential!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-REIT-Market-Set-to-Explode-Experts-Reveal-Massive-Growth-Potential/694bd2b0e10c98d0787b2515</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-REIT-Market-Set-to-Explode-Experts-Reveal-Massive-Growth-Potential/694bd2b0e10c98d0787b2515</guid><description>India's Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT) market is poised for significant expansion, with less than 20% of Grade A office stock currently housed under REITs. Experts see substantial room for growth and new listings across offices, retail, hospitality, and warehousing. With market capitalization reaching $18 billion, REITs are increasingly recognized as equity instruments offering dividends and long-term capital appreciation, driven by strong demand for income-generating commercial assets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:39:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bd2b0e10c98d0787b2514_1766577918404.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Whisky Secret: How Surrinder Kumar Created Global Single Malt Stars and Skyrocketed Stocks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Whisky-Secret-How-Surrinder-Kumar-Created-Global-Single-Malt-Stars-and-Skyrocketed-Stocks/694bd32de10c98d0787b258b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Whisky-Secret-How-Surrinder-Kumar-Created-Global-Single-Malt-Stars-and-Skyrocketed-Stocks/694bd32de10c98d0787b258b</guid><description>Surrinder Kumar, a former agriculture officer, is revolutionizing the Indian single malt whisky industry. He played a pivotal role in developing Amrut Classic and later transformed Indri into India's best-selling single malt. His expertise in distillation, maturation, and flavour profiles has put Indian whiskies on the global map, with sales now surpassing imports and boosting companies like Piccadily Agro Industries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:35:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bd32de10c98d0787b258a_1766577249746.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's STQC Norms Unleash Surge in Domestic Surveillance Tech! Is Your Portfolio Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-STQC-Norms-Unleash-Surge-in-Domestic-Surveillance-Tech-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/694bcdf0e10c98d0787b20a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-STQC-Norms-Unleash-Surge-in-Domestic-Surveillance-Tech-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/694bcdf0e10c98d0787b20a8</guid><description>New government Standardisation Testing and Quality Certification (STQC) norms have significantly boosted India's security and surveillance market. According to Aditya Khemka, founder of Aditya Infotech, these regulations enhance trust and compliance, allowing domestic players to expand capacity and capture more market share. Global firms also see entry opportunities, driven by stricter audits covering supply-chain security and data protection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:07:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bcdf0e10c98d0787b20a7_1766575988021.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>