<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:59 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Torrent Power Buys Nabha Power for ₹6,889 Cr, Entering Northern India Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Buys-Nabha-Power-for-6889-Cr-Entering-Northern-India-Market/6992bc832e6a0b8ae17cb79a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Buys-Nabha-Power-for-6889-Cr-Entering-Northern-India-Market/6992bc832e6a0b8ae17cb79a</guid><description>Torrent Power is buying Nabha Power Limited for ₹6,889 Crores, significantly expanding its power generation capacity by 1,400 MW. This move marks its entry into the northern India power market and is expected to boost revenue and profits, leveraging Nabha Power's operational track record and contracted cash flows.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:43:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992bc832e6a0b8ae17cb799_1771224312515.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Jet Healthcare Plummets: Margin Woes Deepen Amidst Capex Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Plummets-Margin-Woes-Deepen-Amidst-Capex-Risks/6992bc102e6a0b8ae17cb6f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Plummets-Margin-Woes-Deepen-Amidst-Capex-Risks/6992bc102e6a0b8ae17cb6f5</guid><description>Blue Jet Healthcare's stock plunged to a 52-week low after reporting a significant earnings decline for Q3FY26, driven by revenue drops and severe margin compression. Analysts are sharply divided on the company's outlook, with concerns mounting over the execution risks associated with a substantial ₹1,300 crore capital expenditure plan, overshadowing its established strengths. The company's P/E ratio now stands at approximately 19.6x, trading below industry averages but reflecting investor caution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:41:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992bc102e6a0b8ae17cb6f4_1771224289239.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BHEL Stock Navigates Post-OFS Valuation Amidst Energy Policy Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BHEL-Stock-Navigates-Post-OFS-Valuation-Amidst-Energy-Policy-Shift/6992bc012e6a0b8ae17cb6cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BHEL-Stock-Navigates-Post-OFS-Valuation-Amidst-Energy-Policy-Shift/6992bc012e6a0b8ae17cb6cc</guid><description>Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited (BHEL) shares traded higher following the government's successful completion of a 5% stake sale via Offer for Sale (OFS), which raised ₹4,470 crore. Despite recent price volatility, analysts largely maintain a positive outlook, citing a substantial order book of ₹2.23 trillion and potential benefits from India's new National Electricity Policy. However, differing analyst targets and technical indicators suggest investor caution regarding current valuations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:41:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992bc012e6a0b8ae17cb6cb_1771224257019.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ONGC Rally: Bullish Brokerage Calls Meet Capital Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Rally-Bullish-Brokerage-Calls-Meet-Capital-Risk/6992bbae2e6a0b8ae17cb5b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Rally-Bullish-Brokerage-Calls-Meet-Capital-Risk/6992bbae2e6a0b8ae17cb5b8</guid><description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd (ONGC) shares saw a near 2% increase on February 16, supported by CLSA and Jefferies reiterating 'Buy' ratings following solid December-quarter results. The company reported a 23% year-on-year net profit gain, underpinned by expectations of future production increases from new projects. Despite this optimism, concerns around capital allocation strategies and the inherent volatility of crude oil markets present a more complex investment outlook for the energy giant.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:39:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992bbae2e6a0b8ae17cb5b7_1771224117552.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apollo Pipes Rally: Promoter Buys Amidst Deepening Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apollo-Pipes-Rally-Promoter-Buys-Amidst-Deepening-Losses/6992bbab2e6a0b8ae17cb5a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apollo-Pipes-Rally-Promoter-Buys-Amidst-Deepening-Losses/6992bbab2e6a0b8ae17cb5a1</guid><description>Apollo Pipes has surged 24% in February, significantly outperforming the Nifty MidCap index's 1.8% gain, following five months of decline. This rally, bolstered by a promoter stake purchase on February 13, 2026, contrasts sharply with Q3 FY26 results showing a net loss of ₹4.8 crore and declining income. Analysts point to technical improvements, including a trendline break, suggesting potential upside to ₹360 if support holds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:39:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992bbab2e6a0b8ae17cb5a0_1771224119113.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EaseMyTrip Secures ₹500 Cr Capital Raise Amid Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/EaseMyTrip-Secures-500-Cr-Capital-Raise-Amid-Profit-Slump/6992bba52e6a0b8ae17cb588</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/EaseMyTrip-Secures-500-Cr-Capital-Raise-Amid-Profit-Slump/6992bba52e6a0b8ae17cb588</guid><description>EaseMyTrip shares rose 11% following news of a proposed ₹500 crore capital raise. This infusion is intended to bolster hotels, holiday packages, and technology investments. The move comes shortly after the company reported a significant year-on-year drop in net profit for the December quarter, highlighting a strategy to secure growth capital amidst prevailing financial headwinds and a competitive market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:39:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992bba52e6a0b8ae17cb587_1771224079810.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Lending Clampdown Hits Capital Markets: BSE, Angel One Stocks Dive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/RBIs-Lending-Clampdown-Hits-Capital-Markets-BSE-Angel-One-Stocks-Dive/6992bb672e6a0b8ae17cb51e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/RBIs-Lending-Clampdown-Hits-Capital-Markets-BSE-Angel-One-Stocks-Dive/6992bb672e6a0b8ae17cb51e</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's February 13 directive to tighten bank lending for capital market intermediaries sent shockwaves through the sector on February 16, 2026. BSE Ltd shares plummeted by up to 10%, while Angel One Ltd saw declines of over 4% as the new rules restricting proprietary trading and increasing collateral requirements took effect. The Nifty Capital Markets index also registered significant losses, reflecting broader investor concerns over increased operational costs and potential impacts on derivatives market liquidity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:38:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992bb672e6a0b8ae17cb51d_1771224073104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Techno Electric Funds Shift After Project Cancellation; Rs 227 Cr Remain Unused</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Techno-Electric-Funds-Shift-After-Project-Cancellation-Rs-227-Cr-Remain-Unused/6992bb602e6a0b8ae17cb4f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Techno-Electric-Funds-Shift-After-Project-Cancellation-Rs-227-Cr-Remain-Unused/6992bb602e6a0b8ae17cb4f5</guid><description>Techno Electric &amp; Engineering Company Limited reported a deviation in its ₹1,250 crore QIP fund utilization for the quarter ending December 2025. The cancellation of the Government of India's NERGS I project led to a ₹200 crore reallocation towards its Chennai data center. A significant ₹226.68 crore remains unutilized, invested in short-term funds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:38:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992bb602e6a0b8ae17cb4f4_1771224020165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lupin's Q3 Surge Faces Competition Horizon, Analyst Downgrade</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupins-Q3-Surge-Faces-Competition-Horizon-Analyst-Downgrade/6992bab22e6a0b8ae17cb328</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupins-Q3-Surge-Faces-Competition-Horizon-Analyst-Downgrade/6992bab22e6a0b8ae17cb328</guid><description>Lupin posted a robust Q3FY26 with EBITDA surging 62% year-over-year to Rs22 billion, driven by peak US sales from niche products like gTolvaptan and a strong flu season. This marks a significant turnaround over three years, with EBITDA increasing fivefold. However, the company's reliance on three core products, which contribute half of its EPS, faces competition from H2FY27, potentially leading to a PAT decline through FY28, prompting a downgrade to 'Accumulate' by Prabhudas Lilladher.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:35:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992bab22e6a0b8ae17cb327_1771223889313.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HG Infra: Valuation Hopes Clash With Debt, Execution Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HG-Infra-Valuation-Hopes-Clash-With-Debt-Execution-Woes/6992baad2e6a0b8ae17cb30c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HG-Infra-Valuation-Hopes-Clash-With-Debt-Execution-Woes/6992baad2e6a0b8ae17cb30c</guid><description>HG Infra Engineering's Q3 FY26 performance revealed standalone revenue contraction and a significant drop in profit, exacerbated by a surge in debt-to-equity ratio to 1.84x and elevated interest expenses. While management guides for FY27 growth and a brokerage firm retains an 'Accumulate' rating with a target price of ₹724, nearly 40% of its substantial order book remains slow-moving due to execution hurdles. This disconnect between future potential and present financial strain warrants investor caution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:35:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992baad2e6a0b8ae17cb30b_1771223838777.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Home Loan Rates Stable: Borrower Profile Dictates Choice</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Home-Loan-Rates-Stable-Borrower-Profile-Dictates-Choice/6992baa92e6a0b8ae17cb2f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Home-Loan-Rates-Stable-Borrower-Profile-Dictates-Choice/6992baa92e6a0b8ae17cb2f4</guid><description>India's home loan market is experiencing a stable phase as the RBI maintains its repo rate, shifting the crucial decision between fixed and floating options from market prediction to individual financial circumstances. Fixed-rate loans offer predictable EMIs but at a higher cost and potential prepayment penalties, while floating rates, though variable, typically start lower and offer more long-term savings and flexibility. Experts stress that personalized financial assessment, not market timing, should guide this choice in the current environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:35:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992baa92e6a0b8ae17cb2f3_1771223907200.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ONGC Rating Downgrade: Volume Woes Dampen Oil Giant's Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Rating-Downgrade-Volume-Woes-Dampen-Oil-Giants-Outlook/6992baa62e6a0b8ae17cb2dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ONGC-Rating-Downgrade-Volume-Woes-Dampen-Oil-Giants-Outlook/6992baa62e6a0b8ae17cb2dd</guid><description>Prabhudas Lilladher downgraded ONGC to 'Accumulate,' citing challenges in achieving sustainable volume growth and lower oil price realizations. Despite a modest year-over-year profit increase driven by tax benefits, sequential performance and revenue showed declines. The brokerage forecasts a subdued production CAGR and set a target price of ₹297, reflecting these headwinds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:35:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992baa62e6a0b8ae17cb2dc_1771223869965.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Federal Bank Secures ₹6196 Crore Investment from Blackstone Arm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Federal-Bank-Secures-6196-Crore-Investment-from-Blackstone-Arm/6992ba202e6a0b8ae17cb1dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Federal-Bank-Secures-6196-Crore-Investment-from-Blackstone-Arm/6992ba202e6a0b8ae17cb1dc</guid><description>Federal Bank's board has approved a substantial ₹6,196.51 crore preferential allotment of warrants to Asia II Topco XIII Pte. Ltd., an investment entity affiliated with Blackstone. The deal, priced at ₹227 per warrant, is set to strengthen the bank's capital base, with the investor potentially holding 9.99% stake and gaining board representation rights. The transaction awaits shareholder and regulatory approvals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:33:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992ba202e6a0b8ae17cb1db_1771223711440.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Brezza Facelift: Turbo Engine &amp; Premium Push Amidst Segment Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Brezza-Facelift-Turbo-Engine-and-Premium-Push-Amidst-Segment-Shift/6992b9a92e6a0b8ae17cb134</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Brezza-Facelift-Turbo-Engine-and-Premium-Push-Amidst-Segment-Shift/6992b9a92e6a0b8ae17cb134</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki is set to launch a significantly updated 2026 Brezza facelift, featuring a new 1.2-liter turbo petrol engine and a 6-speed gearbox, alongside a premium dual-tone interior with ventilated seats and a larger 10.25-inch infotainment display. This overhaul aims to bolster its competitiveness in the compact SUV segment, which is experiencing a slowdown but remains crucial for market share. However, the facelift is projected for a 3-4 month delay, and notably lacks advanced driver-assistance systems (ADAS) offered by key rivals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b9a92e6a0b8ae17cb133_1771223627503.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asia's Coal Contraction: China's Decline, India's Pause</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Asias-Coal-Contraction-Chinas-Decline-Indias-Pause/6992b8db2e6a0b8ae17cafce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Asias-Coal-Contraction-Chinas-Decline-Indias-Pause/6992b8db2e6a0b8ae17cafce</guid><description>Coal-fired electricity generation in China and India fell in 2025, a historic first in fifty years, according to the IEA. This was driven by slower demand growth and a surge in renewables, especially solar and wind. While China's decline is expected to continue, India's dip is seen as temporary, with coal output poised to rebound. The divergence signals distinct energy transition pathways for the world's largest coal consumers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:27:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b8db2e6a0b8ae17cafcd_1771223379723.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T Sells Power Arm to Torrent Power for ₹3,660 Crore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/LandT-Sells-Power-Arm-to-Torrent-Power-for-3660-Crore/6992b8cc2e6a0b8ae17cafb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/LandT-Sells-Power-Arm-to-Torrent-Power-for-3660-Crore/6992b8cc2e6a0b8ae17cafb2</guid><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T) will sell its entire 100% stake in Nabha Power Limited (NPL) to Torrent Power Limited for ₹3,660.87 crore. This move is part of L&amp;T's strategy to exit non-core assets and focus on its main businesses. For Torrent Power, this acquisition represents a strategic entry into North India's power market, adding a significant operating asset.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:27:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b8cc2e6a0b8ae17cafb1_1771223328701.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kwality Wall's Lists on BSE/NSE After HUL Demerger, New Owner Takes Charge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kwality-Walls-Lists-on-BSENSE-After-HUL-Demerger-New-Owner-Takes-Charge/6992b84f2e6a0b8ae17caefd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kwality-Walls-Lists-on-BSENSE-After-HUL-Demerger-New-Owner-Takes-Charge/6992b84f2e6a0b8ae17caefd</guid><description>Kwality Wall's India Limited has officially listed its shares on the BSE and NSE, marking its debut as a standalone company after demerging from Hindustan Unilever Limited (HUL). The move follows an acquisition deal where The Magnum Ice Cream Company HoldCo 1 Netherlands B.V. (TMICC) is set to acquire a controlling stake. Kwality Wall's aims for focused growth, innovation, and brand building in the dynamic Indian ice cream market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:25:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6992b84f2e6a0b8ae17caefc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>INDO SMC Eyes ₹450 Cr Revenue Amid High Debt Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/INDO-SMC-Eyes-450-Cr-Revenue-Amid-High-Debt-Concerns/6992b8412e6a0b8ae17caee2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/INDO-SMC-Eyes-450-Cr-Revenue-Amid-High-Debt-Concerns/6992b8412e6a0b8ae17caee2</guid><description>INDO SMC Limited outlined ambitious plans for FY27 revenue of ₹450 Cr, driven by diversification into railways, defense, and exports. While Q3 FY26 showed strong sequential growth and improved working capital (receivables down to 40 days), investors must weigh this against a significant Debt-to-Equity ratio of 1.18 and a tight Current Ratio of 1.05. Past negative operating cash flow also requires monitoring.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:25:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b8412e6a0b8ae17caee1_1771223256628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sarda Energy PAT Surges 59%, Debt Drops; Q4 Outlook Positive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sarda-Energy-PAT-Surges-59percent-Debt-Drops-Q4-Outlook-Positive/6992b6d82e6a0b8ae17cad7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sarda-Energy-PAT-Surges-59percent-Debt-Drops-Q4-Outlook-Positive/6992b6d82e6a0b8ae17cad7c</guid><description>Sarda Energy &amp; Minerals Limited reported a strong 59% year-on-year jump in net profit to ₹954 Crores for the first nine months of FY26. The company significantly reduced its consolidated net debt to below ₹500 Crores, from approximately ₹1,500 Crores a year prior. Despite Q3 revenue being impacted by plant shutdowns and weaker prices, EBITDA rose year-on-year. Management projects a better Q4 FY26 and a higher FY27, driven by infrastructure growth and improving commodity prices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:19:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b6d82e6a0b8ae17cad7b_1771222884876.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alivus Life Sciences Plant Fire: Operations Halted, Losses Assessed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alivus-Life-Sciences-Plant-Fire-Operations-Halted-Losses-Assessed/6992b6d72e6a0b8ae17cad66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alivus-Life-Sciences-Plant-Fire-Operations-Halted-Losses-Assessed/6992b6d72e6a0b8ae17cad66</guid><description>A major fire broke out at Alivus Life Sciences' Dahej API manufacturing plant on February 14, 2026. The incident, which caused three injuries, has led to a temporary suspension of operations. The company is currently assessing the financial damage, raising concerns about its production output and financial health.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:19:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b6d72e6a0b8ae17cad65_1771222874247.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindalco: India Strength Masks Novelis Woes, Margin Pressure Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindalco-India-Strength-Masks-Novelis-Woes-Margin-Pressure-Mounts/6992b6682e6a0b8ae17cacd0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindalco-India-Strength-Masks-Novelis-Woes-Margin-Pressure-Mounts/6992b6682e6a0b8ae17cacd0</guid><description>Hindalco Industries reported a mixed Q3FY26. While its Indian operations achieved record profitability, the U.S. subsidiary Novelis faced severe disruptions from plant fires, leading to an increased cash flow impact of $1.3-1.6 billion. Consolidated EBITDA margins compressed to 12.02% from 12.99% year-on-year due to higher costs, and net profit plunged 45% after accounting for a substantial exceptional loss. Despite this, the company maintains comfortable leverage at 1.73x, and its domestic business shows robust growth. Analysts remain mixed, weighing near-term pressures against long-term potential.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:17:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b6682e6a0b8ae17caccf_1771222757249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Syngene Trades at Discount Amid Zoetis Headwinds; Biologics Pivot Eyed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Syngene-Trades-at-Discount-Amid-Zoetis-Headwinds-Biologics-Pivot-Eyed/6992b65e2e6a0b8ae17cacb9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Syngene-Trades-at-Discount-Amid-Zoetis-Headwinds-Biologics-Pivot-Eyed/6992b65e2e6a0b8ae17cacb9</guid><description>Syngene International reported a Q3 FY26 revenue decline of 7% year-over-year in constant currency, primarily due to inventory adjustments by its key client Zoetis, which impacted development and manufacturing services. EBITDA margins compressed to 22.8% amid rising operational costs and facility investments. Despite these short-term headwinds, Syngene is advancing its biologics and clinical services expansion, with new facilities becoming operational. The company's stock now trades at a significant discount to peers in the CRDMO segment, presenting a potential long-term opportunity supported by a strong balance sheet and strategic growth initiatives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:17:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b65e2e6a0b8ae17cacb8_1771222797395.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>R M Drip Pivots to Smart Irrigation Amidst High Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/R-M-Drip-Pivots-to-Smart-Irrigation-Amidst-High-Valuation/6992b4892e6a0b8ae17cabd4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/R-M-Drip-Pivots-to-Smart-Irrigation-Amidst-High-Valuation/6992b4892e6a0b8ae17cabd4</guid><description>R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Limited is transitioning from a traditional manufacturer to an integrated IoT-based digital agriculture solutions provider by entering the smart irrigation automation sector. This pivot aims to leverage a rapidly expanding market, projected to grow to USD 899 million by 2030. The company will introduce diversified revenue streams including data analytics and subscription services, alongside its existing hardware offerings. This move is supported by government subsidies and national water conservation priorities. The current stock valuation, however, reflects aggressive growth expectations, posing significant hurdles for successful execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:09:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b4892e6a0b8ae17cabd3_1771222285098.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Disney, Paramount Target ByteDance AI Over IP Infringement</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Disney-Paramount-Target-ByteDance-AI-Over-IP-Infringement/6992b38e2e6a0b8ae17caa34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Disney-Paramount-Target-ByteDance-AI-Over-IP-Infringement/6992b38e2e6a0b8ae17caa34</guid><description>Walt Disney Pictures and Paramount Skydance have issued cease-and-desist letters to ByteDance, accusing its Seedance 2.0 AI video generator of infringing on intellectual property rights. The core allegations center on the unauthorized use of iconic characters from franchises like Marvel and Star Wars to train the AI model. ByteDance claims it will enhance safeguards, but the move signals a heightened battle over content ownership in the rapidly evolving AI-generated media space. This legal offensive contrasts sharply with Disney's own licensing deals with AI developers like OpenAI, underscoring the complex landscape of intellectual property in generative AI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:05:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b38e2e6a0b8ae17caa33_1771222126341.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Funds Brace for 2026: Large-Caps &amp; Short Debt Lead Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Indian-Funds-Brace-for-2026-Large-Caps-and-Short-Debt-Lead-Strategy/6992b36c2e6a0b8ae17ca99d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Indian-Funds-Brace-for-2026-Large-Caps-and-Short-Debt-Lead-Strategy/6992b36c2e6a0b8ae17ca99d</guid><description>Indian mutual funds are adopting a cautious 2026 strategy, prioritizing large-cap equities and short-duration debt instruments. This reflects a pivot towards stability following 2025's volatility, with a focus on domestic growth drivers like financials and consumer cyclicals, while managing inherent sector risks and leveraging strong domestic inflows.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:04:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b36c2e6a0b8ae17ca99c_1771222050696.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kfin Tech Surges on Jefferies Target; Margin Pressure Seen</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kfin-Tech-Surges-on-Jefferies-Target-Margin-Pressure-Seen/6992b3592e6a0b8ae17ca972</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kfin-Tech-Surges-on-Jefferies-Target-Margin-Pressure-Seen/6992b3592e6a0b8ae17ca972</guid><description>Kfin Technologies Ltd. experienced a significant share price increase on Monday, February 16, driven by a 'buy' rating and a ₹1,300 price target from Jefferies, projecting a 34% upside. The company reported robust third-quarter revenue growth of 27.9% year-on-year, reaching ₹3,708.7 million. However, despite a 16.1% rise in EBITDA to ₹1,516.2 million, net profit saw a modest 2.2% increase to ₹92 crore, and EBITDA margins compressed to 40.9% from 45% a year prior. The RTA yield also contracted sequentially.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:04:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b3592e6a0b8ae17ca971_1771222045327.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys Faces AI Uncertainty Amid IT Sector Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Faces-AI-Uncertainty-Amid-IT-Sector-Slump/6992b3062e6a0b8ae17ca88a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Faces-AI-Uncertainty-Amid-IT-Sector-Slump/6992b3062e6a0b8ae17ca88a</guid><description>Infosys shares traded lower, reflecting a broader downturn in the Indian IT sector. While market-wide weakness contributed, the primary concern centers on the disruptive potential of artificial intelligence, which analysts believe could reshape the company's business model and impact margins. Despite a more attractive valuation post-price correction, the outlook remains cautious as the sector grapples with AI-driven shifts and reduced demand in key markets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:02:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b3062e6a0b8ae17ca889_1771221940431.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GMR Airports &amp; CRISIL: Divergent Fortunes Amidst Market Sell-off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GMR-Airports-and-CRISIL-Divergent-Fortunes-Amidst-Market-Sell-off/6992b3052e6a0b8ae17ca873</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GMR-Airports-and-CRISIL-Divergent-Fortunes-Amidst-Market-Sell-off/6992b3052e6a0b8ae17ca873</guid><description>Despite a broad market downturn, GMR Airports and CRISIL emerged as top performers in the Nifty Midcap 150 index. GMR Airports' significant revenue growth is overshadowed by persistent annual losses, while CRISIL demonstrates robust and consistent profitability. This divergence highlights distinct paths to shareholder value creation within the mid-cap segment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:02:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b3052e6a0b8ae17ca872_1771222097490.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Petronet LNG Faces Margin Squeeze Amidst Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Petronet-LNG-Faces-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Competition/6992b2bb2e6a0b8ae17ca7a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Petronet-LNG-Faces-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Competition/6992b2bb2e6a0b8ae17ca7a5</guid><description>Petronet LNG reported a 2.2% increase in total volume growth, but standalone EBITDA declined 3.9% year-on-year to ₹12.0 billion, primarily due to higher employee costs and a ₹0.3 billion past service cost impact from labor code implementation. Profit after tax also fell 2.2% year-on-year to ₹8.5 billion. For the nine months ended FY26, EBITDA and PAT decreased by 13.3% and 12.3% respectively. Management plans ₹90.0 billion in FY27 capex for PDH and PP projects, with the Dahej terminal expansion due by March 2026. Analysts maintain a 'HOLD' rating, citing concerns over increasing competition impacting future volume growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:01:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b2bb2e6a0b8ae17ca7a4_1771221943377.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Astral Hits 52-Week High Amid Profit Dip &amp; Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astral-Hits-52-Week-High-Amid-Profit-Dip-and-Valuation-Concerns/6992b29f2e6a0b8ae17ca755</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Astral-Hits-52-Week-High-Amid-Profit-Dip-and-Valuation-Concerns/6992b29f2e6a0b8ae17ca755</guid><description>Astral Limited shares ascended to a new 52-week high of ₹1,615.00 on Monday, buoyed by revenue growth and positive market sentiment. However, a deeper look reveals a slight year-on-year dip in net profit for fiscal year 2025 and persistently high valuation multiples, contrasting with a 'Sell' rating from one prominent analyst firm. The company's low debt and strong position in the growing Indian pipe and fittings market are key positives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:01:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b29f2e6a0b8ae17ca754_1771221897957.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cummins India Rallies on Growth, P/E Jumps Amid Mixed Analyst Views</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cummins-India-Rallies-on-Growth-PE-Jumps-Amid-Mixed-Analyst-Views/6992b22d2e6a0b8ae17ca627</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cummins-India-Rallies-on-Growth-PE-Jumps-Amid-Mixed-Analyst-Views/6992b22d2e6a0b8ae17ca627</guid><description>Cummins India shares advanced as robust annual revenue and profit growth, coupled with a lean balance sheet and consistent dividend payouts, underscored its financial strength. The company's stock is trading at a premium valuation, with a P/E ratio around 53-55, reflecting strong market confidence. Despite positive sector tailwinds in Indian manufacturing, analyst sentiment shows a divergence, with some maintaining 'Buy' ratings and others suggesting a 'Hold' or anticipating a slight downside from current levels, creating a complex outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 05:59:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b22d2e6a0b8ae17ca626_1771221806244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSE Shares Tumble Amidst Regulatory Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/BSE-Shares-Tumble-Amidst-Regulatory-Scrutiny/6992b22d2e6a0b8ae17ca610</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/BSE-Shares-Tumble-Amidst-Regulatory-Scrutiny/6992b22d2e6a0b8ae17ca610</guid><description>BSE Limited shares experienced a significant decline on Monday, February 16, 2026, tumbling 9.5% to approximately Rs 2,808.30. This downturn, placing it among the top Nifty Midcap 150 losers, was triggered by new Reserve Bank of India (RBI) regulations for capital market intermediaries, which introduced stricter collateral requirements for proprietary trades and raised concerns about future trading volumes. The sharp sell-off occurred despite BSE's consistently strong financial growth trajectory and recent lucrative corporate actions, including a bonus issue and substantial dividends. The stock's elevated valuation relative to peers and the broader market made it susceptible to such sector-specific regulatory shocks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 05:59:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b22d2e6a0b8ae17ca60f_1771221851637.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Transition: Urgency Amidst Economic Crossroads</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-AI-Transition-Urgency-Amidst-Economic-Crossroads/6992b22c2e6a0b8ae17ca5f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-AI-Transition-Urgency-Amidst-Economic-Crossroads/6992b22c2e6a0b8ae17ca5f9</guid><description>Chief Economic Adviser V. Anantha Nageswaran has underscored the imperative for immediate policy action and structural reforms to navigate India's transition into the artificial intelligence era. He cautioned that delays risk diminishing the nation's strategic flexibility and could precipitate social and economic instability. Key reform areas include a comprehensive overhaul of education and foundational skills, alongside scaling high-quality skill development programs and removing regulatory bottlenecks in labour-intensive services. The opportunity window for securing favourable AI outcomes is identified as time-sensitive, with foresight and relentless execution deemed crucial to harness human abundance alongside machine intelligence. This strategic juncture demands a proactive approach to manage emerging labor-market shifts and ensure inclusive prosperity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 05:59:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b22c2e6a0b8ae17ca5f8_1771221768397.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Draft Rules Mandate Refunds for Bank Mis-selling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Draft-Rules-Mandate-Refunds-for-Bank-Mis-selling/6992b22b2e6a0b8ae17ca5e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Draft-Rules-Mandate-Refunds-for-Bank-Mis-selling/6992b22b2e6a0b8ae17ca5e2</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has issued draft regulations to combat the pervasive issue of mis-selling financial products by banks and Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs). These proposed rules, open for feedback until March 4, mandate full refunds and compensation for proven instances of mis-selling. They also prohibit compulsory bundling of services and deceptive advertising practices, signalling a robust shift towards enhanced consumer safeguards in the Indian financial sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 05:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b22b2e6a0b8ae17ca5e1_1771221708328.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apple AirPods India Output Surges Amid Supply Chain Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apple-AirPods-India-Output-Surges-Amid-Supply-Chain-Pivot/6992b22a2e6a0b8ae17ca5cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apple-AirPods-India-Output-Surges-Amid-Supply-Chain-Pivot/6992b22a2e6a0b8ae17ca5cb</guid><description>Apple has exported over one million AirPods units from India since August 2024, primarily from Foxconn's Hyderabad facility, which now produces approximately 200,000 units monthly. This surge signifies India's expanding importance in Apple's diversified global supply chain, complementing iPhone manufacturing and bolstering a multi-category hardware ecosystem. The move capitalizes on India's growing manufacturing capabilities and strategic 'Make in India' initiatives, aiming for cost efficiencies and enhanced supply chain resilience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 05:59:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b22a2e6a0b8ae17ca5ca_1771221697296.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PI Industries Q3 Revenue Plummets 28%; Valuation Under Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/PI-Industries-Q3-Revenue-Plummets-28percent-Valuation-Under-Scrutiny/6992b2272e6a0b8ae17ca5b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/PI-Industries-Q3-Revenue-Plummets-28percent-Valuation-Under-Scrutiny/6992b2272e6a0b8ae17ca5b4</guid><description>PI Industries disclosed a sharp 28% year-over-year revenue decline to Rs 13,757 million for Q3 FY26, driven by weak performance across its core segments. While a 'HOLD' rating persists, the company's elevated valuation, coupled with industry headwinds and differing analyst outlooks, warrants a cautious perspective on its projected recovery.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 05:59:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b2272e6a0b8ae17ca5b3_1771221672010.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Surges on Strong Q3 Earnings, Europe and US Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Aurobindo-Pharma-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Earnings-Europe-and-US-Growth/6992b13a2e6a0b8ae17ca447</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Aurobindo-Pharma-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Earnings-Europe-and-US-Growth/6992b13a2e6a0b8ae17ca447</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma announced robust third-quarter results for FY26, with consolidated revenue climbing 8.4% year-on-year to ₹8,646 crores. EBITDA grew 9% to ₹1,773 crores, maintaining a healthy 20.5% margin. The company highlighted strong performance in its European business, which grew 27% year-on-year, and continued expansion in the US market. Management expressed confidence in achieving EBITDA break-even in Q4 FY26 and outlined strategic growth drivers including the Pen-G initiative and the pending Lannett acquisition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 05:55:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b13a2e6a0b8ae17ca446_1771221408725.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reganto Enterprises Delays Results Amid Restructuring Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Reganto-Enterprises-Delays-Results-Amid-Restructuring-Woes/6992b0bf2e6a0b8ae17ca3e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Reganto-Enterprises-Delays-Results-Amid-Restructuring-Woes/6992b0bf2e6a0b8ae17ca3e3</guid><description>Reganto Enterprises Limited, previously known as Vintron Informatics Limited, has announced a delay in submitting its financial results for the quarter ending December 31, 2025. The company attributes this postponement to its ongoing corporate restructuring process. This news comes at a time when the company has been undergoing significant changes, including a name change and diversification efforts, but also carries a history of regulatory scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 05:53:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992b0bf2e6a0b8ae17ca3e2_1771221311721.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharat-VISTAAR Launched: AI for Indian Farmers, Data Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Bharat-VISTAAR-Launched-AI-for-Indian-Farmers-Data-Risks-Loom/6992afdd2e6a0b8ae17ca2af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Bharat-VISTAAR-Launched-AI-for-Indian-Farmers-Data-Risks-Loom/6992afdd2e6a0b8ae17ca2af</guid><description>India has launched Bharat-VISTAAR, a new AI-powered multilingual tool designed to assist farmers with critical information ranging from crop planning and pest alerts to weather forecasts and government schemes. Funded with an initial ₹150 crore allocation for FY 2026-27, the initiative integrates national agricultural databases and research outputs. While promising enhanced productivity and risk reduction, significant challenges remain regarding farmer adoption, digital literacy, and data utilization, raising questions about its long-term efficacy and potential risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 05:49:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992afdd2e6a0b8ae17ca2ae_1771221128482.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vivimed Labs in CBI Crosshairs; High Court Grants Interim Stay</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Vivimed-Labs-in-CBI-Crosshairs-High-Court-Grants-Interim-Stay/6992af5d2e6a0b8ae17ca1ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Vivimed-Labs-in-CBI-Crosshairs-High-Court-Grants-Interim-Stay/6992af5d2e6a0b8ae17ca1ff</guid><description>Vivimed Labs Limited has received a notice from the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) regarding a case registered for alleged fraud and corruption, following a complaint by the State Bank of India (SBI) which classified the company's account as 'fraud'. The Telangana High Court has, however, granted an interim stay on further proceedings and coercive steps against the company and its directors. The financial impact remains unquantifiable, adding to existing concerns.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 05:47:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992af5d2e6a0b8ae17ca1fe_1771220965122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>