<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:37:59 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Budget Signals Fiscal Prudence, Corporate Deals Shake Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Signals-Fiscal-Prudence-Corporate-Deals-Shake-Markets/6980eb56cdcede69fb48a834</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Signals-Fiscal-Prudence-Corporate-Deals-Shake-Markets/6980eb56cdcede69fb48a834</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman defended the Union Budget 2026-27, emphasizing policy continuity and fiscal prudence with a projected deficit of 4.3% of GDP and increased capital expenditure. Simultaneously, PB Fintech's stock faced pressure despite strong Q3 results due to a proposed Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) for inorganic growth, while Advent International reportedly prepared a $300 million investment in Aditya Birla Housing Finance, signaling robust private equity interest in the sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:26:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980eb56cdcede69fb48a833_1770056657478.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Veedol Corp Declares 700% Dividend, Posts Strong Q3 Profit Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Veedol-Corp-Declares-700percent-Dividend-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Surge/6980e982cdcede69fb48a20d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Veedol-Corp-Declares-700percent-Dividend-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Surge/6980e982cdcede69fb48a20d</guid><description>Veedol Corporation (formerly Tide Water Oil) announced strong Q3 FY25 results, with standalone PAT up 29.8% YoY to ₹43.64 Cr and consolidated PAT rising 16.65% to ₹43.55 Cr. The company declared a significant Second Interim Dividend of 700% (₹14 per share), rewarding shareholders amidst positive profitability trends. Nine-month performance also shows profit growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:24:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e982cdcede69fb48a20c_1770056663576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ventive Hospitality Posts Stellar Q3 with 27% Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ventive-Hospitality-Posts-Stellar-Q3-with-27percent-Revenue-Surge/6980eb8ccdcede69fb48a966</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ventive-Hospitality-Posts-Stellar-Q3-with-27percent-Revenue-Surge/6980eb8ccdcede69fb48a966</guid><description>Ventive Hospitality Ltd reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue soaring 27% YoY to ₹722 crore and EBITDA climbing 25% YoY to ₹348 crore, maintaining a strong 48% margin. PAT stood at ₹141 crore. The core hospitality segment revenue grew 35% YoY, driven by strong performance in both Indian and international operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Banking Future: Panel to Shape Sector Structure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Banking-Future-Panel-to-Shape-Sector-Structure/6980ea6ccdcede69fb48a51e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Banking-Future-Panel-to-Shape-Sector-Structure/6980ea6ccdcede69fb48a51e</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has initiated the formation of a high-level committee tasked with determining the future architecture of India's banking sector. This panel will deliberate on whether the nation requires a greater quantity of banks, enhanced quality of services, or larger, consolidated entities. Key issues, including the consolidation of public sector banks and the potential entry of large conglomerates into finance, are squarely within the committee's remit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980ea6ccdcede69fb48a51d_1770056435658.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Yes Bank Navigates Fiscal Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Yes-Bank-Navigates-Fiscal-Concerns/6980ea97cdcede69fb48a65a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Yes-Bank-Navigates-Fiscal-Concerns/6980ea97cdcede69fb48a65a</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 presents a dual focus on fiscal consolidation and a significant capex push, while raising concerns over higher government borrowings. For Yes Bank, this context is crucial as it operates within a sector undergoing reform, with its P/E ratio showing it trades at a premium to some peers, despite recent improvements in asset quality and profitability demonstrated in Q3FY26 results. The budget's emphasis on manufacturing, technology, and infrastructure could offer indirect benefits, but high borrowing levels present a headwind for the broader debt market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:21:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980ea97cdcede69fb48a659_1770056517166.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Winzo Co-Founder Nanda Secures Bail in ED Money-Laundering Case</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Winzo-Co-Founder-Nanda-Secures-Bail-in-ED-Money-Laundering-Case/6980e9eecdcede69fb48a39e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Winzo-Co-Founder-Nanda-Secures-Bail-in-ED-Money-Laundering-Case/6980e9eecdcede69fb48a39e</guid><description>Bengaluru court has granted bail to Winzo Games co-founder Paavan Nanda in a high-profile Enforcement Directorate money-laundering investigation. Nanda, who was previously denied bail, must now post a ₹5 lakh bond and surrender his passport. The ED alleges the gaming company engaged in algorithmic manipulation and fund diversion, amounting to ₹177 crore and USD 55 million. This development follows similar bail granted to co-founder Saumya Singh Rathore.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:19:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e9eecdcede69fb48a39d_1770056348159.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: India Bets Big on Sovereign AI, Tech Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Budget-2026-India-Bets-Big-on-Sovereign-AI-Tech-Dominance/6980e973cdcede69fb48a13f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Budget-2026-India-Bets-Big-on-Sovereign-AI-Tech-Dominance/6980e973cdcede69fb48a13f</guid><description>Budget 2026 prioritizes sovereign Artificial Intelligence and scalable technologies, allocating substantial funds for missions like IndiaAI (over ₹10,300 crore) and National Quantum Mission (₹6,003.65 crore). The budget aims for technological self-reliance and inclusive growth by addressing digital literacy gaps and assessing AI's impact on jobs. It also includes significant capital pools for R&amp;D, totaling ₹1 lakh crore for the Research, Development and Innovation Scheme, and reforms to empower the financial sector for faster technology adoption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e973cdcede69fb48a13e_1770056220397.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Capex Surge, Sectoral Bets Signal Growth Trajectory</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Capex-Surge-Sectoral-Bets-Signal-Growth-Trajectory/6980e8d4cdcede69fb489fad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Capex-Surge-Sectoral-Bets-Signal-Growth-Trajectory/6980e8d4cdcede69fb489fad</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 unveiled a substantial ₹12.2 lakh crore capital expenditure outlay, targeting infrastructure like high-speed rail and waterways to bolster domestic growth. Key manufacturing sectors, including semiconductors and electronics, received enhanced support, while measures addressed stress in labour-intensive exports and MSMEs. A data center tax holiday until 2047 aims to attract foreign investment, as the government maintains a fiscal deficit target of 4.3% for FY27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:17:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e8d4cdcede69fb489fac_1770056226225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Veedol Corp Delivers Robust Q3; Declares 700% Interim Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Veedol-Corp-Delivers-Robust-Q3-Declares-700percent-Interim-Dividend/6980e7d8cdcede69fb4881af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Veedol-Corp-Delivers-Robust-Q3-Declares-700percent-Interim-Dividend/6980e7d8cdcede69fb4881af</guid><description>Veedol Corporation reported strong Q3 FY26 consolidated results, with revenue up 11.5% and PAT rising 16.6% YoY. The company also declared a significant second interim dividend of 700% (₹14 per share), signaling confidence in its financial health. Standalone performance also saw profit growth, despite marginal revenue dips for the nine-month period.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e7d8cdcede69fb4881ae_1770055975893.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Saksoft Q3 Revenue Dips Sequentially on Client Spending Slowdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Saksoft-Q3-Revenue-Dips-Sequentially-on-Client-Spending-Slowdown/6980e889cdcede69fb489da8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Saksoft-Q3-Revenue-Dips-Sequentially-on-Client-Spending-Slowdown/6980e889cdcede69fb489da8</guid><description>Saksoft reported a mixed Q3 FY26, with revenue declining 3.0% QoQ due to spending cuts by top clients. However, the nine-month period saw robust 17.9% YoY revenue growth and significant margin expansion. The company continues strategic investments in AI and digital transformation, targeting USD 500 million revenue by 2030, despite near-term client-specific headwinds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:12:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e889cdcede69fb489da7_1770055935913.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Veedol Corp Posts Strong PAT Growth; Declares 700% Interim Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Veedol-Corp-Posts-Strong-PAT-Growth-Declares-700percent-Interim-Dividend/6980e80fcdcede69fb4897f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Veedol-Corp-Posts-Strong-PAT-Growth-Declares-700percent-Interim-Dividend/6980e80fcdcede69fb4897f7</guid><description>Veedol Corporation (formerly Tide Water Oil) reported robust Q3 FY25 standalone PAT growth of 29.80% to ₹43.64 crore, driven by a 67.48% PBT jump. Consolidated PAT rose 16.63% to ₹43.55 crore. The company declared a substantial 700% interim dividend. However, a ₹6.56 crore inventory loss due to fire impacted results, and no future guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:11:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e80fcdcede69fb4897f6_1770055886847.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unveils AI-Driven Growth Strategy: Jobs, Productivity Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Unveils-AI-Driven-Growth-Strategy-Jobs-Productivity-Focus/6980e738cdcede69fb485a72</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Unveils-AI-Driven-Growth-Strategy-Jobs-Productivity-Focus/6980e738cdcede69fb485a72</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has outlined India's post-Budget 2026 strategy to harness Artificial Intelligence (AI), emphasizing its role in boosting national productivity and creating skilled employment opportunities rather than displacing workers. Key initiatives include integrating AI into educational curricula and teacher training, expanding professional upskilling programs, and deploying AI tools like Bharat-VISTAAR for agriculture. The government also plans AI integration in healthcare, particularly for assistive devices, and for enhancing efficiency in financial sectors like income tax and GST.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:10:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e738cdcede69fb485a71_1770055767859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Saksoft Mixed Q3: YoY Growth Continues, But Sequential Revenue Dips on Client Slowdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Saksoft-Mixed-Q3-YoY-Growth-Continues-But-Sequential-Revenue-Dips-on-Client-Slowdown/6980e7b6cdcede69fb487c49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Saksoft-Mixed-Q3-YoY-Growth-Continues-But-Sequential-Revenue-Dips-on-Client-Slowdown/6980e7b6cdcede69fb487c49</guid><description>Saksoft reported a mixed Q3 FY26. While 9M FY26 revenue surged 17.9% YoY and PAT rose 23.6%, Q3 saw a 3.0% revenue decline QoQ and a 19.3% drop in PAT. Management cited spending slowdowns from its top two clients, despite ongoing investments in AI-led digital transformation and a positive long-term outlook towards a USD 500 million revenue goal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:09:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e7b6cdcede69fb487c48_1770055777903.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Defends Budget Amidst Global Turmoil, Eyes Sector Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Defends-Budget-Amidst-Global-Turmoil-Eyes-Sector-Growth/6980e77acdcede69fb487242</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Defends-Budget-Amidst-Global-Turmoil-Eyes-Sector-Growth/6980e77acdcede69fb487242</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has strongly defended the Union Budget 2026-27, asserting policy continuity and robust economic fundamentals despite significant global uncertainty. The budget outlines strategic measures for sectors like textiles and semiconductors, aiming to bolster domestic manufacturing and competitiveness. This comes as the textile industry grapples with substantial US tariffs, prompting a pivot towards diversification and integrated development programs within the sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:08:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e77acdcede69fb487241_1770055729643.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amansa Ups Clean Science Stake as Stock Hits New Low</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Amansa-Ups-Clean-Science-Stake-as-Stock-Hits-New-Low/6980e713cdcede69fb484c74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Amansa-Ups-Clean-Science-Stake-as-Stock-Hits-New-Low/6980e713cdcede69fb484c74</guid><description>Amansa Holdings expanded its holding in specialty chemicals manufacturer Clean Science and Technology by acquiring an additional 1.1% stake on February 2. Despite this institutional buying, Clean Science shares dropped to a new all-time closing low. Other notable transactions included bulk deals in Jinkushal Industries and India Homes, with Lloyds Enterprises increasing its position in the latter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:06:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e713cdcede69fb484c73_1770055614913.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget Bets on Stability, Customs Reform Amid Global Gloom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Bets-on-Stability-Customs-Reform-Amid-Global-Gloom/6980e683cdcede69fb484843</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Bets-on-Stability-Customs-Reform-Amid-Global-Gloom/6980e683cdcede69fb484843</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman underscored stability and policy continuity as central themes of the Union Budget. She emphasized India's attractiveness as an investment destination amidst global uncertainty, driven by consistent policymaking and a commitment to removing red tape. The finance minister also highlighted a comprehensive customs overhaul as a key signature reform, signaling ongoing efforts to boost ease of doing business.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:06:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e683cdcede69fb484842_1770055465154.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RIL Arbitration Appeal Maintainable, HC Rules</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/RIL-Arbitration-Appeal-Maintainable-HC-Rules/6980e643cdcede69fb484665</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/RIL-Arbitration-Appeal-Maintainable-HC-Rules/6980e643cdcede69fb484665</guid><description>The Delhi High Court has ruled the government's appeal against Reliance Industries (RIL) regarding the Panna, Mukta, and Tapti (PMT) gas fields dispute is maintainable. This procedural victory allows the government to pursue enforcement of a 2016 arbitration award for $3.86 billion, rejecting RIL's preliminary objections. The case now proceeds to a hearing on its merits on February 17. The dispute centers on cost recovery provisions, royalties, and taxes stemming from arbitration initiated in 2010.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e643cdcede69fb484664_1770055411863.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPF UAN Glitch Threatens Retirement Fortunes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/EPF-UAN-Glitch-Threatens-Retirement-Fortunes/6980e6b2cdcede69fb4849e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/EPF-UAN-Glitch-Threatens-Retirement-Fortunes/6980e6b2cdcede69fb4849e5</guid><description>Multiple Universal Account Numbers (UANs) can silently undermine Employees' Provident Fund (EPF) savings. This administrative flaw, often arising from job changes, can lead to lost interest on older balances, delayed or rejected claims, and compromised pension calculations. Proactive checking and consolidation of UANs are essential for safeguarding long-term retirement security in India.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:02:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's EV Market Surges 63% on New Entrants and Model Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Market-Surges-63percent-on-New-Entrants-and-Model-Growth/6980e634cdcede69fb4845fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Market-Surges-63percent-on-New-Entrants-and-Model-Growth/6980e634cdcede69fb4845fa</guid><description>Electric four-wheeler registrations in India surged 63% year-on-year to 17,654 units in January 2026. This growth was fueled by broader adoption, new model launches, and the rapid market entry of manufacturers like VinFast. Established players like Tata Motors maintained leadership, while competitive dynamics saw shifts with Mahindra Electric gaining share and Hyundai re-entering the top five.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:02:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980ca713618e07334deaf15_1770050330422.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Exporters Fear Competitiveness Hit from Budgetary Cuts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Exporters-Fear-Competitiveness-Hit-from-Budgetary-Cuts/6980e4cecdcede69fb4825b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Exporters-Fear-Competitiveness-Hit-from-Budgetary-Cuts/6980e4cecdcede69fb4825b7</guid><description>Exporters are raising concerns following sharp cuts to the RoDTEP and RoSCTL schemes for the upcoming fiscal year. Allocations for RoDTEP have been slashed by 45% to ₹10,000 crore, and RoSCTL by 50% to ₹5,000 crore. Industry bodies warn this could erode price competitiveness and delay payments, despite expectations of a revised budget increase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:01:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e4cecdcede69fb4825b6_1770055312580.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RIL Faces $3.86B Claim as Delhi Court Rejects Appeal Objection</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/RIL-Faces-386B-Claim-as-Delhi-Court-Rejects-Appeal-Objection/6980e557cdcede69fb48282b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/RIL-Faces-386B-Claim-as-Delhi-Court-Rejects-Appeal-Objection/6980e557cdcede69fb48282b</guid><description>Reliance Industries (RIL) and its partners must now face a hearing on the merits of a central government appeal seeking recovery of approximately $3.86 billion. The Delhi High Court has overturned a previous dismissal, allowing the government to pursue its claim stemming from a long-standing dispute over the Panna Mukta and Tapti oil and gas fields. The case is now listed for February 17, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e557cdcede69fb48282a_1770055166581.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fiscal Consolidation Pace Slows Amid Revenue Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Consolidation-Pace-Slows-Amid-Revenue-Challenges/6980e500cdcede69fb4826d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Consolidation-Pace-Slows-Amid-Revenue-Challenges/6980e500cdcede69fb4826d7</guid><description>The government is moderating its fiscal consolidation pace, projecting a 4.3% fiscal deficit-GDP ratio for 2026-27. This recalibration follows anticipated shortfalls in net tax and non-tax revenues, partially offset by higher non-debt capital receipts, largely from disinvestment. Concurrently, the 16th Finance Commission's decision to forgo revenue deficit and sector-specific grants will redistribute fiscal resources, potentially straining state finances. A significant overhaul of rural employment schemes, with the new VB-G RAM G program imposing a higher cost-sharing burden on states, further alters the fiscal federal balance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:58:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e500cdcede69fb4826d6_1770055116215.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Manufacturing Roars Back: ISM Index Surges to Fastest Pace Since 2022</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Manufacturing-Roars-Back-ISM-Index-Surges-to-Fastest-Pace-Since-2022/6980e3e2cdcede69fb482294</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Manufacturing-Roars-Back-ISM-Index-Surges-to-Fastest-Pace-Since-2022/6980e3e2cdcede69fb482294</guid><description>US factory activity surged back into expansion territory in January, marking the first growth in a year. The ISM Manufacturing Index leaped to 52.6, exceeding expectations and signaling a robust recovery fueled by strong new orders and production gains. However, persistent input cost inflation and the impact of trade policies continue to present challenges for manufacturers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:56:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e3e2cdcede69fb482293_1770054974718.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manali Petro Profit Soars 3X on Asset Sale, Operations Show Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Manali-Petro-Profit-Soars-3X-on-Asset-Sale-Operations-Show-Strain/6980e451cdcede69fb482423</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Manali-Petro-Profit-Soars-3X-on-Asset-Sale-Operations-Show-Strain/6980e451cdcede69fb482423</guid><description>Manali Petrochemicals Limited (MPL) posted a consolidated net profit of ₹68 crore for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, marking a significant jump from ₹18 crore a year prior. This surge was predominantly fueled by an exceptional gain from the sale of its UK subsidiary. Revenue saw a modest 2% increase to ₹267 crore. Despite the strong consolidated bottom line, underlying operational performance indicated margin pressures and weaker standalone results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:55:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e451cdcede69fb482422_1770054928390.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SMC Global Securities Q3 PAT Plunges 75% YoY, Declares Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SMC-Global-Securities-Q3-PAT-Plunges-75percent-YoY-Declares-Dividend/6980e2fccdcede69fb47db2b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SMC-Global-Securities-Q3-PAT-Plunges-75percent-YoY-Declares-Dividend/6980e2fccdcede69fb47db2b</guid><description>SMC Global Securities' board approved unaudited Q3 FY26 financial results, revealing a steep 75% year-on-year decline in consolidated Net Profit After Tax to ₹2,616.17 Lakhs, down from ₹10,521.50 Lakhs. Standalone PAT also fell 13.5% to ₹2,721.10 Lakhs. Revenue from operations saw significant drops on both standalone and consolidated bases. Despite the profit slump, the company declared an interim dividend of ₹0.60 per equity share and highlighted successful fundraising of ₹11,385.85 lakhs via NCDs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:53:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e2fccdcede69fb47db2a_1770054806643.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta Promoter's $350M Loan Curbs VEDL Assets, Encumbers Shares</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedanta-Promoters-350M-Loan-Curbs-VEDL-Assets-Encumbers-Shares/6980e373cdcede69fb48077e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedanta-Promoters-350M-Loan-Curbs-VEDL-Assets-Encumbers-Shares/6980e373cdcede69fb48077e</guid><description>Vedanta Limited disclosed its promoter group, Vedanta Resources Limited, secured a US$350 million facility. While not a direct party, Vedanta Limited faces significant restrictions on asset sales, investments, and mergers, requiring lender consent, due to encumbrances on its shares. The company claims no direct impact on management or liabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:52:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e373cdcede69fb48077d_1770054670837.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SII Awaits SEZ Duty Clarity Post-Budget</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/SII-Awaits-SEZ-Duty-Clarity-Post-Budget/6980e17ecdcede69fb47c16d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/SII-Awaits-SEZ-Duty-Clarity-Post-Budget/6980e17ecdcede69fb47c16d</guid><description>The 2026 Indian Budget introduced a one-time measure allowing Special Economic Zone (SEZ) units to sell to the Domestic Tariff Area (DTA) at concessional duty rates. This aims to leverage underutilized capacities amid global trade disruptions. Serum Institute of India (SII), a significant vaccine supplier, awaits specific rate disclosures. Currently, SEZ-to-DTA goods face import duties, impacting competitiveness and SII's substantial government contracts, potentially affecting vaccine affordability or company margins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:48:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e17ecdcede69fb47c16c_1770054525905.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Recovers Post-Budget Selloff; Eyes Earnings &amp; 200-DMA</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nifty-Recovers-Post-Budget-Selloff-Eyes-Earnings-and-200-DMA/6980e2eccdcede69fb47d222</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nifty-Recovers-Post-Budget-Selloff-Eyes-Earnings-and-200-DMA/6980e2eccdcede69fb47d222</guid><description>The Nifty 50 index rallied to close above 25,050 on Monday, February 2, 2026, recovering significantly from the sharp sell-off witnessed on Budget Day. The rebound was broad-based, with Auto, Oil &amp; Gas, and Metals sectors leading gains, while the Indian Rupee strengthened. Analysts remain cautious, focusing on the index's ability to clear key technical resistance levels, particularly the 200-day moving average, amid ongoing Q3 earnings season.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:48:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e2eccdcede69fb47d221_1770054488379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Markets Face Headwinds Amid Global Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Markets-Face-Headwinds-Amid-Global-Shifts/6980e221cdcede69fb47d08b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Markets-Face-Headwinds-Amid-Global-Shifts/6980e221cdcede69fb47d08b</guid><description>Despite stable macroeconomic indicators, Indian equity markets are underperforming due to foreign institutional investor (FII) outflows, US tariff uncertainties, and limited AI investment opportunities. Chief Economic Adviser V. Anantha Nageswaran stated this divergence will close as the 'India story' remains intact. The government is preparing for a new world order by promoting indigenisation, self-sufficiency, and investing in critical sectors, alongside skilling the workforce for an AI-driven economy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e221cdcede69fb47d08a_1770054332965.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Precious Metals Tumble as Dollar Surges, Geopolitical Clouds Gather</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Tumble-as-Dollar-Surges-Geopolitical-Clouds-Gather/6980de80cdcede69fb469150</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-Tumble-as-Dollar-Surges-Geopolitical-Clouds-Gather/6980de80cdcede69fb469150</guid><description>Precious metals experienced a sharp downturn in early February 2026, with silver prices plummeting nearly 36% from their late January peak and gold losing over 17%. This steep fall was predominantly attributed to a strengthening US dollar, ongoing geopolitical tensions, and investor reactions to the recent Union Budget. Market participants are now closely monitoring international developments and key US economic indicators for future direction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980de80cdcede69fb46914f_1770054215327.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget FY27: Stability, Growth Pillars Set</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-FY27-Stability-Growth-Pillars-Set/6980e1f6cdcede69fb47cf9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-FY27-Stability-Growth-Pillars-Set/6980e1f6cdcede69fb47cf9e</guid><description>The Union Budget FY27 outlines a framework prioritizing macroeconomic stability and fiscal discipline, eschewing headline incentives for continuity and predictability. Public capital expenditure is sustained at Rs 12.2 lakh crore, forming the primary growth engine. Manufacturing and digital initiatives receive continued support, aiming for productivity-led growth. While the disinvestment target of Rs 80,000 crore faces execution challenges, market sentiment reacted negatively to increased Securities Transaction Tax on derivatives but positively to eased foreign investment norms and rationalized TCS for specific remittances.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Acquires Akzo Nobel India, Renames to JSW Dulux; Q3 Revenue Falls 13.6%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/JSW-Acquires-Akzo-Nobel-India-Renames-to-JSW-Dulux-Q3-Revenue-Falls-136percent/6980de5fcdcede69fb467f04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/JSW-Acquires-Akzo-Nobel-India-Renames-to-JSW-Dulux-Q3-Revenue-Falls-136percent/6980de5fcdcede69fb467f04</guid><description>JSW Paints has acquired a majority stake in Akzo Nobel India, prompting a proposed name change to JSW Dulux Limited. The company reported a 13.6% YoY decline in Q3 revenue to ₹907.7 crore, impacted by divestments. However, on a comparable basis excluding divested businesses, revenue dipped only 1.0% YoY, with profit after tax seeing a 5.9% YoY rise. New management plans integration and innovation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980de5fcdcede69fb467f03_1770054055792.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Awfis Profit Surges 43% On Demand, Stock Hits 52-Week Low</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Awfis-Profit-Surges-43percent-On-Demand-Stock-Hits-52-Week-Low/6980e016cdcede69fb47bf1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Awfis-Profit-Surges-43percent-On-Demand-Stock-Hits-52-Week-Low/6980e016cdcede69fb47bf1f</guid><description>Awfis Space Solutions posted a strong third quarter for FY26, with net profit rising 43% to Rs 21.6 crore on revenues of Rs 382 crore, up 20% year-on-year. Operating EBITDA surged 30% to Rs 139 crore as margins expanded to 36.5%. This performance was driven by robust demand from enterprise clients and Global Capability Centres, alongside network expansion to 257 centres. Despite these solid results, the company's stock experienced significant downward pressure, hitting a 52-week low.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:37:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980e016cdcede69fb47bf1e_1770053875640.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brigade Hotel Ventures Signs ₹1100 Crore Tamil Nadu Hospitality Expansion Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Brigade-Hotel-Ventures-Signs-1100-Crore-Tamil-Nadu-Hospitality-Expansion-Deal/6980df79cdcede69fb47ba81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Brigade-Hotel-Ventures-Signs-1100-Crore-Tamil-Nadu-Hospitality-Expansion-Deal/6980df79cdcede69fb47ba81</guid><description>Brigade Hotel Ventures (BHVL) has inked a significant MoU with the Tamil Nadu government, pledging ₹1100 crore to boost tourism infrastructure. The investment will add over 500 keys across three new hotels in Chennai, creating more than 1000 jobs. This expansion cements BHVL's position as a key player in South India's hospitality sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980df79cdcede69fb47ba80_1770053652412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Faces Scrutiny Over Q3 Results, Apologizes for Reporting Errors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Stallion-India-Fluorochemicals-Faces-Scrutiny-Over-Q3-Results-Apologizes-for-Reporting-Errors/6980dfa0cdcede69fb47bc1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Stallion-India-Fluorochemicals-Faces-Scrutiny-Over-Q3-Results-Apologizes-for-Reporting-Errors/6980dfa0cdcede69fb47bc1c</guid><description>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Limited issued a clarification and apology for inadvertent inconsistencies in its Q3 FY26 financial reporting due to an IR communication lapse. While revenue grew 23.17% YoY, EBITDA declined 5.21% with margin compression. However, nine-month performance remains robust with PAT up 72.81%, and management reiterated FY26 targets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:35:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980dfa0cdcede69fb47bc1b_1770053725189.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Rupee Below ₹90; Budget Targets Foreign Inflows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Rupee-Below-90-Budget-Targets-Foreign-Inflows/6980def4cdcede69fb472369</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Rupee-Below-90-Budget-Targets-Foreign-Inflows/6980def4cdcede69fb472369</guid><description>The Indian rupee has fallen below the significant ₹90 mark against the US dollar, prompting close monitoring by government officials and regulators. The Economic Survey 2025-26 noted a 6.5% depreciation between April 2025 and January 2026, positioning it as a weaker performer among Asian currencies. In response, the Union Budget 2026 introduced measures to attract foreign capital, including amendments for Alternative Investment Funds (AIFs) and an expansion of the Portfolio Investment Scheme (PIS) route for overseas investors. These moves aim to enhance foreign currency inflows and ease operational constraints for investment vehicles.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980def4cdcede69fb472368_1770053514296.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NPS Vatsalya: Child Savings Scheme's Education Funding Limits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NPS-Vatsalya-Child-Savings-Schemes-Education-Funding-Limits/6980deb9cdcede69fb46a362</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NPS-Vatsalya-Child-Savings-Schemes-Education-Funding-Limits/6980deb9cdcede69fb46a362</guid><description>The NPS Vatsalya scheme, a government-backed product regulated by PFRDA, offers minors a long-term savings avenue with market-linked investments. However, its utility for education funding is significantly curtailed by a three-year lock-in period and a strict 25% withdrawal limit on contributions. While providing potential tax benefits under Section 80CCD(1B) and a head start on retirement planning, the scheme is best positioned as a supplementary savings tool rather than a standalone solution for escalating educational expenses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:31:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980deb9cdcede69fb46a361_1770053510728.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>STT Hike Squeezes Arbitrage Fund Returns, Experts Warn</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/STT-Hike-Squeezes-Arbitrage-Fund-Returns-Experts-Warn/6980df5dcdcede69fb47b96c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/STT-Hike-Squeezes-Arbitrage-Fund-Returns-Experts-Warn/6980df5dcdcede69fb47b96c</guid><description>A significant hike in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options (F&amp;O) trades is set to reduce the returns of arbitrage funds. Experts anticipate a 30-50 basis point drop next fiscal. This impacts a category that has quadrupled its assets to ₹2.8 trillion. Despite the reduced profitability, these funds may still offer a post-tax advantage over debt instruments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Suzuki Motorcycle India Sales Surge 15% in January 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Suzuki-Motorcycle-India-Sales-Surge-15percent-in-January-2026/6980de3bcdcede69fb46713d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Suzuki-Motorcycle-India-Sales-Surge-15percent-in-January-2026/6980de3bcdcede69fb46713d</guid><description>Suzuki Motorcycle India (SMIPL) achieved a 15% year-on-year growth in total vehicle sales, reaching 125,786 units in January 2026. This performance was fueled by a 14% rise in domestic sales to 100,296 units and a significant 21% surge in exports to 25,490 units. SMIPL attributes this momentum to enhanced customer engagement, after-sales service, and network expansion. The broader Indian two-wheeler market also saw robust growth across major manufacturers in the same month.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:29:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980de3bcdcede69fb46713c_1770053362571.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets: CEA Cites Global Flux, FII Outflows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-CEA-Cites-Global-Flux-FII-Outflows/6980dd44c69f1b66e1c7f515</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-CEA-Cites-Global-Flux-FII-Outflows/6980dd44c69f1b66e1c7f515</guid><description>Indian equities are navigating a complex global environment marked by persistent foreign institutional investor (FII) outflows and broad economic uncertainty. Chief Economic Adviser V. Anantha Nageswaran acknowledges these pressures, linking them to US policy signals, tariff concerns, and the limited presence of AI-driven investments domestically. Despite temporary market-economy divergences and a shifting global order potentially lasting beyond 2026, Nageswaran reiterates confidence in India's resilient growth fundamentals and the eventual realignment of market valuations with economic realities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980dd44c69f1b66e1c7f514_1770053094270.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>