<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:48:01 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Valecha Engineering Q3 Profit Turns Around, But Auditor Flags Major Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valecha-Engineering-Q3-Profit-Turns-Around-But-Auditor-Flags-Major-Risks/69948b24cffb93b3e928577e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valecha-Engineering-Q3-Profit-Turns-Around-But-Auditor-Flags-Major-Risks/69948b24cffb93b3e928577e</guid><description>Valecha Engineering reported a standalone profit for Q3 FY26, a turnaround from last year. However, consolidated losses persist. Crucially, the auditor's report raises significant concerns about asset recoverability, subsidiary financial distress, and accounting practices, casting a shadow over the results.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:37:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948b24cffb93b3e928577d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHIT to Buy Roads for ₹6,220 Cr, Eyes Equity Raise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NHIT-to-Buy-Roads-for-6220-Cr-Eyes-Equity-Raise/69948ad1cffb93b3e92856de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NHIT-to-Buy-Roads-for-6220-Cr-Eyes-Equity-Raise/69948ad1cffb93b3e92856de</guid><description>National Highways Infra Trust (NHIT) is holding its 6th Extra-Ordinary Meeting on March 12, 2026, to approve the ₹6,220.90 Crore acquisition of 'Round 5 Roads'. The Trust also plans to raise funds through preferential issue and institutional placement to finance this deal and other objectives. Unitholders will vote on these significant proposals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:35:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948ad1cffb93b3e92856dd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asgard Alcobev Buys Breweries, Plans Share Sale Triggering Open Offer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asgard-Alcobev-Buys-Breweries-Plans-Share-Sale-Triggering-Open-Offer/69948acecffb93b3e92856c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asgard-Alcobev-Buys-Breweries-Plans-Share-Sale-Triggering-Open-Offer/69948acecffb93b3e92856c8</guid><description>Asgard Alcobev Limited has approved acquiring 78.90% of CMJ Breweries Private Limited for ₹219 crore via share swap and cash. The company also plans a preferential allotment of shares and warrants at ₹1.45 per unit. This move triggers a SEBI open offer, potentially leading to new promoters taking control.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:35:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948acecffb93b3e92856c7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Great Rotation: Mid-Caps Lead, AI Fuels IT Sector Rebound</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Great-Rotation-Mid-Caps-Lead-AI-Fuels-IT-Sector-Rebound/69948a47cffb93b3e92855f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Great-Rotation-Mid-Caps-Lead-AI-Fuels-IT-Sector-Rebound/69948a47cffb93b3e92855f9</guid><description>A strategic rotation is underway in the Indian equity market, with growth momentum increasingly shifting from Nifty 50 heavyweights to mid and small-cap companies. This broadening of the economic cycle is supported by realistic earnings growth expectations of around 12-15% for 2026, coupled with stabilizing margins. Concurrently, the Information Technology (IT) sector, despite facing headwinds from AI disruption fears and elevated valuations, is being viewed with contrarian optimism by firms like Motilal Oswal AMC, driven by the transformative potential of Artificial Intelligence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:33:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69948a47cffb93b3e92855f8_1771342582757.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ServiceNow Pivots to AI-Executed Workflows, Bets on Trust and India for Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ServiceNow-Pivots-to-AI-Executed-Workflows-Bets-on-Trust-and-India-for-Growth/69948a39cffb93b3e92855db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ServiceNow-Pivots-to-AI-Executed-Workflows-Bets-on-Trust-and-India-for-Growth/69948a39cffb93b3e92855db</guid><description>ServiceNow is intensifying its focus on AI-driven enterprise productivity, preparing for a February 28th launch aimed at enabling an "autonomous workforce." This strategic shift moves beyond AI assistance to AI-executed workflows, a move poised to boost enterprise efficiency and potentially ServiceNow's margins. The company is reinforcing its AI trust and governance framework with its AI Control Tower and Veza acquisition, positioning itself as a secure platform for regulated industries. India plays a dual role, hosting nearly half of its R&amp;D and serving as a key adoption market. Despite recent stock underperformance, analysts maintain a 'Strong Buy' consensus, citing significant upside potential.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:33:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69948a39cffb93b3e92855da_1771342528301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Talks: Pulses Negotiate Beyond Factsheet Revisions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Talks-Pulses-Negotiate-Beyond-Factsheet-Revisions/6994885ccffb93b3e92854c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Talks-Pulses-Negotiate-Beyond-Factsheet-Revisions/6994885ccffb93b3e92854c6</guid><description>Trade negotiations between the United States and India are ongoing regarding agricultural products, specifically pulses, despite their removal from a revised White House factsheet. Sources indicate that while the omission aimed to align the factsheet with the joint statement, discussions on pulses remain active and are expected to be a focus in upcoming Washington meetings. Union Agriculture Minister Shivraj Singh Chouhan has publicly supported the trade deal, emphasizing India's deficit in pulse production and the necessity of imports to meet domestic demand, while criticizing political opposition to the agreement. The intricate nature of agricultural trade encompassing approximately 1,800 tariff lines means not all details are captured in initial joint statements, with further clarity anticipated from face-to-face discussions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:25:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994885ccffb93b3e92854c5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Conglomerates Forge Infrastructure Amid Talent Hunt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Conglomerates-Forge-Infrastructure-Amid-Talent-Hunt/69948767cffb93b3e928540a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Conglomerates-Forge-Infrastructure-Amid-Talent-Hunt/69948767cffb93b3e928540a</guid><description>Reliance Industries and Adani Group are aggressively pursuing AI talent at the India AI Impact Summit, reflecting a broader national strategy to become an AI powerhouse. Significant infrastructure investments, including $100 billion from Adani for data centers and projected national AI investments exceeding $200 billion, underscore this ambition. While talent acquisition is key, the focus is shifting towards comprehensive AI ecosystem development, positioning India as a global hub. This comes as the sector's rapid growth faces scrutiny over talent costs and broader economic headwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:21:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948767cffb93b3e9285409.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Safari Industries: Volume Soars, But Margins Squeeze Amidst Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Safari-Industries-Volume-Soars-But-Margins-Squeeze-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/69948431cffb93b3e92851ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Safari-Industries-Volume-Soars-But-Margins-Squeeze-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/69948431cffb93b3e92851ea</guid><description>Safari Industries posted a 15.7% year-on-year revenue increase to INR 5.1 billion in 3QFY26, propelled by approximately 20% volume growth. However, aggressive discounting to capture market share in a competitive environment led to a sequential contraction in EBITDA and PAT margins. Despite this, analysts maintain a BUY rating, citing growth prospects from new capacities, though the stock's premium valuation faces scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:07:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69948431cffb93b3e92851e9_1771341058927.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Corporate Bill: Digital Oversight Replaces Criminal Fear</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Corporate-Bill-Digital-Oversight-Replaces-Criminal-Fear/699483d0cffb93b3e9285128</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Corporate-Bill-Digital-Oversight-Replaces-Criminal-Fear/699483d0cffb93b3e9285128</guid><description>India's upcoming Corporate Amendment Bill signals a significant regulatory pivot, moving away from criminal prosecution for minor corporate defaults towards intensified real-time digital oversight and administrative adjudication. While the stated aim is to simplify compliance, the reform necessitates substantial operational recalibrations and an increased focus on technology-driven accountability for boards and senior management, potentially creating short-term friction, especially for SMEs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699483d0cffb93b3e9285127_1771340976583.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eli Lilly Pivots India to Global Pharma Supply Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Eli-Lilly-Pivots-India-to-Global-Pharma-Supply-Hub/699483a4cffb93b3e92850a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Eli-Lilly-Pivots-India-to-Global-Pharma-Supply-Hub/699483a4cffb93b3e92850a2</guid><description>Eli Lilly is transforming India into a critical node in its global supply chain, backed by a $1 billion investment in contract manufacturing. This strategic move capitalizes on the immense success of Mounjaro in the Indian market and aims to bolster worldwide distribution of its key pharmaceuticals. The initiative highlights Lilly's proactive approach to global manufacturing diversification and supply chain resilience, positioning it to challenge rivals like Novo Nordisk with an enhanced pipeline and superior efficacy in the booming obesity treatment sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:05:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699483a4cffb93b3e92850a1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Time Technoplast: Q3 Surge Masks Valuation Questions, Growth Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Time-Technoplast-Q3-Surge-Masks-Valuation-Questions-Growth-Concerns/699483a3cffb93b3e928508b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Time-Technoplast-Q3-Surge-Masks-Valuation-Questions-Growth-Concerns/699483a3cffb93b3e928508b</guid><description>Time Technoplast posted strong 3QFY26 results with revenue and PAT up 13% and 25% YoY respectively, alongside significant debt reduction. Value-added products drove margin expansion. While analysts highlight an attractive ~14x FY28E P/E and a INR 280 price target, concerns remain regarding historical sales growth, current P/E premium, and raw material price volatility impacting future margins.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:05:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699483a3cffb93b3e928508a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PFC's 3QFY26 Growth: Dividend Income Masks Margin Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFCs-3QFY26-Growth-Dividend-Income-Masks-Margin-Pressure/6994834acffb93b3e9284f51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFCs-3QFY26-Growth-Dividend-Income-Masks-Margin-Pressure/6994834acffb93b3e9284f51</guid><description>Power Finance Corporation (PFC) posted a robust 15% year-on-year rise in standalone PAT to INR 47.6 billion for 3QFY26, fueled by a 19% increase in Net Interest Income (NII). However, a significant portion of its Other Operating Income stemmed from a INR 6.7 billion dividend payout. While Motilal Oswal reiterated a BUY rating with a target of INR 500, citing attractive valuations, a deeper analysis reveals potential margin compression and the strategic implications of its forthcoming merger with REC, as the market continues to factor in integration risks and potential value unlocks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:03:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994834acffb93b3e9284f50_1771340821654.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samvardhana Motherson: Margin Gains Spark Rally, But Valuation Worries Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Samvardhana-Motherson-Margin-Gains-Spark-Rally-But-Valuation-Worries-Loom/6994833dcffb93b3e9284f31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Samvardhana-Motherson-Margin-Gains-Spark-Rally-But-Valuation-Worries-Loom/6994833dcffb93b3e9284f31</guid><description>Samvardhana Motherson International reported a strong Q3 FY26 with record revenues of INR 31,409 crore and a 21% year-on-year profit jump to INR 10.6 billion. Sequential margin expansion in its Modules and Polymers, and Integrated Assemblies businesses fueled this performance. While analysts reiterate 'BUY' ratings, citing growth opportunities in EV and advanced manufacturing, the company's premium valuation relative to industry averages and potential global demand headwinds present a complex picture.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:03:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994833dcffb93b3e9284f30.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Privi Specialty Chemicals: Growth Surge Meets Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Privi-Specialty-Chemicals-Growth-Surge-Meets-Valuation-Scrutiny/69948335cffb93b3e9284f15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Privi-Specialty-Chemicals-Growth-Surge-Meets-Valuation-Scrutiny/69948335cffb93b3e9284f15</guid><description>Privi Speciality Chemicals posted robust 3Q FY26 results with 25% revenue growth and expanded EBITDA margins to 25.8%. Driven by cost efficiencies and global demand, the company projects significant future growth via a ₹1,200 crore expansion. However, elevated valuation multiples, a sequential revenue dip, and execution risks temper the optimism, contrasting with some 'Strong Buy' analyst calls.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:03:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69948335cffb93b3e9284f14_1771340820846.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prince Pipes: Future Growth Amidst PVC Price Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Prince-Pipes-Future-Growth-Amidst-PVC-Price-Volatility/6994832dcffb93b3e9284efd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Prince-Pipes-Future-Growth-Amidst-PVC-Price-Volatility/6994832dcffb93b3e9284efd</guid><description>Prince Pipes and Fittings reported a subdued quarter, marked by flattish revenue and minimal volume growth, largely due to volatile PVC pricing and weak demand. Despite these headwinds, Motilal Oswal reiterates a 'BUY' rating with a target price of ₹390, projecting a 13% revenue CAGR and a 71% PAT CAGR from FY25 to FY28. This optimism hinges on the company's ability to navigate the current environment and capitalize on future industry expansion, supported by its established market position and product diversification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:03:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6994832dcffb93b3e9284efc_1771340716049.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GJL Q3 Results Spark Rally; Growth Pace Faces Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GJL-Q3-Results-Spark-Rally-Growth-Pace-Faces-Scrutiny/6994832ccffb93b3e9284ee6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GJL-Q3-Results-Spark-Rally-Growth-Pace-Faces-Scrutiny/6994832ccffb93b3e9284ee6</guid><description>P N Gadgil Jewellers announced a significant 36% year-on-year revenue increase in the third quarter of FY26, driven by strong same-store sales growth and a surge in e-commerce channels. Despite aggressive store expansion and analyst optimism, scrutiny remains on the sustainability of these high-growth drivers and the company's competitive positioning relative to larger rivals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:03:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994832ccffb93b3e9284ee5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MIDWEST: Analyst Conviction Outweighs Quarterly Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MIDWEST-Analyst-Conviction-Outweighs-Quarterly-Dip/69948328cffb93b3e9284ecf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MIDWEST-Analyst-Conviction-Outweighs-Quarterly-Dip/69948328cffb93b3e9284ecf</guid><description>Motilal Oswal maintains a BUY rating on MIDWEST with a target of INR 1,700, despite the company reporting a 19% sequential decline in revenue for 3QFY26 and lower granite production and sales volumes. The firm's bullish outlook hinges on MIDWEST's strategic diversification into higher-margin segments like quartz and heavy mineral sands, expected to drive significant future growth and profitability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:03:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948328cffb93b3e9284ece.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titan's Revenue Surge Masks Stalling Customer Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titans-Revenue-Surge-Masks-Stalling-Customer-Growth/699482b3cffb93b3e9284dfc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titans-Revenue-Surge-Masks-Stalling-Customer-Growth/699482b3cffb93b3e9284dfc</guid><description>Titan Company's Q3 FY26 consolidated revenue surged 43% YoY, fueled by strong jewelry demand. However, record gold prices have stalled customer growth, prompting a strategic shift towards affordability and a product mix adjustment. While analysts remain largely optimistic, this reliance on price-driven sales raises questions about long-term margin sustainability amid a premium valuation. The company's P/E ratio stands at approximately 91.80, significantly higher than peers like Kalyan Jewellers (39.94) and PC Jeweller (11.98), within an industry average of 52.08.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:01:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699482b3cffb93b3e9284dfb.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal's Top Picks Face Scrutiny Amidst Valuation Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Motilal-Oswals-Top-Picks-Face-Scrutiny-Amidst-Valuation-Divergence/699481dccffb93b3e9284c9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Motilal-Oswals-Top-Picks-Face-Scrutiny-Amidst-Valuation-Divergence/699481dccffb93b3e9284c9b</guid><description>Brokerage firm Motilal Oswal has identified seven Indian equities with substantial return potential, driven by improving domestic demand and strong quarterly performances. However, a closer examination reveals a complex picture, with outlier valuations, mixed profitability metrics, and differing sectoral tailwinds. While optimism for sectors like consumer durables, financials, and infrastructure remains, the report identifies key risks including margin pressures and the sustainability of growth in a shifting global economic environment. Investors face a landscape where robust domestic drivers are juxtaposed against potential value traps and competitive challenges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:57:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699481dccffb93b3e9284c9a_1771340372093.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys' Nilekani: Legacy Debt Is AI's Biggest Execution Hurdle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Nilekani-Legacy-Debt-Is-AIs-Biggest-Execution-Hurdle/69948161cffb93b3e9284bc7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Nilekani-Legacy-Debt-Is-AIs-Biggest-Execution-Hurdle/69948161cffb93b3e9284bc7</guid><description>Nandan Nilekani, Infosys co-founder, asserts Artificial Intelligence's adoption rate surpasses previous technological shifts, compelling fundamental business changes. He identifies the primary challenge not in AI's capabilities but in enterprises' critical need to modernize decades-old legacy systems. With IT budgets heavily burdened by maintenance costs, Nilekani emphasizes that execution, not opportunity, defines success in this AI-driven era, stressing the immense risk for companies failing to modernize.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:55:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948161cffb93b3e9284bc6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tolins Tyres Posts Strong Revenue Rise, Debt Cleared</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tolins-Tyres-Posts-Strong-Revenue-Rise-Debt-Cleared/69948147cffb93b3e9284b90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tolins-Tyres-Posts-Strong-Revenue-Rise-Debt-Cleared/69948147cffb93b3e9284b90</guid><description>Tolins Tyres reported a significant 32.05% jump in revenue for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025, driven by higher volumes. However, profits saw a slight year-on-year decline, with margins contracting. Positively, the company significantly reduced its borrowings, moving to a net cash position by March 2025, signaling improved financial health.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:55:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69948147cffb93b3e9284b8f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dr. Reddy's Targets GLP-1 Giants with 60% Cheaper Generic</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Targets-GLP-1-Giants-with-60percent-Cheaper-Generic/699480dacffb93b3e9284ad5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Targets-GLP-1-Giants-with-60percent-Cheaper-Generic/699480dacffb93b3e9284ad5</guid><description>Dr. Reddy's Laboratories is poised to launch a generic version of Novo Nordisk's blockbuster weight-loss drug Wegovy at approximately 60% less than the branded price. This move follows recent approval in India for a generic Ozempic and signals aggressive competition in the high-demand GLP-1 market, potentially forcing a recalibration of pricing strategies by major pharmaceutical players.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:53:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699480dacffb93b3e9284ad4_1771340178910.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Private Heli Hub: Ambition Meets Assembly Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Private-Heli-Hub-Ambition-Meets-Assembly-Reality/699480d4cffb93b3e9284abe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Private-Heli-Hub-Ambition-Meets-Assembly-Reality/699480d4cffb93b3e9284abe</guid><description>India's first private sector helicopter final assembly line (FAL) for Airbus's H125 model was inaugurated in Karnataka, a joint venture between Tata Advanced Systems (TASL) and Airbus. The facility, capable of producing both civil and military (H125M) variants, signals a significant push for indigenous aerospace manufacturing. While celebrated as a milestone, the venture faces scrutiny regarding true component indigenization, the pace of civil helicopter market development, and the competitive positioning of its military offering against established domestic players.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:53:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699480d4cffb93b3e9284abd_1771340140455.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Opens Offshore Forex Trading Doors for Indian Banks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Opens-Offshore-Forex-Trading-Doors-for-Indian-Banks/69947ca2cffb93b3e92848d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Opens-Offshore-Forex-Trading-Doors-for-Indian-Banks/69947ca2cffb93b3e92848d0</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has unveiled draft regulations permitting commercial banks and primary dealers to engage in foreign exchange and currency interest rate derivative transactions on overseas electronic trading platforms (ETPs). This initiative, contingent upon stringent international regulatory compliance, aims to foster deeper derivative markets, enhance liquidity, and align Indian financial institutions with global best practices. Key provisions include restrictions on rupee transactions to non-residents and adherence to FATF, CPMI, and IOSCO standards. The move signifies a strategic effort to integrate India's financial markets more comprehensively on the global stage, balancing opportunity with enhanced oversight.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:35:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69947ca2cffb93b3e92848cf.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Investment Accelerates NBFC Efficiency Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Investment-Accelerates-NBFC-Efficiency-Race/69947c9acffb93b3e92848b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Investment-Accelerates-NBFC-Efficiency-Race/69947c9acffb93b3e92848b9</guid><description>India's leading NBFCs are rapidly integrating AI and GenAI across their lending operations, from customer acquisition to collections, to boost efficiency and drive growth. Bajaj Finance, L&amp;T Finance, and Tata Capital are at the forefront, deploying advanced technologies that promise faster decision-making, personalized customer engagement, and stronger risk management. This technological push is not merely about cost savings but represents a strategic imperative to maintain market leadership in an increasingly digital financial ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:35:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69947c9acffb93b3e92848b8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Funds Favor Equities, but Gold Seen Outperforming</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Funds-Favor-Equities-but-Gold-Seen-Outperforming/69947c21cffb93b3e92847f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Funds-Favor-Equities-but-Gold-Seen-Outperforming/69947c21cffb93b3e92847f9</guid><description>Seasoned fund managers at the Moneycontrol Mutual Fund Summit favor equities for 2026, anticipating modest gains contingent on earnings recovery and stable corporate capex, despite global uncertainties. Concurrently, gold is projected for significant outperformance, fueled by structural imbalances and its safe-haven appeal. India's robust economic growth provides a supportive backdrop, though valuations and currency headwinds warrant consideration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:33:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69947c21cffb93b3e92847f8_1771338920643.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Regency Fincorp Raises ₹75 Cr via 14% NCDs Amid Director Disqualification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Regency-Fincorp-Raises-75-Cr-via-14percent-NCDs-Amid-Director-Disqualification/69947ba8cffb93b3e928478d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Regency-Fincorp-Raises-75-Cr-via-14percent-NCDs-Amid-Director-Disqualification/69947ba8cffb93b3e928478d</guid><description>Regency Fincorp Limited announced plans to raise ₹75 Crores through Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) at a 14% interest rate. This comes as the company faces governance challenges, with a director disqualified for missing board meetings and another director resigning. The NCDs are secured and will be issued via private placement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69947ba8cffb93b3e928478c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AM/NS India Elevates Value-Added Steel Push with Premium Offerings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AMNS-India-Elevates-Value-Added-Steel-Push-with-Premium-Offerings/69947a46cffb93b3e92846b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AMNS-India-Elevates-Value-Added-Steel-Push-with-Premium-Offerings/69947a46cffb93b3e92846b0</guid><description>ArcelorMittal Nippon Steel India (AM/NS India) is intensifying its focus on high-margin, value-added steel, aiming to increase its contribution to overall revenue from 60-65% to 75%. This strategic push is underscored by the launch of two premium coated steel products, AM/NS Vibrance and AM/NS Optima, designed to meet the sophisticated demands of Original Equipment Manufacturers (OEMs) in appliance and industrial sectors. The move aligns with strong projected growth for India's coated steel market, driven by manufacturing expansion and government initiatives.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:25:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69947a46cffb93b3e92846af.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emergent Surges to $100M ARR; AI Coding Platform Faces Intense Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Emergent-Surges-to-100M-ARR-AI-Coding-Platform-Faces-Intense-Competition/699478dbcffb93b3e928457f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Emergent-Surges-to-100M-ARR-AI-Coding-Platform-Faces-Intense-Competition/699478dbcffb93b3e928457f</guid><description>Emergent, an AI-driven "vibe-coding" platform, announced it has reached an annual run-rate revenue of over $100 million, just eight months post-launch. This milestone underscores the surging demand for accessible software development tools, particularly among small businesses and non-technical users. The company's rapid ascent, fueled by a recent $70 million Series B funding round, positions it as a notable player in the burgeoning AI development space. However, Emergent operates in a hyper-competitive market, contending with well-funded rivals and the inherent challenges of scaling AI-generated code for enterprise-grade applications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:19:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699478dbcffb93b3e928457e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shalibhadra Finance AUM Surges 37%, Profit Sees Modest Climb</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shalibhadra-Finance-AUM-Surges-37percent-Profit-Sees-Modest-Climb/699478d8cffb93b3e9284568</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shalibhadra-Finance-AUM-Surges-37percent-Profit-Sees-Modest-Climb/699478d8cffb93b3e9284568</guid><description>Shalibhadra Finance Limited reported strong Q3 FY26 results, with Assets Under Management (AUM) surging 37% year-on-year to ₹212.49 Crores. The company saw a 13% rise in total income and a 7% increase in profit after tax to ₹5.03 Crores. Net Interest Income grew by a robust 31%. Despite funding growth through borrowings causing a slight moderation in its very strong Capital Adequacy Ratio, management remains optimistic, expecting to meet its AUM target and continue business momentum driven by improving two-wheeler demand.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:19:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699478d8cffb93b3e9284567.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SWELECT Energy Forms USA JV for Solar Battery Storage Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/SWELECT-Energy-Forms-USA-JV-for-Solar-Battery-Storage-Expansion/699476fbcffb93b3e92843db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/SWELECT-Energy-Forms-USA-JV-for-Solar-Battery-Storage-Expansion/699476fbcffb93b3e92843db</guid><description>SWELECT ENERGY SYSTEMS LIMITED has partnered with FortifyGrid LLC of the USA to establish a joint venture company in India. This strategic alliance will focus on developing and installing Solar Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS). The move aims to bolster SWELECT's international presence and leverage advanced BESS technology, AI, and FortifyGrid's expertise to strengthen its position in the global energy storage market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699476fbcffb93b3e92843da.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KNR Constructions LOA Stalled by Madras HC Stay</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-LOA-Stalled-by-Madras-HC-Stay/699476facffb93b3e92843c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-LOA-Stalled-by-Madras-HC-Stay/699476facffb93b3e92843c5</guid><description>KNR Constructions Limited secured a Letter of Acceptance (LOA) for a significant Rs 2,163.07 crore elevated corridor project on the East Coast Road in Tamil Nadu, to be executed under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM). However, the project's immediate future is uncertain as the Madras High Court has issued an interim stay on the work order issuance, following a legal challenge by a disqualified bidder. This development casts a shadow over the award, despite the company's substantial order book and specific financial metrics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:11:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699476facffb93b3e92843c4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCG to Raise ₹425 Cr via Rights Issue for Shareholder Funding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HCG-to-Raise-425-Cr-via-Rights-Issue-for-Shareholder-Funding/699476f7cffb93b3e92843ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HCG-to-Raise-425-Cr-via-Rights-Issue-for-Shareholder-Funding/699476f7cffb93b3e92843ae</guid><description>HealthCare Global Enterprises Limited (HCG) has announced that its Board of Directors has approved a plan to raise up to ₹42,500 Lakhs (₹425 Crores) through a rights issue of equity shares. This move aims to infuse capital into the company, though specific terms like the issue price and record date are yet to be finalized. Existing shareholders will be given the first chance to subscribe to these new shares.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:11:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699476f7cffb93b3e92843ad.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Senco Gold Q3 Profit Surges 689% On Gold Prices, But Volume Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Senco-Gold-Q3-Profit-Surges-689percent-On-Gold-Prices-But-Volume-Dips/69947521cffb93b3e928425e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Senco-Gold-Q3-Profit-Surges-689percent-On-Gold-Prices-But-Volume-Dips/69947521cffb93b3e928425e</guid><description>Senco Gold reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with profit soaring 689% YoY to ₹264 Crores, fueled by a 50% revenue jump to ₹3,000 Crores, largely due to high gold prices. However, the company saw a 3% decline in gold volumes. Strategic moves include launching 9-carat gold, expanding its store network, and the planned acquisition of Melorra to attract younger customers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:03:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69947521cffb93b3e928425d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BHEL Secures ₹1500 Cr Power Plant Order from SAIL for IISCO Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BHEL-Secures-1500-Cr-Power-Plant-Order-from-SAIL-for-IISCO-Expansion/699474b0cffb93b3e92841b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BHEL-Secures-1500-Cr-Power-Plant-Order-from-SAIL-for-IISCO-Expansion/699474b0cffb93b3e92841b7</guid><description>Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited (BHEL) has landed a significant order valued between ₹1200-1500 crore from Steel Authority of India Limited (SAIL). The contract is for a Captive Power Plant (CPP) package for SAIL's IISCO Steel Plant expansion in Burnpur. Executed on a turnkey basis, the project is expected to be completed within 39 months, bolstering BHEL's order book and strengthening its position in the industrial infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:01:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699474b0cffb93b3e92841b6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Bond Buying Binge: Can It Sustain India's Record Debt Load?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Bond-Buying-Binge-Can-It-Sustain-Indias-Record-Debt-Load/6994743bcffb93b3e92840ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Bond-Buying-Binge-Can-It-Sustain-Indias-Record-Debt-Load/6994743bcffb93b3e92840ef</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has aggressively purchased 47% of the Centre's government bond issuances in FY26, injecting Rs 6.39 lakh crore to cushion banking system liquidity against substantial government borrowing. Despite these interventions, bond yields remain volatile due to geopolitical tensions, rate cycle expectations, and a record-breaking Rs 17.2 lakh crore gross borrowing target for FY27, which has already pushed the 10-year yield to multi-year highs. The central bank's sustained OMO operations raise questions about the market's capacity to absorb future debt without continuous support.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:59:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994743bcffb93b3e92840ee.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ventive Hospitality Buys Soho House India Rights for ₹59.8 Crore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ventive-Hospitality-Buys-Soho-House-India-Rights-for-598-Crore/6994742dcffb93b3e92840d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ventive-Hospitality-Buys-Soho-House-India-Rights-for-598-Crore/6994742dcffb93b3e92840d8</guid><description>Ventive Hospitality Limited, through its subsidiary Panchshil Corporate Park Private Limited, has acquired 100% of Finest-VN Business Park Private Limited for ₹59.83 Crores. This strategic move gives Ventive control over the exclusive rights for Soho House's expansion in India and the operation of Soho House Mumbai, aiming to tap into the country's growing premium hospitality market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:59:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6994742dcffb93b3e92840d7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Khosla's AI Forecast: India IT Faces Disruption, Bets on Sovereign AI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Khoslas-AI-Forecast-India-IT-Faces-Disruption-Bets-on-Sovereign-AI/699473b8cffb93b3e9284069</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Khoslas-AI-Forecast-India-IT-Faces-Disruption-Bets-on-Sovereign-AI/699473b8cffb93b3e9284069</guid><description>Tech luminary Vinod Khosla has issued a dire warning, predicting artificial intelligence could render 80% of jobs obsolete by 2030 and wipe out India's IT and BPO sectors within five years. While forecasting widespread disruption, Khosla also champions India's sovereign AI ambitions, evidenced by his investment in Sarvam AI, a venture focused on developing indigenous AI models. This poses a critical inflection point for the Indian technology services industry, which has historically relied on a labor-intensive outsourcing model but is now facing unprecedented AI-driven automation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:57:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699473b8cffb93b3e9284068.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Power Sector Pivot: Hybrid &amp; Storage Drive Reliability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Sector-Pivot-Hybrid-and-Storage-Drive-Reliability/699472c1cffb93b3e9283f9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Sector-Pivot-Hybrid-and-Storage-Drive-Reliability/699472c1cffb93b3e9283f9b</guid><description>India's power sector is strategically pivoting towards hybrid and energy storage-based projects, moving beyond traditional solar installations. This shift is driven by the imperative to enhance energy reliability and ensure seamless integration of renewable energy sources into the grid. Low solar-hour electricity prices in January 2026, hovering around Rs 4.3 per kWh, underscore an oversupply during peak daylight. This abundance, however, highlights the growing need for solutions that can manage intermittency. The country's overall power demand saw a robust 4.8% year-on-year increase in January 2026, with peak demand rising approximately 3% YoY to 245 GW, signaling sustained economic activity. Electricity trading on the Indian Energy Exchange (IEX) surged by 19.6% YoY, particularly in the Real-Time Market (RTM), which jumped 52.8%, indicating a dynamic market response to evolving energy needs. However, a concurrent 13% decline in Renewable Energy Certificate (REC) volumes suggests a market recalibrating towards integrated generation and storage solutions rather than solely certificate-based compliance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699472c1cffb93b3e9283f9a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IIFL Capital Profit Drops 27% QoQ Amid Cost Rise, Tax Probe Continues</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Capital-Profit-Drops-27percent-QoQ-Amid-Cost-Rise-Tax-Probe-Continues/69947158cffb93b3e9283ed3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Capital-Profit-Drops-27percent-QoQ-Amid-Cost-Rise-Tax-Probe-Continues/69947158cffb93b3e9283ed3</guid><description>IIFL Capital Services saw its operational profit before tax (PBT) fall by 27% quarter-on-quarter to INR 119 crores in Q3 FY'26, driven by a 14% rise in employee costs and other expenses. While revenue remained flat, the company is also navigating ongoing proceedings from an Income Tax Department search conducted in January 2025. Management is optimistic about reaching break-even in wealth management by FY'27.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:47:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69947158cffb93b3e9283ed2.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>