<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:57:16 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Zydus Wellness Q3: Revenue Soars 113%, EBITDA Jumps 312%, But Net Loss Persists</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zydus-Wellness-Q3-Revenue-Soars-113percent-EBITDA-Jumps-312percent-But-Net-Loss-Persists/6989661ab81b2b81dcfe671d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Zydus-Wellness-Q3-Revenue-Soars-113percent-EBITDA-Jumps-312percent-But-Net-Loss-Persists/6989661ab81b2b81dcfe671d</guid><description>Zydus Wellness reported a blockbuster Q3 FY2026 with consolidated Net Sales surging 113.7% YoY, fueled by the Comfort Click acquisition. EBITDA also leaped 312.2% to ₹610 million, with margins expanding significantly. However, the company posted a net loss of ₹399 million, primarily due to substantial interest expenses and amortization related to acquisition funding, alongside one-off costs. Management remains optimistic, expecting the current fiscal year to be the profitability bottom, with cash EPS accretion projected from FY27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:44:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989661ab81b2b81dcfe671c_1770612376756.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Strategic Energy Pivot: Balancing Geopolitics, Trade, and Supply Dynamics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Strategic-Energy-Pivot-Balancing-Geopolitics-Trade-and-Supply-Dynamics/698964b6b81b2b81dcfe6563</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Strategic-Energy-Pivot-Balancing-Geopolitics-Trade-and-Supply-Dynamics/698964b6b81b2b81dcfe6563</guid><description>India's refiners are significantly scaling back purchases of Russian crude oil for April deliveries, a critical pivot reportedly tied to securing a new trade framework with the United States. This strategic shift, moving away from heavily discounted Russian supplies, aims to balance geopolitical alignment with energy security priorities. While facilitating a trade pact that could lower tariffs on Indian goods, the move necessitates diversification towards alternative sources, potentially impacting India's refining economics and global supply chains. Analysts suggest the reduction will be gradual, with Russian oil volumes likely to remain a notable, albeit diminished, part of India's import basket.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:38:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698964b6b81b2b81dcfe6562_1770612054688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MGL Earnings: Profit Dip Amid Revenue Rise, Analysts Divided</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/MGL-Earnings-Profit-Dip-Amid-Revenue-Rise-Analysts-Divided/6989643cb81b2b81dcfe644f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/MGL-Earnings-Profit-Dip-Amid-Revenue-Rise-Analysts-Divided/6989643cb81b2b81dcfe644f</guid><description>Mahanagar Gas Ltd. (MGL) posted a revenue increase but a year-on-year profit decline for its third quarter, despite a sequential improvement in operating margins. While volumes grew, brokerages issued contrasting ratings, with some expressing long-term growth caution and a recent 'Sell' rating highlighting mixed financial signals. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹12 per share.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:36:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989643cb81b2b81dcfe644e_1770611902203.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Norway's Oil Fund: From Savings to Global Wealth Engine</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Norways-Oil-Fund-From-Savings-to-Global-Wealth-Engine/6989634cb81b2b81dcfe61f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Norways-Oil-Fund-From-Savings-to-Global-Wealth-Engine/6989634cb81b2b81dcfe61f0</guid><description>Norway's Government Pension Fund Global, the world's largest sovereign wealth fund, has evolved significantly since its inception. Fueled by oil revenues, its strategic shift towards aggressive global investment has made financial returns the primary growth driver, surpassing direct resource contributions. Managed by Norges Bank Investment Management, the fund's disciplined approach aims to secure Norway's long-term economic future by leveraging global capital markets, demonstrating a transformation from a resource savings vehicle to an active wealth generator on the world stage. Its vast scale and diversified portfolio position it as a critical force in global finance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:32:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989634cb81b2b81dcfe61ef_1770611650716.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEPC Surges on Stellar Profit Growth &amp; Major Order Wins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEPC-Surges-on-Stellar-Profit-Growth-and-Major-Order-Wins/69896201b81b2b81dcfe5e5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEPC-Surges-on-Stellar-Profit-Growth-and-Major-Order-Wins/69896201b81b2b81dcfe5e5b</guid><description>SEPC Limited reported a remarkable Q3 FY26, with Net Profit soaring 236.62% YoY to ₹14.96 crore. For the nine months ended December 2025 (9M FY26), Net Profit surged 168.66% YoY to ₹39.81 crore, already surpassing full-year FY25 PAT. Revenue also saw substantial growth. The company secured significant orders including a ₹230 crore MOIL contract, a ₹269.69 crore railway EPC sub-contract, and a ₹86 crore airport project, alongside an international order in the UAE. These wins underscore SEPC's robust execution and growing pipeline.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:26:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69896201b81b2b81dcfe5e5a_1770611424859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Boosts Exports, But Valuations Pose Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Boosts-Exports-But-Valuations-Pose-Caution/698961e4b81b2b81dcfe5dae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Boosts-Exports-But-Valuations-Pose-Caution/698961e4b81b2b81dcfe5dae</guid><description>The interim trade framework between India and the United States significantly lowers US reciprocal tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, a move expected to boost exports and enhance India's competitive standing against Asian peers. While this offers a clear sentiment positive for Indian equities, particularly export-oriented sectors, elevated market valuations suggest that foreign institutional investor inflows may materialize gradually rather than immediately. The deal also brings geopolitical considerations, including India's commitment to alter Russian oil import policies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:26:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698961e4b81b2b81dcfe5dad_1770611333796.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Relief Sparks Indian Market Rally, But Caution Lingers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Relief-Sparks-Indian-Market-Rally-But-Caution-Lingers/6989600bb81b2b81dcfe5bb7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Relief-Sparks-Indian-Market-Rally-But-Caution-Lingers/6989600bb81b2b81dcfe5bb7</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks, Nifty50 and BSE Sensex, opened significantly higher on Monday, driven by positive news from a joint India-US trade deal statement and the US revoking a 25% penal tariff. The Nifty50 surpassed 25,800, while the Sensex gained over 500 points. Global markets, including Asian equities and Wall Street, also posted gains, buoyed by advances in semiconductor companies like Nvidia. Gold and silver prices continued their upward trend amid a weakening dollar. Despite the optimism, market analysts anticipate range-bound trading ahead, with stock-specific movements dictated by earnings and persistent global uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:18:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989600bb81b2b81dcfe5bb6_1770610875726.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kaynes Technology: Order Book Surge Masked by Execution Lags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kaynes-Technology-Order-Book-Surge-Masked-by-Execution-Lags/69895f18b81b2b81dcfe59a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kaynes-Technology-Order-Book-Surge-Masked-by-Execution-Lags/69895f18b81b2b81dcfe59a8</guid><description>Kaynes Technology reported a 50% YoY increase in its order book, exceeding Rs 9,100 crore. However, Q3 FY26 performance lagged expectations due to execution delays in key segments, leading to a downward revision of FY26 revenue guidance to Rs 4,100 crore. Persistent elevated working capital days and cash flow generation remain significant risks despite strategic expansion into OSAT and PCB manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:14:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895f18b81b2b81dcfe59a7_1770610741955.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Data Patterns: High Valuation Meets Defence Growth Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Data-Patterns-High-Valuation-Meets-Defence-Growth-Ambition/69895ebbb81b2b81dcfe5847</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Data-Patterns-High-Valuation-Meets-Defence-Growth-Ambition/69895ebbb81b2b81dcfe5847</guid><description>Data Patterns announced robust year-over-year revenue and EBITDA growth in Q3FY26, bolstered by a record order book of Rs 1,868 crore. The company is strategically transitioning to a full systems integrator, aligning with India's 'Atmanirbhar Bharat' initiative. However, its current trading multiple of approximately 61.7x earnings outpaces many peers, suggesting market expectations are running high against a backdrop of extended working capital cycles.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:12:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895ebbb81b2b81dcfe5846_1770610580583.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VST Tillers Tractors Hits Record Turnover, Power Tiller Sales Surge 55%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VST-Tillers-Tractors-Hits-Record-Turnover-Power-Tiller-Sales-Surge-55percent/69895e9eb81b2b81dcfe5760</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VST-Tillers-Tractors-Hits-Record-Turnover-Power-Tiller-Sales-Surge-55percent/69895e9eb81b2b81dcfe5760</guid><description>V.S.T. Tillers Tractors Ltd. has reported record financial results for the nine months and third quarter of FY26. The company achieved its highest-ever turnover for the 9-month period at ₹912 Cr, a 32% year-on-year increase. Power tiller sales grew by 55.1% and power weeder sales by 63.3%. For Q3 FY26, revenue hit a record ₹314 Cr, up 44% YoY, with significant volume growth in power tillers and weeders. EBITDA margins saw substantial improvement, particularly in Q3 FY26, reaching 13.0% from 8.9% YoY. Operational cash generation also improved significantly.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:12:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895e9eb81b2b81dcfe575f_1770610611218.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hi-Tech Pipes Boosts Capacity To 1 Million Tons With New UP Facility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Pipes-Boosts-Capacity-To-1-Million-Tons-With-New-UP-Facility/69895dacb81b2b81dcfe55b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Pipes-Boosts-Capacity-To-1-Million-Tons-With-New-UP-Facility/69895dacb81b2b81dcfe55b7</guid><description>Hi-Tech Pipes Limited has commenced commercial production at its new greenfield manufacturing facility in Sikandrabad, Uttar Pradesh (Unit-III). This adds 1,20,000 MTPA capacity, bringing the company's total installed capacity to 10,50,000 MTPA. The Rs. 85 Cr investment, funded by internal accruals, is strategically located to enhance efficiency and customer response. The company anticipates strong demand driven by infrastructure development and expects improved operating leverage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:08:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895dacb81b2b81dcfe55b6_1770610313205.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Britannia Q3: Margin Boost Meets New CEO Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannia-Q3-Margin-Boost-Meets-New-CEO-Scrutiny/69895cdab81b2b81dcfe5399</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Britannia-Q3-Margin-Boost-Meets-New-CEO-Scrutiny/69895cdab81b2b81dcfe5399</guid><description>Britannia is poised to report strong Q3FY26 earnings, with net profit projected up 18% and revenue up 10% year-on-year. This growth is largely attributed to expanding gross margins, driven by softer commodity prices and strategic pricing initiatives like grammage additions. However, the market's focus is shifting to the sustainability of these gains and the strategic direction under the new CEO, especially concerning adjacent businesses and competitive pressures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:04:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895cdab81b2b81dcfe5398_1770610120889.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IREDA Raises ₹2,994 Cr Via QIP Amidst Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IREDA-Raises-2994-Cr-Via-QIP-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/69895cbdb81b2b81dcfe52b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IREDA-Raises-2994-Cr-Via-QIP-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/69895cbdb81b2b81dcfe52b4</guid><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency (IREDA) secured board approval for a ₹2,994 crore Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP). Despite the news, the stock remains significantly down year-over-year and trades below its last QIP price. The move aims to bolster capital adequacy, but raises ongoing concerns about government stake dilution and the company's valuation relative to peers in the rapidly expanding Indian renewable energy sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:04:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895cbdb81b2b81dcfe52b3_1770609978327.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PhonePe IPO: OFS signals exit amid fintech race with Paytm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/PhonePe-IPO-OFS-signals-exit-amid-fintech-race-with-Paytm/69895adeb81b2b81dcfe503d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/PhonePe-IPO-OFS-signals-exit-amid-fintech-race-with-Paytm/69895adeb81b2b81dcfe503d</guid><description>PhonePe's much-anticipated IPO is structured entirely as an Offer for Sale (OFS), signaling an exit for early investors like Walmart and Tiger Global, at a $15 billion valuation. This move diverges from typical growth IPOs and highlights PhonePe's focus on scaling its dominant payments platform. It sets up a direct strategic comparison with rival Paytm, which has achieved profitability through a broader super-app model, even as PhonePe leads in consumer engagement metrics. The Indian fintech market, projected for substantial growth, faces evolving regulatory scrutiny as both players vie for market supremacy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:56:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895adeb81b2b81dcfe503c_1770609642746.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Bonds Under Pressure: State Debt Surge Meets RBI Liquidity Pause</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Bonds-Under-Pressure-State-Debt-Surge-Meets-RBI-Liquidity-Pause/69895a81b81b2b81dcfe4e74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Bonds-Under-Pressure-State-Debt-Surge-Meets-RBI-Liquidity-Pause/69895a81b81b2b81dcfe4e74</guid><description>Indian government bonds are set to extend their decline as states prepare to issue ₹486.15 billion ($5.37 billion) in debt, the largest sale this fiscal year. This substantial supply shock, occurring without explicit liquidity injections from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI), is pressuring yields. Despite the RBI's rate pause, attributed to a robust economic outlook, market participants are concerned about system liquidity, exacerbated by deposit growth lagging credit demand. The benchmark 10-year bond yield is anticipated to trade within a higher band.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:54:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895a81b81b2b81dcfe4e73_1770609553341.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PB Fintech Stock: Valuation Jitters Trump Fundraising Denials</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PB-Fintech-Stock-Valuation-Jitters-Trump-Fundraising-Denials/69895a6cb81b2b81dcfe4dd5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PB-Fintech-Stock-Valuation-Jitters-Trump-Fundraising-Denials/69895a6cb81b2b81dcfe4dd5</guid><description>PB Fintech has officially denied reports of reviving a $1 billion fundraising plan via a qualified institutional placement (QIP). While this denial led to a stock surge, it did little to quell underlying investor skepticism. The company's persistently high valuation, coupled with past concerns over capital allocation to ventures like healthcare and international expansion, continues to cast a shadow over its market performance. Investors remain wary, scrutinizing future strategic moves for their potential impact on profitability and shareholder value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:54:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895a6cb81b2b81dcfe4dd4_1770609384610.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axiscades Arm Wins ₹80 Cr Avionics Order for India's LCA Jet</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Axiscades-Arm-Wins-80-Cr-Avionics-Order-for-Indias-LCA-Jet/69895972b81b2b81dcfe4c4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Axiscades-Arm-Wins-80-Cr-Avionics-Order-for-Indias-LCA-Jet/69895972b81b2b81dcfe4c4a</guid><description>AXISCADES Technologies, via its subsidiary Mistral Solutions, has landed a substantial ₹80 crore production order for avionics hardware from Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL) for the LCA Mk1A program. This significant win strengthens the company's 'Make in India' defence push and its partnerships with HAL and DRDO. The order for critical electronic hardware, including Mission Computers and Smart Multifunction Displays, will be manufactured at its new Devanahalli facility, positioning Mistral for future defence projects and implying positive near-term revenue growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:50:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895972b81b2b81dcfe4c49_1770609117273.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>V2 Retail Q3 Profit Soars 99% On 57% Revenue Surge, Eyes 150 New Stores</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/V2-Retail-Q3-Profit-Soars-99percent-On-57percent-Revenue-Surge-Eyes-150-New-Stores/69895794b81b2b81dcfe4a3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/V2-Retail-Q3-Profit-Soars-99percent-On-57percent-Revenue-Surge-Eyes-150-New-Stores/69895794b81b2b81dcfe4a3a</guid><description>V2 Retail reported a robust Q3 FY2026 with revenue soaring 57% YoY to ₹929 crore and Profit After Tax (PAT) jumping 99% YoY to ₹102 crore, exceeding FY2025 PAT. The company raised ₹400 crore via QIP, resolved an asset write-off, and aligned lease accounting, resulting in an exceptional gain. With 304 stores and 31.9 lakh sq ft, V2 Retail plans to aggressively expand by opening 150 new stores in FY2027, targeting 50% revenue growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:42:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895794b81b2b81dcfe4a39_1770608661858.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Hits Record Revenue Amid Strong Demand and Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Hits-Record-Revenue-Amid-Strong-Demand-and-Global-Expansion/6989571bb81b2b81dcfe48e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Hits-Record-Revenue-Amid-Strong-Demand-and-Global-Expansion/6989571bb81b2b81dcfe48e7</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp achieved its highest-ever quarterly revenue in Q3 FY26, with a 20.7% year-on-year increase driven by robust volume growth. The company saw its EBITDA margin expand by 22 basis points, despite EV investments. A positive demand outlook persists, with management expecting double-digit industry growth in Q4 FY26 and high single-digit growth in FY27. Exports and the parts/accessories business also set new revenue records.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:40:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989571bb81b2b81dcfe48e6_1770608545762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets: Steel &amp; Banking Shine, Consumer Faces Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Markets-Steel-and-Banking-Shine-Consumer-Faces-Headwinds/6989553cb81b2b81dcfe461b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Markets-Steel-and-Banking-Shine-Consumer-Faces-Headwinds/6989553cb81b2b81dcfe461b</guid><description>Indian markets opened positively, buoyed by Asian gains and strong Q3 earnings from manufacturing giant Tata Steel and banking behemoth SBI. Tata Steel's net profit surged over 700%, while SBI posted its highest-ever quarterly profit. Conversely, Sula Vineyards reported a significant profit decline due to destocking and subdued demand. Bharti Airtel's request for a moratorium on AGR dues highlights ongoing telecom sector regulatory concerns. Strategic expansions by Tata Chemicals and BEML, alongside PFC's acquisition of REC, signal future growth initiatives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:32:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989553cb81b2b81dcfe461a_1770608054503.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fractal IPO Opens at Premium Valuation Amid Talent Churn Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Fractal-IPO-Opens-at-Premium-Valuation-Amid-Talent-Churn-Concerns/698952e1b81b2b81dcfe42fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Fractal-IPO-Opens-at-Premium-Valuation-Amid-Talent-Churn-Concerns/698952e1b81b2b81dcfe42fc</guid><description>Fractal Analytics Ltd. opened its IPO on February 9, 2026, seeking to raise ₹2,834 crore. The company, India's first pure-play AI firm to go public, is priced at a premium, reflecting ambitious growth expectations in the enterprise AI sector. However, market sentiment is tempered by elevated valuations, a high attrition rate, and potential client insourcing risks. While anchor investors showed confidence, a cautious approach prevails among some analysts, emphasizing the need to monitor post-listing performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:22:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698952e1b81b2b81dcfe42fb_1770607443243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Diverges: IT Tumbles on AI Fears, Select Stocks Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Diverges-IT-Tumbles-on-AI-Fears-Select-Stocks-Surge/69895180b81b2b81dcfe4163</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Diverges-IT-Tumbles-on-AI-Fears-Select-Stocks-Surge/69895180b81b2b81dcfe4163</guid><description>The Indian equity market exhibited significant divergence, with the Nifty IT index plummeting nearly 7% on escalating artificial intelligence concerns. In contrast, the broader Nifty index navigated extreme volatility, influenced by tariff relief measures that briefly buoyed sentiment. Select stocks, including Bajaj Finance and Larsen &amp; Toubro, demonstrated resilience and technical strength, signaling a bifurcated market driven by specific catalysts rather than uniform optimism. The Bank Nifty also posted weekly gains, underscoring strength in the financial sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69895180b81b2b81dcfe4162_1770607093843.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Technical Breakouts Signal Caution: SEIL High P/E, Senores Weak Fundamentals, Sundaram Finance Stands Out</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Technical-Breakouts-Signal-Caution-SEIL-High-PE-Senores-Weak-Fundamentals-Sundaram-Finance-Stands-Out/69894e36b81b2b81dcfe3f16</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Technical-Breakouts-Signal-Caution-SEIL-High-PE-Senores-Weak-Fundamentals-Sundaram-Finance-Stands-Out/69894e36b81b2b81dcfe3f16</guid><description>Schneider Electric Infrastructure (SEIL) shows a high P/E of 71x despite a strong order book, raising valuation concerns and a 'Sell' rating from analysts due to high debt. Senores Pharmaceuticals exhibits a very high P/E and weak underlying fundamentals like negative cash flow and poor ROE. Sundaram Finance, conversely, presents a balanced profile with fair valuation, solid growth, declining NPAs, and a 'Buy' rating, making it the most compelling of the three technical breakouts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:02:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69894e36b81b2b81dcfe3f15_1770606247319.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Tariff Relief Masks Strategic Conflict</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariff-Relief-Masks-Strategic-Conflict/69894df2b81b2b81dcfe3d39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariff-Relief-Masks-Strategic-Conflict/69894df2b81b2b81dcfe3d39</guid><description>India and the United States have agreed to a trade deal framework, reducing US tariffs on Indian goods to 18% and eliminating certain barriers for US exports. New Delhi commits to substantial purchases of US energy, aircraft, and goods totaling $500 billion over five years. However, the accord faces scrutiny for potentially undermining India's 'Viksit Bharat' self-reliance agenda, particularly regarding coking coal imports and the impact on domestic agriculture, despite official assurances of farmer protection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:01:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69894df2b81b2b81dcfe3d38_1770606243400.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tea Exports Hit Record High, But Regulatory Hurdles Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Tea-Exports-Hit-Record-High-But-Regulatory-Hurdles-Loom/69894de0b81b2b81dcfe3c7e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Tea-Exports-Hit-Record-High-But-Regulatory-Hurdles-Loom/69894de0b81b2b81dcfe3c7e</guid><description>India achieved a record 280.4 million kg in tea exports for 2025, a 9.5% increase from 256.17 million kg in 2024. Key drivers included robust shipments to Iraq and China, with exports more than doubling to China. Despite this volume surge, tightening European Union pesticide regulations present a substantial challenge, potentially impacting a significant portion of high-value exports and forcing a strategic re-evaluation beyond sheer tonnage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:00:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69894de0b81b2b81dcfe3c7d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dow Jones at 50K: Trump's Bullish Forecast Clashes with Tariff Ruling Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dow-Jones-at-50K-Trumps-Bullish-Forecast-Clashes-with-Tariff-Ruling-Risk/69894dbfb81b2b81dcfe3b9f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dow-Jones-at-50K-Trumps-Bullish-Forecast-Clashes-with-Tariff-Ruling-Risk/69894dbfb81b2b81dcfe3b9f</guid><description>The Dow Jones Industrial Average has surpassed 50,000, with former President Trump forecasting a 100,000 target, buoyed by prior market gains and tariffs. However, a critical Supreme Court ruling on the legality of these tariffs, due by February 20, poses a substantial risk, potentially introducing widespread market volatility and impacting inflation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:00:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69894dbfb81b2b81dcfe3b9e_1770606133738.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SGBs Deliver 216% Gain Amidst Tax Rule Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/SGBs-Deliver-216percent-Gain-Amidst-Tax-Rule-Overhaul/69894cccb81b2b81dcfe39f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/SGBs-Deliver-216percent-Gain-Amidst-Tax-Rule-Overhaul/69894cccb81b2b81dcfe39f2</guid><description>Sovereign Gold Bond (SGB) 2020–21 Series-XI investors are set to achieve approximately 216% capital appreciation upon premature redemption on February 9, 2026. The redemption price of ₹15,374 per unit reflects substantial growth since the ₹4,862 issue price in 2021. However, proposed tax amendments from the Union Budget 2026 will now restrict capital gains tax exemption solely to original subscribers holding bonds until maturity, significantly impacting secondary market participants.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:56:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69894cccb81b2b81dcfe39f1_1770605896564.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SIP Pauses: The Stealth Wealth Killer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/SIP-Pauses-The-Stealth-Wealth-Killer/69894aeeb81b2b81dcfe3799</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/SIP-Pauses-The-Stealth-Wealth-Killer/69894aeeb81b2b81dcfe3799</guid><description>Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) are often paused due to perceived responsibility during income disruptions, a flawed framing that breaks the vital habit of consistent investment. This failure to maintain continuity leads to significant, irreversible wealth erosion over time. The core issue is not the pause itself, but the psychological inertia that prevents investors from restarting, ultimately sacrificing long-term compounding for temporary financial flexibility. The market rewards continuous participation, not good intentions or absent distress.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69894aeeb81b2b81dcfe3798_1770605441780.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Prices Ease as Geopolitical Relief Outweighs Lingering Supply Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Ease-as-Geopolitical-Relief-Outweighs-Lingering-Supply-Risks/698945f2b81b2b81dcfe1cca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Ease-as-Geopolitical-Relief-Outweighs-Lingering-Supply-Risks/698945f2b81b2b81dcfe1cca</guid><description>Oil prices retreated Monday as diplomatic progress between the U.S. and Iran eased immediate conflict fears. Brent crude fell 0.72% to $67.56, and WTI dipped 0.66% to $63.13. Despite this short-term relief, the market faces persistent geopolitical risks in the Strait of Hormuz and complex shifts in global supply due to sanctions impacting Russian exports and India's changing import strategies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:26:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698945f2b81b2b81dcfe1cc9_1770604132859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Recovers $5K Amid Rate Cut Bets, Silver's Volatility Peaks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Recovers-5K-Amid-Rate-Cut-Bets-Silvers-Volatility-Peaks/698945deb81b2b81dcfe1c03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Recovers-5K-Amid-Rate-Cut-Bets-Silvers-Volatility-Peaks/698945deb81b2b81dcfe1c03</guid><description>Gold surged back above $5,000 per ounce, buoyed by anticipation of U.S. interest rate reductions and a weaker dollar. Silver, however, experienced a highly volatile rebound, showcasing the risks inherent in leveraged positions. Upcoming U.S. economic data will be critical in shaping Federal Reserve policy expectations and dictating the trajectory of precious metals prices, with analysts pointing to significant technical resistance and the potential for sharp price swings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:26:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698945deb81b2b81dcfe1c02.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Tariff Cuts: Tech Access Key to Long-Term Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-US-Tariff-Cuts-Tech-Access-Key-to-Long-Term-Gains/698945c4b81b2b81dcfe1aed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-US-Tariff-Cuts-Tech-Access-Key-to-Long-Term-Gains/698945c4b81b2b81dcfe1aed</guid><description>The United States is poised to enact tariff reductions on Indian exports following recent trade negotiations. While this move offers immediate relief and boosted the Nifty 50 by 3.38% this past week, India's focus extends to securing concessions on advanced technology components like GPUs and Nvidia chips. Minister Piyush Goyal indicated a comprehensive legal document will be signed by mid-March, with USTR Jamieson Greer expected in New Delhi.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:26:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698945c4b81b2b81dcfe1aec_1770604114791.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Rebounds Sharply Amidst Aggressive CME Margin Hikes and Macro Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Rebounds-Sharply-Amidst-Aggressive-CME-Margin-Hikes-and-Macro-Shifts/69894369b81b2b81dcfe18aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Rebounds-Sharply-Amidst-Aggressive-CME-Margin-Hikes-and-Macro-Shifts/69894369b81b2b81dcfe18aa</guid><description>Silver prices experienced a sharp rebound on February 9, 2026, climbing to $80.25 per ounce after a precipitous 40% decline from late January's record highs near $120. This volatility was amplified by a strengthening US Dollar, influenced by hawkish Federal Reserve nominee Kevin Warsh, and a perceived de-escalation in geopolitical tensions. The CME Group's aggressive hiking of margin requirements added significant pressure, forcing liquidations. Despite the extreme swings, a cautious long-term positive outlook persists, awaiting key economic data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:16:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69894369b81b2b81dcfe18a9_1770603535301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Capital Surge: PFC QIP, BEML Rail Plant, IDBI Sale Signal Strategic Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Capital-Surge-PFC-QIP-BEML-Rail-Plant-IDBI-Sale-Signal-Strategic-Overhaul/698942f6b81b2b81dcfe174c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Capital-Surge-PFC-QIP-BEML-Rail-Plant-IDBI-Sale-Signal-Strategic-Overhaul/698942f6b81b2b81dcfe174c</guid><description>State-owned enterprises are at the forefront of strategic market activity. Power Finance Corporation (PFC) is raising up to ₹2,994 crore via Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) to fuel renewable energy investments. Concurrently, BEML Limited approved a ₹1,500 crore greenfield rail manufacturing facility. Meanwhile, the disinvestment process for IDBI Bank moves forward with financial bids submitted, though Kotak Mahindra Bank clarified its non-participation. These moves signal a concerted effort to bolster capital, expand capacity, and optimize asset portfolios across key sectors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:14:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698942f6b81b2b81dcfe174b_1770603412751.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Spending Scrutiny Mounts Amid Reflation Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/AI-Spending-Scrutiny-Mounts-Amid-Reflation-Hopes/69893f36b81b2b81dcfe14bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/AI-Spending-Scrutiny-Mounts-Amid-Reflation-Hopes/69893f36b81b2b81dcfe14bc</guid><description>Asian markets surged, led by Japan's Nikkei hitting all-time highs following Prime Minister Takaichi's decisive election victory, fueling expectations for reflationary policies. Wall Street's rebound and strong gains in chip stocks like Nvidia and AMD also bolstered sentiment, supported by growing bets on Federal Reserve rate cuts. However, underlying concerns about the substantial capital expenditure on AI and its uncertain return on investment are prompting a strategic investor rotation from AI 'spenders' to 'beneficiaries'. Simultaneously, Japan's fiscal expansionary stance has put pressure on the Yen, raising intervention concerns, while political instability weighs on Sterling.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:58:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69893f36b81b2b81dcfe14bb_1770602494396.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Breakouts Face Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Tech-Breakouts-Face-Valuation-Scrutiny/69893ebfb81b2b81dcfe1368</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Tech-Breakouts-Face-Valuation-Scrutiny/69893ebfb81b2b81dcfe1368</guid><description>Navin Fluorine International, Hitachi Energy India, and FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) have all achieved significant technical breakouts, driven by robust volume and positive momentum indicators. Navin Fluorine hit an all-time high, Hitachi Energy demonstrated a strong trend reversal, and Nykaa signals a bullish reversal. However, elevated valuations, particularly for Nykaa and Hitachi, alongside nuanced profitability concerns for Navin Fluorine, introduce underlying risks to these rallies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:56:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69893ebfb81b2b81dcfe1367_1770602357310.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Earnings Diverge: SBI Shines, Tata Steel Faces Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Earnings-Diverge-SBI-Shines-Tata-Steel-Faces-Global-Headwinds/69893e43b81b2b81dcfe1219</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Earnings-Diverge-SBI-Shines-Tata-Steel-Faces-Global-Headwinds/69893e43b81b2b81dcfe1219</guid><description>India's third-quarter earnings season is revealing distinct market narratives. State Bank of India (SBI) demonstrated robust performance, bolstered by provisions and operational efficiency, while Tata Steel reported a significant year-on-year profit surge, heavily influenced by domestic demand and import tariffs, yet grappling with international operational losses. Aurobindo Pharma is set to report, with analyst sentiment mixed amid sector-wide valuations. The market is evaluating companies based on their exposure to domestic versus global economic forces.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:54:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69893e43b81b2b81dcfe1218_1770602195126.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goldman Warns: US Stocks Face More Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Goldman-Warns-US-Stocks-Face-More-Selling-Pressure/69893dcab81b2b81dcfe10c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Goldman-Warns-US-Stocks-Face-More-Selling-Pressure/69893dcab81b2b81dcfe10c4</guid><description>Goldman Sachs' trading desk forecasts further US stock selling this week, driven by algorithmic traders and tight liquidity. Despite a rebound, trend-following funds are expected to remain net sellers, potentially triggering billions in outflows and magnifying market swings amid 'short gamma' positioning.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:52:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69893dcab81b2b81dcfe10c3_1770602054369.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>USFDA Issues 11 Observations at Aurobindo Pharma's Unit III; Shares Under Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/USFDA-Issues-11-Observations-at-Aurobindo-Pharmas-Unit-III-Shares-Under-Pressure/6989383cb81b2b81dcfe0d87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/USFDA-Issues-11-Observations-at-Aurobindo-Pharmas-Unit-III-Shares-Under-Pressure/6989383cb81b2b81dcfe0d87</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma Ltd. shares are poised for a weak opening as the US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) issued 11 observations following an inspection of its Unit III manufacturing facility. This facility produces formulations. The inspection, conducted from January 27 to February 6, adds to existing regulatory concerns at the site, which previously received an Official Action Indicated status in May 2024 and a warning letter in August 2024. Aurobindo Pharma shares closed 1.13% higher at ₹1,195 on Friday, remaining flat year-to-date.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:28:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989383cb81b2b81dcfe0d86_1770600650397.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samsung's HBM4 Race: Chasing SK Hynix, Nvidia Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Samsungs-HBM4-Race-Chasing-SK-Hynix-Nvidia-Key/6989382cb81b2b81dcfe0ca4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Samsungs-HBM4-Race-Chasing-SK-Hynix-Nvidia-Key/6989382cb81b2b81dcfe0ca4</guid><description>Samsung Electronics Co. is initiating mass production of HBM4 memory chips, a critical component for AI infrastructure, with immediate plans to supply Nvidia Corp.'s upcoming Vera Rubin accelerators. This move signals Samsung's intensified efforts to challenge SK Hynix Inc.'s current dominance in the high-bandwidth memory market. While the HBM sector experiences unprecedented demand, Samsung's aggressive timeline and market share aspirations are under scrutiny against SK Hynix's established position and production stability. Broader memory shortages also continue to impact various technology segments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:28:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989382cb81b2b81dcfe0ca3_1770600605839.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fractal Analytics IPO Opens Amid Valuation Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Opens-Amid-Valuation-Debate/69893213b81b2b81dcfe09e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Opens-Amid-Valuation-Debate/69893213b81b2b81dcfe09e3</guid><description>Fractal Analytics' ₹2,834 crore Initial Public Offering (IPO) opened for subscription on February 9, 2026. The artificial intelligence solutions provider is seeking to capitalize on robust enterprise AI demand, but faces a divided market sentiment. While analysts acknowledge its 'pure-play' AI status and turnaround financials, concerns over its elevated valuation multiples and execution risks, including client attrition, temper enthusiasm, leading to mixed brokerage ratings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 01:02:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69893213b81b2b81dcfe09e2_1770599080592.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>