<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 18:24:00 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Economy Roars Ahead! See How India Outshines Global Giants Amidst Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-Roars-Ahead-See-How-India-Outshines-Global-Giants-Amidst-Uncertainty/694d8085e10c98d0788d3aff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-Roars-Ahead-See-How-India-Outshines-Global-Giants-Amidst-Uncertainty/694d8085e10c98d0788d3aff</guid><description>India's economy is showing robust growth, with GDP expected to exceed 7% for the full year 2025-26, outpacing global averages. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has revised its growth forecast upwards to 7.3% and reduced the repo rate to 5.25% amid benign inflation. The government is prioritizing capital expenditure, though tax revenues face some challenges. Despite global uncertainties, India's economic outlook remains strong, projected to continue at 6.5-6.8% growth in the medium term.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 18:11:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d8085e10c98d0788d3afe_1766686959690.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerage Fees Crash! Banks Fight Discount Rivals in Fierce Price War!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Brokerage-Fees-Crash-Banks-Fight-Discount-Rivals-in-Fierce-Price-War/694d7947e10c98d0788bdd55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Brokerage-Fees-Crash-Banks-Fight-Discount-Rivals-in-Fierce-Price-War/694d7947e10c98d0788bdd55</guid><description>Bank-owned stock brokers are aggressively cutting fees, with HDFC Securities, Axis Securities, and SBICap Securities matching discount brokers like Zerodha and Groww at Rs 20 per transaction. Kotak Securities offers the lowest at Rs 10. This competitive 'race to the bottom' is a survival tactic amidst tighter regulations and slower trading. Brokers are now focusing on diversified revenue streams and value-added research services to retain clients, as discount players continue to dominate active user share.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 17:42:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d7947e10c98d0788bdd54_1766685087288.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlocking Coal Power: New Policy Allows Exports &amp; Any Use – Major Boost for Industries!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Unlocking-Coal-Power-New-Policy-Allows-Exports-and-Any-Use-Major-Boost-for-Industries/694d6a18e10c98d0788a1e48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Unlocking-Coal-Power-New-Policy-Allows-Exports-and-Any-Use-Major-Boost-for-Industries/694d6a18e10c98d0788a1e48</guid><description>India's Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs (CCEA) has approved the CoalSETU policy, creating a new window for coal linkage auctions. This policy allows entities to use procured coal for their own industrial needs, exports, or washing, removing previous end-use restrictions. However, resale within India is prohibited. This move is expected to significantly benefit crucial industries like cement, steel, sponge iron, and captive power units, addressing their long-standing demand for flexible coal procurement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:34:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d6a18e10c98d0788a1e47_1766681384085.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Insurance &amp; Pension Reforms Crucial for India's Financial Future? Tax Parity &amp; Rural Support Demanded!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Budget-2026-Insurance-and-Pension-Reforms-Crucial-for-Indias-Financial-Future-Tax-Parity-and-Rural-Support-Demanded/694d6999e10c98d07889fd8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Budget-2026-Insurance-and-Pension-Reforms-Crucial-for-Indias-Financial-Future-Tax-Parity-and-Rural-Support-Demanded/694d6999e10c98d07889fd8e</guid><description>India's insurance penetration (3.7% of GDP) and pension coverage (&lt;25% workforce) lag global averages, especially in rural areas. Ahead of Budget 2026, experts urge policy changes to ensure equitable tax treatment for retirement products like annuities and NPS, and parity for high-value traditional insurance policies versus ULIPs. Calls are also made to exempt rural and social sector policies from stamp duty to boost affordability and financial inclusion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:31:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d6999e10c98d07889fd8d_1766681380561.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Stocks Puzzle: Weak Demand vs. Energy Boom! Is India's Power Sector Set for a Shock?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Power-Stocks-Puzzle-Weak-Demand-vs-Energy-Boom-Is-Indias-Power-Sector-Set-for-a-Shock/694d64e8e10c98d07889c824</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Power-Stocks-Puzzle-Weak-Demand-vs-Energy-Boom-Is-Indias-Power-Sector-Set-for-a-Shock/694d64e8e10c98d07889c824</guid><description>India's power sector faces a paradox: despite strong economic growth, power demand is weak, and supply is abundant. However, long-term opportunities are emerging from energy transition policies, reforms in nuclear energy via the Shanti Bill, and upgrades in transmission and distribution. Major companies are investing in Small Modular Reactors (SMRs), but near-term earnings and valuations could be pressured by current economics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:14:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d64e8e10c98d07889c823_1766679983266.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Data Law Shockwave: Construction &amp; Industrial Giants Face Data Fiduciary Reckoning!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Data-Law-Shockwave-Construction-and-Industrial-Giants-Face-Data-Fiduciary-Reckoning/694d6337e10c98d07889c528</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Data-Law-Shockwave-Construction-and-Industrial-Giants-Face-Data-Fiduciary-Reckoning/694d6337e10c98d07889c528</guid><description>India's new Digital Personal Data Protection Rules, 2025, effective May 2027, will classify Industrial Products and Construction (IP&amp;C) companies as data fiduciaries. This mandates stringent consent, breach reporting, and data erasure protocols, necessitating significant operational and contractual overhauls for IP&amp;C firms as they adapt to enhanced data governance requirements.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:04:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d6337e10c98d07889c527_1766679538012.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Sparks Hope! 5 Bold Moves to Revolutionize India's Logistics Sector!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Budget-2026-Sparks-Hope-5-Bold-Moves-to-Revolutionize-Indias-Logistics-Sector/694d5ae0e10c98d078897f02</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Budget-2026-Sparks-Hope-5-Bold-Moves-to-Revolutionize-Indias-Logistics-Sector/694d5ae0e10c98d078897f02</guid><description>Budget 2026 is set to introduce transformative measures for India's logistics sector, aiming to reduce logistics costs to below 10% of GDP by 2028. Key proposals include creating integrated digital platforms, establishing a National Digital Logistics Grid, championing green logistics with incentives for electric fleets and sustainable warehousing, and designing policies specifically for MSMEs and exporters to foster global competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:31:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d5ae0e10c98d078897f01_1766677413620.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NPS Shocker! Major Rule Changes Let You Access Retirement Funds Sooner - Find Out How!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NPS-Shocker-Major-Rule-Changes-Let-You-Access-Retirement-Funds-Sooner-Find-Out-How/694d5a7ee10c98d078897e40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NPS-Shocker-Major-Rule-Changes-Let-You-Access-Retirement-Funds-Sooner-Find-Out-How/694d5a7ee10c98d078897e40</guid><description>The Pension Fund Regulatory and Development Authority (PFRDA) has significantly relaxed the National Pension System (NPS) withdrawal rules. Subscribers can now close accounts after 15 years of membership, withdraw up to 80% of their corpus as a lump sum (with only 20% for annuity), and make partial withdrawals anytime without a 5-year lock-in. The maximum age for staying invested has also been extended to 85. However, government employees still face more stringent annuity rules.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:29:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d5a7ee10c98d078897e3f_1766677299300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Medical Tech Leap: Zoho-backed Startup Unveils First Indigenous MRI Scanner!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Medical-Tech-Leap-Zoho-backed-Startup-Unveils-First-Indigenous-MRI-Scanner/694d5a4fe10c98d078897dea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Medical-Tech-Leap-Zoho-backed-Startup-Unveils-First-Indigenous-MRI-Scanner/694d5a4fe10c98d078897dea</guid><description>Zoho-backed VoxelGrids has successfully developed India's first indigenous Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) scanner, a crucial medical diagnostic tool. Deployed at Chandrapur Cancer Care Foundation, the 1.5 tesla scanner boasts technological advancements including the absence of liquid helium, making it approximately 40% cheaper to build than imported models. VoxelGrids also offers innovative pay-per-use models to improve accessibility for smaller hospitals. The company plans a commercial launch by fiscal year-end, with a manufacturing capacity of 20-25 scanners annually.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:29:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d5a4fe10c98d078897de9_1766677158033.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AVG Logistics Powers Up: New LNG Deal Promises Greener, Cheaper Transport!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/AVG-Logistics-Powers-Up-New-LNG-Deal-Promises-Greener-Cheaper-Transport/694d4e27e10c98d0788972bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/AVG-Logistics-Powers-Up-New-LNG-Deal-Promises-Greener-Cheaper-Transport/694d4e27e10c98d0788972bb</guid><description>AVG Logistics Limited has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Baidyanath LNG Private Limited to accelerate the adoption of Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG) in the transportation sector. The partnership aims to deploy LNG-powered fleets and refuelling infrastructure for industries like steel, FMCG, and cement, expecting to cut fuel costs, improve operating efficiency, and support margin expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:35:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d4e27e10c98d0788972ba_1766674043863.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Export Surge Alert! Huge $10 Billion Opportunity in New Zealand Unlocked – Can India Replace China?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indias-Export-Surge-Alert-Huge-10-Billion-Opportunity-in-New-Zealand-Unlocked-Can-India-Replace-China/694d4e33e10c98d0788972f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indias-Export-Surge-Alert-Huge-10-Billion-Opportunity-in-New-Zealand-Unlocked-Can-India-Replace-China/694d4e33e10c98d0788972f8</guid><description>Indian exporters across sectors like agriculture, pharma, apparel, and auto can significantly boost shipments to New Zealand, helping the island nation reduce its heavy reliance on China. A GTRI report highlights vast untapped potential, with New Zealand importing over $10 billion from China versus just $711 million from India annually. The bilateral free trade agreement provides a strong foundation for Indian companies to expand their market share in New Zealand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:35:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d4e33e10c98d0788972f7_1766674151389.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KNR Constructions Sells 4 Road Projects for ₹1,543 Crore: Major Financial Shift Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-Sells-4-Road-Projects-for-1543-Crore-Major-Financial-Shift-Unveiled/694d3ed0e10c98d078896692</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-Sells-4-Road-Projects-for-1543-Crore-Major-Financial-Shift-Unveiled/694d3ed0e10c98d078896692</guid><description>KNR Constructions Limited has signed agreements to sell its entire 100% stake, including sub-debt, in four road special purpose vehicles (SPVs) to Indus Infra Trust for ₹1,543.19 crore. The deal, which includes ₹1,398.65 crore in sale consideration and ₹144.54 crore in estimated cash surplus, is subject to approvals and is expected to finalize by September 30, 2026. KNR Constructions invested ₹566.83 crore in these projects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 13:29:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d3ed0e10c98d078896691_1766670271021.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Insurance Sector Ignites: Policy Reforms &amp; Digital Surge Propel 2025 Growth, Bullish 2026 Outlook!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Sector-Ignites-Policy-Reforms-and-Digital-Surge-Propel-2025-Growth-Bullish-2026-Outlook/694d3cdbe10c98d0788964de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Sector-Ignites-Policy-Reforms-and-Digital-Surge-Propel-2025-Growth-Bullish-2026-Outlook/694d3cdbe10c98d0788964de</guid><description>India's insurance sector experienced a transformative 2025, marked by landmark policy reforms including 100% FDI and GST exemption on premiums, alongside a significant digital acceleration. Leaders anticipate continued bullish growth in 2026, emphasizing enhanced customer trust and simpler products. Health insurance premiums saw a robust 10.4% increase.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 13:20:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d3cdbe10c98d0788964dd_1766669808312.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zepto Files Secret IPO Papers! Quick Commerce Giant Preps for Stock Market Debut Next Year!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zepto-Files-Secret-IPO-Papers-Quick-Commerce-Giant-Preps-for-Stock-Market-Debut-Next-Year/694d3bcde10c98d0788962ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zepto-Files-Secret-IPO-Papers-Quick-Commerce-Giant-Preps-for-Stock-Market-Debut-Next-Year/694d3bcde10c98d0788962ff</guid><description>Quick commerce platform Zepto is set to file its draft red herring prospectus (DRHP) on December 26 using the confidential route. The company aims to list on Indian stock exchanges next year, positioning itself against competitors like Blinkit and Swiggy Instamart. This move makes Zepto one of India's youngest startups to target a public listing within six years of its inception.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 13:19:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d3bcde10c98d0788962fe_1766669333080.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tesla vs. Waymo: The Shocking Robotaxi Truth Elon Musk Hides!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tesla-vs-Waymo-The-Shocking-Robotaxi-Truth-Elon-Musk-Hides/694d3c3fe10c98d07889638f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tesla-vs-Waymo-The-Shocking-Robotaxi-Truth-Elon-Musk-Hides/694d3c3fe10c98d07889638f</guid><description>Alphabet's Waymo is leading the robotaxi race with millions of actual driverless rides and operations in six cities, while Tesla's service still requires human monitors in most vehicles and faces regulatory hurdles. Waymo's multi-sensor technology and consistent, slow-and-steady expansion contrast sharply with Tesla's ambitious promises and vision-only approach, suggesting Waymo is currently winning the operational battle despite Tesla's higher market valuation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 13:19:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d3c3fe10c98d07889638e_1766669517839.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Hit By Massive ₹83 Crore GST Blow! Legal Fight Looms!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Hit-By-Massive-83-Crore-GST-Blow-Legal-Fight-Looms/694d3641e10c98d078895e46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Hit-By-Massive-83-Crore-GST-Blow-Legal-Fight-Looms/694d3641e10c98d078895e46</guid><description>Vodafone Idea Ltd. has been hit with two Goods and Services Tax (GST) penalty orders totaling over ₹83 crore from Mumbai and Bengaluru tax authorities. The penalties stem from alleged issues related to license fees, spectrum usage charges, and tax claims between fiscal years 2018-19 and 2022-23. The company stated it disagrees with the orders and plans to pursue legal action to challenge them.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:56:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d3641e10c98d078895e45_1766668003779.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chennai Real Estate Giant Casagrand Refiles Rs 1,220 Crore IPO - Will This Be Their Big Break?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Chennai-Real-Estate-Giant-Casagrand-Refiles-Rs-1220-Crore-IPO-Will-This-Be-Their-Big-Break/694d3555e10c98d078895cf4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Chennai-Real-Estate-Giant-Casagrand-Refiles-Rs-1220-Crore-IPO-Will-This-Be-Their-Big-Break/694d3555e10c98d078895cf4</guid><description>Chennai-based real estate firm Casagrand has refiled its draft IPO papers with SEBI, aiming to raise Rs 1,220 crore. The offer size has been increased from Rs 1,100 crore, comprising Rs 1,200 crore through a fresh issue and Rs 20 crore via an offer-for-sale. The company plans to use Rs 900 crore of the proceeds for debt repayment, with outstanding borrowings at Rs 4,913.6 crore. Casagrand operates across multiple cities and has seen pre-sales volume growth, though its profit declined in fiscal 2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:52:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d3555e10c98d078895cf3_1766667702286.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VC Frenzy for Home Services: Can Indian Startups Survive Cash Burn &amp; Stand Out?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/VC-Frenzy-for-Home-Services-Can-Indian-Startups-Survive-Cash-Burn-and-Stand-Out/694d3572e10c98d078895d38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/VC-Frenzy-for-Home-Services-Can-Indian-Startups-Survive-Cash-Burn-and-Stand-Out/694d3572e10c98d078895d38</guid><description>Quick home services startups in India are attracting venture capital interest due to market potential and changing consumer habits, particularly among younger generations seeking convenience. However, companies like Snabbit and Pronto face significant challenges in differentiating themselves and cracking unit economics in a cost-intensive sector. Recently listed Urban Company's financial performance, including losses in its new 'Insta Help' vertical, highlights the investment hurdles. The online segment, though growing at 18-22% CAGR, is still small compared to the overall $60 billion market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:51:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d3572e10c98d078895d37_1766667877305.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Bags Massive ₹367 Crore Govt Incentive: EV Ambitions Soar!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Bags-Massive-367-Crore-Govt-Incentive-EV-Ambitions-Soar/694d33e5e10c98d078895b33</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Bags-Massive-367-Crore-Govt-Incentive-EV-Ambitions-Soar/694d33e5e10c98d078895b33</guid><description>Ola Electric has received a significant ₹366.78 crore incentive under India's Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme for FY25. This payment, sanctioned by the Ministry of Heavy Industries, supports the company's manufacturing capabilities and commitment to developing advanced EV technology in India. This follows an earlier ₹73.74 crore incentive received in March for FY24 sales.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:45:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d33e5e10c98d078895b32_1766667314403.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RVNL Rockets to Rs 360 Target! Analyst Flags Bullish Breakout - Is This Indian Railway Stock Your Next Big Win?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RVNL-Rockets-to-Rs-360-Target-Analyst-Flags-Bullish-Breakout-Is-This-Indian-Railway-Stock-Your-Next-Big-Win/694d2f4ce10c98d078895692</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RVNL-Rockets-to-Rs-360-Target-Analyst-Flags-Bullish-Breakout-Is-This-Indian-Railway-Stock-Your-Next-Big-Win/694d2f4ce10c98d078895692</guid><description>Analyst Vatsal Bhuva from LKP Securities recommends buying Rail Vikas Nigam Limited (RVNL) with a target of Rs 360. The stock is showing strong upward momentum, marked by a breakout from a falling channel, heavy volumes, and reaching a three-month high. This positive technical outlook comes despite a recent 20% dip in the company's September quarter net profit due to increased expenses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:24:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d2f4ce10c98d078895691_1766666287031.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Labour Revolution: New Codes in 2026 Promise Fair Wages &amp; Universal Security for Millions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Labour-Revolution-New-Codes-in-2026-Promise-Fair-Wages-and-Universal-Security-for-Millions/694d2ef1e10c98d0788955cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Labour-Revolution-New-Codes-in-2026-Promise-Fair-Wages-and-Universal-Security-for-Millions/694d2ef1e10c98d0788955cf</guid><description>India is set to fully implement four consolidated Labour Codes in 2026, aiming to guarantee minimum wages and universal social security for all workers. This reform modernizes 29 existing labour laws into a streamlined framework. The government is also enhancing the Employees' Provident Fund Organisation (EPFO) system, facilitating faster withdrawals and pension settlements. These initiatives are designed to foster a more formal, inclusive, and future-ready labour market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:24:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d2ef1e10c98d0788955ce_1766666183537.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amazon Unleashes $35 Billion Power Play: India Set to Revolutionize Global Delivery!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazon-Unleashes-35-Billion-Power-Play-India-Set-to-Revolutionize-Global-Delivery/694d2efae10c98d0788955fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazon-Unleashes-35-Billion-Power-Play-India-Set-to-Revolutionize-Global-Delivery/694d2efae10c98d0788955fc</guid><description>Amazon is investing $35 billion in India by 2030, making it the largest foreign direct investor. This expands its operations in infrastructure, AI, technology, and exports, aiming to empower 15 million sellers and upskill 4 million students. India is becoming a hub for Amazon's global innovations, particularly in quick commerce and delivery models like the Hub Points Program, which are now being adopted worldwide. Amazon's cumulative exports from India have already surpassed $20 billion, with a target of $80 billion by 2030.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:24:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d2efae10c98d0788955fb_1766666042456.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's CPSEs Workforce Shock: Regular Jobs Vanish as Contract Hires Skyrocket!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-CPSEs-Workforce-Shock-Regular-Jobs-Vanish-as-Contract-Hires-Skyrocket/694d2c72e10c98d07889537c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-CPSEs-Workforce-Shock-Regular-Jobs-Vanish-as-Contract-Hires-Skyrocket/694d2c72e10c98d07889537c</guid><description>Central Public Sector Enterprises (CPSEs) are increasingly relying on casual and contract workers while regular employee numbers decline over five years. The Public Enterprises Survey for FY25 shows a 1.61% overall employment growth driven by over 54,000 new casual/contract hires, contrasting with a loss of around 30,000 regular employees. This shift is attributed to managing wage bills and reducing statutory payments. The share of women in the total CPSE workforce has also decreased.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:12:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d2c72e10c98d07889537b_1766665518077.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ukraine Drones Strike Russia's HUGE Gas Plant! Global Energy Shockwave Imminent?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Ukraine-Drones-Strike-Russias-HUGE-Gas-Plant-Global-Energy-Shockwave-Imminent/694d2afae10c98d0788951f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Ukraine-Drones-Strike-Russias-HUGE-Gas-Plant-Global-Energy-Shockwave-Imminent/694d2afae10c98d0788951f8</guid><description>Ukraine has reportedly struck Russia's largest gas processing plant in the Orenburg region with long-range drones. This attack, approximately 1,700 km from Kyiv, targets a critical energy asset processing gas from Russia and Kazakhstan. While not independently verified, regional authorities confirmed drone activity and minor damage to an unnamed industrial facility. This incident escalates Ukraine's strategy of targeting Russian energy infrastructure, potentially impacting global energy supplies and prices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:06:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d2afae10c98d0788951f7_1766665028408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New Airlines Get Green Light in India? Why Your Flights Won't Change Soon!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/New-Airlines-Get-Green-Light-in-India-Why-Your-Flights-Wont-Change-Soon/694d2634e10c98d078894e7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/New-Airlines-Get-Green-Light-in-India-Why-Your-Flights-Wont-Change-Soon/694d2634e10c98d078894e7c</guid><description>India's aviation ministry has issued No-Objection Certificates (NOCs) to three new proposed airlines: Shankh Air, Al Hind Air, and FlyExpress, joining Air Kerala. While this signals potential new competition, experts caution that an NOC is just the first easy step. New airlines face significant regulatory hurdles, capital requirements, and aircraft acquisition challenges before they can even apply for an Air Operator Certificate (AOC) from the DGCA. These approvals are unlikely to break the current duopoly of IndiGo and Air India anytime soon, as many aspiring airlines fail before commencing operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:46:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d2634e10c98d078894e7b_1766663875398.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Chaos: 67 Flights Axed Amid Fog Drama, DGCA Watch Intensifies!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Chaos-67-Flights-Axed-Amid-Fog-Drama-DGCA-Watch-Intensifies/694d25cfe10c98d078894ddb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Chaos-67-Flights-Axed-Amid-Fog-Drama-DGCA-Watch-Intensifies/694d25cfe10c98d078894ddb</guid><description>IndiGo cancelled 67 flights on Thursday due to forecasted fog and operational issues, adding to ongoing winter disruptions. This occurs during the DGCA's declared fog season and amid heightened regulatory scrutiny following earlier large-scale cancellations that impacted thousands of passengers. The airline is operating a reduced schedule after the government mandated a 10% cut in domestic flights.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:45:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d25cfe10c98d078894dda_1766663690768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Govt's Rs 15,000 Cr SWAMIH-2 Fund: 1 Lakh Homebuyers Get Hope as Stalled Projects Revived!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Govts-Rs-15000-Cr-SWAMIH-2-Fund-1-Lakh-Homebuyers-Get-Hope-as-Stalled-Projects-Revived/694d25b1e10c98d078894d68</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Govts-Rs-15000-Cr-SWAMIH-2-Fund-1-Lakh-Homebuyers-Get-Hope-as-Stalled-Projects-Revived/694d25b1e10c98d078894d68</guid><description>The Indian government is set to launch the SWAMIH-2 Fund, a Rs 15,000 crore initiative aimed at providing last-mile financing to complete stalled housing projects. With Rs 1,500 crore earmarked as seed capital, the fund expects to help nearly one lakh middle-class homebuyers whose investments are currently stuck. This move aims to revive commercially viable projects and unlock investments in distressed residential properties across India.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:44:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d25b1e10c98d078894d67_1766663727372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Confident Consumers: Spending Cautiously as Premium Buys Surge! What's Next for the Market?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Confident-Consumers-Spending-Cautiously-as-Premium-Buys-Surge-Whats-Next-for-the-Market/694d255ae10c98d078894cb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Confident-Consumers-Spending-Cautiously-as-Premium-Buys-Surge-Whats-Next-for-the-Market/694d255ae10c98d078894cb2</guid><description>India's consumer sentiment is globally high, with a clear shift towards premium products like smartphones and smart appliances. However, broad mass consumption recovery remains slow and uneven, with sales growth faltering after a brief festival boost. While value-driven sectors face slowdowns, companies are banking on premiumization, rural demand, and technological advancements for future growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:41:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d255ae10c98d078894cb1_1766663576277.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eicher Motors Stock Soars to Record High! But Can Growth Outpace Margin Woes?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Stock-Soars-to-Record-High-But-Can-Growth-Outpace-Margin-Woes/694d1ff6e10c98d078894817</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Stock-Soars-to-Record-High-But-Can-Growth-Outpace-Margin-Woes/694d1ff6e10c98d078894817</guid><description>Eicher Motors, the maker of Royal Enfield, has hit an all-time high, with its stock gaining approximately 52.7% this year, significantly outperforming the Nifty Auto index. This surge is driven by strong volume gains, particularly in Royal Enfield's motorcycle segment over 250cc, where it commands a dominant 87.3% market share, boosted by demand for the Bullet 350. However, concerns linger regarding future margin expansion and the stock's high valuations, even as brokerages like Nomura upgrade to neutral, while Motilal Oswal maintains a sell rating citing expensive multiples relative to expected earnings growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:18:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d1ff6e10c98d078894816_1766662256693.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Office Boom: Global Giants Fueling Flexible Space Surge, Awfis CEO Reveals Growth Secrets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Office-Boom-Global-Giants-Fueling-Flexible-Space-Surge-Awfis-CEO-Reveals-Growth-Secrets/694d1fd4e10c98d0788947d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Office-Boom-Global-Giants-Fueling-Flexible-Space-Surge-Awfis-CEO-Reveals-Growth-Secrets/694d1fd4e10c98d0788947d2</guid><description>Global Capability Centres (GCCs) are becoming the main engine for India's flexible and managed office space market. Awfis Chairman and Managing Director Amit Ramani stated that GCCs now form over 70% of their large enterprise demand. This trend is driven by the need for flexibility, speed, and cost savings. GCCs often choose managed offices for faster setup, especially first-time entrants to India. Awfis projects GCCs to contribute 50-60% of industry demand and is targeting over ₹1,500 crore revenue in FY26, with a 30% growth rate.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:18:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d1fd4e10c98d0788947d1_1766662312251.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Is Your Phone Call About to Be Handled by AI? Big Tech Shift Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Is-Your-Phone-Call-About-to-Be-Handled-by-AI-Big-Tech-Shift-Revealed/694d1dcee10c98d0788945e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Is-Your-Phone-Call-About-to-Be-Handled-by-AI-Big-Tech-Shift-Revealed/694d1dcee10c98d0788945e3</guid><description>New autonomous voice AI technology is transforming customer service by handling entire phone conversations from start to finish, a significant upgrade from traditional Interactive Voice Response (IVR) systems. Unlike IVR, which primarily routes calls, this AI understands natural speech, accesses business systems in real-time, and resolves customer issues directly, reducing the need for human agents. This shift aims to improve efficiency, cut costs for businesses, and provide quicker resolutions for customers, making voice calls a more powerful operational tool.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:11:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d1dcee10c98d0788945e2_1766661650657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking 25%+ Returns! Top PSU Funds Turn ₹10k SIPs into Lakhs in Just 5 Years – Are You Missing Out?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Shocking-25percent-Returns-Top-PSU-Funds-Turn-10k-SIPs-into-Lakhs-in-Just-5-Years-Are-You-Missing-Out/694d1cffe10c98d0788944d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Shocking-25percent-Returns-Top-PSU-Funds-Turn-10k-SIPs-into-Lakhs-in-Just-5-Years-Are-You-Missing-Out/694d1cffe10c98d0788944d4</guid><description>PSU thematic mutual funds have been outstanding performers over the last five years, with three leading schemes delivering over 25% annualized returns through Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs). SBI PSU Fund, Invesco India PSU Equity Fund, and Aditya Birla Sun Life PSU Equity Fund are highlighted for turning a ₹10,000 monthly SIP into more than ₹11.47 lakh. The article details why PSU stocks have seen this revival, including government reforms and improved profitability, while also cautioning investors about the inherent risks and volatility associated with thematic investments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:08:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d1cffe10c98d0788944d3_1766661672896.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Berger Paints' Bold South India Blitz: Massive Dealer Network Expansion Underway!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Berger-Paints-Bold-South-India-Blitz-Massive-Dealer-Network-Expansion-Underway/694d1ccee10c98d078894471</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Berger-Paints-Bold-South-India-Blitz-Massive-Dealer-Network-Expansion-Underway/694d1ccee10c98d078894471</guid><description>Berger Paints is aggressively expanding its presence in South India, targeting Karnataka, Tamil Nadu, and Telangana. The company aims to significantly scale up its dealer networks in these regions, which currently lag behind Kerala and Andhra Pradesh. CEO Abhijit Roy highlighted the strategy involves partnering with ambitious dealers and engaging applicators, crucial for brand choice. Growth drivers include waterproofing, construction chemicals (12% of revenue), and premium paints (30-35% of revenue), supporting a ₹20,000 crore revenue target by 2030.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d1ccee10c98d078894470_1766661402605.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tech Stocks: Who Soared and Who Crashed in 2025? Uncover the Shocking Gainers &amp; Losers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Tech-Stocks-Who-Soared-and-Who-Crashed-in-2025-Uncover-the-Shocking-Gainers-and-Losers/694d1c20e10c98d0788943c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Tech-Stocks-Who-Soared-and-Who-Crashed-in-2025-Uncover-the-Shocking-Gainers-and-Losers/694d1c20e10c98d0788943c6</guid><description>In 2025, India's new-age tech companies showed a divided performance. CarTrade Technologies emerged as a top gainer, rising 85% due to strong profits. Yatra Online and Nykaa also made remarkable turnarounds. Conversely, DroneAcharya Aerial Innovations, MobiKwik, and Ola Electric faced major declines, losing nearly 60% of their value amidst controversies, subdued financials, and regulatory challenges, illustrating the volatile nature of this sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:05:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d1c20e10c98d0788943c5_1766661224130.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Children's Funds Skyrocket: Are You Missing Out on This 160% Growth? Your Child's Future Depends On It!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Childrens-Funds-Skyrocket-Are-You-Missing-Out-on-This-160percent-Growth-Your-Childs-Future-Depends-On-It/694d17e2e10c98d078894004</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Childrens-Funds-Skyrocket-Are-You-Missing-Out-on-This-160percent-Growth-Your-Childs-Future-Depends-On-It/694d17e2e10c98d078894004</guid><description>Children's mutual funds are gaining significant traction, with assets under management (AUM) surging by 160% to nearly ₹26,000 crore over the past five years. This growth is driven by investors' focus on long-term goals like education, aided by the funds' mandatory lock-in period of five years or until the child turns 18, whichever is earlier. Experts note that while AUM has grown substantially, the number of new schemes remains limited, with a significant portion of assets concentrated in a few large funds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 10:45:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d17e2e10c98d078894003_1766660272130.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2025: The Year of MEGA Reforms! Taxes, Jobs, Laws Transformed – What You MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-The-Year-of-MEGA-Reforms-Taxes-Jobs-Laws-Transformed-What-You-MUST-Know/694d177be10c98d078893f8a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-The-Year-of-MEGA-Reforms-Taxes-Jobs-Laws-Transformed-What-You-MUST-Know/694d177be10c98d078893f8a</guid><description>India's 2025 was a landmark year for reforms, driven by Prime Minister Narendra Modi's administration. Sweeping changes across taxation, labor, trade, and business regulations aimed to simplify governance and boost economic growth, which reached 8.2% GDP. Key initiatives included a simplified Goods and Services Tax (GST), income tax relief, modernized labor codes, new trade pacts like with the UK and Oman, and expanded Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSME) definitions. These reforms aim to enhance competitiveness, attract foreign investment, and streamline business operations nationwide.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 10:40:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d177be10c98d078893f89_1766660213991.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Logistics Sector Records All-Time High Demand: Leasing Soars to 76.5 Million Sq Ft!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Logistics-Sector-Records-All-Time-High-Demand-Leasing-Soars-to-765-Million-Sq-Ft/694d1671e10c98d078893e4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Logistics-Sector-Records-All-Time-High-Demand-Leasing-Soars-to-765-Million-Sq-Ft/694d1671e10c98d078893e4d</guid><description>Industrial and logistics space demand in India reached an unprecedented 76.5 million square feet across 24 major cities this year, marking a nearly 19% increase from the previous year. Key drivers include the manufacturing sector (29%), third-party logistics firms (28%), and e-commerce players (12%). Tier-1 cities led growth with a 20% rise, while tier-II and tier-III cities also showed significant expansion. Savills India forecasts continued growth, projecting absorption to exceed 80 million sq ft next year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 10:38:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d1671e10c98d078893e4c_1766659837617.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Engineering Exports Soar to $11 Billion in November: A Massive Rebound!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Engineering-Exports-Soar-to-11-Billion-in-November-A-Massive-Rebound/694d14cee10c98d078893c7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Engineering-Exports-Soar-to-11-Billion-in-November-A-Massive-Rebound/694d14cee10c98d078893c7f</guid><description>India's engineering goods exports surged to $11.01 billion in November 2025, marking a strong rebound after a significant drop in October. This represents a 23.76% year-on-year growth, driven by increased shipments to key markets like the United States and the European Union. The Engineering Export Promotion Council of India (EEPC) highlighted this achievement as a testament to exporters' resilience and positive global trade trends. Cumulative exports for April-November 2025-26 also showed a healthy increase.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 10:33:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d14cee10c98d078893c7e_1766659345011.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's IPO Frenzy: 190+ Giants Poised to Unleash ₹2.5 Lakh Crore Blast in 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Indias-IPO-Frenzy-190-Giants-Poised-to-Unleash-25-Lakh-Crore-Blast-in-2026/694d149ce10c98d078893c37</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Indias-IPO-Frenzy-190-Giants-Poised-to-Unleash-25-Lakh-Crore-Blast-in-2026/694d149ce10c98d078893c37</guid><description>India's IPO market is gearing up for a massive year in 2026, with over 190 companies planning to list and aiming to raise more than ₹2.5 lakh crore. Key expected debuts include Reliance Jio, National Stock Exchange, Flipkart, and PhonePe, spanning sectors from telecom and fintech to e-commerce and financial services. This surge promises significant fundraising and potential market liquidity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 10:29:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d149ce10c98d078893c36_1766659475915.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCX Stock Split Alert: Record Date Set, Analyst Slams 'BUY' Button - Should You Invest?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/MCX-Stock-Split-Alert-Record-Date-Set-Analyst-Slams-BUY-Button-Should-You-Invest/694d1150e10c98d07889394c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/MCX-Stock-Split-Alert-Record-Date-Set-Analyst-Slams-BUY-Button-Should-You-Invest/694d1150e10c98d07889394c</guid><description>Multi Commodity Exchange (MCX) announced its stock split record date as January 2, 2026, with a 5:1 ratio, transforming each Rs 10 share into five Rs 2 shares. This corporate action follows strong investor returns, with MCX shares up 70% year-to-date and 30% in three months. Analysts like Pradip Halder of PHD Capital maintain a positive outlook, predicting a rise to Rs 11,000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 10:12:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d1150e10c98d07889394b_1766658530050.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>