<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:18:47 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Hindustan Bio Sciences Posts Massive Revenue Surge, Turns Profitable</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Hindustan-Bio-Sciences-Posts-Massive-Revenue-Surge-Turns-Profitable/697dd7635fc43f26c54fcffb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Hindustan-Bio-Sciences-Posts-Massive-Revenue-Surge-Turns-Profitable/697dd7635fc43f26c54fcffb</guid><description>Hindustan Bio Sciences Ltd. reported a remarkable Q3 FY26, with revenue soaring over 5320% YoY to ₹3825 Lakhs and turning a net profit of ₹8.20 Lakhs from a prior year loss. However, operational revenue declined 48% for the nine-month period, and a significant "Other Income" component raises questions about sustainability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:06:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697dd7635fc43f26c54fcffa_1769871979777.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nitin Castings Proposes BSE Delisting; Promoters Seek Full Control</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Nitin-Castings-Proposes-BSE-Delisting-Promoters-Seek-Full-Control/697dd5f85fc43f26c54fcf25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Nitin-Castings-Proposes-BSE-Delisting-Promoters-Seek-Full-Control/697dd5f85fc43f26c54fcf25</guid><description>Nitin Castings Limited has filed a proposal for voluntary delisting from the BSE. Promoters, holding 71.39%, aim to acquire the remaining 28.61% stake from public shareholders. The process, managed by Navigant Corporate Advisors, will involve a reverse book-building mechanism to determine the acquisition price, offering public investors an exit route and enabling greater operational flexibility for the company.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:06:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697dd5f85fc43f26c54fcf24_1769871979217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MosChip Q3 Profit Plummets 61% on Labour Code Charge; Revenue Up 19%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MosChip-Q3-Profit-Plummets-61percent-on-Labour-Code-Charge-Revenue-Up-19percent/697dd7d85fc43f26c54fd083</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MosChip-Q3-Profit-Plummets-61percent-on-Labour-Code-Charge-Revenue-Up-19percent/697dd7d85fc43f26c54fd083</guid><description>MosChip Technologies posted a 19.2% YoY revenue growth for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹15,068 lakhs. However, net profit plummeted by 60.8% to ₹433.60 lakhs, heavily impacted by a one-time ₹581.86 lakhs exceptional charge related to new Labour Codes, increasing gratuity and leave liabilities. Standalone results mirrored this trend. The company provided no forward-looking guidance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:05:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697dd7d85fc43f26c54fd082_1769871898486.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MosChip Profit Plummets 61% YoY Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MosChip-Profit-Plummets-61percent-YoY-Despite-Revenue-Growth/697dd84d5fc43f26c54fd0ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MosChip-Profit-Plummets-61percent-YoY-Despite-Revenue-Growth/697dd84d5fc43f26c54fd0ff</guid><description>MosChip Technologies reported a significant ~61% year-on-year drop in consolidated net profit to ₹433.60 lakhs for Q3 FY26, despite a healthy 19.2% revenue growth to ₹15,068.44 lakhs. The sharp decline was primarily driven by a one-time exceptional item of ₹581.86 lakhs related to new Labour Codes, impacting gratuity and leave liabilities. Standalone profit also saw a steep fall.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:02:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697dd84d5fc43f26c54fd0fe_1769871758880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TFS Secures 11-Year Deal for 33 F&amp;B Outlets at Delhi Airport T1</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/TFS-Secures-11-Year-Deal-for-33-FandB-Outlets-at-Delhi-Airport-T1/697dd8c45fc43f26c54fd1ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/TFS-Secures-11-Year-Deal-for-33-FandB-Outlets-at-Delhi-Airport-T1/697dd8c45fc43f26c54fd1ad</guid><description>Travel Food Services Limited's subsidiary, TFS Gurgaon Airport Services, has received a Letter of Intent from DIAL for operating 33 F&amp;B outlets at Delhi Airport's Terminal 1. The significant 11-year contract, valid until 2036, promises long-term revenue visibility and strengthens TFS's footprint in a key travel hub.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:01:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697dd8c45fc43f26c54fd1ac_1769871705798.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fujiyama Power Systems Surges on Robust Q3 Earnings, Manufacturing Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Fujiyama-Power-Systems-Surges-on-Robust-Q3-Earnings-Manufacturing-Boost/697e18275fc43f26c5501ce8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Fujiyama-Power-Systems-Surges-on-Robust-Q3-Earnings-Manufacturing-Boost/697e18275fc43f26c5501ce8</guid><description>Fujiyama Power Systems posted a stellar Q3 FY26, with revenue up 73.8% YoY to Rs 588.5 Cr and PAT soaring 124.3% to Rs 67.3 Cr. Margins expanded significantly to 18.7% (EBITDA) and 11.4% (PAT), driven by a new 1 GW solar cell manufacturing unit in Dadri and ongoing capacity expansion, signaling strong operational leverage and backward integration benefits.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e18275fc43f26c5501ce7_1769871571369.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Launches 'Chakra' to Fund India's Sunrise Sector Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SBI-Launches-Chakra-to-Fund-Indias-Sunrise-Sector-Growth/697e18125fc43f26c5501c6c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SBI-Launches-Chakra-to-Fund-Indias-Sunrise-Sector-Growth/697e18125fc43f26c5501c6c</guid><description>State Bank of India launched its 'Chakra' Centre of Excellence to finance eight key sunrise sectors. The initiative aims to channel an estimated ₹22 lakh crore in debt financing over five years, addressing a total projected capital requirement of ₹100 lakh crore by 2030. This strategic move aligns with the Department of Financial Services' call for public sector banks to diversify risk through focused sector investments and marks a shift towards proactive 'strategic expansion'. International lenders, including Japan's SMBC and MUFG, are participating in the platform.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:58:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e18125fc43f26c5501c6b_1769871525234.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Affle 3i Q3: Standalone Revenue Up 20%, PAT Soars 25%, But PBT Growth Lags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Affle-3i-Q3-Standalone-Revenue-Up-20percent-PAT-Soars-25percent-But-PBT-Growth-Lags/697ddaa75fc43f26c54fd30d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Affle-3i-Q3-Standalone-Revenue-Up-20percent-PAT-Soars-25percent-But-PBT-Growth-Lags/697ddaa75fc43f26c54fd30d</guid><description>Affle 3i Limited's Q3 FY26 results show strong standalone revenue growth of 20.59% to INR 2,423 million and a 25.35% PAT surge to INR 367 million. Standalone PBT grew only 2.50%, indicating margin pressure. Consolidated revenue rose 19.25% YoY. A significant stake in Bobble™ is classified as held for sale. The auditor's report noted reliance on unreviewed subsidiary financials.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:56:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ddaa75fc43f26c54fd30c_1769871374715.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC FIRST Bank Posts 48% YoY Profit Jump, NPAs Decline in Q3 FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-FIRST-Bank-Posts-48percent-YoY-Profit-Jump-NPAs-Decline-in-Q3-FY26/697ddb1c5fc43f26c54fd3dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-FIRST-Bank-Posts-48percent-YoY-Profit-Jump-NPAs-Decline-in-Q3-FY26/697ddb1c5fc43f26c54fd3dc</guid><description>IDFC FIRST Bank reported a robust 48.08% YoY increase in standalone Net Profit to ₹50,254 Lakh for Q3 FY26. Total income rose 12.76% YoY. The bank also saw a decrease in Gross NPAs to 1.69% and a 25.6% YoY growth in Net Worth, signaling improved asset quality and financial strength.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:55:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ddb1c5fc43f26c54fd3db_1769871345565.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ellenbarrie Gases Posts 36% PAT Jump on Robust Q3 Results, Expands Capacity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ellenbarrie-Gases-Posts-36percent-PAT-Jump-on-Robust-Q3-Results-Expands-Capacity/697e16b35fc43f26c5501b11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ellenbarrie-Gases-Posts-36percent-PAT-Jump-on-Robust-Q3-Results-Expands-Capacity/697e16b35fc43f26c5501b11</guid><description>Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases reported a stellar Q3 FY25 with Profit After Tax jumping 35.9% YoY to ₹26.09 Cr, driven by a 19.6% YoY increase in revenue. The company also announced strategic acquisitions, including Truair Industrial Gases and a stake in Pattikonda Renewables for captive power, alongside efficient utilization of IPO proceeds, signalling growth expansion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:53:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e16b35fc43f26c5501b10_1769871231547.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RR Kabel Surges: Q3 PAT Zooms 72% on Record Revenue &amp; Margin Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RR-Kabel-Surges-Q3-PAT-Zooms-72percent-on-Record-Revenue-and-Margin-Expansion/697e16a35fc43f26c5501ae2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RR-Kabel-Surges-Q3-PAT-Zooms-72percent-on-Record-Revenue-and-Margin-Expansion/697e16a35fc43f26c5501ae2</guid><description>RR Kabel Limited posted its highest-ever nine-month revenue, EBITDA, and PAT for Q3 FY26. Revenue surged 42.3% YoY to ₹2,535.9 Cr, while PAT jumped 72.4% YoY to ₹118.2 Cr. Operating EBITDA margin improved significantly to 8.1% from 6.2% YoY. The company also showed strong year-to-date growth and improved debt-to-equity ratio to 0.1x.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:52:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e16a35fc43f26c5501ae1_1769871169304.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ellenbarrie Gases Posts 36% PAT Surge, Eyes Expansion via Acquisitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ellenbarrie-Gases-Posts-36percent-PAT-Surge-Eyes-Expansion-via-Acquisitions/697e16355fc43f26c5501a66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ellenbarrie-Gases-Posts-36percent-PAT-Surge-Eyes-Expansion-via-Acquisitions/697e16355fc43f26c5501a66</guid><description>Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases reported a strong Q3 FY26 with Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 35.9% year-on-year to ₹26.09 Crores and revenue growing 19.6% to ₹81.35 Crores. For the nine-month period, PAT rose 25.3% and revenue climbed 10.5%. The company commissioned its new Uluberia-II plant, acquired manufacturing facilities of Truair Industrial Gases for ₹5.40 Crores, and acquired a 26% stake in Pattikonda Renewables for ₹70.80 Crores.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:52:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e16355fc43f26c5501a65_1769871002060.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MosChip Q3 Revenue Jumps 18%, Profit Crumbles 60% on Exceptional Charge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MosChip-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-18percent-Profit-Crumbles-60percent-on-Exceptional-Charge/697ddc0f5fc43f26c54fd5c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MosChip-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-18percent-Profit-Crumbles-60percent-on-Exceptional-Charge/697ddc0f5fc43f26c54fd5c1</guid><description>MosChip's Q3 FY26 revenue jumped 18.42% YoY to ₹149.39 Cr. However, consolidated net profit plummeted 60.78% to ₹43.36 Cr, heavily impacted by an ₹5.82 Cr exceptional charge for increased gratuity and leave liabilities due to new Labour Codes. Standalone revenue rose 17.46%, but profit fell sharply by 71.63%. EPS also declined significantly.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ddc0f5fc43f26c54fd5c0_1769870972206.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC FIRST Bank Q3 Profit Surges 48% on Strong Income Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-FIRST-Bank-Q3-Profit-Surges-48percent-on-Strong-Income-Growth/697ddb315fc43f26c54fd437</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-FIRST-Bank-Q3-Profit-Surges-48percent-on-Strong-Income-Growth/697ddb315fc43f26c54fd437</guid><description>IDFC FIRST Bank posted robust Q3 FY26 results with standalone net profit soaring 48.1% year-on-year to ₹50,254 lakhs, driven by a 12.7% rise in total income. Operating profit also saw a healthy 15.6% increase. Asset quality improved, marked by lower Gross NPAs. However, the bank's Debt-Equity ratio increased notably from the previous year.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ddb315fc43f26c54fd436_1769870976151.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Brace for Historic Sunday Budget Session</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/India-Markets-Brace-for-Historic-Sunday-Budget-Session/697ddd7c5fc43f26c54fd7b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/India-Markets-Brace-for-Historic-Sunday-Budget-Session/697ddd7c5fc43f26c54fd7b0</guid><description>Indian equity and commodity markets are set for an exceptional trading day on Sunday, February 1, 2026, to accommodate the presentation of the Union Budget 2026. This special session follows a trading week where benchmark indices eked out modest gains. Despite positive triggers like the India-EU FTA, performance was tempered by mixed corporate results, a weaker rupee, and foreign investor selling. Domestic institutional investors provided crucial support. Sectoral leaders included defence and energy, while pharma and FMCG lagged. Technical indicators suggest ongoing positive broader trends despite near-term caution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:48:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ddd7c5fc43f26c54fd7af_1769870785247.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manaksia Steels Reports Stellar Q3 Turnaround, Revenue Surges 109% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Manaksia-Steels-Reports-Stellar-Q3-Turnaround-Revenue-Surges-109percent-YoY/697ddc855fc43f26c54fd65b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Manaksia-Steels-Reports-Stellar-Q3-Turnaround-Revenue-Surges-109percent-YoY/697ddc855fc43f26c54fd65b</guid><description>Manaksia Steels Limited has reported a significant turnaround in its Q3 FY26 results. Standalone revenue from operations surged 109.66% year-on-year to ₹29,834 lacs, with Net Profit After Tax (PAT) turning positive at ₹947.84 lacs from a loss in the prior year. Standalone EBITDA also saw a substantial jump of 225.65%. The nine-month period also showed robust growth across revenue, PAT, and EBITDA, with EPS nearly quadrupling YoY.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ddc855fc43f26c54fd65a_1769870709949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nath Bio-Genes Q3: Revenue Surges, PAT Drops; Auditors Flag Labour Code Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Nath-Bio-Genes-Q3-Revenue-Surges-PAT-Drops-Auditors-Flag-Labour-Code-Risk/697ddd045fc43f26c54fd70f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Nath-Bio-Genes-Q3-Revenue-Surges-PAT-Drops-Auditors-Flag-Labour-Code-Risk/697ddd045fc43f26c54fd70f</guid><description>Nath Bio-Genes Q3 FY2026 reported a strong 78.8% YoY revenue jump to ₹6596L on a standalone basis. Standalone PAT surged 172.4% to ₹723L, boosted by other income and exceptional items. However, consolidated PAT declined 39.4% to ₹160L, with margins compressing to 2.43%. Crucially, auditors issued a qualified opinion, unable to assess the financial impact of new Labour Codes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:43:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ddd045fc43f26c54fd70e_1769870621407.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IKIO Tech Posts Mixed Q3 Results: Consolidated PAT Surges, But 9M Profit Dives, Standalone Slips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IKIO-Tech-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Results-Consolidated-PAT-Surges-But-9M-Profit-Dives-Standalone-Slips/697e14c65fc43f26c5501964</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IKIO-Tech-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Results-Consolidated-PAT-Surges-But-9M-Profit-Dives-Standalone-Slips/697e14c65fc43f26c5501964</guid><description>IKIO Technologies posted a mixed Q3 FY26, with consolidated PAT jumping 38.09% YoY to ₹107.68 Million. However, the nine-month period saw a significant 38.61% YoY decline in consolidated PAT to ₹203.20 Million. Standalone operations reported a sharp fall in revenue and profit for both Q3 and the nine-month period. The company has utilized ₹2721.77 Million of its IPO proceeds, with the full ₹500 Million for debt repayment already deployed. No forward guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:43:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e14c65fc43f26c5501963_1769870613104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Taxpayers Demand Relief Amidst Compliance Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Taxpayers-Demand-Relief-Amidst-Compliance-Overhaul/697dde015fc43f26c54fd898</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Taxpayers-Demand-Relief-Amidst-Compliance-Overhaul/697dde015fc43f26c54fd898</guid><description>India's Budget 2026 is anticipated to address significant taxpayer demands, including personal income tax rate reductions and higher exemptions for the middle class. Expectations lean towards simplifying compliance for property transactions, particularly for Non-Resident Indians, and enhancing the appeal of the new tax regime. The budget also faces pressure to introduce sustainability incentives, especially for electric vehicles, while concurrently aiming to reduce tax litigation and administrative burdens through the new Income Tax Act of 2025.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697dde015fc43f26c54fd897_1769870428139.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Insurers Demand Tax Relief, GST Clarity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Budget-2026-Insurers-Demand-Tax-Relief-GST-Clarity/697dddf45fc43f26c54fd851</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Budget-2026-Insurers-Demand-Tax-Relief-GST-Clarity/697dddf45fc43f26c54fd851</guid><description>As the Union Budget 2026 approaches, the Indian insurance industry is pressing for significant fiscal policy adjustments. Key demands include increased tax deductions for health and life policies, extending these benefits to the new tax regime, and resolving the input tax credit (ITC) anomaly under GST. These measures are pitched as essential to counter rising medical inflation, improve policy affordability, and expand insurance penetration, which remains notably below global averages.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697dddf45fc43f26c54fd850_1769870486936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Crypto Firms Demand Budget 2026 Tax Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Crypto-Firms-Demand-Budget-2026-Tax-Overhaul/697dde135fc43f26c54fd8df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Crypto-Firms-Demand-Budget-2026-Tax-Overhaul/697dde135fc43f26c54fd8df</guid><description>India's cryptocurrency sector is pushing for significant tax reforms ahead of Budget 2026. Industry leaders advocate for reducing the 1% TDS to 0.01%, revising the flat 30% capital gains tax, and introducing loss set-off provisions. They argue current measures stifle domestic trading, drive users overseas, and hinder innovation, seeking clearer regulations to foster sustainable growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697dde135fc43f26c54fd8de_1769870318508.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stove Kraft Profit Skids 66% Amid Consumer Demand Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Stove-Kraft-Profit-Skids-66percent-Amid-Consumer-Demand-Slump/697ddedd5fc43f26c54fd9c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Stove-Kraft-Profit-Skids-66percent-Amid-Consumer-Demand-Slump/697ddedd5fc43f26c54fd9c6</guid><description>Stove Kraft's profitability took a severe hit in the third quarter of FY26, with net profit plummeting 66.6% year-on-year to ₹4 crore, driven by a 6.4% drop in revenue to ₹378.3 crore. Muted demand in the consumer durables segment, coupled with ₹3.14 crore in one-time expenses including gratuity provisions and forex losses, weighed on performance. Operating margins narrowed to 9% from 10% a year prior.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:38:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ddedd5fc43f26c54fd9c5_1769870307186.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Power Urges Budget Push for Discom Privatisation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Urges-Budget-Push-for-Discom-Privatisation/697ddf595fc43f26c54fda83</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Urges-Budget-Push-for-Discom-Privatisation/697ddf595fc43f26c54fda83</guid><description>Adani Power Managing Director Anil Sardana has urged the upcoming Union Budget 2026 to prioritize reforms, specifically the privatization of state-run power distribution companies (discoms). Despite recent financial improvements in the sector, Sardana noted a slackening pace of reform, citing Uttar Pradesh's stalled discom privatization plans as 'bad news.' Industry participants are keenly watching for a clear signal from the budget to reignite momentum for deeper structural changes essential for the sector's long-term viability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:37:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ddf595fc43f26c54fda82_1769870243967.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget Focus Shifts to Part B for Economic Vision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Focus-Shifts-to-Part-B-for-Economic-Vision/697e12895fc43f26c5501772</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Focus-Shifts-to-Part-B-for-Economic-Vision/697e12895fc43f26c5501772</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman is set to deliver her ninth consecutive Union Budget, a significant departure from tradition by placing Part B at the forefront of outlining India's economic vision and reform agenda. This strategic shift aims to detail immediate policy actions and long-term economic objectives, focusing on leveraging domestic strengths to enhance global competitiveness amidst a slowdown and trade pressures. Key initiatives are expected in trade, customs rationalization, and the consolidation of export and manufacturing zones.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e12895fc43f26c5501771_1769870127702.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Delhi HC Orders Blocking of Cricket Piracy Streams</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Delhi-HC-Orders-Blocking-of-Cricket-Piracy-Streams/697e12765fc43f26c550171e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Delhi-HC-Orders-Blocking-of-Cricket-Piracy-Streams/697e12765fc43f26c550171e</guid><description>The Delhi High Court has ordered immediate, real-time blocking of websites and applications illegally streaming the Under-19 Men’s Cricket World Cup and the upcoming ICC Men’s T20 Cricket World Cup 2026. This swift action, initiated by JioStar India Private Limited as the exclusive media rights holder, aims to prevent significant revenue losses and safeguard intellectual property against pervasive digital piracy. The ruling empowers authorities to act rapidly on reported infringing content.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:35:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e12765fc43f26c550171d_1769870100829.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Twamev Construction Profit Plummets 59% Amid Auditor's Grave Subsidiary Warnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Twamev-Construction-Profit-Plummets-59percent-Amid-Auditors-Grave-Subsidiary-Warnings/697ddedd5fc43f26c54fd9d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Twamev-Construction-Profit-Plummets-59percent-Amid-Auditors-Grave-Subsidiary-Warnings/697ddedd5fc43f26c54fd9d2</guid><description>Twamev Construction's Q3 FY26 results reveal a sharp 59% YoY decline in net profit, despite a 38% revenue jump. The company's auditor issued a qualified opinion, citing significant issues with subsidiaries, including substantial arbitration claims, NPA status, and potential misstatements.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:34:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ddedd5fc43f26c54fd9d1_1769870018447.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Infra Auditors Resign Amidst Fraud Allegations, Investigations Mount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Reliance-Infra-Auditors-Resign-Amidst-Fraud-Allegations-Investigations-Mount/697e110a5fc43f26c550157c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Reliance-Infra-Auditors-Resign-Amidst-Fraud-Allegations-Investigations-Mount/697e110a5fc43f26c550157c</guid><description>Reliance Infrastructure's Q3 FY26 results are critically marred by its statutory auditors' intention to resign, citing fraud allegations and an ADT-4 filing. The company faces escalating probes from SEBI, ED, and SFIO, alongside significant "going concern" uncertainties across multiple subsidiaries. Auditors issued a disclaimer, unable to form a conclusive opinion on the financial statements, raising serious doubts about the reliability of the reported figures. While consolidated profit before tax showed a YoY improvement, the underlying governance and regulatory crisis is the dominant narrative.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:32:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e110a5fc43f26c550157b_1769869827589.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Duroply Sees 3.6% YoY Revenue Jump, But Q3 Earnings Dip Sequentially</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Duroply-Sees-36percent-YoY-Revenue-Jump-But-Q3-Earnings-Dip-Sequentially/697de1385fc43f26c54fdc0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Duroply-Sees-36percent-YoY-Revenue-Jump-But-Q3-Earnings-Dip-Sequentially/697de1385fc43f26c54fdc0b</guid><description>Duroply Industries reported Q3 FY26 revenue growth of 3.6% YoY to Rs 93.06 crores, with EBIT up 20%. However, sequential Q3 earnings declined significantly due to demand headwinds, particularly in NCR from GRAP-4 restrictions. For 9M FY26, revenue grew 9.7% YoY and EBIT surged 42.6%. Management cited procurement efficiency and improved realisations for margin gains and expressed confidence in long-term strategy despite near-term uneven conditions, following the SAP implementation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:31:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697de1385fc43f26c54fdc0a_1769869893692.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>R R Kabel Posts Stellar Q3 Results, PAT Surges 70% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/R-R-Kabel-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-PAT-Surges-70percent-YoY/697e11815fc43f26c550161f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/R-R-Kabel-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-PAT-Surges-70percent-YoY/697e11815fc43f26c550161f</guid><description>R R Kabel Limited reported a strong Q3 FY26 with standalone revenue up 42.3% YoY to ₹2535.86 Cr and PAT surging 70.4% to ₹116.12 Cr. The nine-month period also saw PAT grow 76.5% YoY to ₹320.83 Cr. An exceptional item of ₹19.01 Cr related to new labour codes was recognized, impacting profit before tax. Consolidated PAT also demonstrated robust growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e11815fc43f26c550161e_1769869822324.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Fiscal Policy Shifts: Debt-to-GDP Becomes New Anchor</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Fiscal-Policy-Shifts-Debt-to-GDP-Becomes-New-Anchor/697de2a05fc43f26c54fddc4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Fiscal-Policy-Shifts-Debt-to-GDP-Becomes-New-Anchor/697de2a05fc43f26c54fddc4</guid><description>India's fiscal strategy is recalibrating towards the debt-to-GDP ratio as the primary anchor, moving away from strict deficit targets in preparation for Budget 2026-27. This recalibration aims to enhance fiscal transparency and flexibility by targeting a debt-to-GDP level of approximately 50±1% by March 31, 2031. This shift acknowledges the nation's progress on its fiscal consolidation glide path, seeking to rebuild economic buffers and enable growth-enhancing expenditures.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697de2a05fc43f26c54fddc3_1769869567504.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Launches 'Chakra' to Fund India's ₹100 Trillion Sunrise Sector Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Launches-Chakra-to-Fund-Indias-100-Trillion-Sunrise-Sector-Boom/697de2485fc43f26c54fdd30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Launches-Chakra-to-Fund-Indias-100-Trillion-Sunrise-Sector-Boom/697de2485fc43f26c54fdd30</guid><description>State Bank of India has launched 'Chakra,' a new Center of Excellence designed to finance India's high-potential sunrise sectors. These eight sectors, including renewables, semiconductors, and electric mobility, are projected to unlock over ₹100 trillion in capital expenditure by 2030. The initiative aims to build expertise in risk assessment and finance structuring for these evolving industries, requiring diverse capital sources beyond traditional banking.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697de2485fc43f26c54fdd2f_1769869629579.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: PLI Schemes Drive India's Manufacturing Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-PLI-Schemes-Drive-Indias-Manufacturing-Ambitions/697e108c5fc43f26c55014bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-PLI-Schemes-Drive-Indias-Manufacturing-Ambitions/697e108c5fc43f26c55014bb</guid><description>India's economic strategy is pivoting from services to domestic manufacturing, powered by Production Linked Incentive (PLI) schemes. With a projected 7.4% GDP growth for FY26, these outcome-oriented incentives aim to attract foreign investment. Industry leaders are calling for expanded PLI coverage to more sectors and streamlined application processes to fully unlock manufacturing potential.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:27:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e108c5fc43f26c55014ba_1769869648413.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manaksia Steels Rockets: Q3 Profit Soars 241% on Record Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Manaksia-Steels-Rockets-Q3-Profit-Soars-241percent-on-Record-Revenue-Growth/697de31d5fc43f26c54fde6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Manaksia-Steels-Rockets-Q3-Profit-Soars-241percent-on-Record-Revenue-Growth/697de31d5fc43f26c54fde6a</guid><description>Manaksia Steels reported stellar Q3 FY26 results, with standalone PAT surging 241.20% to ₹9.1 Cr on 111.50% revenue growth to ₹301 Cr. EBITDA jumped 225.62% as margins improved. The company cited strong capacity utilization, market expansion, and an export-led strategy for its robust performance, with new capacity set to boost higher-value products.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697de31d5fc43f26c54fde69_1769869461434.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unick Printers' Q3 Loss Widens, Revenue Drops 24%, EPS Inconsistency Flags Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Unick-Printers-Q3-Loss-Widens-Revenue-Drops-24percent-EPS-Inconsistency-Flags-Concern/697de3355fc43f26c54fdeb9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Unick-Printers-Q3-Loss-Widens-Revenue-Drops-24percent-EPS-Inconsistency-Flags-Concern/697de3355fc43f26c54fdeb9</guid><description>Unick Fix-a-form &amp; Printers Ltd reported a widening net loss for Q3 FY26, with revenue flat YoY. The nine-month period saw a steep 23.75% revenue drop and a significant reversal from profit to loss. A major red flag emerges from the reported Basic EPS of ₹1.95 for 9M FY26, inconsistent with the net loss, raising accounting concerns.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:24:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697de3355fc43f26c54fdeb8_1769869458709.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mamata Machinery Q3 Profit Dips; Net Cash Positive &amp; Eyes Global Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mamata-Machinery-Q3-Profit-Dips-Net-Cash-Positive-and-Eyes-Global-Growth/697de4075fc43f26c54fe0db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mamata-Machinery-Q3-Profit-Dips-Net-Cash-Positive-and-Eyes-Global-Growth/697de4075fc43f26c54fe0db</guid><description>Mamata Machinery posted a mixed Q3FY26, with YoY revenue and PAT declining 8% and 10% respectively, hurt by margin compression. Despite operational softness, the company strengthened its balance sheet to become net cash positive in FY25 and secured a significant packaging machine order. Management is targeting substantial export market expansion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:22:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697de4075fc43f26c54fe0da_1769869334672.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Belrise Industries Posts 26% PAT Growth, Eyes Defense Sector Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Belrise-Industries-Posts-26percent-PAT-Growth-Eyes-Defense-Sector-Expansion/697e0f275fc43f26c5501329</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Belrise-Industries-Posts-26percent-PAT-Growth-Eyes-Defense-Sector-Expansion/697e0f275fc43f26c5501329</guid><description>Belrise Industries reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with adjusted PAT surging 26.0% YoY to ₹1,267.7 Mn and margins improving. The company also made significant strategic strides, entering the aerospace and defense sectors through international acquisition and a key alliance. Aggressive expansion plans and substantial debt reduction signal a strong growth trajectory, though interest cover requires monitoring.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e0f275fc43f26c5501328_1769869210641.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Part B Takes Center Stage</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Part-B-Takes-Center-Stage/697e0eb25fc43f26c5501274</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Part-B-Takes-Center-Stage/697e0eb25fc43f26c5501274</guid><description>The 2026 Union Budget presentation breaks a 75-year tradition by elevating Part B of the Finance Minister's speech, transforming it into the primary platform for detailing India's economic strategy. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman will reportedly dedicate significant emphasis to this section, which will outline immediate stability priorities and long-term growth objectives. This strategic reorientation is poised to draw heightened attention from economists and market participants seeking clear directional cues on reforms and the nation's global economic positioning.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e0eb25fc43f26c5501273_1769869175906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: India Telecom Seeks Fiscal Firepower</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Budget-2026-India-Telecom-Seeks-Fiscal-Firepower/697de34e5fc43f26c54fdf61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Budget-2026-India-Telecom-Seeks-Fiscal-Firepower/697de34e5fc43f26c54fdf61</guid><description>As India gears up for Budget 2026, the telecom sector, a cornerstone of its digital economy, is advocating for critical fiscal policy adjustments. Recommendations from industry stakeholders, including KPMG's Naveen Aggarwal, target enhanced innovation, alleviation of financial burdens, resolution of tax disputes, and indirect tax reforms. These measures are aimed at bolstering domestic manufacturing, ensuring network expansion, and maintaining India's trajectory as a global digital leader. The proposed changes address key industry pain points, seeking to align fiscal pragmatism with ambitious technological goals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:21:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697de34e5fc43f26c54fdf60_1769869307175.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Banks Revamp Services &amp; Compliance in Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Revamp-Services-and-Compliance-in-Feb-2026/697de3935fc43f26c54fe044</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Revamp-Services-and-Compliance-in-Feb-2026/697de3935fc43f26c54fe044</guid><description>Major Indian banks are set to implement significant customer-facing changes in February 2026. State Bank of India will adjust IMPS transaction fees, ICICI Bank will discontinue complimentary movie benefits on select credit cards, and HDFC Bank will cap Infinia card reward redemptions. Concurrently, Punjab National Bank is enforcing strict KYC updates ahead of an RBI deadline, reflecting a broader regulatory push for compliance across the sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:17:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697de3935fc43f26c54fe043_1769869058754.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sambhv Steel Tubes Posts Stellar Q3, IPO Funds Repay Debt; Analysts Watch Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sambhv-Steel-Tubes-Posts-Stellar-Q3-IPO-Funds-Repay-Debt-Analysts-Watch-Outlook/697e0dbf5fc43f26c550116f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sambhv-Steel-Tubes-Posts-Stellar-Q3-IPO-Funds-Repay-Debt-Analysts-Watch-Outlook/697e0dbf5fc43f26c550116f</guid><description>Sambhv Steel Tubes Limited posted a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue up 59.6% YoY to ₹5,891.35M and PAT surging 131.0% to ₹243.68M. Nine-month performance also showed robust growth. The company utilized IPO proceeds primarily for debt prepayment, strengthening its balance sheet. However, a subsidiary is involved in an FIR concerning alleged fraud. No forward-looking guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:16:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e0dbf5fc43f26c550116e_1769868996917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>