<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:55:14 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Pine Labs, OpenAI Partner to Revolutionize Indian Commerce with AI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Pine-Labs-OpenAI-Partner-to-Revolutionize-Indian-Commerce-with-AI/6996b176d25eafd9cd00565d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Pine-Labs-OpenAI-Partner-to-Revolutionize-Indian-Commerce-with-AI/6996b176d25eafd9cd00565d</guid><description>Fintech firm Pine Labs has announced a significant partnership with OpenAI to introduce "Agentic Commerce" in India. This collaboration will embed OpenAI's advanced AI models into Pine Labs' extensive merchant network. The goal is to enable autonomous financial actions and significantly optimize business workflows, marking a new era for commerce and financial transactions in the country.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:45:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996b176d25eafd9cd00565c_1771483616697.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brand Concepts Ramps Up Revenue, Adds Superdry &amp; Off-White, But Costs Spike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Brand-Concepts-Ramps-Up-Revenue-Adds-Superdry-and-Off-White-But-Costs-Spike/6996af8fd25eafd9cd005574</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Brand-Concepts-Ramps-Up-Revenue-Adds-Superdry-and-Off-White-But-Costs-Spike/6996af8fd25eafd9cd005574</guid><description>Brand Concepts reported a strong 23% revenue jump in Q3 FY26, driven by its B2C segment and plans to launch premium brands Superdry and Off-White. The company is investing heavily in in-house manufacturing, leading to higher expenses and increased inventory levels. Management aims for significant growth and margin improvement over the next three years, targeting a 20-25% revenue CAGR.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:37:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996af8fd25eafd9cd005573.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emmforce Autotech Revenue Up 6% But Profit Dips; Huge US Order Boosts Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Emmforce-Autotech-Revenue-Up-6percent-But-Profit-Dips-Huge-US-Order-Boosts-Outlook/6996aea0d25eafd9cd0054a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Emmforce-Autotech-Revenue-Up-6percent-But-Profit-Dips-Huge-US-Order-Boosts-Outlook/6996aea0d25eafd9cd0054a9</guid><description>Emmforce Autotech reported a 6% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹89 crore for FY25, though profit after tax (PAT) saw a dip to ₹8 crore from ₹9 crore in FY24. This decline was linked to higher depreciation costs from new asset investments. However, the company secured a significant U.S. export order worth ₹470 crore, which is expected to drive substantial future revenue, alongside plans to expand its Agri division and migrate to the main stock exchange board.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:33:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996aea0d25eafd9cd0054a8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindware Home Sees Profit Jump, Eyes Growth in Bathware &amp; Kitchen Appliances</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindware-Home-Sees-Profit-Jump-Eyes-Growth-in-Bathware-and-Kitchen-Appliances/6996aea0d25eafd9cd005493</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindware-Home-Sees-Profit-Jump-Eyes-Growth-in-Bathware-and-Kitchen-Appliances/6996aea0d25eafd9cd005493</guid><description>Hindware Home Innovation Limited reported a significant jump in profitability for Q3 FY26, with EBITDA growing 38% year-on-year to ₹52 crore and margins improving to 8%. The Bathware segment led the charge with 14% revenue growth and improved profitability. The company is strategically exiting loss-making consumer appliance categories to focus on kitchen appliances and aims for mid-teens growth in Bathware with margin expansion. However, the Pipes business continues to face challenges with negative PBT, despite volume growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:33:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996aea0d25eafd9cd005492_1771482892025.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Flomic Logistics Sees Revenue Drop, Posts Loss After Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Flomic-Logistics-Sees-Revenue-Drop-Posts-Loss-After-Growth/6996ae29d25eafd9cd00540b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Flomic-Logistics-Sees-Revenue-Drop-Posts-Loss-After-Growth/6996ae29d25eafd9cd00540b</guid><description>Flomic Global Logistics reported a challenging Q3 FY26 with a 19.3% drop in revenue and a 31.9% fall in profit. The nine-month period saw a significant reversal from profit to a net loss of ₹3.22 crore. This comes after a period of strong growth in FY25, raising concerns about current performance and increasing debt levels.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996ae29d25eafd9cd00540a_1771482778409.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold/Silver ETFs Surge on Margin Relief Amid Fed Policy Split</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/GoldSilver-ETFs-Surge-on-Margin-Relief-Amid-Fed-Policy-Split/6996acdfd25eafd9cd00526a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/GoldSilver-ETFs-Surge-on-Margin-Relief-Amid-Fed-Policy-Split/6996acdfd25eafd9cd00526a</guid><description>Gold and silver exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in India saw significant gains on Thursday, February 19, 2026, primarily driven by the Multi Commodity Exchange (MCX) and National Stock Exchange (NSE) Clearing's decision to withdraw additional margin requirements on futures contracts. This move reduces capital obligations for traders, aiming to boost liquidity. However, the rally occurs against a backdrop of mixed global cues, including a divided Federal Reserve stance on interest rates and a 'liquidity vacuum' in global bullion markets due to the Lunar New Year holidays.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:25:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996acdfd25eafd9cd005269_1771482562411.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Netweb Surges on AI Leap, But Valuation Faces Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Netweb-Surges-on-AI-Leap-But-Valuation-Faces-Scrutiny/6996acd4d25eafd9cd005250</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Netweb-Surges-on-AI-Leap-But-Valuation-Faces-Scrutiny/6996acd4d25eafd9cd005250</guid><description>Netweb Technologies India's stock surged following the launch of its 'Make in India' AI supercomputer and record Q3 FY26 results. With market capitalization around ₹19,000 crore and a P/E ratio exceeding 98x, the valuation is significantly elevated compared to sector peers and global leaders. While AI hardware demand is strong, Netweb's premium pricing and competitive positioning warrant careful consideration of sustainability risks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:25:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996acd4d25eafd9cd00524f_1771482492558.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bhandari Hosiery to raise ₹49.30 Cr via Rights Issue at steep discount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Bhandari-Hosiery-to-raise-4930-Cr-via-Rights-Issue-at-steep-discount/6996accbd25eafd9cd00521a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Bhandari-Hosiery-to-raise-4930-Cr-via-Rights-Issue-at-steep-discount/6996accbd25eafd9cd00521a</guid><description>Bhandari Hosiery Exports Limited has greenlit a Rights Issue aiming to raise up to ₹49.30 Crores by offering new shares at ₹2.56 each. The funds will primarily bolster working capital and reduce existing loans. This move comes as the company navigates a challenging financial landscape, marked by a significant decline in share price and competitive pressures in the textile export market. The rights entitlement ratio is set at 4 equity shares for every 5 held.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:25:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996accbd25eafd9cd005219_1771482412074.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Validation Surge: Anthropic's India Push Sparks Enterprise Race Amidst Market Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Validation-Surge-Anthropics-India-Push-Sparks-Enterprise-Race-Amidst-Market-Scrutiny/6996ac56d25eafd9cd00512a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Validation-Surge-Anthropics-India-Push-Sparks-Enterprise-Race-Amidst-Market-Scrutiny/6996ac56d25eafd9cd00512a</guid><description>Anthropic's strategic deepening in India, marked by its Bengaluru office opening and a significant partnership with Infosys, underscores tangible enterprise AI adoption. CEO Dario Amodei noted Anthropic's run-rate revenue doubled, and Infosys shares saw a notable rise following the collaboration announcement. This move validates AI's economic potential in India, a market poised for substantial growth and intense competition from global tech giants, even as analysts question market readiness and company valuations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:23:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996ac56d25eafd9cd005129_1771482332928.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crude Surge Hits Indian Oil Stocks Amid Surplus Forecasts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Crude-Surge-Hits-Indian-Oil-Stocks-Amid-Surplus-Forecasts/6996ac50d25eafd9cd005110</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Crude-Surge-Hits-Indian-Oil-Stocks-Amid-Surplus-Forecasts/6996ac50d25eafd9cd005110</guid><description>Indian oil marketing companies (OMCs) saw shares decline as crude oil prices surpassed $70/barrel due to Middle East tensions and supply fears. This surge, up 14% year-to-date, pressures OMC margins. While upstream firms benefit from higher realisations, downstream players face potential compression. Forecasts from the IEA point to a significant global oil supply surplus in 2026, suggesting current price spikes may be temporary, creating a complex outlook for the sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:23:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996ac50d25eafd9cd00510f_1771482312381.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JM Financial Launches ₹1,500 Cr Pre-IPO Fund Amidst Crowded Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/JM-Financial-Launches-1500-Cr-Pre-IPO-Fund-Amidst-Crowded-Market/6996ac49d25eafd9cd0050f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/JM-Financial-Launches-1500-Cr-Pre-IPO-Fund-Amidst-Crowded-Market/6996ac49d25eafd9cd0050f9</guid><description>JM Financial Asset Management has deployed its first ₹1,500 crore Alternative Investment Fund (AIF) specifically targeting pre-Initial Public Offering (IPO) opportunities. This Category II fund, approved by SEBI, aims to invest in companies expected to list within 18 months. The launch occurs as India's private markets mature and see significant domestic capital inflows, yet face intensified competition and increasing regulatory scrutiny on pre-IPO ventures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:23:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996ac49d25eafd9cd0050f8_1771482372269.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ascent: Ambition Meets Ecosystem Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ascent-Ambition-Meets-Ecosystem-Reality/6996aa9fd25eafd9cd004f2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ascent-Ambition-Meets-Ecosystem-Reality/6996aa9fd25eafd9cd004f2a</guid><description>India is aggressively pursuing global AI leadership, marked by the India AI Impact Summit and a 'design in India' mandate. Despite strong government support and a growing startup ecosystem, the nation confronts substantial challenges. Critical compute capacity gaps, reliance on foreign technology, and intense global competition require massive investment to translate ambition into reality. Concerns also persist regarding AI's impact on India's IT services sector and market concentration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:15:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996aa9fd25eafd9cd004f29_1771481831491.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Compute Gaps Cloud Sovereign Goals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Compute-Gaps-Cloud-Sovereign-Goals/6996aa77d25eafd9cd004f08</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Compute-Gaps-Cloud-Sovereign-Goals/6996aa77d25eafd9cd004f08</guid><description>India unveiled a comprehensive five-layer AI strategy targeting global leadership and 'AI for all'. While boasting a strong talent pool and renewable energy push, critical execution challenges persist. The nation's compute infrastructure lags behind global leaders like the U.S. and China, creating a 'Frontier Gap' in research and model development. Data center investments are surging, but energy demands and reliance on foreign hardware pose risks to achieving true technological sovereignty. The strategy must navigate these complexities to translate ambition into tangible global competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:15:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996aa77d25eafd9cd004f07_1771481841505.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC Mutual Fund Boosts Stake in Five-Star Business Finance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-Mutual-Fund-Boosts-Stake-in-Five-Star-Business-Finance/6996a9f2d25eafd9cd004e56</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-Mutual-Fund-Boosts-Stake-in-Five-Star-Business-Finance/6996a9f2d25eafd9cd004e56</guid><description>HDFC Mutual Fund schemes have significantly increased their investment in Five-Star Business Finance Limited. The aggregate shareholding rose by 2.15%, reaching a total of 7.15% by February 17, 2026. This move, executed through open market purchases, indicates growing institutional confidence in the small business lender's prospects. The disclosure was made as per SEBI takeover regulations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:13:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996a9f2d25eafd9cd004e55_1771481694718.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anthropic Taps India for AI Governance Influence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-Taps-India-for-AI-Governance-Influence/6996a97bd25eafd9cd004dd1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-Taps-India-for-AI-Governance-Influence/6996a97bd25eafd9cd004dd1</guid><description>Anthropic's CEO, Dario Amodei, has identified India as a strategic partner for global AI governance, announcing a new Bengaluru office. This move signals a commitment to collaborating on AI safety and economic impact, leveraging India's unique 'Third Way' regulatory approach. The initiative comes as Anthropic achieves a $380 billion valuation and faces heightened scrutiny over AI's potential for misuse, positioning India as a pivotal player in shaping the future of artificial intelligence on the global stage. India's own AI market is set for significant expansion, fueled by domestic innovation and international engagements.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996a97bd25eafd9cd004dd0_1771481598926.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Poojawestern Metaliks Buys Singapore Firm to Go Global</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Poojawestern-Metaliks-Buys-Singapore-Firm-to-Go-Global/6996a888d25eafd9cd004d2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Poojawestern-Metaliks-Buys-Singapore-Firm-to-Go-Global/6996a888d25eafd9cd004d2c</guid><description>Poojawestern Metaliks Limited has approved a deal to acquire up to 51% of Saffron Feathers Pte. Ltd. in Singapore. This move is part of the company's strategy to expand its business footprint internationally, focusing on markets like Singapore and beyond. The acquisition aims to strengthen its global presence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:07:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996a888d25eafd9cd004d2b_1771481335917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra Lifespace Gets Top Ratings for Borrowing Plans</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Mahindra-Lifespace-Gets-Top-Ratings-for-Borrowing-Plans/6996a662d25eafd9cd004b57</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Mahindra-Lifespace-Gets-Top-Ratings-for-Borrowing-Plans/6996a662d25eafd9cd004b57</guid><description>Mahindra Lifespace Developers Limited has received strong credit ratings for its upcoming borrowing plans. Crisil Ratings assigned 'Crisil AA/Stable' to its proposed ₹100 crore fund-based bank limits and 'Crisil A1+' to its ₹300 crore commercial paper issuance. These ratings, communicated on February 18, 2026, indicate the company's solid financial health and low risk for investors lending to it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:57:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996a662d25eafd9cd004b56_1771480782513.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indo US Bio-Tech's Ambitious Roadmap Faces Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indo-US-Bio-Techs-Ambitious-Roadmap-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/6996a636d25eafd9cd004b02</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indo-US-Bio-Techs-Ambitious-Roadmap-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/6996a636d25eafd9cd004b02</guid><description>Ahmedabad-based Indo US Bio-Tech Limited has announced a significant Rs 71.51 crore investment roadmap extending to fiscal year 2030-31, focusing on infrastructure, international expansion, and crop-specific research. The plan includes a 100-acre R&amp;D facility and processing plant by 2026-27, with key investments earmarked for export markets in the US and Africa. Despite ambitious revenue targets and a focus on developing disease-resistant crop varieties, the company's recent financial performance shows a decline in net profit and revenue, coupled with a 'Sell' rating from MarketsMOJO and a lack of analyst coverage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:57:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996a636d25eafd9cd004b01_1771480856837.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kwality Wall's IPO Dive: Margin Squeeze, Competition Bite New Ice Cream Giant</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kwality-Walls-IPO-Dive-Margin-Squeeze-Competition-Bite-New-Ice-Cream-Giant/6996a620d25eafd9cd004abc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kwality-Walls-IPO-Dive-Margin-Squeeze-Competition-Bite-New-Ice-Cream-Giant/6996a620d25eafd9cd004abc</guid><description>Kwality Wall's, India's demerged pure-play ice cream entity, commenced trading at a sharp discount, over 20% below its discovered price, with its shares hitting a 52-week low shortly after listing. This performance signals investor apprehension stemming from the company's meager 7.1% EBITDA margin in FY25, which compressed to break-even by H1FY26, starkly contrasting with peers like Vadilal's 18.5%. Analysts point to the capital-intensive, seasonal nature of the ice cream business, brutal competition from players like Amul, and a market rotation away from FMCG stocks as key concerns. Investors await clearer standalone financial performance, anticipating Q1FY27 results for potential signs of margin recovery driven by a possible GST cut.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:56:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996a620d25eafd9cd004abb.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>F&amp;B Firms Shine, But High Valuations Cast Shadow on Staples Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FandB-Firms-Shine-But-High-Valuations-Cast-Shadow-on-Staples-Sector/6996a5c2d25eafd9cd004a43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/FandB-Firms-Shine-But-High-Valuations-Cast-Shadow-on-Staples-Sector/6996a5c2d25eafd9cd004a43</guid><description>Food and Beverage (F&amp;B) companies are outperforming their Home and Personal Care (HPC) peers in the staples sector, driven by robust Q3 FY26 sales and EBITDA growth, with stable margins aided by raw material costs. However, the sector's average P/E of 53x, coupled with high multiples for key players like Britannia Industries (61x) and Honasa Consumer (63-117x), presents a valuation headwind. While analysts maintain 'Buy' ratings, potential upside is constrained, and risks from margin pressures and competition remain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:55:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996a5c2d25eafd9cd004a42.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FII Exodus: Indian IT Faces AI Reckoning as Capital Chases Cyclicals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/FII-Exodus-Indian-IT-Faces-AI-Reckoning-as-Capital-Chases-Cyclicals/6996a557d25eafd9cd00493e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/FII-Exodus-Indian-IT-Faces-AI-Reckoning-as-Capital-Chases-Cyclicals/6996a557d25eafd9cd00493e</guid><description>Foreign institutional investors (FIIs) initiated a significant capital withdrawal from Indian equities in early February 2026, pulling over ₹13,000 crore. The information technology (IT) sector bore the brunt, experiencing outflows exceeding ₹10,956 crore, driving the Nifty IT index down by 14%. This sell-off is largely attributed to escalating concerns over artificial intelligence (AI) potentially disrupting traditional IT services and business models. Conversely, sectors like capital goods, financial services, and oil &amp; gas attracted substantial FII inflows, signaling a strategic reallocation of capital towards more cyclical and infrastructure-oriented segments of the Indian economy. The IT sector's investment levels have reached a four-year low, prompting a critical re-evaluation of its growth prospects in an AI-driven future.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:53:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996a557d25eafd9cd00493d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CLSA Boosts Coforge; Stock Wobbles Amidst AI Optimism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CLSA-Boosts-Coforge-Stock-Wobbles-Amidst-AI-Optimism/6996a543d25eafd9cd004927</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CLSA-Boosts-Coforge-Stock-Wobbles-Amidst-AI-Optimism/6996a543d25eafd9cd004927</guid><description>Coforge Ltd. shares experienced a rally following CLSA's initiation of 'high-conviction outperform' coverage with a ₹2,426 price target, implying substantial upside. This optimism is fueled by a major 13-year, $1.56 billion deal with travel tech firm Sabre and Sabre's guidance for AI infusion. However, Coforge's stock has seen a notable decline in recent weeks, juxtaposing the bullish analyst view against prevailing market conditions and sector headwinds. The company's valuation and technical indicators present a complex picture for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:53:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996a543d25eafd9cd004926.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anlon Healthcare Surges 279% in Q3 Driven by Acquisitions, Eyes 30% CAGR</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anlon-Healthcare-Surges-279percent-in-Q3-Driven-by-Acquisitions-Eyes-30percent-CAGR/6996a533d25eafd9cd0048b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anlon-Healthcare-Surges-279percent-in-Q3-Driven-by-Acquisitions-Eyes-30percent-CAGR/6996a533d25eafd9cd0048b0</guid><description>Anlon Healthcare Limited reported a massive 279.6% revenue jump to ₹35.58 Cr in Q3 FY26 compared to last year, turning profitable with a PAT of ₹5.15 Cr. For the first nine months, revenue grew 69.7% to ₹121.08 Cr, with PAT soaring over 365%. The company is strategically expanding through acquisitions like Apiqo and Bizotic, and aims for a 30% revenue CAGR over the next three years, supported by capacity expansion and new API launches.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:52:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996a533d25eafd9cd0048af.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ACME Solar Seals 190MW Hybrid PPA, Bolstering India's Energy Transition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ACME-Solar-Seals-190MW-Hybrid-PPA-Bolstering-Indias-Energy-Transition/6996a527d25eafd9cd00488b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ACME-Solar-Seals-190MW-Hybrid-PPA-Bolstering-Indias-Energy-Transition/6996a527d25eafd9cd00488b</guid><description>ACME Solar Holdings' subsidiary, ACME Urja One Pvt Ltd, has secured a 25-year Power Purchase Agreement (PPA) with SECI Ltd for a 190 MW wind-solar hybrid project. Featuring an integrated Battery Energy Storage System (BESS), the project aims to provide assured peak power supply and is slated for commercial operation by February 27, 2028. This deal increases ACME Solar's total PPA-signed portfolio to 5,820 MW, reinforcing its strategic push into hybrid energy solutions amid India's growing demand for grid stability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:52:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996a527d25eafd9cd00488a_1771480461963.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TATA Steel's Mega Expansion: Balancing Growth Ambition with Execution Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TATA-Steels-Mega-Expansion-Balancing-Growth-Ambition-with-Execution-Risk/6996a45ad25eafd9cd00474b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TATA-Steels-Mega-Expansion-Balancing-Growth-Ambition-with-Execution-Risk/6996a45ad25eafd9cd00474b</guid><description>TATA Steel is undertaking an ambitious expansion, aiming for 40 million tonnes per annum (mtpa) capacity by FY31 and investing in green steel technologies. This strategy is underpinned by robust domestic demand forecasts, projected at 8-10% annual growth. However, the company faces significant execution risks tied to its multi-year, capital-intensive projects. These are compounded by potential global steel oversupply, price pressures, and a higher debt-to-equity ratio compared to some peers, raising questions about the financing and operational feasibility of its aggressive growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:49:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996a45ad25eafd9cd00474a_1771480279469.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JK Cement: Execution Edge Amidst Capacity Overhang</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/JK-Cement-Execution-Edge-Amidst-Capacity-Overhang/6996a452d25eafd9cd004734</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/JK-Cement-Execution-Edge-Amidst-Capacity-Overhang/6996a452d25eafd9cd004734</guid><description>JK Cement is expanding capacity aggressively, prompting concerns about future oversupply. However, the company's robust volume growth, market share gains, and successful project execution in key North and Central regions suggest resilience. Despite margin pressures, sustained infrastructure spending and a positive regional demand outlook provide a counterbalance to potential industry headwinds, positioning JK Cement to navigate a competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:49:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996a452d25eafd9cd004733.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver's Volatile Climb: Dollar Strength vs. Fed Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silvers-Volatile-Climb-Dollar-Strength-vs-Fed-Uncertainty/6996a2f1d25eafd9cd004628</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silvers-Volatile-Climb-Dollar-Strength-vs-Fed-Uncertainty/6996a2f1d25eafd9cd004628</guid><description>Silver's value climbed 1.04% today to ₹245,720/kg, driven by a complex mix of global economic crosscurrents. Investors are weighing a strengthening US dollar, geopolitical tensions, and a divided Federal Reserve stance on interest rates against robust industrial demand. This creates a volatile trading environment where silver's dual nature as a safe-haven asset and industrial commodity dictates price action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:43:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996a2f1d25eafd9cd004627_1771479921045.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SpiceJet Plans Major Fleet Expansion, Targets 300 Daily Flights</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Plans-Major-Fleet-Expansion-Targets-300-Daily-Flights/6996a0d0d25eafd9cd004505</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Plans-Major-Fleet-Expansion-Targets-300-Daily-Flights/6996a0d0d25eafd9cd004505</guid><description>SpiceJet is pushing for a major comeback, signing a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to bring in 10 more aircraft. The airline plans to significantly boost its operations, targeting over 300 daily flights and doubling its capacity to 220 crore Available Seat Kilometres (ASKMs) by Winter 2026. This ambitious move comes after the airline already doubled its capacity in the last quarter. However, this expansion happens against a backdrop of historical financial struggles and operational challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:34:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996a0d0d25eafd9cd004504_1771479353655.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India: Export Boom Can't Hide Domestic Market Share Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Export-Boom-Cant-Hide-Domestic-Market-Share-Slump/69969fe2d25eafd9cd004460</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Export-Boom-Cant-Hide-Domestic-Market-Share-Slump/69969fe2d25eafd9cd004460</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India's Q3 FY26 results reveal a stark dichotomy: robust export growth offset by persistent domestic market share erosion and compressed margins. Despite revenue and profit increases, the company's inability to capitalize on industry recovery and a growing SUV segment, coupled with new plant costs, presents significant challenges. FY27 guidance anticipates moderate growth, but competitive pressures loom large.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:30:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69969fe2d25eafd9cd00445f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Company Eyes Growth with Stock Split and Bonus Share Payout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Company-Eyes-Growth-with-Stock-Split-and-Bonus-Share-Payout/69969e50d25eafd9cd004390</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Company-Eyes-Growth-with-Stock-Split-and-Bonus-Share-Payout/69969e50d25eafd9cd004390</guid><description>A prominent Indian company has announced a record date of March 6, 2026, for two major corporate actions. Shareholders will benefit from a 1:5 equity share sub-division, reducing the face value to ₹2, and a 1:1 bonus share issuance. These moves aim to enhance share accessibility and reward investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:23:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69969e50d25eafd9cd00438f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NFIL: Analysts Cheer Growth Amidst Premium Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/NFIL-Analysts-Cheer-Growth-Amidst-Premium-Valuation-Concerns/69969ddcd25eafd9cd004293</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/NFIL-Analysts-Cheer-Growth-Amidst-Premium-Valuation-Concerns/69969ddcd25eafd9cd004293</guid><description>Navin Fluorine International (NFIL) is experiencing renewed analyst confidence, with 'Add' and 'Buy' ratings from Emkay Global and JM Financial, respectively. The company's robust growth in its Contract Development and Manufacturing Organisation (CDMO) segment and strategic R32 refrigerant expansion are key drivers. Despite strong recent stock performance and optimistic revenue targets, NFIL's premium valuation relative to peers and a projected slowdown in the broader specialty chemicals market in 2026 present headwinds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:21:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69969ddcd25eafd9cd004292_1771478590111.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel Hits New High Amidst Margin Concerns, EU Regulatory Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Hits-New-High-Amidst-Margin-Concerns-EU-Regulatory-Headwinds/69969dd7d25eafd9cd00427c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Hits-New-High-Amidst-Margin-Concerns-EU-Regulatory-Headwinds/69969dd7d25eafd9cd00427c</guid><description>Tata Steel shares surged to a new all-time high of ₹211.35, buoyed by strong Indian demand and positive Q3 FY26 results, including record domestic deliveries. However, the company saw a sequential dip in EBITDA margins to 14.4%, and faces an uncertain European market due to the implementation of the Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (CBAM) and slower demand recovery. Despite these headwinds, analysts maintain a constructive outlook, with most brokerages reiterating 'Buy' ratings and raising price targets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:21:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69969dd7d25eafd9cd00427b_1771478596438.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Regulatory Stay Sparks Refex Rally Amidst Revenue Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Regulatory-Stay-Sparks-Refex-Rally-Amidst-Revenue-Slump/69969dc0d25eafd9cd004246</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Regulatory-Stay-Sparks-Refex-Rally-Amidst-Revenue-Slump/69969dc0d25eafd9cd004246</guid><description>Refex Industries shares experienced an 8.3% surge on the BSE, reaching an intra-day high of ₹264. This rally was primarily triggered by the Securities Appellate Tribunal (SAT) granting a stay on a SEBI-imposed penalty against promoter Anil Jain, related to alleged insider trading. The SAT order requires a 50% deposit of the penalty amount within four weeks. This regulatory relief overshadowed a mixed quarterly performance, where net profit rose 8.3% year-on-year to ₹54.21 crore, but revenue from operations declined 16% to ₹576 crore. The company also announced the discontinuation of its refrigerant gas business, a strategic move to reallocate capital to higher-growth segments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:21:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69969dc0d25eafd9cd004245_1771478592569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Stocks Rebound: AI Deal Buoys Indian Tech, But Structural Shifts Persist</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-Rebound-AI-Deal-Buoys-Indian-Tech-But-Structural-Shifts-Persist/69969d50d25eafd9cd0041b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-Rebound-AI-Deal-Buoys-Indian-Tech-But-Structural-Shifts-Persist/69969d50d25eafd9cd0041b0</guid><description>Indian IT stocks experienced a significant rebound on February 19, 2026, driven by Nvidia's multi-year AI chip deal with Meta, which alleviated immediate concerns about AI-led disruption. The Nifty IT index climbed over 1.5%, with major players like Tata Consultancy Services and Infosys showing gains. Analysts are labeling this a tactical bounce supported by value-buying after a substantial correction, which saw the Nifty IT index shed 8.2% last week and approximately 15% over the past month. While the immediate threat perception has lessened, the debate continues regarding AI's long-term structural impact on the sector's business models, margins, and the imperative for strategic adaptation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:19:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69969d50d25eafd9cd0041af_1771478480957.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Touch Technologies Splits Stock 1:5, Approves Bonus Shares</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silver-Touch-Technologies-Splits-Stock-15-Approves-Bonus-Shares/69969bdfd25eafd9cd0040b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silver-Touch-Technologies-Splits-Stock-15-Approves-Bonus-Shares/69969bdfd25eafd9cd0040b3</guid><description>Silver Touch Technologies Limited shareholders have overwhelmingly approved a 1:5 stock split, turning each ₹10 share into five ₹2 shares. They also greenlit a bonus share issuance and an increase in authorized capital. These moves aim to boost share liquidity and reward investors, signalling management confidence in the company's future prospects. The resolutions are effective from February 18, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:13:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69969bdfd25eafd9cd0040b2_1771478091027.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Waaree Eyes Energy Independence with ₹8,175 Cr Gigafactory</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Waaree-Eyes-Energy-Independence-with-8175-Cr-Gigafactory/69969b6dd25eafd9cd004038</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Waaree-Eyes-Energy-Independence-with-8175-Cr-Gigafactory/69969b6dd25eafd9cd004038</guid><description>Waaree Energies is establishing India's largest integrated lithium-ion battery gigafactory in Andhra Pradesh with an ₹8,175 crore investment. The 16 GWh facility will cover the full battery value chain, from cell manufacturing to Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS), aiming to significantly reduce import dependence and create 3,000 jobs. This move aligns with national ambitions to bolster domestic manufacturing in the strategic clean energy sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:11:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69969b6dd25eafd9cd004037_1771478027356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Akums Drugs Posts Strong Growth, But IT Probe Casts Shadow</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Akums-Drugs-Posts-Strong-Growth-But-IT-Probe-Casts-Shadow/69969a01d25eafd9cd003f49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Akums-Drugs-Posts-Strong-Growth-But-IT-Probe-Casts-Shadow/69969a01d25eafd9cd003f49</guid><description>Akums Drugs and Pharmaceuticals reported robust growth in its third quarter of fiscal year 2026, with revenue jumping 14.8% year-over-year to ₹1,160 Cr and EBITDA climbing 21% to ₹147 Cr. The company also highlighted progress in its European expansion and strong cash reserves. However, an ongoing Income Tax investigation initiated in January 2025, along with a past fine for board non-compliance, casts a significant shadow over its future prospects, with the potential impact currently unascertainable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:05:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69969a01d25eafd9cd003f48_1771477633673.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sudarshan Pharma Secures Key Certifications Amidst Market Skepticism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sudarshan-Pharma-Secures-Key-Certifications-Amidst-Market-Skepticism/69969753d25eafd9cd003dd0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sudarshan-Pharma-Secures-Key-Certifications-Amidst-Market-Skepticism/69969753d25eafd9cd003dd0</guid><description>Sudarshan Pharma Industries Limited has achieved significant regulatory milestones, receiving Good Manufacturing Practice (GMP) certification from UK Certification &amp; Inspection Limited and ISO 9001:2015 certification from Staunchly Management and System Services Private Limited for its Hyderabad facility. These approvals validate the company's adherence to international quality standards for API production. However, despite these credentials and reported revenue growth, the company's stock performance has been volatile, marked by recent declines and significant leverage concerns, contrasting with its historical stock surges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:53:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69969753d25eafd9cd003dcf.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OpenAI's $850B+ Valuation Fuels AI Infrastructure Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAIs-850B-Valuation-Fuels-AI-Infrastructure-Dominance/699696ded25eafd9cd003d24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAIs-850B-Valuation-Fuels-AI-Infrastructure-Dominance/699696ded25eafd9cd003d24</guid><description>OpenAI is finalizing a monumental funding round, potentially surpassing $850 billion in valuation, with over $100 billion committed in the initial phase. This capital infusion, primarily from strategic investors like Amazon, SoftBank, Nvidia, and Microsoft, is earmarked for extensive AI infrastructure development. The deal underscores OpenAI's ambition to dominate the burgeoning AI hardware and cloud computing sectors, setting a new benchmark for tech valuations amid robust AI market growth forecasts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:51:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699696ded25eafd9cd003d23_1771476837728.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerage Divergence: Momentum vs. Future Growth in Indian Equities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerage-Divergence-Momentum-vs-Future-Growth-in-Indian-Equities/69969685d25eafd9cd003c80</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerage-Divergence-Momentum-vs-Future-Growth-in-Indian-Equities/69969685d25eafd9cd003c80</guid><description>Following Q3FY26 earnings, top brokerages Morgan Stanley and Jefferies have issued distinct outlooks. Morgan Stanley employs a bifurcated approach, favoring momentum stocks while signaling caution on sectors facing competitive headwinds and input cost pressures like paints and electronics. Jefferies, conversely, prioritizes companies poised for significant FY27 earnings growth, especially in financials and cyclical sectors. This divergence offers investors a nuanced view of market opportunities and potential risks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:50:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69969685d25eafd9cd003c7f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>