<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:56:08 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Ajanta Pharma's Bold Move: Biocon Deal Sparks Global Growth &amp; Big Profits!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ajanta-Pharmas-Bold-Move-Biocon-Deal-Sparks-Global-Growth-and-Big-Profits/694e0238e10c98d0788dc18b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ajanta-Pharmas-Bold-Move-Biocon-Deal-Sparks-Global-Growth-and-Big-Profits/694e0238e10c98d0788dc18b</guid><description>PL Capital rates Ajanta Pharma 'Buy' with a ₹3,200 target after its in-licensing deal with Biocon to market semaglutide across 26 emerging markets. Biocon will supply, Ajanta will commercialize. The brokerage forecasts strong Ebitda and PAT growth (17%/14% CAGR FY25-28) and expects ₹200 crore in FY28 sales from this venture, noting a strong strategic fit with Ajanta's existing global franchise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:25:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e0238e10c98d0788dc18a_1766720258773.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Arvind Smartspaces SURGES 21%? Axis Securities REITERATES BUY with BIG Target!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Arvind-Smartspaces-SURGES-21percent-Axis-Securities-REITERATES-BUY-with-BIG-Target/694e01a7e10c98d0788dc0d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Arvind-Smartspaces-SURGES-21percent-Axis-Securities-REITERATES-BUY-with-BIG-Target/694e01a7e10c98d0788dc0d2</guid><description>Axis Securities has maintained a 'Buy' rating on Arvind Smartspaces, setting a target price of ₹740 per share, signaling a 21% potential upside. The brokerage is optimistic about the company's strategic transformation, new management led by CEO Priyansh Kapoor, and its 'tri-city' model focused on Ahmedabad, Bengaluru, and Mumbai, expecting accelerated growth and improved operational efficiencies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:24:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e01a7e10c98d0788dc0d1_1766720006847.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lenskart Gets 'Add' Rating From Avendus: Can Shares Leap Beyond 10% Target?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskart-Gets-Add-Rating-From-Avendus-Can-Shares-Leap-Beyond-10percent-Target/694e01a4e10c98d0788dc0a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskart-Gets-Add-Rating-From-Avendus-Can-Shares-Leap-Beyond-10percent-Target/694e01a4e10c98d0788dc0a7</guid><description>Avendus Spark initiated coverage on Lenskart Solutions with an "Add" rating and a ₹490 price target, implying a modest 10% upside. Avendus praised Lenskart's M2C model and technology, projecting 21% revenue CAGR and significant EBITDA margin expansion through FY25-28. Despite recent dips, the company's Q1 performance showed strong revenue growth and margin improvement. Analyst sentiment is mixed but leans positive, with 3 out of 5 recommending a buy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:24:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e01a4e10c98d0788dc0a6_1766720009061.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Boardrooms: Empathy Crisis Sparks Mass Layoffs, Trust Shattered! Will Leaders Step Up?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Boardrooms-Empathy-Crisis-Sparks-Mass-Layoffs-Trust-Shattered-Will-Leaders-Step-Up/694e0281e10c98d0788dc1ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Boardrooms-Empathy-Crisis-Sparks-Mass-Layoffs-Trust-Shattered-Will-Leaders-Step-Up/694e0281e10c98d0788dc1ec</guid><description>Indian employee engagement has hit a global low of 19% in 2025, with half the workforce job-hunting and 30% reporting daily stress. Major firms like Infosys and TCS conducted brutal layoffs, contrasting sharply with managed executive exits. Volkswagen India offered a rare counter-example of empathetic handling. Experts stress empathy as a crucial leadership skill, warning that corporate indifference risks reputational damage and fuels distrust in capitalism. Rebuilding trust requires transparency, fair severance, and equitable treatment for all employees.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:19:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e0281e10c98d0788dc1eb_1766720219341.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gujarat Kidney IPO: Allotment Status Out Soon! Don't Miss Checking Your Shares</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Gujarat-Kidney-IPO-Allotment-Status-Out-Soon-Dont-Miss-Checking-Your-Shares/694dff12e10c98d0788dbc9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Gujarat-Kidney-IPO-Allotment-Status-Out-Soon-Dont-Miss-Checking-Your-Shares/694dff12e10c98d0788dbc9b</guid><description>Investors eagerly awaiting Gujarat Kidney IPO allotment can check their status on December 26th. The IPO, which closed on December 24th with a price band of ₹108-₹114, saw robust subscription. Listing is scheduled for December 30th on BSE and NSE. Follow our guide to check your allotment via BSE, NSE, or registrar MUFG Intime.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:14:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694dff12e10c98d0788dbc9a_1766719366424.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asian Granito Promoters Go All-In: Massive Share Buys Signal Confidence Amidst Staggering Profit Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asian-Granito-Promoters-Go-All-In-Massive-Share-Buys-Signal-Confidence-Amidst-Staggering-Profit-Surge/694dfab3e10c98d0788db875</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asian-Granito-Promoters-Go-All-In-Massive-Share-Buys-Signal-Confidence-Amidst-Staggering-Profit-Surge/694dfab3e10c98d0788db875</guid><description>Promoters of Asian Granito India Ltd, including Chairman Kamlesh Patel and Managing Director Mukesh Patel, have collectively acquired 6 lakh equity shares in open market transactions. This move comes as the company reported a significant turnaround in H1FY26, posting a consolidated net profit of ₹23.2 crore against a loss last year, with net sales up 8% and EBITDA surging 102%. Promoter holding now stands at 33.72%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694dfab3e10c98d0788db874_1766718365642.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>M&amp;B Engineering Poised for Rocket Growth? Equirus Hits 'Long' with Massive ₹515 Target!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/MandB-Engineering-Poised-for-Rocket-Growth-Equirus-Hits-Long-with-Massive-515-Target/694dfac4e10c98d0788db8a4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/MandB-Engineering-Poised-for-Rocket-Growth-Equirus-Hits-Long-with-Massive-515-Target/694dfac4e10c98d0788db8a4</guid><description>Equirus Securities has initiated coverage on M&amp;B Engineering (MBEL) with a 'Long' rating and a ₹515 target price. Analysts project robust multi-year growth (23% revenue CAGR, 30% Ebitda CAGR, 36% PAT CAGR FY25-28) driven by the expanding pre-engineered building sector and the company's strong post-IPO, debt-free financial position. Capacity expansion and increasing exports are key growth drivers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:49:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694dfac4e10c98d0788db8a3_1766719282598.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Top 3 Stocks Analysts Are Buying NOW: Airtel, Coal India, HCLTech - See Targets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Top-3-Stocks-Analysts-Are-Buying-NOW-Airtel-Coal-India-HCLTech-See-Targets/694dfa58e10c98d0788db7d9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Top-3-Stocks-Analysts-Are-Buying-NOW-Airtel-Coal-India-HCLTech-See-Targets/694dfa58e10c98d0788db7d9</guid><description>Indian markets saw lackluster trading with consolidation after a recent surge. However, Ajit Mishra from Religare Broking highlights three stocks with strong buy recommendations: Bharti Airtel Limited, Coal India Limited, and HCL Technologies. Detailed targets and stop-loss levels are provided for investors looking for specific opportunities amid selective stock-picking in a mixed market environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:49:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694dfa58e10c98d0788db7d8_1766719032425.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coforge Shares Tumble Ahead of Crucial Board Meeting: Will a New Fund Raise Trigger More Pain?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-Shares-Tumble-Ahead-of-Crucial-Board-Meeting-Will-a-New-Fund-Raise-Trigger-More-Pain/694dfa1de10c98d0788db73d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforge-Shares-Tumble-Ahead-of-Crucial-Board-Meeting-Will-a-New-Fund-Raise-Trigger-More-Pain/694dfa1de10c98d0788db73d</guid><description>Coforge Ltd. shares are under pressure, having fallen 7% in two days, ahead of a board meeting on December 26 to consider a fund raising proposal. This follows a previous ₹2,240 crore fund raise for Cigniti Technologies acquisition. Investors are concerned about potential share dilution, the company's weak cash conversion guidance, and its negligible cash reserves despite aiming for a $2 billion revenue run-rate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:49:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694dfa1de10c98d0788db73c_1766718081499.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shockwaves in Energy Market: Regulator Eyes Major Fee Cuts for Power Exchanges, IEX Stock Plunges!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Shockwaves-in-Energy-Market-Regulator-Eyes-Major-Fee-Cuts-for-Power-Exchanges-IEX-Stock-Plunges/694df98fe10c98d0788db690</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Shockwaves-in-Energy-Market-Regulator-Eyes-Major-Fee-Cuts-for-Power-Exchanges-IEX-Stock-Plunges/694df98fe10c98d0788db690</guid><description>India's power regulator, CERC, is reportedly considering slashing transaction fees for power exchanges like Indian Energy Exchange (IEX). The proposed reduction could lower fees from the current ~4 paise per kWh to around 1.5 paise per kWh. While discussions are preliminary, the news has put IEX shares under pressure, highlighting potential revenue impacts for the exchange.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:49:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df98fe10c98d0788db68f_1766718423830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sovereign Gold Bond Surprise: Investors Set to Pocket Nearly 5X Returns as Scheme Matures!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sovereign-Gold-Bond-Surprise-Investors-Set-to-Pocket-Nearly-5X-Returns-as-Scheme-Matures/694df863e10c98d0788db449</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sovereign-Gold-Bond-Surprise-Investors-Set-to-Pocket-Nearly-5X-Returns-as-Scheme-Matures/694df863e10c98d0788db449</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has announced the final redemption price for Sovereign Gold Bonds 2017-18 Series XIII at ₹13,563 per unit. Maturing on December 26, 2025, after an eight-year tenure, these bonds offer investors a capital appreciation of nearly 4.7 times their initial investment from December 2017, alongside a steady 2.5% annual interest, marking a highly successful government debt instrument.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:44:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df863e10c98d0788db448_1766717637667.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver SMASH Stocks in 2025! Will 2026 See a Shocking Reversal? Investors REEL!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Gold-and-Silver-SMASH-Stocks-in-2025-Will-2026-See-a-Shocking-Reversal-Investors-REEL/694df8dde10c98d0788db52d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Gold-and-Silver-SMASH-Stocks-in-2025-Will-2026-See-a-Shocking-Reversal-Investors-REEL/694df8dde10c98d0788db52d</guid><description>Gold and silver significantly outperformed Indian equities in 2025 as foreign investors pulled $17.9 billion amid high valuations and weak earnings. Experts predict a potential return of foreign capital and range-bound bullion prices in 2026, but uncertainty remains for small and mid-caps, with large-caps likely to continue their dominance. The market regulator's crackdown on futures and options trading aimed at protecting retail investors showed early results, but the full impact will be clearer next year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:43:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df8dde10c98d0788db52c_1766719204689.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Stocks Flat Outlook: What Investors MUST Know Before Trading!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Stocks-Flat-Outlook-What-Investors-MUST-Know-Before-Trading/694df7c7e10c98d0788db32b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Stocks-Flat-Outlook-What-Investors-MUST-Know-Before-Trading/694df7c7e10c98d0788db32b</guid><description>Indian stock markets are poised for a flat to positive opening on Friday, according to GIFT Nifty, trading near the 26,100-26,150 zone. Analysts anticipate thin volumes and a lacklustre market due to limited triggers, despite supportive global cues from record US highs and buoyant Asian markets. Experts suggest a 'buy-on-dips' strategy, focusing on sectors like private banks, metals, and auto, while cautioning that year-end book-squaring might cap sharp moves. The long-term outlook remains constructive, with expectations of steady growth in 2026 driven by earnings recovery and policy support.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:38:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df7c7e10c98d0788db32a_1766717443045.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks Alert: Bajaj Broking Reveals Top Picks for 2025 - Will These Banks &amp; Energy Stocks Soar?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/India-Stocks-Alert-Bajaj-Broking-Reveals-Top-Picks-for-2025-Will-These-Banks-and-Energy-Stocks-Soar/694df73fe10c98d0788db287</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/India-Stocks-Alert-Bajaj-Broking-Reveals-Top-Picks-for-2025-Will-These-Banks-and-Energy-Stocks-Soar/694df73fe10c98d0788db287</guid><description>Bajaj Broking has identified Lloyds Metals and Energy and Kotak Mahindra Bank as top stock picks for December 26, 2025. The Nifty and Bank Nifty are expected to continue consolidating after recent gains, with specific support and resistance levels highlighted. Both recommended stocks have shown technical breakouts, suggesting potential for significant returns over the next 12 months.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:33:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df73fe10c98d0788db286_1766717317191.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Jobs: India's Unique Advantage Revealed! IT Secretary Explains Lower Risk Than West</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Jobs-Indias-Unique-Advantage-Revealed-IT-Secretary-Explains-Lower-Risk-Than-West/694df5d2e10c98d0788db09e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Jobs-Indias-Unique-Advantage-Revealed-IT-Secretary-Explains-Lower-Risk-Than-West/694df5d2e10c98d0788db09e</guid><description>India faces a lower risk of AI-driven job disruption compared to Western economies, according to IT secretary S Krishnan. He highlighted India's workforce structure, with fewer white-collar roles and a strong STEM focus, as key factors creating new AI job opportunities. Krishnan believes AI will enhance human capabilities and productivity, not replace workers, emphasizing the need for trained professionals to develop AI applications.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:33:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df5d2e10c98d0788db09d_1766716990381.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indians Binge on Festive Feasts: Restaurants Booked Solid as Year-End Spending Surges!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indians-Binge-on-Festive-Feasts-Restaurants-Booked-Solid-as-Year-End-Spending-Surges/694df5bbe10c98d0788db068</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indians-Binge-on-Festive-Feasts-Restaurants-Booked-Solid-as-Year-End-Spending-Surges/694df5bbe10c98d0788db068</guid><description>Indian restaurants are experiencing a significant surge in business this festive season, with advance bookings for Christmas and New Year's Eve selling out across major cities. Brands are reporting stronger performance than last year, driven by both increased dine-in customers and robust delivery orders, signaling a healthy rise in consumer discretionary spending.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:33:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df5bbe10c98d0788db067_1766716918775.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trillion-Dollar Pharma Boom: Obesity Drugs &amp; AI Revolutionize Indian Healthcare!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Trillion-Dollar-Pharma-Boom-Obesity-Drugs-and-AI-Revolutionize-Indian-Healthcare/694df629e10c98d0788db129</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Trillion-Dollar-Pharma-Boom-Obesity-Drugs-and-AI-Revolutionize-Indian-Healthcare/694df629e10c98d0788db129</guid><description>Weight-loss drugs are set to drive substantial growth in India's pharmaceutical sector by 2026, fueled by rising demand for metabolic therapies and upcoming affordable generics. AI is accelerating drug discovery and innovation. Key GLP-1 medicines like Wegovy and Mounjaro are now available, with Ozempic recently launched. The market, already valued over ₹1,000 crore and grown tenfold in five years, is largely under-penetrated, offering significant opportunities for both innovators and generic makers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:31:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df629e10c98d0788db128_1766717228387.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Analyst's Hidden Gems: Manappuram Finance, Indus Towers &amp; Nuvama Wealth Breakout Signals Huge Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Analysts-Hidden-Gems-Manappuram-Finance-Indus-Towers-and-Nuvama-Wealth-Breakout-Signals-Huge-Gains/694df1c6e10c98d0788d94c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Analysts-Hidden-Gems-Manappuram-Finance-Indus-Towers-and-Nuvama-Wealth-Breakout-Signals-Huge-Gains/694df1c6e10c98d0788d94c3</guid><description>Kunal Kamble of Bonanza has identified Manappuram Finance, Nuvama Wealth Management, and Indus Towers as strong technical buy recommendations. He highlights significant bullish breakouts, increased volumes, and positive momentum indicators for Manappuram Finance and Indus Towers, alongside an uptrend confirmation for Nuvama Wealth Management. Specific buy ranges, stop-losses, and targets are provided, suggesting potential short-to-medium term gains for investors following these technical setups.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:16:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df1c6e10c98d0788d94c2_1766716070817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tokyo Inflation Cools Unexpectedly, But BoJ Signals More Rate Hikes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tokyo-Inflation-Cools-Unexpectedly-But-BoJ-Signals-More-Rate-Hikes/694df1b8e10c98d0788d947c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tokyo-Inflation-Cools-Unexpectedly-But-BoJ-Signals-More-Rate-Hikes/694df1b8e10c98d0788d947c</guid><description>Tokyo's consumer inflation slowed more than anticipated in December, dropping to 2.3% from 2.8% due to softer food price gains and falling energy costs. Economists had forecast a 2.5% reading. This marks the first deceleration since August. Despite the relief, the Bank of Japan is widely expected to continue its path of interest rate hikes. Inflation remains above the central bank's 2% target, prompting concerns about further monetary tightening. Japanese equity markets responded positively, with the Nikkei 225 seeing gains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:14:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df1b8e10c98d0788d947b_1766716043655.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia Strikes Big! Acquires Hot AI Startup Tech &amp; Top Talent in Major AI Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Strikes-Big-Acquires-Hot-AI-Startup-Tech-and-Top-Talent-in-Major-AI-Play/694df20ee10c98d0788d9526</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Strikes-Big-Acquires-Hot-AI-Startup-Tech-and-Top-Talent-in-Major-AI-Play/694df20ee10c98d0788d9526</guid><description>Nvidia is licensing chip technology from AI startup Groq and hiring its CEO, Jonathan Ross, along with key engineers. Groq specializes in AI inference, a crucial but competitive area for Nvidia, which dominates AI model training. This strategic move, mirroring recent trends of big tech acquiring talent and technology without full acquisitions, aims to bolster Nvidia's inference capabilities against rivals, though it raises potential antitrust concerns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:14:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df20ee10c98d0788d9525_1766715993091.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's BFSI Sector 2025: PSU Banks Soar, Microfinance Stumbles - Your Investment Guide!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-BFSI-Sector-2025-PSU-Banks-Soar-Microfinance-Stumbles-Your-Investment-Guide/694df0eae10c98d0788d932b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-BFSI-Sector-2025-PSU-Banks-Soar-Microfinance-Stumbles-Your-Investment-Guide/694df0eae10c98d0788d932b</guid><description>India's BFSI sector showed significant divergence in 2025. Public sector banks emerged as top performers with strong loan growth and cleaner balance sheets, seeing substantial gains. Gold financiers benefited from rising gold prices. However, microfinance faced pressure due to muted growth prospects, and insurance stocks delivered mixed results, impacted by margin pressure from input tax credit loss. This trend highlights a year of selective opportunities rather than broad market gains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:05:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694df0eae10c98d0788d932a_1766715818986.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Movers: Lenskart's Global Bet, KNR's Big Sale, Ola Electric's PLI Boost &amp; More Stocks in Focus!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Market-Movers-Lenskarts-Global-Bet-KNRs-Big-Sale-Ola-Electrics-PLI-Boost-and-More-Stocks-in-Focus/694defc4e10c98d0788d91fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Market-Movers-Lenskarts-Global-Bet-KNRs-Big-Sale-Ola-Electrics-PLI-Boost-and-More-Stocks-in-Focus/694defc4e10c98d0788d91fa</guid><description>On December 26, Indian stocks in focus include Lenskart Solutions' foreign investment in Korean tech startup iiNeer Corp, KNR Constructions' Rs 1,543 crore asset sale, Ola Electric Mobility receiving Rs 366 crore PLI incentives, and Vikran Engineering securing a Rs 459 crore EPC contract. Castrol India faces an open offer, while Gujarat Gas, Vodafone Idea, Strides Pharma, and others also make headlines.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:05:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694defc4e10c98d0788d91f9_1766715685657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dalmia Bharat's Eastern Gamble: Will Cement Demand Surge Overcome Pricing Woes?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dalmia-Bharats-Eastern-Gamble-Will-Cement-Demand-Surge-Overcome-Pricing-Woes/694decf9e10c98d0788d900e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dalmia-Bharats-Eastern-Gamble-Will-Cement-Demand-Surge-Overcome-Pricing-Woes/694decf9e10c98d0788d900e</guid><description>Dalmia Bharat anticipates mid-to-high single-digit volume growth in Q3FY26 as cement demand improves, reversing an H1FY26 decline. The company targets 75 mtpa capacity by FY28. However, intense competition in its key eastern and southern markets is pressuring prices, expected to lower sequential blended realisations by 3-4% in Q3FY26. Analysts suggest the stock reflects this pricing weakness, but potential industry price hikes from January could lift sentiment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:56:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694decf9e10c98d0788d900d_1766714717007.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's ₹2 Lakh Crore Food Subsidy Overhaul: Cash for Grains to End Massive Leakage?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2-Lakh-Crore-Food-Subsidy-Overhaul-Cash-for-Grains-to-End-Massive-Leakage/694deb8ae10c98d0788d8ea7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2-Lakh-Crore-Food-Subsidy-Overhaul-Cash-for-Grains-to-End-Massive-Leakage/694deb8ae10c98d0788d8ea7</guid><description>India's Public Distribution System (PDS) faces criticism for its ₹2.05 lakh crore annual subsidy cost and significant inefficiencies, with 28% of subsidized grain being diverted or lost, costing ₹69,108 crore. A proposed reform suggests replacing physical grain distribution with Direct Benefit Transfer (DBT), directly depositing cash into beneficiaries' accounts. This aims to reduce leakages, empower consumers, enhance transparency, and free up fiscal resources, drawing lessons from successful cash transfer initiatives.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694deb8ae10c98d0788d8ea6_1766714330288.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Labour Laws REWRITTEN: Contract Worker Rules Spark Debate – Is This a Game Changer for Businesses?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Labour-Laws-REWRITTEN-Contract-Worker-Rules-Spark-Debate-Is-This-a-Game-Changer-for-Businesses/694deb79e10c98d0788d8e76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Labour-Laws-REWRITTEN-Contract-Worker-Rules-Spark-Debate-Is-This-a-Game-Changer-for-Businesses/694deb79e10c98d0788d8e76</guid><description>India's new Occupational Safety and Health and Working Conditions Code (OSHWCC), 2020, significantly liberalises contract labour laws. It raises the applicability threshold and allows more flexibility for employers in core activities under certain conditions. While proponents argue for economic efficiency, trade unions express concerns about potential exploitation and lack of social security. The OSHWCC aims to replace older regulations, but its broad interpretation and relaxed licensing are drawing criticism, following historical judicial pronouncements on contract labour rights.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:50:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694deb79e10c98d0788d8e75_1766714311576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VC's 'Wet Blanket' Year: India's Startup Funding Hits Dramatic Reset in 2025 – What Happened?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/VCs-Wet-Blanket-Year-Indias-Startup-Funding-Hits-Dramatic-Reset-in-2025-What-Happened/694deb34e10c98d0788d8e22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/VCs-Wet-Blanket-Year-Indias-Startup-Funding-Hits-Dramatic-Reset-in-2025-What-Happened/694deb34e10c98d0788d8e22</guid><description>India's venture capital market underwent a significant 'reset' in 2025. Total funding reached approximately $11 billion, a decrease from the previous year's $12 billion, with fewer deals sealed. Investors became more risk-averse, hesitant to deploy capital due to exit uncertainties and stricter scrutiny on valuations. The market saw a shift towards prioritizing founders with proven execution experience and clear, plausible exit pathways, impacting early, growth, and late-stage investments unevenly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:48:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694deb34e10c98d0788d8e21_1766714353787.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Surges: US Blockade &amp; Nigeria Strikes Send Prices Soaring – What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Surges-US-Blockade-and-Nigeria-Strikes-Send-Prices-Soaring-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694de9b4e10c98d0788d8cc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Surges-US-Blockade-and-Nigeria-Strikes-Send-Prices-Soaring-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694de9b4e10c98d0788d8cc3</guid><description>Global oil prices are set for their largest weekly gain since late October, driven by a partial US blockade of Venezuelan crude shipments and a US military strike against ISIS in Nigeria. West Texas Intermediate (WTI) crude futures climbed above $58 a barrel, marking a more than 3% increase for the week. The US is intensifying efforts to pressure Venezuela, focusing on economic blockades, while also conducting counter-terrorism operations in Nigeria.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:42:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694de9b4e10c98d0788d8cc2_1766713858235.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2025 Stock Market Shock: 2024's Leaders Crash, Underdogs Soar - What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2025-Stock-Market-Shock-2024s-Leaders-Crash-Underdogs-Soar-Whats-Next/694de6a6e10c98d0788d8aa2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2025-Stock-Market-Shock-2024s-Leaders-Crash-Underdogs-Soar-Whats-Next/694de6a6e10c98d0788d8aa2</guid><description>Indian stock markets are witnessing a significant reversal in 2025. Many companies that led the rally in 2024 are now underperforming, while previous laggards have surged. Data from the BSE 200 index shows a stark contrast, with a lower percentage of companies delivering strong returns this year. Top gainers in 2025 include Aditya Birla Capital and TVS Motor, while fashion retailer Trent and IT firm Oracle Financial Services Software are among the biggest losers. This trend highlights market volatility and the potential for portfolio rotation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:28:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694de6a6e10c98d0788d8aa1_1766713155251.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's ₹10,000 Crore Drone Budget: 3 Stocks Poised for Explosive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-10000-Crore-Drone-Budget-3-Stocks-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/694de48ae10c98d0788d88ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-10000-Crore-Drone-Budget-3-Stocks-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/694de48ae10c98d0788d88ae</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 is expected to unveil a ₹10,000 crore, multi-year incentive package to boost domestic drone manufacturing under the 'Drone Shakti' initiative. This scheme will combine investment-linked subsidies (10-15% on Capex) and manufacturing output subsidies (10-15%), requiring 50-60% local content to enhance cost-competitiveness. Key beneficiaries anticipated include Zen Technologies, Paras Defence and Space Technologies, and IdeaForge Technology.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:18:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694de48ae10c98d0788d88ad_1766712524328.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hidden Gems: Stocks Poised to Profit from India's Cement Boom WITHOUT Owning Cement!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hidden-Gems-Stocks-Poised-to-Profit-from-Indias-Cement-Boom-WITHOUT-Owning-Cement/694de449e10c98d0788d8839</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hidden-Gems-Stocks-Poised-to-Profit-from-Indias-Cement-Boom-WITHOUT-Owning-Cement/694de449e10c98d0788d8839</guid><description>India's cement production surged 14.5% year-on-year in November, signaling robust demand from infrastructure and housing. This increased output puts stress on cement plant machinery, creating a lucrative 'recurring revenue' opportunity for companies supplying critical wear parts, refractories, gears, and engineering solutions for maintenance and upgrades. This article highlights four such 'stealth' stocks: AIA Engineering, Elecon Engineering Company, RHI Magnesita India, and ISGEC Heavy Engineering, which stand to benefit from the ongoing cement supercycle.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:18:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694de449e10c98d0788d8838_1766712592263.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Defense Boom: SME Stocks Skyrocket with 75%+ Profit Growth Fueling Investor Frenzy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Defense-Boom-SME-Stocks-Skyrocket-with-75percent-Profit-Growth-Fueling-Investor-Frenzy/694de42fe10c98d0788d8806</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Defense-Boom-SME-Stocks-Skyrocket-with-75percent-Profit-Growth-Fueling-Investor-Frenzy/694de42fe10c98d0788d8806</guid><description>Two lesser-known Indian SME defense stocks, Krishna Defence &amp; Allied Industries Ltd and CFF Fluid Control Ltd, are showing impressive profit growth exceeding 75%, driven by the 'Aatmanirbhar Bharat' policy and rising defense exports. While offering substantial returns, investors are cautioned about the inherent risks of SME stocks, including low liquidity and potential manipulation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:18:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694de42fe10c98d0788d8805_1766712611561.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock Growth: India's Big Bet on Spending vs. Tax Cuts - What Works Best?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Unlock-Growth-Indias-Big-Bet-on-Spending-vs-Tax-Cuts-What-Works-Best/694de428e10c98d0788d87be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Unlock-Growth-Indias-Big-Bet-on-Spending-vs-Tax-Cuts-What-Works-Best/694de428e10c98d0788d87be</guid><description>India's government is using fiscal policy to boost growth, employing both income tax benefits and GST rate rationalization. While tax cuts aim to increase spending, analysis suggests direct government expenditure programs, like free food schemes and farmer subsidies, are more effective in driving consumption and development. The debate centers on whether tax benefits translate into sustained economic activity or are saved, contrasting with the targeted impact of direct spending. The effectiveness hinges on sustained demand and job creation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:15:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694de428e10c98d0788d87bd_1766712436375.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Dairy Export Dream: Can It Go From Milk Giant To Global Trader by 2026?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Dairy-Export-Dream-Can-It-Go-From-Milk-Giant-To-Global-Trader-by-2026/694ddf5be10c98d0788d83fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Dairy-Export-Dream-Can-It-Go-From-Milk-Giant-To-Global-Trader-by-2026/694ddf5be10c98d0788d83fd</guid><description>India, the world's largest milk producer, is poised to significantly boost its dairy exports, targeting $490 million in FY25 with plans to capture a larger global market share by 2026. While production is abundant, the nation faces hurdles in quality, compliance, and cold chain logistics to fully leverage its potential in value-added products like cheese and skimmed milk powder.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:53:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddf5be10c98d0788d83fc_1766711198679.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pet Care Wars: Giants &amp; Startups Brace for 2026 Indian Market Explosion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pet-Care-Wars-Giants-and-Startups-Brace-for-2026-Indian-Market-Explosion/694ddfc8e10c98d0788d848a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pet-Care-Wars-Giants-and-Startups-Brace-for-2026-Indian-Market-Explosion/694ddfc8e10c98d0788d848a</guid><description>India's pet care market is rapidly expanding and becoming fiercely competitive. Major FMCG players like Reliance Retail, Nestlé SA, Godrej Consumer Products, and Wipro Consumer Care are increasing investments and launching new brands for 2026. The market is projected to grow significantly, reaching an estimated ₹35,000 crore, driven by indulgent pet owners seeking premium nutrition. Startups are also attracting funding, intensifying the competition in this burgeoning sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:53:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddfc8e10c98d0788d8489_1766711309040.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's EV Boom: Massive ₹857 Crore Electric 3-Wheeler Subsidy Fund EXHAUSTED 3 Months Early!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Boom-Massive-857-Crore-Electric-3-Wheeler-Subsidy-Fund-EXHAUSTED-3-Months-Early/694ddeebe10c98d0788d82e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Boom-Massive-857-Crore-Electric-3-Wheeler-Subsidy-Fund-EXHAUSTED-3-Months-Early/694ddeebe10c98d0788d82e9</guid><description>India's government is set to exhaust its ₹857 crore subsidy fund for electric three-wheelers (L5 category) under the PM E-Drive scheme three months ahead of the March 2026 deadline. This rapid depletion is driven by unexpectedly high consumer adoption of electric three-wheelers. The Ministry of Heavy Industries will cease issuing incentives once the allocated funds are disbursed or the target of 288,809 vehicles is met, whichever comes first, as per a letter to manufacturers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:53:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddeebe10c98d0788d82e8_1766711084423.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Investor Alert! Analyst Raja Venkatraman Reveals 3 Must-Buy Stocks for December 26th Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Investor-Alert-Analyst-Raja-Venkatraman-Reveals-3-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-December-26th-Surge/694ddea9e10c98d0788d825c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Investor-Alert-Analyst-Raja-Venkatraman-Reveals-3-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-December-26th-Surge/694ddea9e10c98d0788d825c</guid><description>Top analyst Raja Venkatraman of NeoTrader has identified three promising stocks for investors to consider on December 26th. Amidst market uncertainty and FII selling, Venkatraman recommends Gravita India, Laurus Labs, and PNB Housing Finance, providing specific buy levels, stop losses, and target prices. The Indian market closed lower on December 24th, with the Sensex and Nifty experiencing modest declines.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:53:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddea9e10c98d0788d825b_1766711227786.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Defence Stocks Dip 15%: Rally Over or Just a Pause? Investors Must Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Defence-Stocks-Dip-15percent-Rally-Over-or-Just-a-Pause-Investors-Must-Know/694dde9ee10c98d0788d822d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Defence-Stocks-Dip-15percent-Rally-Over-or-Just-a-Pause-Investors-Must-Know/694dde9ee10c98d0788d822d</guid><description>India's defence stocks have corrected by approximately 15% over the last six months, underperforming the Nifty50. Many leading companies are significantly below their 52-week highs. Despite institutional confidence, including HDFC Mutual Fund resuming SIPs and Tonbo Imaging filing its draft prospectus, experts warn of rich valuations, lumpy growth, and cash-flow risks. Outperformance is expected to be limited, with consistent delivery being key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:53:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694dde9ee10c98d0788d822c_1766711014074.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Gold Rush Soars 50% But Sebi Warning Sparks Caution: What Investors Must Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Digital-Gold-Rush-Soars-50percent-But-Sebi-Warning-Sparks-Caution-What-Investors-Must-Know/694ddde9e10c98d0788d816a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Digital-Gold-Rush-Soars-50percent-But-Sebi-Warning-Sparks-Caution-What-Investors-Must-Know/694ddde9e10c98d0788d816a</guid><description>Indian investors, especially young buyers, purchased approximately 12 tonnes of digital gold, valued at ₹16,670 crore, between January and November. This represents a significant surge, but demand has slowed following a warning from the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) highlighting the product's unregulated status. Industry players are now advocating for a regulatory framework, with the India Bullion &amp; Jewellers Association forming a self-regulatory organization to ensure customer protection and backed holdings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:50:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddde9e10c98d0788d8169_1766710855544.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 35-Year Economic Model Broken? Shocking Crisis Demands a NEW Path!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-35-Year-Economic-Model-Broken-Shocking-Crisis-Demands-a-NEW-Path/694ddd4ae10c98d0788d808a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-35-Year-Economic-Model-Broken-Shocking-Crisis-Demands-a-NEW-Path/694ddd4ae10c98d0788d808a</guid><description>India's 35-year-old economic model, credited with GDP growth, is now facing a severe socio-economic crisis. Key failures include a critical shortage of well-paying jobs, a surge in food subsidies affecting over 800 million people, and distress in the agricultural sector, especially for the 60% rural population. Urban centers grapple with pollution and congestion, while India lags in crucial emerging technologies. Experts argue the current model is unsustainable and advocate for a comprehensive overhaul, not just piecemeal fixes, to address these deep-rooted issues and build a better future by 2047.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:47:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ddd4ae10c98d0788d8089_1766710703127.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026: India Inc's Big Shift! Gig Work Booms, AI Disrupts, &amp; Talent Hunts Beyond Metros!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-India-Incs-Big-Shift-Gig-Work-Booms-AI-Disrupts-and-Talent-Hunts-Beyond-Metros/694dd876e10c98d0788d7de2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-India-Incs-Big-Shift-Gig-Work-Booms-AI-Disrupts-and-Talent-Hunts-Beyond-Metros/694dd876e10c98d0788d7de2</guid><description>Experts predict India Inc will see major shifts in 2026. Companies will increasingly hire from smaller cities, reducing reliance on metros. The gig workforce is set to significantly grow, boosted by new labor codes offering social security. Artificial intelligence will continue to disrupt workplaces, prompting a focus on upskilling and restructuring roles, with fewer people potentially doing more AI-assisted work.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:26:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694dd876e10c98d0788d7de1_1766709561385.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>