<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:29:02 +0000</pubDate><item><title>AI Express Bets $70M on Hybrid Model Amidst FY26 Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/AI-Express-Bets-70M-on-Hybrid-Model-Amidst-FY26-Losses/6983b1f3bf48f011a29aa071</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/AI-Express-Bets-70M-on-Hybrid-Model-Amidst-FY26-Losses/6983b1f3bf48f011a29aa071</guid><description>Air India Express is investing $70 million to modernize its fleet and reposition as a hybrid carrier, integrating 50 "white tail" B737 MAXs. Despite expecting an operating profit in H2 FY26, the airline anticipates a net loss for the full fiscal year. This strategic shift aims to capture a more premium market segment, but faces intense competition from established players like IndiGo and industry-wide financial pressures. The investment focuses on standardizing aircraft interiors and upgrading legacy planes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:54:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983b1f3bf48f011a29aa070_1770238597877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Elevates Delivery Platforms to Essential Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Elevates-Delivery-Platforms-to-Essential-Infrastructure/6983b17dbf48f011a29a9f1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Elevates-Delivery-Platforms-to-Essential-Infrastructure/6983b17dbf48f011a29a9f1e</guid><description>Swiggy CEO Sriharsha Majety believes the Union Budget's emphasis on City Economic Regions and formalisation will transform food and quick commerce delivery from discretionary services into essential urban infrastructure. This strategic shift is expected to accelerate economic growth in Tier II and III cities, fostering new opportunities and solidifying the necessity of these platforms beyond major metropolitan areas. The government's proposed investments aim to boost consumption and formalise economic activity, creating a more robust demand environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:52:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983b17dbf48f011a29a9f1d_1770238456439.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Warburg Pincus: India Journey from Pioneer to Market Navigator</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Warburg-Pincus-India-Journey-from-Pioneer-to-Market-Navigator/6983abefbf48f011a29a9a10</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Warburg-Pincus-India-Journey-from-Pioneer-to-Market-Navigator/6983abefbf48f011a29a9a10</guid><description>Warburg Pincus celebrates three decades in India, a market now its second-largest global investment hub. Since entering in 1998, the firm has deployed $10 billion across 80 investments, partnering with foundational Indian companies. This milestone highlights Warburg's adaptation to India's rapidly evolving financial ecosystem, characterized by the ascendance of domestic capital and a more sophisticated exit landscape.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:28:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983abefbf48f011a29a9a0f_1770237110661.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ambani Projects Energy Security, Trillion-Dollar GDP Leap for India</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Ambani-Projects-Energy-Security-Trillion-Dollar-GDP-Leap-for-India/6983abd7bf48f011a29a9923</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Ambani-Projects-Energy-Security-Trillion-Dollar-GDP-Leap-for-India/6983abd7bf48f011a29a9923</guid><description>Reliance Chairman Mukesh Ambani forecasts India will achieve energy self-sufficiency within 20-30 years, projecting a GDP surge to $25-30 trillion. BlackRock CEO Larry Fink echoed optimism, identifying the next two decades as a prime investment "era" for India. Both highlighted the need for patient capital in infrastructure and technology.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:28:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983abd7bf48f011a29a9922_1770237049363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 'Golden Share' Revival: Control vs. Capital Unlock?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Golden-Share-Revival-Control-vs-Capital-Unlock/6983a982bf48f011a29a970d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Golden-Share-Revival-Control-vs-Capital-Unlock/6983a982bf48f011a29a970d</guid><description>The Indian government is reviving the 'golden share' concept for Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs) to maintain strategic oversight while potentially unlocking INR 12.5 lakh crore. This policy aims to grant veto power over critical decisions, even with reduced equity stakes. While intended to safeguard national interests, the mechanism introduces a delicate balance, raising concerns about stifling operational efficiency and deterring private investment, a stark contrast to pure market-driven growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:18:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983a982bf48f011a29a970c_1770236469777.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>API Eyes India Office Amid US-India Trade Talks, Energy Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/API-Eyes-India-Office-Amid-US-India-Trade-Talks-Energy-Growth/6983a6b3bf48f011a29a94de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/API-Eyes-India-Office-Amid-US-India-Trade-Talks-Energy-Growth/6983a6b3bf48f011a29a94de</guid><description>The American Petroleum Institute (API), a global energy standards body, is establishing its first representative office in New Delhi. This strategic move aligns with India's growing energy consumption and the proposed US-India trade deal, aiming for deeper engagement with policymakers and industry. API's experience in infrastructure and safety frameworks is set to become increasingly relevant for India's energy transformation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:06:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983a6b3bf48f011a29a94dd_1770235719587.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Faces CCI Probe: Dominance Under Scrutiny Amidst Cancellations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Faces-CCI-Probe-Dominance-Under-Scrutiny-Amidst-Cancellations/6983a278bf48f011a29a91e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Faces-CCI-Probe-Dominance-Under-Scrutiny-Amidst-Cancellations/6983a278bf48f011a29a91e6</guid><description>The Competition Commission of India (CCI) has ordered a 90-day investigation into IndiGo, alleging that the airline's large-scale flight cancellations in December 2025 may have created an "appreciable adverse effect" on consumers and potentially constituted an "artificial scarcity" of services. This regulatory action, stemming from operational disruptions that affected over 300,000 passengers, intensifies scrutiny on the dominant carrier. IndiGo's market share hovers around 62-65%, with a significantly larger fleet than rivals like Air India. The investigation will examine whether these actions constituted an abuse of its dominant position under the Competition Act.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:48:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983a278bf48f011a29a91e5_1770234807226.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DLF Exits Kolkata Portfolio for ₹670 Cr, Bolsters Core Rental Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/DLF-Exits-Kolkata-Portfolio-for-670-Cr-Bolsters-Core-Rental-Business/6983a211bf48f011a29a9045</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/DLF-Exits-Kolkata-Portfolio-for-670-Cr-Bolsters-Core-Rental-Business/6983a211bf48f011a29a9045</guid><description>DLF has completed the divestment of its Kolkata technology park and land parcels for a total of ₹670 crore to Srijan Group, marking a strategic exit from the city. This move allows DLF to sharpen its focus on its robust rental business, DLF Cyber City Developers Limited (DCCDL), which reported strong Q3 FY26 performance with 18% year-on-year revenue growth and low vacancy rates. The company's core operations remain strong, evidenced by a 14% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹1,203 crore and revenue growth of 32% to ₹2,020 crore in Q3 FY26. DLF's development arm also achieved a significant milestone by reaching zero gross debt.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:46:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983a211bf48f011a29a9044_1770234588668.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jabil Leases Pune Hub Amid India Supply Chain Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jabil-Leases-Pune-Hub-Amid-India-Supply-Chain-Pivot/6983a205bf48f011a29a8fc6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jabil-Leases-Pune-Hub-Amid-India-Supply-Chain-Pivot/6983a205bf48f011a29a8fc6</guid><description>Jabil Circuit India has secured over 410,000 sq ft of warehousing space in Pune for a decade, involving a monthly rent exceeding ₹94.84 lakh. This strategic expansion deepens the US-based manufacturer's operational base in India, supporting its role as a key supplier for Apple and aligning with global supply chain diversification trends away from China. The move underscores India's growing importance as a manufacturing hub.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:46:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983a205bf48f011a29a8fc5_1770235042264.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's PSBs Eye Global Top 20; Reform Pace Faces Structural Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-PSBs-Eye-Global-Top-20-Reform-Pace-Faces-Structural-Hurdles/6983a193bf48f011a29a8e90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-PSBs-Eye-Global-Top-20-Reform-Pace-Faces-Structural-Hurdles/6983a193bf48f011a29a8e90</guid><description>Government is planning a strategic conclave for state-run banks, targeting global competitiveness aligned with 'Viksit Bharat 2047'. This follows a strong H1 FY26 performance with ₹93,675 crore net profit and a multi-year low 2.30% NPA. The ambition is to place at least two PSBs among the world's top 20 by 2047. However, this pursuit faces headwinds from stagnant deposit growth, an imperative for digital transformation, and competition from agile private sector banks, juxtaposed against a persistently low credit-to-GDP ratio.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:44:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983a193bf48f011a29a8e8f_1770234410214.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Dual-Speed Demand: MNCs Ride Premium Wave Post-GST</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Dual-Speed-Demand-MNCs-Ride-Premium-Wave-Post-GST/6983991dbf48f011a29a89d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Dual-Speed-Demand-MNCs-Ride-Premium-Wave-Post-GST/6983991dbf48f011a29a89d5</guid><description>Multinational corporations reported robust Q4 2025 growth in India, boosted by GST rate rationalization and strong domestic demand, particularly in premium electronics and appliances. Apple and AO Smith posted record performances. However, underlying demand from lower-income urban consumers remains soft, indicating a bifurcated recovery. Analysts predict continued growth for India's consumer market, driven by policy support and an expanding middle class.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:08:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983991dbf48f011a29a89d4_1770232184533.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lupin Secures US FDA Approval for Topiramate XR Capsules</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Secures-US-FDA-Approval-for-Topiramate-XR-Capsules/6983919abf48f011a299f88f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Secures-US-FDA-Approval-for-Topiramate-XR-Capsules/6983919abf48f011a299f88f</guid><description>Lupin Ltd. has received US FDA approval for its Topiramate extended-release capsules in multiple strengths, enabling market entry in the United States. This approval, based on an Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA), positions Lupin to compete in the estimated $164 million US market for this epilepsy and migraine treatment. The drug is bioequivalent to Supernus Pharmaceuticals' Trokendi XR. This launch aligns with Lupin's broader strategy to expand its generics footprint in key international markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983919abf48f011a299f88e_1770230924172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PhonePe IPO: Tech Debt or Profit Path?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PhonePe-IPO-Tech-Debt-or-Profit-Path/698390aebf48f011a299f716</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PhonePe-IPO-Tech-Debt-or-Profit-Path/698390aebf48f011a299f716</guid><description>PhonePe is preparing for a significant IPO, highlighting its Rs 33.73 billion investment in proprietary on-premises technology infrastructure as a key competitive advantage and pathway to profitability. However, the substantial capital expenditure on data centers and hardware raises questions about the speed and certainty of achieving sustainable earnings. Competitors like Google Pay often leverage cloud-native approaches. The fintech sector, including PhonePe, is shifting from a growth-at-all-costs mentality to demanding clear unit economics and profitability from public markets, making PhonePe's infrastructure cost-versus-earnings equation a critical IPO narrative.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:32:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698390aebf48f011a299f715_1770230084013.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Parag Milk Foods Hits Record Revenue, But Margins Squeeze Amidst Cost Hikes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Parag-Milk-Foods-Hits-Record-Revenue-But-Margins-Squeeze-Amidst-Cost-Hikes/69838e51bf48f011a296c4a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Parag-Milk-Foods-Hits-Record-Revenue-But-Margins-Squeeze-Amidst-Cost-Hikes/69838e51bf48f011a296c4a7</guid><description>Parag Milk Foods achieved its highest-ever quarterly revenue of INR 1013 Cr, up 14% YoY, driven by 8% volume growth and strong performance in core dairy products. However, rising milk prices squeezed margins, with EBITDA margin falling to 7.6% from 9.0% YoY, and PAT (before exceptional items) declined 3% to INR 35 Cr. The company's new-age business segments, Pride of Cows and Avvatar, saw a remarkable 123% YoY surge, crossing INR 100 Cr. Management cited calibrated pricing and portfolio mix for cost pass-through.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:22:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69838e51bf48f011a296c4a6_1770229436288.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Tumbles as AMD Miss Fuels AI Disruption Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Tumbles-as-AMD-Miss-Fuels-AI-Disruption-Fears/69838b0bc5e5e71e2c90470e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Tumbles-as-AMD-Miss-Fuels-AI-Disruption-Fears/69838b0bc5e5e71e2c90470e</guid><description>U.S. equities retreated Wednesday, led by a 16% plunge in Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) following a disappointing first-quarter forecast. This sell-off reverberated across the technology sector, with semiconductors and software firms facing pressure. Fears of AI-driven disruption, spurred by new agent capabilities, exacerbated concerns over elevated tech valuations, leading to a broad market downturn.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:08:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69838b0bc5e5e71e2c90470d_1770228877227.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Pivots: Chile Mineral Venture Signals Strategic Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Coal-India-Pivots-Chile-Mineral-Venture-Signals-Strategic-Shift/6983892a1bdb702afea0baac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Coal-India-Pivots-Chile-Mineral-Venture-Signals-Strategic-Shift/6983892a1bdb702afea0baac</guid><description>Coal India Ltd. (CIL) is strategically expanding beyond its core coal operations. The company approved establishing a wholly-owned subsidiary in Chile to explore critical minerals like lithium and copper, coinciding with India's nearing free trade agreement with Chile. Concurrently, CIL is making substantial domestic investments, including an equity infusion for an energy joint venture with Damodar Valley Corporation (DVC) and funding a coal-to-ammonium nitrate project through its subsidiary BCGCL. These moves signify a deliberate diversification strategy aimed at capitalizing on future energy and material demands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:00:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983892a1bdb702afea0baab_1770228189734.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India Express Bets on Cabin Overhaul for Profitability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Express-Bets-on-Cabin-Overhaul-for-Profitability/6983883f1bdb702afea0b98a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Express-Bets-on-Cabin-Overhaul-for-Profitability/6983883f1bdb702afea0b98a</guid><description>Air India Express anticipates an operating profit in the latter half of FY2026, underpinned by improved efficiency and cost controls. The airline is investing $70 million in cabin refurbishments across its fleet, including 26 Boeing 737 NGs and 50 Boeing 737 MAXs, with plans to convert over 40 MAX business class seats to all-economy configurations. This strategic move aims to bolster its position as a value carrier. The carrier is aggressively expanding its fleet, targeting 300 aircraft by FY2031, and aims for a 25% market share. Despite a significant loss of ₹5,678.2 crore in FY25, the airline is focused on turning its operations around within the dynamic Indian aviation sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:56:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983883f1bdb702afea0b989_1770227872564.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Parag Milk Foods Hits Record Revenue; Profit Dips Amidst Inflation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Parag-Milk-Foods-Hits-Record-Revenue-Profit-Dips-Amidst-Inflation/6983865cf5a3f0ebac9ee5d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Parag-Milk-Foods-Hits-Record-Revenue-Profit-Dips-Amidst-Inflation/6983865cf5a3f0ebac9ee5d1</guid><description>Parag Milk Foods achieved its highest-ever quarterly revenue of INR 1,013 Cr in Q3 FY26, a 14% YoY jump fueled by 8% volume growth and strong performance in core categories and its 'New Age Business' (+123% YoY). However, soaring milk prices (+20% YoY) compressed margins, leading to a 3% EBITDA fall and an 18% YoY decline in reported Profit After Tax (PAT) to INR 30 Cr. For 9M FY26, revenue grew 14% to INR 2,872 Cr, with PAT up 11% to INR 103 Cr.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Geopolitics: Supply Chain Fragmentation Fuels National Sovereignty Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Geopolitics-Supply-Chain-Fragmentation-Fuels-National-Sovereignty-Race/6983860af5a3f0ebac9ee439</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Geopolitics-Supply-Chain-Fragmentation-Fuels-National-Sovereignty-Race/6983860af5a3f0ebac9ee439</guid><description>The artificial intelligence race has escalated into a geopolitical contest, fragmenting the global AI supply chain into national "islands." Nations prioritize sovereignty over foundational elements like chips and data, creating a complex environment. While established tech leaders face new challenges, emerging contenders, notably India leveraging data and domestic models, are positioned to gain strategic influence in this evolving technological order.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:46:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983860af5a3f0ebac9ee438_1770227705536.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India Express Signals Operating Profit, But Group Losses Persist</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Express-Signals-Operating-Profit-But-Group-Losses-Persist/698385f2f5a3f0ebac9ee2c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Express-Signals-Operating-Profit-But-Group-Losses-Persist/698385f2f5a3f0ebac9ee2c4</guid><description>Air India Express anticipates its first operating profit in the second half of fiscal year 2027, citing improved unit economics and cost management. This comes as part of an ambitious plan to triple its size by FY31 with a 25% market share. However, the airline is still expected to report a net loss for the full fiscal year. This follows a trend of substantial losses within the broader Tata aviation group, including Air India's Rs 10,859 crore loss in FY25, underscoring the challenges in achieving group-wide profitability despite strategic investments and fleet modernization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:46:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698385f2f5a3f0ebac9ee2c3_1770228311814.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Eyes Indonesian EV, Defence Markets via PT Pindad JV</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ashok-Leyland-Eyes-Indonesian-EV-Defence-Markets-via-PT-Pindad-JV/698385e1f5a3f0ebac9ee241</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ashok-Leyland-Eyes-Indonesian-EV-Defence-Markets-via-PT-Pindad-JV/698385e1f5a3f0ebac9ee241</guid><description>Ashok Leyland has signed a strategic memorandum of understanding with Indonesia's state-owned PT Pindad to jointly develop and manufacture electric buses and defense vehicles. This collaboration aims to leverage Ashok Leyland's global commercial EV and defense expertise against PT Pindad's local manufacturing strength, targeting Indonesia's specific mobility and national security needs while expanding the company's international footprint. The move capitalizes on Indonesia's growing demand for sustainable transport and defense modernization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:46:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698385e1f5a3f0ebac9ee240_1770228027535.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ElevenLabs Valued $11B After $500M Funding, Eyes India Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ElevenLabs-Valued-11B-After-500M-Funding-Eyes-India-Growth/69838568f5a3f0ebac9ee149</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ElevenLabs-Valued-11B-After-500M-Funding-Eyes-India-Growth/69838568f5a3f0ebac9ee149</guid><description>Voice AI startup ElevenLabs secured $500 million in a Series D funding round, valuing the company at $11 billion. Led by Sequoia Capital, the investment more than triples its valuation from last year. This capital infusion will fuel expansion beyond text-to-speech into a full audio stack, including music and conversational AI. ElevenLabs also highlighted its significant growth in India, its largest global market, with plans to further invest in local research and operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:44:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69838568f5a3f0ebac9ee148_1770227184816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Oil Diversification: Geopolitics Expose Supply Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Oil-Diversification-Geopolitics-Expose-Supply-Vulnerabilities/69838513f5a3f0ebac9edfde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Oil-Diversification-Geopolitics-Expose-Supply-Vulnerabilities/69838513f5a3f0ebac9edfde</guid><description>Kremlin spokespersons state India's oil supplier diversification is routine, refuting claims by U.S. President Trump regarding a pivot from Russian to American and Venezuelan crude. Industry experts highlight significant technical and cost hurdles for India to replace Russian imports entirely. The geopolitical rhetoric, however, exposes India's substantial reliance on imported oil and underscores the potential for market volatility, recalling past price spikes when Russia altered export flows. Recent data shows a slight decrease in Indian imports of Russian crude, while US oil's share has grown.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MSWIL Navigates Copper Headwinds, Fuels EV Growth Post Q3 FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MSWIL-Navigates-Copper-Headwinds-Fuels-EV-Growth-Post-Q3-FY26/698384f3f5a3f0ebac9eded6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MSWIL-Navigates-Copper-Headwinds-Fuels-EV-Growth-Post-Q3-FY26/698384f3f5a3f0ebac9eded6</guid><description>Motherson Sumi Wiring India (MSWIL) posted robust revenue growth of 26% YoY to ₹2,887 crore in Q3 FY26. While copper inflation squeezed margins by ~2%, the company has price pass-throughs. MSWIL continues strategic investments in greenfield projects for EV/hybrid platforms, aiming for debt-free status and plant utilization within 2-3 quarters. Capex for FY26 is projected at ₹220 crore.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:42:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698384f3f5a3f0ebac9eded5_1770227008268.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Slashes Long-Haul Flights Amid Geopolitical Airspace Chaos</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Slashes-Long-Haul-Flights-Amid-Geopolitical-Airspace-Chaos/6983847cf5a3f0ebac9eb7ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Slashes-Long-Haul-Flights-Amid-Geopolitical-Airspace-Chaos/6983847cf5a3f0ebac9eb7ee</guid><description>IndiGo is drastically scaling back long-haul operations, suspending its Copenhagen route and significantly reducing flights to London and Manchester. The airline cites escalating geopolitical airspace concerns and severe airport congestion as the drivers, disrupting its leased Boeing 787-9 schedule and passenger reliability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>4baseCare Fuels AI Drive to Bridge Global Cancer Data Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/4baseCare-Fuels-AI-Drive-to-Bridge-Global-Cancer-Data-Gap/698383fff5a3f0ebac9e8749</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/4baseCare-Fuels-AI-Drive-to-Bridge-Global-Cancer-Data-Gap/698383fff5a3f0ebac9e8749</guid><description>Precision oncology startup 4baseCare has secured ₹90 crore in Series B funding, co-led by Ashish Kacholia and Lashit Sanghvi. The capital infusion targets expansion of its hospital-linked lab network and strengthening its AI-driven oncology digital twin platform, Oncotwin. This strategic move aims to address a significant global data diversity gap in cancer research and democratize access to advanced diagnostics for underserved patient populations worldwide.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:38:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698383fff5a3f0ebac9e8748_1770229150262.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Timken India's Profit Squeezed Amidst Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Timken-Indias-Profit-Squeezed-Amidst-Revenue-Growth/698383aaf5a3f0ebac9e8627</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Timken-Indias-Profit-Squeezed-Amidst-Revenue-Growth/698383aaf5a3f0ebac9e8627</guid><description>Timken India's third-quarter results showed a significant 30.3% year-on-year net profit decline to ₹54.5 crore, contrasting with a 14% revenue increase to ₹779.6 crore. This profitability squeeze was driven by an 8.8% drop in EBITDA and a compression in EBITDA margin to 13% from 16.2%. The company also appointed Michael Discenza as a Non-Executive Director. The stock closed relatively flat on February 4, 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:36:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698383aaf5a3f0ebac9e8626_1770230746466.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apollo Tyres: ₹5,810 Cr Expansion Signals Ambition Amidst Market Crosswinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Apollo-Tyres-5810-Cr-Expansion-Signals-Ambition-Amidst-Market-Crosswinds/6983838cf5a3f0ebac9e8564</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Apollo-Tyres-5810-Cr-Expansion-Signals-Ambition-Amidst-Market-Crosswinds/6983838cf5a3f0ebac9e8564</guid><description>Apollo Tyres is investing ₹5,810 crore to significantly expand its manufacturing capacity for passenger car and truck/bus radials by 2029. This aggressive move follows a robust third quarter ending December 31, 2025, where net profit surged 40% to ₹471 crore and revenue rose 12% to ₹7,743 crore. The expansion aims to meet projected market demand, though its funding mix and the company's valuation relative to peers warrant close observation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:36:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983838cf5a3f0ebac9e8563_1770229340835.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo, Air India rerouting flights amid geopolitical tension</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Air-India-rerouting-flights-amid-geopolitical-tension/69838330f5a3f0ebac9e83f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Air-India-rerouting-flights-amid-geopolitical-tension/69838330f5a3f0ebac9e83f9</guid><description>Indian carriers IndiGo and Air India have ceased using Iranian airspace, diverting long-haul flights to avoid geopolitical volatility. This operational pivot leads to extended flight times and higher fuel expenditures, forcing IndiGo to suspend certain routes and reduce frequencies. Air India is also monitoring the situation while employing alternative flight paths to destinations in the US, UK, and Europe. The shift underscores significant external operational constraints affecting the airlines' network efficiency and cost structures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:34:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69838330f5a3f0ebac9e83f8_1770229871947.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fink Dismisses AI Bubble, Eyes Massive India Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fink-Dismisses-AI-Bubble-Eyes-Massive-India-Growth/69838312f5a3f0ebac9e8310</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fink-Dismisses-AI-Bubble-Eyes-Massive-India-Growth/69838312f5a3f0ebac9e8310</guid><description>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink stated he does not believe an Artificial Intelligence bubble exists, instead identifying a lack of investment as the primary risk. He highlighted the transformative potential of AI across all sectors, citing Anthropic's Claude as an example of disruptive yet opportunity-creating technology. Fink, speaking alongside Reliance Chairman Mukesh Ambani in Mumbai, emphasized India's imminent 20-25 year growth phase, urging increased capital market investment to align with the nation's economic ascent.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:34:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69838312f5a3f0ebac9e830f_1770226517265.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MPS Acquires US Firm Unbound Medicine for $16.5M, Eyes Healthcare Tech Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MPS-Acquires-US-Firm-Unbound-Medicine-for-165M-Eyes-Healthcare-Tech-Expansion/69838298f5a3f0ebac9e81f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MPS-Acquires-US-Firm-Unbound-Medicine-for-165M-Eyes-Healthcare-Tech-Expansion/69838298f5a3f0ebac9e81f5</guid><description>MPS Limited, through its subsidiary MPS North America LLC, is acquiring US-based Unbound Medicine, Inc. for $16.5 million. This strategic move aims to expand MPS's footprint in the healthcare learning technology sector. Funding will be a blend of internal accruals, inter-company loans totalling $4.94 million, and a new INR 420 million term loan from ICICI Bank, alongside an equity infusion of $9.81 million.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:32:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69838298f5a3f0ebac9e81f4_1770229715253.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Marico Acquires Cosmix, Eyes D2C Wellness Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Marico-Acquires-Cosmix-Eyes-D2C-Wellness-Boom/69838260f5a3f0ebac9e8076</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Marico-Acquires-Cosmix-Eyes-D2C-Wellness-Boom/69838260f5a3f0ebac9e8076</guid><description>Marico Limited has acquired a 60% majority stake in direct-to-consumer (D2C) wellness brand Cosmix for ₹226 crore, valuing the startup at approximately ₹375 crore. This strategic move amplifies Marico's digital-first portfolio and taps into the rapidly growing Indian wellness and plant-based nutrition sectors. Cosmix, founded in 2019, is profitable and specializes in plant-based protein powders and superfood blends, aligning with increasing consumer demand for specialized health products. The acquisition follows Marico's recent purchase of the 4700BC popcorn brand and demonstrates a broader FMCG trend of acquiring agile startups to capture evolving market preferences.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:31:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69838260f5a3f0ebac9e8075_1770231665951.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cognizant's Fresher Surge: AI-Driven Efficiency Aims for Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cognizants-Fresher-Surge-AI-Driven-Efficiency-Aims-for-Margin-Gains/69838238f5a3f0ebac9e7f84</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cognizants-Fresher-Surge-AI-Driven-Efficiency-Aims-for-Margin-Gains/69838238f5a3f0ebac9e7f84</guid><description>Cognizant plans to hire 24,000-25,000 freshers in 2026, a 20% increase, to bolster its "broader pyramid" strategy and AI integration. This move aims to decouple revenue growth from headcount expansion, enhancing margin leverage. The company reported robust Q4 2025 results, with revenue up 4.9% and net income up 18.7%, while its stock trades around $77, with analysts largely holding a "Buy" consensus.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:30:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69838238f5a3f0ebac9e7f83_1770231182275.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Investment Era: Can Jio BlackRock Shift Deep-Rooted Savings?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Investment-Era-Can-Jio-BlackRock-Shift-Deep-Rooted-Savings/6983822bf5a3f0ebac9e7efa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Investment-Era-Can-Jio-BlackRock-Shift-Deep-Rooted-Savings/6983822bf5a3f0ebac9e7efa</guid><description>BlackRock Chairman Larry Fink forecasts India's GDP to grow 8-10% annually for the next decade, urging a shift from traditional savings in bank deposits, gold, and silver to capital markets. The Jio BlackRock joint venture aims to leverage technology to attract new investors, a critical but challenging endeavor given established saving behaviors. While industry AUM is growing, competition is fierce, and valuation metrics warrant careful monitoring amidst ambitious growth projections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:30:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983822bf5a3f0ebac9e7ef9_1770226354257.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC Orders SIT in RCom Fraud Probe, Anil Ambani Faces Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SC-Orders-SIT-in-RCom-Fraud-Probe-Anil-Ambani-Faces-Scrutiny/698381adf5a3f0ebac9e6626</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SC-Orders-SIT-in-RCom-Fraud-Probe-Anil-Ambani-Faces-Scrutiny/698381adf5a3f0ebac9e6626</guid><description>The Supreme Court has directed the Enforcement Directorate to establish a Special Investigation Team to probe allegations of extensive bank fraud linked to Reliance Communications (RCom) and its chairman, Anil Ambani. This escalation follows findings of over ₹40,000 crore in loans being potentially defrauded, with several accounts declared fraudulent. Anil Ambani faces travel restrictions as his counsel provided an undertaking to the apex court, while the CBI will investigate complicity among bank officials. The move intensifies scrutiny on the Reliance Group, which has already seen significant asset attachments by the ED.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:28:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698381adf5a3f0ebac9e6625_1770226351300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Probe: Regulatory Spotlight on Cancellations, Competitors Gain Ground</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Probe-Regulatory-Spotlight-on-Cancellations-Competitors-Gain-Ground/6983815ef5a3f0ebac9e484c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Probe-Regulatory-Spotlight-on-Cancellations-Competitors-Gain-Ground/6983815ef5a3f0ebac9e484c</guid><description>IndiGo is under a Competition Commission of India (CCI) investigation for potential artificial flight cancellations amidst significant operational disruptions in December. The airline's issues affected 9.82 lakh passengers, leading to ₹22.74 crore in compensation and a 9.65% cancellation rate, while competitors Air India Group, Akasa Air, and SpiceJet capitalized on the instability to grow their market presence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:26:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983815ef5a3f0ebac9e484b_1770231126469.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW Cement posts strong Q3, plans $39M UAE grinding unit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Cement-posts-strong-Q3-plans-39M-UAE-grinding-unit/69838146f5a3f0ebac9e3964</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Cement-posts-strong-Q3-plans-39M-UAE-grinding-unit/69838146f5a3f0ebac9e3964</guid><description>JSW Cement showcased robust financial performance in Q3 FY26, with revenue climbing 13% YoY to ₹1,621 crore and operating EBITDA surging 32% YoY to ₹285.1 crore. The company achieved a Profit After Tax (PAT) of ₹130.6 crore, a significant turnaround from the prior year's loss. Key strategic moves include establishing a 1.65 MTPA grinding unit in Fujairah, UAE, involving a USD 39 million capital expenditure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:26:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69838146f5a3f0ebac9e3963_1770232175746.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ganesh Consumer Products Q3 Profit Surges 57.6% on Margin Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ganesh-Consumer-Products-Q3-Profit-Surges-576percent-on-Margin-Boost/698380bdf5a3f0ebac9e2a3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ganesh-Consumer-Products-Q3-Profit-Surges-576percent-on-Margin-Boost/698380bdf5a3f0ebac9e2a3f</guid><description>Ganesh Consumer Products Limited (GCPL) reported a robust Q3 FY26, with net profit soaring 57.6% YoY to ₹121 Mn on a 37.0% EBITDA increase to ₹228 Mn. This profitability surge was fueled by a significant 315 bps expansion in EBITDA margins to 10.8%, driven by improved realisations and a strategic portfolio shift. Despite a 3.5% revenue dip in 9M FY26, the company highlights a debt-free status and ambitious B2C expansion plans into tier 2/3 cities and new states.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:24:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698380bdf5a3f0ebac9e2a3e_1770226006023.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auditor Flags Going Concern Risk for India Homes; Operations Ceased</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Risk-for-India-Homes-Operations-Ceased/6983808cf5a3f0ebac9e28c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Risk-for-India-Homes-Operations-Ceased/6983808cf5a3f0ebac9e28c8</guid><description>India Homes Limited, formerly India Steel Works, has disclosed a dire financial situation. Its auditor, Laxmikant Kabra &amp; Co LLP, has issued a qualified report, raising material uncertainty about the company's ability to continue as a going concern. Operations have reportedly ceased, current liabilities far exceed assets, and the company is unable to discharge its obligations. Significant inventory valuation issues and potential asset overstatements further compound the crisis, leading to a substantial net loss for the nine-month period.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:23:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983808cf5a3f0ebac9e28c7_1770231812104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Homes Reports Profit Amidst Grave Auditor Warnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/India-Homes-Reports-Profit-Amidst-Grave-Auditor-Warnings/6983806df5a3f0ebac9e279f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/India-Homes-Reports-Profit-Amidst-Grave-Auditor-Warnings/6983806df5a3f0ebac9e279f</guid><description>India Homes Limited reported a net profit of ₹29.42 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, a significant turnaround from a loss of ₹133.93 Lakhs in Q3 FY25. Total income rose 15.11% YoY to ₹142.97 Lakhs. However, the company's financial health is overshadowed by an adverse audit report detailing severe accounting deficiencies and raising material uncertainty about its ability to continue as a going concern.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:22:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983806df5a3f0ebac9e279e_1770231939956.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>