<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:25:22 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Adani Defence Boosts Air Works India Stake to 99.98% in MRO Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Defence-Boosts-Air-Works-India-Stake-to-9998percent-in-MRO-Consolidation/69a40323edbd0c0ef0196a0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Defence-Boosts-Air-Works-India-Stake-to-9998percent-in-MRO-Consolidation/69a40323edbd0c0ef0196a0a</guid><description>Adani Defence Systems &amp; Technologies Ltd (ADSTL) has acquired an additional 14.2% stake in Air Works India from Punj Lloyd Aviation Ltd (PLAL). This transaction raises ADSTL's total ownership in the aviation MRO firm to 99.98%, significantly consolidating its control. The move is part of Adani Group's strategy to bolster its defence and aerospace capabilities, integrating Air Works' extensive maintenance, repair, and overhaul services into its growing ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a40323edbd0c0ef0196a09_1772356500733.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Loans Surge: Higher LTVs Mask Borrower Volatility Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Loans-Surge-Higher-LTVs-Mask-Borrower-Volatility-Risk/69a3f9d3edbd0c0ef0196696</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Loans-Surge-Higher-LTVs-Mask-Borrower-Volatility-Risk/69a3f9d3edbd0c0ef0196696</guid><description>Gold loans are experiencing explosive growth, surpassing Rs 3.3 lakh crore, driven by geopolitical tensions and tighter unsecured lending norms. While the RBI's new tiered Loan-to-Value (LTV) ratios, effective April 2026, aim to boost credit access for smaller borrowers, this expansion into a volatile commodity market presents substantial risks. Borrowers face increased potential for rapid collateral auctions and financial distress if gold prices correct sharply, a factor often underestimated amid the allure of higher immediate liquidity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 08:33:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3f9d3edbd0c0ef0196695_1772354213081.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kia India Sets Record Sales Amidst Intense Auto Market Rivalry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Kia-India-Sets-Record-Sales-Amidst-Intense-Auto-Market-Rivalry/69a3f94bedbd0c0ef01965cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Kia-India-Sets-Record-Sales-Amidst-Intense-Auto-Market-Rivalry/69a3f94bedbd0c0ef01965cc</guid><description>Kia India achieved its highest-ever February sales, selling 27,610 units for a 10.3% year-over-year increase, driven by strong demand for models like the Seltos and Sonet. This performance underscores sustained customer confidence. However, the competitive Indian automotive landscape is intensifying, with rivals like Hyundai and Tata Motors posting significant growth. Kia Corporation, the parent company, maintains a moderate P/E ratio, suggesting investors are weighing localized success against broader industry dynamics and global challenges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 08:31:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3f94bedbd0c0ef01965cb_1772353980161.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW MG Motor India's Premium SUV Gambit Amidst 24% Sales Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-MG-Motor-Indias-Premium-SUV-Gambit-Amidst-24percent-Sales-Surge/69a3f8faedbd0c0ef019654e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-MG-Motor-Indias-Premium-SUV-Gambit-Amidst-24percent-Sales-Surge/69a3f8faedbd0c0ef019654e</guid><description>JSW MG Motor India posted a 24% year-on-year increase in February wholesales, reaching 4,957 units. This growth spans both internal combustion engine (ICE) and electric vehicle (EV) segments. The company also initiated pre-bookings for its new premium SUV, the MG MAJESTOR, signaling a strategic push into higher-margin segments. This move comes as the broader Indian automotive market experiences robust demand, with analysts forecasting continued growth driven by economic factors and new model introductions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 08:29:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3f8faedbd0c0ef019654d_1772353914600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eicher Motors Feb Sales Jump 11%; Invests ₹958 Cr for Royal Enfield Capacity Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Feb-Sales-Jump-11percent-Invests-958-Cr-for-Royal-Enfield-Capacity-Hike/69a3f2bbedbd0c0ef0196303</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Feb-Sales-Jump-11percent-Invests-958-Cr-for-Royal-Enfield-Capacity-Hike/69a3f2bbedbd0c0ef0196303</guid><description>Eicher Motors' iconic Royal Enfield brand posted an 11% year-on-year sales increase in February 2026, selling 1,00,905 motorcycles. To meet surging demand, the company has approved a significant ₹958 crore investment for brownfield expansion at its Cheyyar facility, aiming to boost annual production capacity from 14.6 lakh to 20 lakh units within 18 months.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 08:03:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3f2bbedbd0c0ef0196302_1772352330430.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Customs Duty Deferral Scheme: A Closer Look</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-New-Customs-Duty-Deferral-Scheme-A-Closer-Look/69a3ed4bedbd0c0ef01960f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-New-Customs-Duty-Deferral-Scheme-A-Closer-Look/69a3ed4bedbd0c0ef01960f1</guid><description>Starting April 1, 2026, India will implement the Eligible Manufacturer Importer (EMI) scheme, permitting approved businesses to defer customs duty payments monthly instead of upfront. This move aims to improve working capital and bolster domestic manufacturing. The scheme, valid until March 31, 2028, encourages businesses to achieve higher Authorized Economic Operator (AEO) status, while introducing potential fiscal risks for the government and favoring compliant, established entities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:39:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3ed4bedbd0c0ef01960f0_1772350877599.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor Feb Sales Surge 31%; International Biz Hits Record High</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Feb-Sales-Surge-31percent-International-Biz-Hits-Record-High/69a3eca9edbd0c0ef0196064</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Feb-Sales-Surge-31percent-International-Biz-Hits-Record-High/69a3eca9edbd0c0ef0196064</guid><description>TVS Motor Company reported a robust 31% year-on-year sales growth for February 2026, selling 529,308 units. The company achieved its highest-ever monthly sales in its international business segment, shipping 158,268 units. This strong performance was broad-based, with three-wheelers up 77% and electric vehicles seeing a 60% increase, underscoring continued demand across diverse segments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:37:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3eca9edbd0c0ef0196063_1772350742356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors PV Sales Feb'26: Volume Surges 57% on EV, IB Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-PV-Sales-Feb26-Volume-Surges-57percent-on-EV-IB-Strength/69a3e9d8edbd0c0ef0195f25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-PV-Sales-Feb26-Volume-Surges-57percent-on-EV-IB-Strength/69a3e9d8edbd0c0ef0195f25</guid><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd. reported a robust 57% year-on-year increase in total sales for February 2026, reaching 63,331 units. This growth was driven by strong performance in its international business (up 167%) and a significant 57% rise in electric vehicle sales. Domestic sales also showed solid momentum, climbing 34%. The company now operates under the new name, reflecting a strategic focus on its core passenger vehicle operations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:25:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e9d8edbd0c0ef0195f24_1772350039308.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vardhman Textiles Commences New Technical Textiles Plant in Baddi</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Vardhman-Textiles-Commences-New-Technical-Textiles-Plant-in-Baddi/69a3e777edbd0c0ef0195e28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Vardhman-Textiles-Commences-New-Technical-Textiles-Plant-in-Baddi/69a3e777edbd0c0ef0195e28</guid><description>Vardhman Textiles Limited has announced the commencement of commercial production at its new Technical Textiles Plant in Baddi, Himachal Pradesh, effective March 1, 2026. This facility is a significant addition, capable of producing 15 lakh meters of fabric monthly, marking a key step in the company's strategic capacity expansion plans first revealed in May 2024.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:15:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e777edbd0c0ef0195e27_1772349411336.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors Feb CV Sales Surge 32% on Strong Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Feb-CV-Sales-Surge-32percent-on-Strong-Demand/69a3e6a2edbd0c0ef0195d57</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Feb-CV-Sales-Surge-32percent-on-Strong-Demand/69a3e6a2edbd0c0ef0195d57</guid><description>Tata Motors Limited posted a robust 32% year-on-year growth in commercial vehicle sales for February 2026, selling 42,940 units. The strong performance was driven by a significant 32.8% increase in domestic sales and a 17.9% rise in international business, highlighting broad market demand.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:11:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e6a2edbd0c0ef0195d56_1772349196474.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FPIs Re-Enter India Equities: Sector Rotation Amid AI Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FPIs-Re-Enter-India-Equities-Sector-Rotation-Amid-AI-Fears/69a3e617edbd0c0ef0195ce4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FPIs-Re-Enter-India-Equities-Sector-Rotation-Amid-AI-Fears/69a3e617edbd0c0ef0195ce4</guid><description>Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) injected ₹22,615 crore into Indian equities in February, the highest monthly inflow in 17 months, signaling a turnaround from substantial 2025 outflows. This shift was propelled by an interim India-US trade agreement, corrected domestic valuations, and robust Q3 FY26 corporate earnings, which grew 14.7%. FPIs favored financials and capital goods while divesting from the IT sector amid AI disruption concerns. Market capitalization for Indian listed companies reached $5.001 trillion in January 2026, with the Nifty 50 P/E ratio around 22.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:09:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e617edbd0c0ef0195ce3_1772349104430.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki Sales: Exports Surge, UVs Shine, Compact Cars Lag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Sales-Exports-Surge-UVs-Shine-Compact-Cars-Lag/69a3e3beedbd0c0ef0195b0e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Sales-Exports-Surge-UVs-Shine-Compact-Cars-Lag/69a3e3beedbd0c0ef0195b0e</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki India's total sales for February 2026 rose 7.32% year-over-year to 213,995 units, propelled by a significant surge in exports (+56.5%) and strong utility vehicle (UV) demand. However, domestic passenger vehicle sales remained flat at 161,000 units, with a notable decline in the compact car segment contrasting sharply with UV performance. Hyundai Motor India posted a robust 12.6% growth, achieving its best-ever February sales, while Mahindra &amp; Mahindra saw 18% expansion driven by SUVs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:59:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e3beedbd0c0ef0195b0d_1772348556782.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India Hits Record February Sales Amid Market Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Hits-Record-February-Sales-Amid-Market-Boom/69a3e3bbedbd0c0ef0195af7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Hits-Record-February-Sales-Amid-Market-Boom/69a3e3bbedbd0c0ef0195af7</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India Limited (HMIL) achieved record-breaking total and domestic sales for February, selling 66,134 units. Domestic sales rose 9.8% to 52,407 units, while exports surged 24.8% to 13,727 units. This performance follows January's record-breaking month, underscoring HMIL's sustained sales momentum and its competitive edge in a booming Indian automotive sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e3bbedbd0c0ef0195af6_1772348474350.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India Hits Record Sales Amidst Sector Slowdown &amp; AI Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Hits-Record-Sales-Amidst-Sector-Slowdown-and-AI-Pivot/69a3e3b7edbd0c0ef0195ae0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Hits-Record-Sales-Amidst-Sector-Slowdown-and-AI-Pivot/69a3e3b7edbd0c0ef0195ae0</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India Ltd. (HMIL) achieved its highest-ever February sales in 2026, selling 66,134 units, a 12.6% year-on-year increase. Domestic sales grew 9.8% to 52,407 units, while exports surged 24.8% to 13,727 units. This performance contrasts with a projected slowdown in the broader Indian automotive sector, which anticipates a moderate 3-6% growth for FY2026-27. Furthermore, HMIL's parent, Hyundai Motor Company, is making substantial investments in AI and robotics, signaling a long-term strategic evolution beyond traditional automotive sales.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:59:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e3b7edbd0c0ef0195adf_1772348518604.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Feb Sales: 97,177 Units | Auto &amp; Tractor Growth Surges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Feb-Sales-97177-Units-Auto-and-Tractor-Growth-Surges/69a3d716edbd0c0ef0195730</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Feb-Sales-97177-Units-Auto-and-Tractor-Growth-Surges/69a3d716edbd0c0ef0195730</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra reported strong February 2026 sales, with total auto volumes up 18% YoY to 97,177 units, led by a 19% jump in domestic UV sales. The farm equipment sector also posted significant gains, with domestic tractor sales rising 35% YoY. These figures highlight robust demand across key segments, though management monitors external challenges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:05:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d716edbd0c0ef019572f_1772345208760.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mafatlal's Bold Pivot: "Uniforms to AI" Drive Record Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mafatlals-Bold-Pivot-Uniforms-to-AI-Drive-Record-Growth/69a3d5a6edbd0c0ef0195624</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mafatlals-Bold-Pivot-Uniforms-to-AI-Drive-Record-Growth/69a3d5a6edbd0c0ef0195624</guid><description>Mafatlal Industries, the flagship of the Arvind Mafatlal Group, is aggressively pivoting beyond its textile legacy, aiming for leadership in education, AI, and health/hygiene. The company has achieved record revenues, signaling a strong turnaround driven by both core textile operations and new ventures in future skills and hygiene products. This ambitious "uniforms to AI" strategy faces significant execution challenges, juxtaposing established manufacturing with nascent technology sectors in a bid to redefine the group's future.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:59:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d5a6edbd0c0ef0195623_1772344913565.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE IPO Proceeds as OFS, Regulatory Hurdle Blocks Self-Listing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-IPO-Proceeds-as-OFS-Regulatory-Hurdle-Blocks-Self-Listing/69a3d531edbd0c0ef019559f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-IPO-Proceeds-as-OFS-Regulatory-Hurdle-Blocks-Self-Listing/69a3d531edbd0c0ef019559f</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange (NSE) is preparing for its Initial Public Offering (IPO) after receiving a no-objection certificate from SEBI. However, Indian regulations will prevent the NSE from listing on its own platform, requiring an alternative exchange. The IPO will be structured solely as an Offer for Sale (OFS), meaning no new capital will be raised for the company; instead, existing shareholders will sell a portion of their holdings. This structure aims to provide liquidity to its approximately 195,000 shareholders and enhance corporate governance through public scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:57:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d531edbd0c0ef019559e_1772344790616.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Escorts Kubota Feb Sales Surge; Tractor Growth Leads</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Feb-Sales-Surge-Tractor-Growth-Leads/69a3d451edbd0c0ef01954e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Feb-Sales-Surge-Tractor-Growth-Leads/69a3d451edbd0c0ef01954e4</guid><description>Escorts Kubota reported robust February 2026 sales, with tractor volumes climbing 20.4% year-on-year to 10,339 units and construction equipment sales rising 4.8% to 588 units. The strong performance reflects positive rural sentiment and infrastructure project execution, signaling continued industry momentum, though past market share concerns persist.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:53:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d451edbd0c0ef01954e3_1772344493977.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GAIL Appoints Deepak Gupta as CMD from March 1, Leveraging 35+ Yrs Experience</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GAIL-Appoints-Deepak-Gupta-as-CMD-from-March-1-Leveraging-35-Yrs-Experience/69a3d3caedbd0c0ef019545e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GAIL-Appoints-Deepak-Gupta-as-CMD-from-March-1-Leveraging-35-Yrs-Experience/69a3d3caedbd0c0ef019545e</guid><description>Shri Deepak Gupta has taken charge as Chairman and Managing Director (CMD) of GAIL (India) Limited, effective March 1, 2026. With over 35 years of experience in the oil and gas sector, including his recent role as Director (Projects) at GAIL, Mr. Gupta is expected to steer the Maharatna PSU through India's energy transition. His appointment signifies a leadership transition at a critical juncture for the company, which operates an extensive natural gas and LPG pipeline network.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:51:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d3caedbd0c0ef019545d_1772344374240.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bijoy Hans Board to Decide on Promoter Reclassification on March 4</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Bijoy-Hans-Board-to-Decide-on-Promoter-Reclassification-on-March-4/69a3d260edbd0c0ef0195389</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Bijoy-Hans-Board-to-Decide-on-Promoter-Reclassification-on-March-4/69a3d260edbd0c0ef0195389</guid><description>Bijoy Hans Limited's Board of Directors will convene on March 4, 2026, to deliberate on a crucial request for reclassifying certain individuals from its promoter and promoter group to the public shareholder category. This move, aligned with SEBI Listing Regulations, could significantly alter the company's shareholding structure and free float.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d260edbd0c0ef0195388_1772344043347.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VOC Port's ₹15,000 Cr Outer Harbour: A Bid to Outpace Rivals?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/VOC-Ports-15000-Cr-Outer-Harbour-A-Bid-to-Outpace-Rivals/69a3cf1aedbd0c0ef0195245</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/VOC-Ports-15000-Cr-Outer-Harbour-A-Bid-to-Outpace-Rivals/69a3cf1aedbd0c0ef0195245</guid><description>VO Chidambaranar Port Authority is investing ₹15,000 crore in its Outer Harbour project to dramatically increase cargo handling capacity and position Tamil Nadu as a premier South Indian transshipment hub. This strategic move aims to compete directly with established international ports like Singapore and Colombo, driven by recent growth in cargo and container volumes. Funding is secured through a tripartite agreement with IRFC and Sagarmala Finance Corporation Limited, signaling a significant push towards modernizing infrastructure and attracting larger vessels.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:31:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3cf1aedbd0c0ef0195244_1772343188525.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market Cap Shrinks Amid AI Fears, Geopolitical Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Market-Cap-Shrinks-Amid-AI-Fears-Geopolitical-Woes/69a3c90bedbd0c0ef0195018</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Market-Cap-Shrinks-Amid-AI-Fears-Geopolitical-Woes/69a3c90bedbd0c0ef0195018</guid><description>India's largest companies experienced a significant erosion in market capitalization last week, with the combined value of nine top-10 firms dropping by approximately ₹2.18 lakh crore. The downturn was fueled by a confluence of geopolitical tensions, concerns over Artificial Intelligence impacting the IT sector, and increased interest rate sensitivity in banking stocks. Hindustan Unilever was a notable exception, bucking the bearish trend as a defensive consumer staple.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:05:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3c90bedbd0c0ef0195017_1772341730976.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Shockwaves Trigger Market Sell-off, Oil Surges to $100 Fear</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitical-Shockwaves-Trigger-Market-Sell-off-Oil-Surges-to-100-Fear/69a3ba7fedbd0c0ef0194c26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitical-Shockwaves-Trigger-Market-Sell-off-Oil-Surges-to-100-Fear/69a3ba7fedbd0c0ef0194c26</guid><description>Indian markets experienced a sharp decline on Friday, mirroring global sentiment as geopolitical tensions escalated over the weekend. The Nifty 50 fell below its 200-day moving average, signaling bearish momentum. Crude oil prices surged, with Barclays predicting a potential rise to $100 per barrel, creating significant headwinds for downstream refiners but benefiting upstream players like ONGC and Oil India. Companies with substantial Middle East exposure, including L&amp;T, Kalyan Jewellers, Welspun Corp, and KEC International, face heightened risks from regional retaliation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:03:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3ba7fedbd0c0ef0194c25_1772337945169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Risk Premium Hits Indian Aviation Hard</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Geopolitical-Risk-Premium-Hits-Indian-Aviation-Hard/69a3b734edbd0c0ef0194ac8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Geopolitical-Risk-Premium-Hits-Indian-Aviation-Hard/69a3b734edbd0c0ef0194ac8</guid><description>Escalating Middle East tensions and airspace closures have led to significant flight cancellations by Indian carriers, including IndiGo and Air India. Beyond immediate disruptions, the geopolitical conflict is exacerbating already thin airline margins through increased operational costs like fuel and rerouting. While government agencies monitor the situation, the aviation sector faces a sustained "geopolitical risk premium" affecting profitability and market valuations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 03:49:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3b734edbd0c0ef0194ac7_1772337069671.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPFO Poised to Hold 8.25% Interest Rate Amidst Market Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFO-Poised-to-Hold-825percent-Interest-Rate-Amidst-Market-Headwinds/69a3af38edbd0c0ef019487e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFO-Poised-to-Hold-825percent-Interest-Rate-Amidst-Market-Headwinds/69a3af38edbd0c0ef019487e</guid><description>The Employees' Provident Fund Organisation (EPFO) is anticipated to recommend maintaining its interest rate at 8.25% for the fiscal year 2026. This decision, expected from the Central Board of Trustees (CBT) meeting on March 2, comes despite muted government bond yields and a year where Indian equities underperformed global markets. EPFO's substantial corpus, coupled with an adequate surplus and strategic initiatives to diversify investments, underpins the confidence in sustaining this rate for a third consecutive year. The move is also influenced by the need to maintain employee sentiment ahead of upcoming state elections.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3af38edbd0c0ef019487d_1772335030890.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dividend Surge Signals Shareholder Focus Amidst Valuation Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dividend-Surge-Signals-Shareholder-Focus-Amidst-Valuation-Divergence/69a3a99dedbd0c0ef01946b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dividend-Surge-Signals-Shareholder-Focus-Amidst-Valuation-Divergence/69a3a99dedbd0c0ef01946b8</guid><description>As the financial year concludes, a wave of dividend declarations is set to reward shareholders across various Indian sectors. Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs) like Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL) and Bharat Electronics (BEL) are leading payouts, alongside entities in insurance and infrastructure. However, the scale of these payouts, coupled with significant valuation disparities among these companies, is prompting a closer look at the sustainability of such shareholder returns, especially for those trading at premium multiples.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:51:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3a99dedbd0c0ef01946b7_1772333633360.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerage Surge: 7 Indian Stocks Eye Double-Digit Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerage-Surge-7-Indian-Stocks-Eye-Double-Digit-Gains/69a3a1a7edbd0c0ef0192da6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerage-Surge-7-Indian-Stocks-Eye-Double-Digit-Gains/69a3a1a7edbd0c0ef0192da6</guid><description>A wave of positive analyst sentiment is driving significant upside targets for seven prominent Indian stocks. Brokerages like Jefferies, Motilal Oswal, and JM Financial have issued 'Buy' ratings, citing improving earnings visibility, market share gains, margin expansion, and technology-driven efficiencies. The chosen companies span critical sectors including banking, telecom, consumer durables, financial services, and hospitality, indicating broad confidence in the economic outlook.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:17:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3a1a7edbd0c0ef0192da5_1772331551635.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hormuz Flashpoint: India's Energy Reserves Tested Amid Asian Security Divide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Hormuz-Flashpoint-Indias-Energy-Reserves-Tested-Amid-Asian-Security-Divide/69a3984aedbd0c0ef0192b56</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Hormuz-Flashpoint-Indias-Energy-Reserves-Tested-Amid-Asian-Security-Divide/69a3984aedbd0c0ef0192b56</guid><description>Military actions near the Strait of Hormuz are heightening global energy market anxieties. While India activates contingency plans, bolstering reserves and exploring alternative routes, the event starkly reveals the varied energy security postures of Asian nations. Japan and South Korea remain highly vulnerable, contrasting with China's diversified approach and India's proactive measures, even as oil prices react to the escalating geopolitical premium.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:37:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3984aedbd0c0ef0192b55_1772329152992.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fear Overdrive: Market Dips Ignore Economic Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fear-Overdrive-Market-Dips-Ignore-Economic-Fundamentals/69a3922dedbd0c0ef019292b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fear-Overdrive-Market-Dips-Ignore-Economic-Fundamentals/69a3922dedbd0c0ef019292b</guid><description>A sensationalist report predicting AI-induced economic collapse due to job losses has spooked markets. However, economic analysis, supported by historical precedent, indicates AI's role as a productivity enhancer will ultimately increase aggregate income and consumption, not trigger a crisis. This disconnect between fear-driven narratives and economic reality may present buying opportunities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:11:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3922dedbd0c0ef019292a_1772327667589.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>March Market Volatility: Geopolitics &amp; Inflation Trump Seasonality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/March-Market-Volatility-Geopolitics-and-Inflation-Trump-Seasonality/69a3922aedbd0c0ef0192914</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/March-Market-Volatility-Geopolitics-and-Inflation-Trump-Seasonality/69a3922aedbd0c0ef0192914</guid><description>February's market turbulence extends into March 2026, fueled by escalating Middle East conflict and stubborn US inflation data, which diminishes hopes for immediate interest rate cuts. While historical seasonal patterns offer a statistical edge for Pidilite Industries, Cummins India, and AIA Engineering, the current macro-economic climate introduces significant, unpredictable risks. A stock-specific strategy is essential, but investors must navigate this volatile environment with heightened caution as external shocks may override established trends.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:11:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3922aedbd0c0ef0192913_1772327698039.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>