<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:42:57 +0000</pubDate><item><title>EPFO Plans ₹31 Trillion Equity Shift: Eyes Sectoral, Factor Indices</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/EPFO-Plans-31-Trillion-Equity-Shift-Eyes-Sectoral-Factor-Indices/6984e13ae769d12df1d3ad69</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/EPFO-Plans-31-Trillion-Equity-Shift-Eyes-Sectoral-Factor-Indices/6984e13ae769d12df1d3ad69</guid><description>India's EPFO, managing ₹31 trillion, is preparing a significant shift in its equity investment strategy. The fund manager aims to move beyond traditional Sensex and Nifty ETFs, exploring investments in sectoral, factor-based, and emerging industries like defence and rare earths. This diversification push follows a similar, unfruitful attempt in 2016 and could reallocate substantial capital.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Power's Mundra Loss Deepens Amidst PPA Negotiation Deadlock</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Tata-Powers-Mundra-Loss-Deepens-Amidst-PPA-Negotiation-Deadlock/6984df74e769d12df1d23497</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Tata-Powers-Mundra-Loss-Deepens-Amidst-PPA-Negotiation-Deadlock/6984df74e769d12df1d23497</guid><description>Tata Power's 4,000 MW Mundra plant incurred a substantial loss of approximately ₹800 crore in the first nine months of the fiscal year due to an extended six-month shutdown. This operational halt, during which no capacity charges were received while fixed costs persisted, significantly impacted consolidated profits. The plant's restart hinges on finalizing a new Power Purchase Agreement (PPA) with the Gujarat government, but negotiations are stalled over contract duration and the company's transition to greener energy sources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MSE's Liquidity Push Faces Uphill Battle Against Duopoly</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/MSEs-Liquidity-Push-Faces-Uphill-Battle-Against-Duopoly/6984df5ee769d12df1d233a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/MSEs-Liquidity-Push-Faces-Uphill-Battle-Against-Duopoly/6984df5ee769d12df1d233a1</guid><description>Metropolitan Stock Exchange (MSE) has relaunched its equity segment, implementing a liquidity enhancement scheme (LES) and upgraded systems to challenge the NSE-BSE duopoly. Bolstered by over ₹1,240 crore in recent funding from prominent brokers, MSE aims to attract participants through market maker incentives. However, early traction shows modest gains against the dominant market share of its rivals, with an evolving competitive landscape including NCDEX's planned entry into equities, all amidst cautious global investor sentiment and a volatile domestic market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Startup Policy Pivot to Deep Tech, Patient Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Policy-Pivot-to-Deep-Tech-Patient-Capital/6984de82e769d12df1d21b9a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Policy-Pivot-to-Deep-Tech-Patient-Capital/6984de82e769d12df1d21b9a</guid><description>India's government has substantially updated startup recognition policies, doubling the turnover threshold to ₹200 crore and establishing a new category for 'Deep Tech Startups' with an extended age limit to 20 years and a ₹300 crore turnover cap. This strategic pivot aims to nurture R&amp;D-intensive enterprises with long gestation periods and attract patient capital. The policy also extends recognition to cooperative societies, fostering grassroots innovation. These reforms target a more predictable, inclusive, and future-ready innovation ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vi's AGR Reckoning: Committee Decision Looms Amidst Network Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vis-AGR-Reckoning-Committee-Decision-Looms-Amidst-Network-Push/6984de6ee769d12df1d20de1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vis-AGR-Reckoning-Committee-Decision-Looms-Amidst-Network-Push/6984de6ee769d12df1d20de1</guid><description>India's telecom sector's total Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) dues exceed ₹1.77 lakh crore by FY25. Vodafone Idea (Vi) accounts for the largest share at ₹89,952 crore, with a government committee now reassessing its frozen dues. This comes as Vi initiates a $4.89 billion network expansion plan, aiming to regain competitiveness against market leaders Bharti Airtel and Reliance Jio, despite persistent financial strain and a negative P/E ratio.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sai Life Sciences Q3 Profit Surges 86%, Revenue Climbs 27% on Strong Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Q3-Profit-Surges-86percent-Revenue-Climbs-27percent-on-Strong-Growth/6984dc12e769d12df1d1e794</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Q3-Profit-Surges-86percent-Revenue-Climbs-27percent-on-Strong-Growth/6984dc12e769d12df1d1e794</guid><description>Sai Life Sciences reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 86% year-on-year to ₹100 Cr. Revenue from operations grew by a strong 27% to ₹556 Cr, driven by excellent performance in CRO and CDMO services, improved operational efficiencies, and strategic investments in AI and digital platforms. EBITDA also saw a significant 54% jump to ₹191 Cr, with margins expanding substantially. The nine-month period also showcased impressive growth, with PAT up 199% and revenue up 43%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Eyes LLP Shift for AIFs, Global Appeal vs. Local Comforts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Eyes-LLP-Shift-for-AIFs-Global-Appeal-vs-Local-Comforts/6984d9c4e769d12df1d19ab7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Eyes-LLP-Shift-for-AIFs-Global-Appeal-vs-Local-Comforts/6984d9c4e769d12df1d19ab7</guid><description>India is poised to amend the LLP Act, encouraging Alternative Investment Funds (AIFs) to transition from prevalent trust structures to Limited Liability Partnerships (LLPs). This move aims to streamline compliance, enhance transparency, and attract greater foreign capital, aligning Indian fund structures with global norms. While LLPs offer tax efficiency and limited liability, the shift may trade the privacy of trust structures for increased public disclosure, a key consideration for investors. The AIF sector in India has shown robust growth, with commitments reaching ₹15.74 trillion in December 2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Auto Components Poised for Global Surge on EU, US FTAs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Components-Poised-for-Global-Surge-on-EU-US-FTAs/6984d8c9e769d12df1d15bae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Components-Poised-for-Global-Surge-on-EU-US-FTAs/6984d8c9e769d12df1d15bae</guid><description>Union Minister Jitin Prasada declared India's auto component industry is at a defining inflection point. New Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) with the European Union and the United States are poised to reshape global sourcing and manufacturing. These pacts create a narrow, critical window for Indian suppliers to integrate deeply into global automotive value chains, positioning India as a preferred manufacturing and sourcing hub.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Budget: Strategic Tariffs Bolster Manufacturing Ahead of FTAs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Strategic-Tariffs-Bolster-Manufacturing-Ahead-of-FTAs/6984d76de769d12df1d14f81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Strategic-Tariffs-Bolster-Manufacturing-Ahead-of-FTAs/6984d76de769d12df1d14f81</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 introduces a strategic recalibration of customs duties, focusing on boosting domestic manufacturing competitiveness and resilience. The measures, explicitly framed as proactive steps ahead of anticipated Free Trade Agreements (FTAs), target critical sectors like renewable energy, electric vehicles, defense, and MSMEs. This policy shift prioritizes long-term industrial strength over immediate revenue implications, preparing Indian industries to vie in global markets while navigating evolving trade headwinds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Greenlights Blackstone Stake; Federal Bank Posts Strong Q3 Amid Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Greenlights-Blackstone-Stake-Federal-Bank-Posts-Strong-Q3-Amid-Valuation-Scrutiny/6984d432e769d12df1d0d606</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Greenlights-Blackstone-Stake-Federal-Bank-Posts-Strong-Q3-Amid-Valuation-Scrutiny/6984d432e769d12df1d0d606</guid><description>Federal Bank has received Reserve Bank of India approval for Asia II Topco XIII Pte. Ltd. (an affiliate of Blackstone) to acquire up to 9.99% of its paid-up share capital. This strategic investment follows robust third-quarter results where the bank's net profit rose 9% to ₹1,041 crore and Net Interest Income grew 9% to ₹2,653 crore, both exceeding analyst expectations. Asset quality improved sequentially, with Gross NPAs decreasing to 1.72%. Despite these positive indicators and recent stock highs, Federal Bank shares closed marginally down 0.12% on February 5, 2026, amidst broader market and sector-specific valuation discussions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Viyash Scientific Q3: Consolidated PAT Surges, Standalone Earnings Dip Amid Amalgamation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Viyash-Scientific-Q3-Consolidated-PAT-Surges-Standalone-Earnings-Dip-Amid-Amalgamation/6984d41de769d12df1d0d56e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Viyash-Scientific-Q3-Consolidated-PAT-Surges-Standalone-Earnings-Dip-Amid-Amalgamation/6984d41de769d12df1d0d56e</guid><description>Viyash Scientific reported mixed Q3 FY26 results. Consolidated PAT jumped 33.6% YoY to ₹273.70 crore, driven by strong revenue growth. However, standalone PAT fell 19.6% to ₹400.60 crore, and consolidated EPS declined YoY due to increased share count post-amalgamation. Significant exceptional costs of ₹412.60 crore were incurred for the Composite Scheme of Amalgamation, which also led to prior period restatements.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ola Electric Challenges Musk on Battery Tech; EV Race Heats Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Challenges-Musk-on-Battery-Tech-EV-Race-Heats-Up/6984d3c0e769d12df1d0d418</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Challenges-Musk-on-Battery-Tech-EV-Race-Heats-Up/6984d3c0e769d12df1d0d418</guid><description>Ola Electric asserts its dry electrode battery manufacturing process is fully operational, powering its electric scooters. This claim directly counters Tesla CEO Elon Musk's recent assessment of the technology's scalability challenges. The development underscores the intensifying race for cost-effective battery production, with dry electrode technology offering significant potential for reduced manufacturing costs and environmental impact.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DEE Development Engineers Posts Stellar Q3 YoY Growth, Flags Rs 4.2 Cr Labor Code Hit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DEE-Development-Engineers-Posts-Stellar-Q3-YoY-Growth-Flags-Rs-42-Cr-Labor-Code-Hit/6984d3a3e769d12df1d0d334</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DEE-Development-Engineers-Posts-Stellar-Q3-YoY-Growth-Flags-Rs-42-Cr-Labor-Code-Hit/6984d3a3e769d12df1d0d334</guid><description>DEE Development Engineers reported a strong Q3 FY26, with revenue soaring 77% YoY to ₹286.7 Cr and PAT jumping 308.2% to ₹18.6 Cr. Growth was propelled by core segments like Process Piping and Heavy Fabrications. The company also highlighted improved leverage ratios and a robust order book of ₹1303 Cr, with a new seamless pipe plant set to commence operations. However, results were adjusted for a ₹4.2 Cr one-time labor code liability, causing a marginal QoQ EBITDA dip.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>VIL Debt Crisis: Dues Reassessment Sparks Sector Realignments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/VIL-Debt-Crisis-Dues-Reassessment-Sparks-Sector-Realignments/6984d32ae769d12df1d0d1d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/VIL-Debt-Crisis-Dues-Reassessment-Sparks-Sector-Realignments/6984d32ae769d12df1d0d1d3</guid><description>A committee is reassessing Vodafone Idea's (VIL) frozen AGR dues, a critical juncture for the debt-laden operator. While VIL grapples with over ₹2 lakh crore in total debt and a negative net worth, its financially robust competitors, Bharti Airtel and Reliance Jio, continue to dominate the Indian telecom market. The outcome of VIL's debt reassessment and its ability to secure essential funding are paramount, potentially reshaping the industry's competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Air India Fleet Woes Spark DGCA Scrutiny, Peer Impact Assessed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Fleet-Woes-Spark-DGCA-Scrutiny-Peer-Impact-Assessed/6984d264e769d12df1d0d027</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Fleet-Woes-Spark-DGCA-Scrutiny-Peer-Impact-Assessed/6984d264e769d12df1d0d027</guid><description>Government data reveals a significant portion of the Air India Group's analyzed fleet, nearly 72%, exhibits recurring defects. This revelation has led to intensified surveillance by the Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA), which is also expanding its technical workforce. While IndiGo and SpiceJet also reported instances of fleet issues, the scale of Air India's findings highlights potential systemic operational challenges and increased regulatory pressure across the Indian aviation industry.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp's EV Bet: Strong Q3 Masks Long-Term Valuation Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorps-EV-Bet-Strong-Q3-Masks-Long-Term-Valuation-Debate/6984d240e769d12df1d0cf50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorps-EV-Bet-Strong-Q3-Masks-Long-Term-Valuation-Debate/6984d240e769d12df1d0cf50</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp posted strong Q3 FY26 results with net profit up 14.4% to ₹1,267.55 crore and revenue growing 21.7% to ₹12,486.82 crore. The company approved an additional ₹275 crore investment in electric vehicle maker Euler Motors and a solar power project. Despite these positive developments, the stock closed down 1.51% on February 5, 2026. This suggests investors are weighing the immediate financial gains against the execution and profitability of its ambitious electric mobility and sustainability strategies amidst a competitive market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PhysicsWallah Soars: Q3 Revenue Jumps 33.7%, Eyes K-12 Expansion.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PhysicsWallah-Soars-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-337percent-Eyes-K-12-Expansion/6984d1f4e769d12df1d0cddc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PhysicsWallah-Soars-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-337percent-Eyes-K-12-Expansion/6984d1f4e769d12df1d0cddc</guid><description>PhysicsWallah (PWL) reported a strong Q3 FY26, with revenue climbing 33.7% YoY to ₹10,824 million and Adjusted EBITDA up 33.7% YoY to ₹3,512 million. For 9M FY26, revenue grew 31% to ₹29,807 million, surpassing full FY25. The company is strategically expanding into K-12 and non-Hindi regions, investing heavily in AI, and reported a robust treasury balance of ₹50,544 million. Profit After Tax for 9M FY26 was ₹450 million, impacted by ₹236 million in one-time expenses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sebi Bans 15 in Unison Metals Manipulation Scheme</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Bans-15-in-Unison-Metals-Manipulation-Scheme/6984d1d6e769d12df1d0cd1d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Bans-15-in-Unison-Metals-Manipulation-Scheme/6984d1d6e769d12df1d0cd1d</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) has penalized 15 individuals with a three-year market ban and Rs 3.6 crore in fines for orchestrating a 'pump and dump' scheme involving Unison Metals Ltd. (UML) shares. An additional Rs 3.87 crore was ordered to be disgorged by 10 entities. The manipulation reportedly occurred through misleading recommendations circulated on Telegram channels, artificially inflating stock prices and volumes to the detriment of retail investors. This action underscores the ongoing challenge regulators face in combating digital-driven market manipulation, particularly in the small-cap segment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trent Stock Jumps as Margin Gains Outweigh Growth Slowdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Stock-Jumps-as-Margin-Gains-Outweigh-Growth-Slowdown/6984d1a2e769d12df1d0cc37</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Stock-Jumps-as-Margin-Gains-Outweigh-Growth-Slowdown/6984d1a2e769d12df1d0cc37</guid><description>Trent's third-quarter performance showed slower same-store and like-for-like growth, but margins expanded significantly, with Ebitda rising 194 basis points. Aggressive store network expansion, particularly for Zudio, bolstered revenue by 16%. Analysts largely view the growth concerns as priced in, with a majority recommending a 'buy' and setting an average target price above the current trading level.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Expands Startup Definition, Bolstering Deep Tech and Co-ops</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-Expands-Startup-Definition-Bolstering-Deep-Tech-and-Co-ops/6984d059e769d12df1d0bcf7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-Expands-Startup-Definition-Bolstering-Deep-Tech-and-Co-ops/6984d059e769d12df1d0bcf7</guid><description>India has significantly revised its startup recognition criteria. The turnover threshold has been doubled to ₹200 crore, and a new 'Deep Tech Startup' category has been introduced with a ₹300 crore turnover limit and a 20-year recognition period. Cooperative enterprises are now also eligible for startup status, aimed at supporting grassroots innovation in sectors like agriculture. These changes address the evolving nature of the Indian startup ecosystem, characterized by longer innovation cycles and higher capital intensity, particularly in R&amp;D-driven sectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sai Life Sciences PAT Surges 86% on Strong Revenue Growth, Flags ₹83M One-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-PAT-Surges-86percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth-Flags-83M-One-Off/6984d00ee769d12df1d0bbe4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-PAT-Surges-86percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth-Flags-83M-One-Off/6984d00ee769d12df1d0bbe4</guid><description>Sai Life Sciences reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated PAT soaring 86.39% YoY to ₹1,003.75 million on a 26.53% revenue increase to ₹5,564.64 million. Nine-month PAT jumped 198.33% YoY. The company recognized an ₹82.93 million one-off loss related to new Labour Codes, classified as non-recurring. Diluted EPS grew substantially, and auditors issued an unmodified conclusion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TRAI Spam Crackdown: Operator Compliance Costs Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/TRAI-Spam-Crackdown-Operator-Compliance-Costs-Rise/6984cfe8e769d12df1d0bae4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/TRAI-Spam-Crackdown-Operator-Compliance-Costs-Rise/6984cfe8e769d12df1d0bae4</guid><description>The Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI) has disconnected approximately 21 lakh telecom connections to combat unsolicited commercial communications (UCC). This intensified crackdown, bolstered by February 2025 regulatory amendments, imposes significant operational and financial burdens on telecom service providers (TSPs). While aimed at consumer protection, the move raises concerns about increased compliance costs and potential impacts on TSPs' growth strategies amidst an already consolidated market landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sai Life Sciences Posts Stellar Q3: PAT Soars 86% YoY on 26.5% Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Posts-Stellar-Q3-PAT-Soars-86percent-YoY-on-265percent-Revenue-Surge/6984cf69e769d12df1d0b969</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Posts-Stellar-Q3-PAT-Soars-86percent-YoY-on-265percent-Revenue-Surge/6984cf69e769d12df1d0b969</guid><description>Sai Life Sciences announced strong Q3 FY2025 results, with consolidated PAT jumping 86.39% YoY to ₹1,003.75 million on a 26.53% revenue increase to ₹5,564.64 million. Nine-month consolidated PAT soared 198.33% YoY. The company also recognized an ₹82.93 million one-off loss related to new Labour Codes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Bets Big on EVs and Solar Amidst Steady Earnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Bets-Big-on-EVs-and-Solar-Amidst-Steady-Earnings/6984cf30e769d12df1d0b81a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Bets-Big-on-EVs-and-Solar-Amidst-Steady-Earnings/6984cf30e769d12df1d0b81a</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp posted third-quarter results exceeding revenue and EBITDA expectations, though slightly missing net profit forecasts. Revenue climbed 20.7% year-over-year to ₹12,328.3 crore, with EBITDA rising 22.6% to ₹1,809.9 crore. The company declared a ₹110 per share interim dividend and committed ₹275 crore to Euler Motors, signaling a strategic push into electric mobility. Significant investments in solar power projects for its plants underscore a growing commitment to sustainability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Stove Kraft Q3 PAT Plunges 66% Amid Export Woes, Eyes IKEA Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stove-Kraft-Q3-PAT-Plunges-66percent-Amid-Export-Woes-Eyes-IKEA-Boost/6984cf10e769d12df1d0b74f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stove-Kraft-Q3-PAT-Plunges-66percent-Amid-Export-Woes-Eyes-IKEA-Boost/6984cf10e769d12df1d0b74f</guid><description>Stove Kraft reported a sharp 66.6% year-on-year drop in Q3 FY26 net profit to ₹4.1 crore, impacted by a 6.4% revenue decline due to muted export sales amid global headwinds and US tariffs. Despite this, domestic business remained robust, contributing 96% of sales. The company is strategically expanding its retail network, advancing its IKEA partnership expected to yield revenue from FY27, and making significant progress towards a cash debt-free status by March 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:10:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Michael Burry Warns: Bitcoin's Death Spiral Accelerates, Threatens Gold</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Michael-Burry-Warns-Bitcoins-Death-Spiral-Accelerates-Threatens-Gold/6984cef6e769d12df1d0b6a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Michael-Burry-Warns-Bitcoins-Death-Spiral-Accelerates-Threatens-Gold/6984cef6e769d12df1d0b6a9</guid><description>Michael Burry, known for predicting the 2008 crisis, has issued a dire warning about Bitcoin. He stated the cryptocurrency has been exposed as a purely speculative asset, failing as a hedge against inflation. Burry cautioned that a further 10% drop could trigger massive losses for corporate holders and impact precious metals markets. Bitcoin has already fallen over 40% from its October peak, erasing gains since late 2024.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dalmia Sugar Profits Soar 17% on Margins, Revenue Dips 17% in Q3</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Dalmia-Sugar-Profits-Soar-17percent-on-Margins-Revenue-Dips-17percent-in-Q3/6984ce79e769d12df1d0b57f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Dalmia-Sugar-Profits-Soar-17percent-on-Margins-Revenue-Dips-17percent-in-Q3/6984ce79e769d12df1d0b57f</guid><description>Dalmia Bharat Sugar reported a mixed Q3 FY26. While consolidated revenue declined 17% YoY to Rs. 698 Cr, operating EBITDA rose 8% to Rs. 109 Cr, boosting EBITDA margins to 16% from 12% a year ago. Profit After Tax (PAT) jumped 17% YoY to Rs. 70 Cr, with EPS at Rs. 8.59. The company is expanding distillery capacity and venturing into Compressed Bio Gas (CBG), signalling diversification, while declaring an interim dividend of Rs. 4.50 per share.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India CPI Revamp: New Basket Signals Less Volatile, Higher Inflation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-CPI-Revamp-New-Basket-Signals-Less-Volatile-Higher-Inflation/6984ce33e769d12df1d0b46c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-CPI-Revamp-New-Basket-Signals-Less-Volatile-Higher-Inflation/6984ce33e769d12df1d0b46c</guid><description>India's Consumer Price Index (CPI) has undergone a significant overhaul, shifting its base year to 2024 from 2011-12 and redefining its basket of goods and services. This recalibration, based on the latest Household Consumption Expenditure Survey, aims to better reflect current household spending patterns by reducing the weight of volatile food items and increasing the emphasis on housing and services. Experts estimate this will lead to less volatile, though potentially marginally higher, inflation readings, influencing monetary policy and economic analysis.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:06:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Q3 Loss: JLR Cyberattack Dominates, Domestic Strength Offers Contrast</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Q3-Loss-JLR-Cyberattack-Dominates-Domestic-Strength-Offers-Contrast/6984ce0de769d12df1d0b36e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Q3-Loss-JLR-Cyberattack-Dominates-Domestic-Strength-Offers-Contrast/6984ce0de769d12df1d0b36e</guid><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles incurred a consolidated loss of ₹3,486 crore in Q3 FY26, primarily driven by Jaguar Land Rover's severe production disruptions following a cyberattack, which led to a 39% revenue drop for JLR. Despite this, the company's domestic business saw a robust 25% revenue increase, yet the overall financial health was strained by negative cash flow and rising net debt. The situation highlights JLR's significant drag against the resilience of the Indian market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:06:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KNR Constructions Posts 90% Profit Drop, Eyes ₹15,432 Cr Asset Sale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-Posts-90percent-Profit-Drop-Eyes-15432-Cr-Asset-Sale/6984cd91e769d12df1d0b20c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-Posts-90percent-Profit-Drop-Eyes-15432-Cr-Asset-Sale/6984cd91e769d12df1d0b20c</guid><description>KNR Constructions reported a dismal Q3 FY26 with standalone revenue down 21% YoY to ₹5,850.6 million and Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeting 90% YoY to ₹176.3 million. EBITDA margins compressed sharply from 20.4% to 5.2%. The company announced a strategic ₹15,432 million asset monetization plan by selling four SPVs to Indus Infra Trust, aiming to unlock value amidst the performance downturn. A new ₹3,192 million bridge project LOA was also secured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Declares Rs 110 Dividend, Boosts EV Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Declares-Rs-110-Dividend-Boosts-EV-Stake/6984cd12e769d12df1d0b0b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Declares-Rs-110-Dividend-Boosts-EV-Stake/6984cd12e769d12df1d0b0b1</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp's board approved Q3 FY26 results and declared a substantial interim dividend of Rs 110 per share. The company also boosted its EV market push with a Rs 275 crore investment in Euler Motors, increasing its stake to approximately 36%. Additional funds will support renewable energy projects, signaling a strategic focus on electrification and sustainability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HealthCare Global Revenue Surges, Profit Tumbles Amidst Rising Debt Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HealthCare-Global-Revenue-Surges-Profit-Tumbles-Amidst-Rising-Debt-Concerns/6984cc9de769d12df1d0af64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HealthCare-Global-Revenue-Surges-Profit-Tumbles-Amidst-Rising-Debt-Concerns/6984cc9de769d12df1d0af64</guid><description>HealthCare Global Enterprises (HCG) reported a 13% YoY revenue jump to INR 6,331 million in Q3FY26, with EBITDA up 20%. However, Adjusted PAT declined sharply to INR 6 million from INR 70 million a year ago, driven by higher depreciation, interest costs, and a prior-year corporate restructuring benefit. Net debt rose to INR 16,337 million, and interest cover fell to a critical ~1.28x. The North Bangalore Greenfield Hospital is slated for Q4FY26 operation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dalmia Bharat Sugar Posts Robust Q3 Profit Jump, Declares Rs 4.5 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Dalmia-Bharat-Sugar-Posts-Robust-Q3-Profit-Jump-Declares-Rs-45-Dividend/6984cc21e769d12df1d0ae61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Dalmia-Bharat-Sugar-Posts-Robust-Q3-Profit-Jump-Declares-Rs-45-Dividend/6984cc21e769d12df1d0ae61</guid><description>Dalmia Bharat Sugar and Industries Limited reported a strong third quarter for FY26, with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 38.27% YoY to ₹69.56 Crore, despite a 28.65% drop in Revenue from Operations to ₹597.75 Crore. For the nine-month period, however, PAT declined 20.76% YoY to ₹132.14 Crore on revenue growth of 24.55%. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹4.50 per share and approved significant capital expenditure for a Compressed Bio-Gas project and steam saving initiative.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashiana Housing Buys Pune Land for Senior Living Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ashiana-Housing-Buys-Pune-Land-for-Senior-Living-Project/6984cbb1e769d12df1d0ac9f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ashiana-Housing-Buys-Pune-Land-for-Senior-Living-Project/6984cbb1e769d12df1d0ac9f</guid><description>Ashiana Housing Ltd. has acquired a substantial 8.83-acre land parcel in Pune, Maharashtra, for an outright purchase. The company plans to develop a Senior Living project on this land, targeting an estimated saleable area of 4.50 lakh square feet. This strategic move signifies Ashiana Housing's commitment to expanding its footprint in the rapidly growing senior living market in India, bolstering its future project pipeline and revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Declares Huge ₹110 Dividend, Invests ₹275 Cr in EV Firm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Declares-Huge-110-Dividend-Invests-275-Cr-in-EV-Firm/6984cbabe769d12df1d0ac54</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Declares-Huge-110-Dividend-Invests-275-Cr-in-EV-Firm/6984cbabe769d12df1d0ac54</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp's Board approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and 9MFY25-26, though detailed figures were not disclosed in this announcement. The company declared a substantial interim dividend of ₹110 per share (5,500%). Strategically, it approved an additional ₹275 crore investment in EV player Euler Motors Private Limited, alongside solar power wheeling projects. Mr. Prabhat Singh was appointed Company Secretary.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sebi Proposes Smoother Exits for Alternative Funds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sebi-Proposes-Smoother-Exits-for-Alternative-Funds/6984cb51e769d12df1d0aaf9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sebi-Proposes-Smoother-Exits-for-Alternative-Funds/6984cb51e769d12df1d0aaf9</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) is proposing significant changes to the exit process for Alternative Investment Funds (AIFs). The reforms aim to streamline winding-up procedures by allowing AIFs to retain limited funds for operational expenses beyond their permitted fund life for up to three years. Additionally, AIFs with no active investments or funds but facing potential future inflows from litigation or tax matters may seek 'inoperative' status. These proposals seek to balance operational efficiency for fund managers with investor protection, requiring investor consent for certain liabilities. Public comments are due by February 26.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pearson CEO: AI Ready? No Nation, India Faces Critical Skill Shortage</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Pearson-CEO-AI-Ready-No-Nation-India-Faces-Critical-Skill-Shortage/6984cb3ce769d12df1d0a9d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Pearson-CEO-AI-Ready-No-Nation-India-Faces-Critical-Skill-Shortage/6984cb3ce769d12df1d0a9d8</guid><description>Pearson Global CEO Omar Abbosh stated no country is prepared for AI's job impact, highlighting India's severe skill gaps. Vocational shortages and hiring disruptions due to AI-driven resumes and screenings create a "signalling failure," costing economies trillions annually and hindering inclusive growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dalmia Bharat Sugar Posts Q3 Profit Jump, Declares ₹4.50 Dividend Amid Revenue Drop</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Dalmia-Bharat-Sugar-Posts-Q3-Profit-Jump-Declares-450-Dividend-Amid-Revenue-Drop/6984cb31e769d12df1d0a971</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Dalmia-Bharat-Sugar-Posts-Q3-Profit-Jump-Declares-450-Dividend-Amid-Revenue-Drop/6984cb31e769d12df1d0a971</guid><description>Dalmia Bharat Sugar reported a 17.3% year-on-year rise in Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹69.56 Cr for Q3 FY26, even as revenues declined 28.6% to ₹697.75 Cr. EBITDA grew 13.6% with margins improving to 21.1%. However, for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, PAT fell 20.8% to ₹132.14 Cr on a 24.6% revenue increase. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹4.50 per share and approved ₹107 Cr in capital expenditure for biogas and efficiency projects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Declares Rs 110 Dividend, Invests Rs 275 Cr in EV Entity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Declares-Rs-110-Dividend-Invests-Rs-275-Cr-in-EV-Entity/6984cae7e769d12df1d0a81d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Declares-Rs-110-Dividend-Invests-Rs-275-Cr-in-EV-Entity/6984cae7e769d12df1d0a81d</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp's Board approved a substantial interim dividend of Rs 110 per share for FY26. The company also greenlit an additional Rs 275 crore investment in EV firm Euler Motors Private Limited and significant capital allocation for solar power projects across its facilities to boost renewable energy adoption. Mr. Prabhat Singh was appointed Company Secretary.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Depositories Face Scrutiny After NSDL Glitch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Depositories-Face-Scrutiny-After-NSDL-Glitch/6984cacde769d12df1d0a764</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Depositories-Face-Scrutiny-After-NSDL-Glitch/6984cacde769d12df1d0a764</guid><description>National Securities Depository Ltd. (NSDL) expects to clear all delayed equity trades by Thursday night following a technical network issue. This incident, which disrupted inter-depository settlement flows and delayed securities crediting, highlights ongoing concerns about the robustness of India's financial market infrastructure. The event intensifies regulatory focus on cybersecurity and business continuity planning for key entities like NSDL and its competitor, CDSL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>