<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 21:14:57 +0000</pubDate><item><title>PM Surya Ghar Scheme Gets Major Boost! New Plan to Speed Up Rooftop Solar in 1 Crore Homes - Will It Hit Target?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/PM-Surya-Ghar-Scheme-Gets-Major-Boost-New-Plan-to-Speed-Up-Rooftop-Solar-in-1-Crore-Homes-Will-It-Hit-Target/695182b64342f77179db2c41</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/PM-Surya-Ghar-Scheme-Gets-Major-Boost-New-Plan-to-Speed-Up-Rooftop-Solar-in-1-Crore-Homes-Will-It-Hit-Target/695182b64342f77179db2c41</guid><description>India's PM Surya Ghar Muft Bijli Yojana aims for 1 crore rooftop solar installations by FY27, but only 25 lakh homes are covered. A new utility-led model where discoms install systems for households is expected to accelerate progress. Parliament's energy committee highlighted slow adoption due to lack of awareness and states/discoms needing to participate more actively.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:12:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695182b64342f77179db2c40_1766949626591.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bandhan Bank Sells Rs 3,212 Crore Bad Loans to ARCIL: A Major Balance Sheet Clean-Up Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bandhan-Bank-Sells-Rs-3212-Crore-Bad-Loans-to-ARCIL-A-Major-Balance-Sheet-Clean-Up-Unveiled/695182054342f77179db2b49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bandhan-Bank-Sells-Rs-3212-Crore-Bad-Loans-to-ARCIL-A-Major-Balance-Sheet-Clean-Up-Unveiled/695182054342f77179db2b49</guid><description>Bandhan Bank has successfully sold a portfolio of microfinance non-performing loans (NPLs) valued at ₹3,212 crore to Asset Reconstruction Company (India) Limited (ARCIL) for approximately ₹578 crore. This strategic move, executed via a Swiss Challenge process where ARCIL was the sole qualified bidder, aims to significantly reduce the bank's gross Non-Performing Assets (NPAs). The sale addresses the ongoing stress in the microfinance segment, which has impacted the bank's asset quality. Bandhan Bank is also initiating a separate sale of another ₹3,720 crore loan portfolio.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:08:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695182054342f77179db2b48_1766949783095.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks Plea to RBI: Extend Crucial Export Relief! Will Exporters Get More Breathing Room?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Banks-Plea-to-RBI-Extend-Crucial-Export-Relief-Will-Exporters-Get-More-Breathing-Room/695181fb4342f77179db2b1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Banks-Plea-to-RBI-Extend-Crucial-Export-Relief-Will-Exporters-Get-More-Breathing-Room/695181fb4342f77179db2b1e</guid><description>Banks are asking the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to prolong trade relief measures, including loan moratoriums, for exporters beyond December 31. These measures, introduced to help exporters facing delays and tariff impacts, are crucial for sectors like marine products. While current uptake is modest, banks believe extending the scheme by another quarter is vital for continued support against global trade uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:08:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695181fb4342f77179db2b1d_1766949626150.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Cinema's Box Office Roars Back: 12% Surge in Collections as Audiences Embrace Strong Storylines!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indian-Cinemas-Box-Office-Roars-Back-12percent-Surge-in-Collections-as-Audiences-Embrace-Strong-Storylines/695175be4342f77179db1c32</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indian-Cinemas-Box-Office-Roars-Back-12percent-Surge-in-Collections-as-Audiences-Embrace-Strong-Storylines/695175be4342f77179db1c32</guid><description>The Indian film industry experienced a robust 12% growth in net box-office collections in 2025, reaching ₹10,453 crore, with Hindi films alone seeing a 20% rise. Audiences are now prioritizing compelling stories and diverse genres over star power and film length. Mid-budget, content-led films are increasingly outperforming big-ticket releases, indicating a demand for value-for-money entertainment. Hollywood films also saw significant growth in India.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 18:16:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695175be4342f77179db1c31_1766946313569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rights Issues Hit 28-Year Peak Amid Market Plunge &amp; Sebi Shake-Up! QIPs Plummet - What Investors Need to Know Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rights-Issues-Hit-28-Year-Peak-Amid-Market-Plunge-and-Sebi-Shake-Up-QIPs-Plummet-What-Investors-Need-to-Know-Now/69516eaa4342f77179db179f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rights-Issues-Hit-28-Year-Peak-Amid-Market-Plunge-and-Sebi-Shake-Up-QIPs-Plummet-What-Investors-Need-to-Know-Now/69516eaa4342f77179db179f</guid><description>Rights issues surged to a 28-year high in 2025, with companies raising ₹43,906 crore. This significant increase occurred as Qualified Institutional Placements (QIPs) sharply declined amid a broad market correction and new, faster regulations from the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi). Sebi's revised framework simplifies the process, making rights issues more attractive for listed firms seeking capital, especially during challenging market conditions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:46:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69516eaa4342f77179db179e_1766944505081.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Farmers Rejoice! India Rolls Out FIRST Ever Electric Tractor Testing Standard, Igniting Green Farming Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Farmers-Rejoice-India-Rolls-Out-FIRST-Ever-Electric-Tractor-Testing-Standard-Igniting-Green-Farming-Boom/69516b794342f77179db14fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Farmers-Rejoice-India-Rolls-Out-FIRST-Ever-Electric-Tractor-Testing-Standard-Igniting-Green-Farming-Boom/69516b794342f77179db14fb</guid><description>The Bureau of Indian Standards (BIS) has introduced India's first official testing standard, IS 19262:2025, for electric agricultural tractors. This crucial step ensures the safety, reliability, and performance of these eco-friendly machines, aiming to significantly boost their adoption across the nation and drive down agricultural emissions and operating costs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:30:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69516b794342f77179db14fa_1766943684858.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tyre Stocks Surge on Demand Boom &amp; Cost Cuts! Expert Sees Big Gains, But Watch Out for Global Risks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tyre-Stocks-Surge-on-Demand-Boom-and-Cost-Cuts-Expert-Sees-Big-Gains-But-Watch-Out-for-Global-Risks/695167854342f77179db10fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tyre-Stocks-Surge-on-Demand-Boom-and-Cost-Cuts-Expert-Sees-Big-Gains-But-Watch-Out-for-Global-Risks/695167854342f77179db10fb</guid><description>Indian tyre stocks like MRF, JK Tyre, Ceat, and Apollo Tyres are outperforming the market, gaining an average of 18% in six months. This rally is driven by falling raw material costs for rubber and oil, coupled with strong demand from automakers due to GST rate reductions and robust festival sales. Analysts expect margins to expand further, with several brokerages maintaining 'buy' ratings and setting high price targets. However, global uncertainties like US tariffs and geopolitical tensions pose potential risks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:12:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695167854342f77179db10fa_1766942804085.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai Tenders Fly: Anthony Waste Secures Massive Rs 1,300 Crore Deals Amidst Election Buzz!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mumbai-Tenders-Fly-Anthony-Waste-Secures-Massive-Rs-1300-Crore-Deals-Amidst-Election-Buzz/695163bb4342f77179db0d0f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Mumbai-Tenders-Fly-Anthony-Waste-Secures-Massive-Rs-1300-Crore-Deals-Amidst-Election-Buzz/695163bb4342f77179db0d0f</guid><description>Anthony Waste Handling Cell Ltd has secured major seven-year contracts worth approximately Rs 1,300 crore from the Brihanmumbai Municipal Corporation (BMC). These contracts cover vehicle operation, manpower, and maintenance across seven wards and are unaffected by the approaching civic elections. The company is also focusing on revenue diversification through waste-to-energy projects and recycling ventures.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:54:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695163bb4342f77179db0d0e_1766941726639.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Revolution Ignites: Gautam Adani Unveils Grand Vision for India's Tech Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Revolution-Ignites-Gautam-Adani-Unveils-Grand-Vision-for-Indias-Tech-Future/6951628f4342f77179db0b53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Revolution-Ignites-Gautam-Adani-Unveils-Grand-Vision-for-Indias-Tech-Future/6951628f4342f77179db0b53</guid><description>Industrialist Gautam Adani inaugurated a new Artificial Intelligence Centre in Baramati, Maharashtra. He hailed the facility as a 'symbol of transformation' and a significant step for India's technological progress. Adani emphasized the critical need for India to develop its own AI models to achieve technological sovereignty and secure its future global standing, likening AI's impact to previous industrial revolutions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:54:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951628f4342f77179db0b52_1766941426828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes 80 New Air Force Planes: US Giant Lockheed Martin Pitches C-130J Deal with HUGE India Manufacturing Plan!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Eyes-80-New-Air-Force-Planes-US-Giant-Lockheed-Martin-Pitches-C-130J-Deal-with-HUGE-India-Manufacturing-Plan/6951629a4342f77179db0b82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Eyes-80-New-Air-Force-Planes-US-Giant-Lockheed-Martin-Pitches-C-130J-Deal-with-HUGE-India-Manufacturing-Plan/6951629a4342f77179db0b82</guid><description>India is set to procure up to 80 military transport aircraft in a multi-billion-dollar deal. US aerospace firm Lockheed Martin is proposing its C-130J Super Hercules, highlighting its superior capabilities and existing use by the Indian Air Force. A key part of the pitch includes establishing Lockheed Martin's first global production hub for the C-130J outside the US in India, partnering with Tata Advanced Systems. This significant defense procurement is expected to be cleared by the Defence Acquisition Council shortly, with Embraer and Airbus also competing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:54:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951629a4342f77179db0b81_1766941644499.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fittr's Bold Leap: Rs 15 Crore Investment to Revolutionize Preventive Healthcare Across India!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Fittrs-Bold-Leap-Rs-15-Crore-Investment-to-Revolutionize-Preventive-Healthcare-Across-India/695162684342f77179db0ae4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Fittrs-Bold-Leap-Rs-15-Crore-Investment-to-Revolutionize-Preventive-Healthcare-Across-India/695162684342f77179db0ae4</guid><description>Fitness platform Fittr is transforming into a preventive healthcare giant, investing up to ₹15 crore to launch diagnostic labs in five major Indian metro cities. This strategic move aims to integrate diagnostics, doctor consultations, coaching, and wearable monitoring to combat lifestyle-related non-communicable diseases, which cause a significant portion of deaths in India. Fittr plans to expand its diagnostic network to 5,000 pin codes nationwide, shifting focus from purely fitness to holistic well-being.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:54:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695162684342f77179db0ae3_1766941363957.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Unlocks Bank M&amp;A Financing: India's Finance Sector Set for Seismic Shift in 2025!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Unlocks-Bank-MandA-Financing-Indias-Finance-Sector-Set-for-Seismic-Shift-in-2025/69515e564342f77179db067d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Unlocks-Bank-MandA-Financing-Indias-Finance-Sector-Set-for-Seismic-Shift-in-2025/69515e564342f77179db067d</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is paving the way for Indian banks to finance mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;A), a segment previously dominated by foreign entities. Draft regulations allow banks aggregate M&amp;A finance exposure up to 10% of Tier-I capital. Further reforms include a new Regulatory Review Cell for systematic policy evaluation, risk-based deposit insurance premiums, the resumption of Urban Cooperative Bank licenses, and a special campaign to resolve customer grievances. These changes signal a significant transformation in India's financial landscape for 2025.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:35:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69515e564342f77179db067c_1766940546578.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Legendary IBM CEO Who Saved 'Big Blue' Dies at 83 - A True Business Masterclass Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Legendary-IBM-CEO-Who-Saved-Big-Blue-Dies-at-83-A-True-Business-Masterclass-Revealed/69515a834342f77179db02eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Legendary-IBM-CEO-Who-Saved-Big-Blue-Dies-at-83-A-True-Business-Masterclass-Revealed/69515a834342f77179db02eb</guid><description>Louis Gerstner, the transformative CEO credited with saving International Business Machines Corp. (IBM) from collapse, has died at 83. Taking the helm in 1993 when IBM faced bankruptcy, Gerstner famously pivoted the tech giant from hardware to services, slashed costs, and fostered company-wide integration. His nine-year tenure is a celebrated case study in corporate turnaround, dramatically increasing IBM's market value and share price, and solidifying its leadership in the technology sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:16:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69515a834342f77179db02ea_1766939601793.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Visa Shake-Up: Indian Tech Dreams Face New Hurdles as Lottery Replaced by Wage-Based System!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Visa-Shake-Up-Indian-Tech-Dreams-Face-New-Hurdles-as-Lottery-Replaced-by-Wage-Based-System/6951548c4342f77179dafd00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Visa-Shake-Up-Indian-Tech-Dreams-Face-New-Hurdles-as-Lottery-Replaced-by-Wage-Based-System/6951548c4342f77179dafd00</guid><description>The United States is reshaping its H-1B visa program by replacing the lottery system with a wage-based allocation. This change prioritizes high-skilled, high-paying talent, making it harder for entry-level professionals and volume-driven employers. New regulations include expanded social media vetting and a steep $100,000 fee for first-time applications, significantly impacting Indian students and tech workers aspiring for US careers. While major tech firms and Indian IT companies are adapting by increasing local hiring and investing in India, the pathway to US opportunities is becoming narrower and more expensive.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:50:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951548c4342f77179dafcff_1766938028449.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI's 2025 Balancing Act: Tough Enforcement Meets Investor Ease – What It Means For Your Money!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-2025-Balancing-Act-Tough-Enforcement-Meets-Investor-Ease-What-It-Means-For-Your-Money/69514e404342f77179daf7d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-2025-Balancing-Act-Tough-Enforcement-Meets-Investor-Ease-What-It-Means-For-Your-Money/69514e404342f77179daf7d6</guid><description>In 2025, India's capital markets regulator SEBI, under new Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey, adopted a calibrated approach, balancing investor protection with ease of doing business. After an aggressive 2024, SEBI overhauled broker and mutual fund regulations, relaxed IPO norms, and extended compliance timelines. However, the derivatives market saw tightened margin requirements and position limits due to retail participation surge. Scrutiny on SME IPOs intensified, and actions were taken against finfluencers. Major reforms like T+0 settlement faced delays, indicating a deliberate, data-driven, and consultative regulatory evolution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:18:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69514e404342f77179daf7d5_1766936187472.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-EU Trade Deal Looms? Aviation Shake-up &amp; Political Shifts Unfold!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-EU-Trade-Deal-Looms-Aviation-Shake-up-and-Political-Shifts-Unfold/69514bb24342f77179daf544</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-EU-Trade-Deal-Looms-Aviation-Shake-up-and-Political-Shifts-Unfold/69514bb24342f77179daf544</guid><description>Key developments include potential breakthroughs in the India-European Union Free Trade Agreement negotiations, facing hurdles like CBAM. Simultaneously, India's aviation sector anticipates increased competition with new airline NOCs, though practical hurdles remain. Political narratives in Karnataka and Tamil Nadu also unfold with alliance speculations and pre-election welfare schemes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:18:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69514bb24342f77179daf543_1766935732737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCS Dividend Alert! Record Date Jan 17 for Q3 Payout - Board Meeting on Jan 12</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Dividend-Alert-Record-Date-Jan-17-for-Q3-Payout-Board-Meeting-on-Jan-12/695146d34342f77179daf145</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Dividend-Alert-Record-Date-Jan-17-for-Q3-Payout-Board-Meeting-on-Jan-12/695146d34342f77179daf145</guid><description>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) announced a third interim dividend for the quarter ending December 31, 2025. The company's board will meet on January 12, 2026, to approve financial results. The record date to determine eligible shareholders for this dividend is set for January 17, 2026, though the exact dividend amount has not yet been disclosed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:56:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695146d34342f77179daf144_1766934564350.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo's Grip Loosens: Market Share Drops Amidst Major Operational Chaos!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-Grip-Loosens-Market-Share-Drops-Amidst-Major-Operational-Chaos/695145764342f77179daef8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-Grip-Loosens-Market-Share-Drops-Amidst-Major-Operational-Chaos/695145764342f77179daef8f</guid><description>IndiGo, India's largest airline, saw its domestic market share decline to 63.6% in November from 65.6% in October due to operational disruptions and a 10% winter schedule cut ordered by the DGCA. Meanwhile, the Air India Group expanded its share to 26.7%, and SpiceJet increased its stake to 3.7%. Despite these shifts, overall passenger traffic continued to grow by 4.26% year-on-year, though flight-related customer complaints remained significant.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:49:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695145764342f77179daef8e_1766933965703.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Poised for Strength! Fed Minutes to Guide Next Big Move - Analysts Reveal Price Targets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Poised-for-Strength-Fed-Minutes-to-Guide-Next-Big-Move-Analysts-Reveal-Price-Targets/69513f554342f77179daea44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Poised-for-Strength-Fed-Minutes-to-Guide-Next-Big-Move-Analysts-Reveal-Price-Targets/69513f554342f77179daea44</guid><description>Gold and silver prices are expected to maintain their strength next week, with traders closely watching the US Federal Reserve's FOMC meeting minutes for monetary policy cues. Analysts foresee continued upward momentum in 2026, driven by anticipated global rate cuts, safe-haven demand, and robust industrial requirements, though the pace of gains may slow after an exceptional 2025. Specific price targets have been set for both gold and silver on MCX and international markets.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:23:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69513f554342f77179daea43_1766932391864.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mobile Retailer SS Retail Eyes Rs 500 Crore IPO: Are You Ready for the Next Big Tech Stock?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mobile-Retailer-SS-Retail-Eyes-Rs-500-Crore-IPO-Are-You-Ready-for-the-Next-Big-Tech-Stock/69513e984342f77179dae91d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mobile-Retailer-SS-Retail-Eyes-Rs-500-Crore-IPO-Are-You-Ready-for-the-Next-Big-Tech-Stock/69513e984342f77179dae91d</guid><description>Mobile phone retailer SS Retail has filed draft papers with SEBI to raise ₹500 crore via an IPO. The issue includes ₹300 crore from fresh shares and ₹200 crore from existing shareholders via offer-for-sale. The company plans to use funds for new store setups and working capital. SS Retail reported a profit of nearly ₹40 crore for FY25.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:19:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69513e984342f77179dae91c_1766932325812.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Shatters Records: A Decade of Unstoppable Growth Ignites India's Market!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Shatters-Records-A-Decade-of-Unstoppable-Growth-Ignites-Indias-Market/69513d654342f77179dae75d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Shatters-Records-A-Decade-of-Unstoppable-Growth-Ignites-Indias-Market/69513d654342f77179dae75d</guid><description>India's Nifty 50 index is poised for its longest-ever winning streak, marking ten consecutive years of positive returns. Despite global headwinds, the Nifty has shown remarkable resilience, outperforming major international indices like the Dow Jones and Shanghai Composite. This sustained growth underscores strong investor confidence in India's robust economic outlook, vast skilled workforce, and supportive government policies, positioning the nation as a premier global investment destination.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:14:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69513d654342f77179dae75c_1766932024505.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Aviation Ministry Launches 24x7 Control Room to Tackle Passenger Grievances Promptly</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Aviation-Ministry-Launches-24x7-Control-Room-to-Tackle-Passenger-Grievances-Promptly/695136cf4342f77179dae048</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Aviation-Ministry-Launches-24x7-Control-Room-to-Tackle-Passenger-Grievances-Promptly/695136cf4342f77179dae048</guid><description>The Indian Civil Aviation Ministry has established a 24x7 Passenger Assistance Control Room (PACR) to swiftly resolve air traveller issues. Staffed by officials from the ministry, DGCA, airlines, and AAI, the center addresses concerns like flight cancellations, delays, and lost baggage. This initiative aims to improve grievance redressal, following recent disruptions, with over 13,000 cases already resolved.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:43:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695136cf4342f77179dae047_1766930327670.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI's 2025 Rulebook: From Creation to Execution! Kotak COO Reveals Major Shift Impacting Your Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-2025-Rulebook-From-Creation-to-Execution-Kotak-COO-Reveals-Major-Shift-Impacting-Your-Investments/69512df94342f77179dad834</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-2025-Rulebook-From-Creation-to-Execution-Kotak-COO-Reveals-Major-Shift-Impacting-Your-Investments/69512df94342f77179dad834</guid><description>In 2025, India's market regulator SEBI shifted its focus from creating new rules to enforcing existing ones, a change highlighted by Sandeep Chordia, COO of Kotak Securities. This transition means more execution and less new rule-making compared to 2024. Key implementations like T+0 settlement are anticipated in 2026, pending system readiness across exchanges, brokers, and custodians. Additionally, measures to curb excessive speculation in equity derivatives, such as adjusting lot sizes and limiting weekly expiries, have successfully reduced retail participation in these high-risk products.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:07:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69512df94342f77179dad833_1766927945095.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Satellite Internet Launch Stuck! Security &amp; Price Hurdles Block Starlink in India; VIL Relief Debate Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Satellite-Internet-Launch-Stuck-Security-and-Price-Hurdles-Block-Starlink-in-India-VIL-Relief-Debate-Intensifies/695127934342f77179dad22a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Satellite-Internet-Launch-Stuck-Security-and-Price-Hurdles-Block-Starlink-in-India-VIL-Relief-Debate-Intensifies/695127934342f77179dad22a</guid><description>India's ambitious satellite internet rollout faces delays as major players like Starlink must first comply with security agency demands regarding international gateways and data localization. Union Telecom Minister Jyotiraditya Scindia stated that spectrum allocation hinges on these clearances and the finalization of spectrum pricing by the Department of Telecom and Telecom Regulatory Authority of India. Meanwhile, discussions continue on potential relief measures for Vodafone Idea, which has substantial dues to the government.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:39:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695127934342f77179dad229_1766926440215.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Ignites EV Race: Deliveries Surge With In-House 'Bharat Cell' Battery!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Ignites-EV-Race-Deliveries-Surge-With-In-House-Bharat-Cell-Battery/6951276c4342f77179dad1da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Ignites-EV-Race-Deliveries-Surge-With-In-House-Bharat-Cell-Battery/6951276c4342f77179dad1da</guid><description>Ola Electric is significantly increasing deliveries of its S1 Pro+ electric scooter, now powered by its in-house manufactured '4680 Bharat Cell' battery. Deliveries have begun in Tamil Nadu, Kerala, Telangana, and Karnataka, with plans for a nationwide rollout. This marks a major milestone for Ola Electric, establishing it as India's first company to fully own its cell and battery pack manufacturing process, bolstering its integrated EV ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:38:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951276c4342f77179dad1d9_1766926394129.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Poised for Satellite Internet: Security &amp; Spectrum Hurdles Near Resolution; Vodafone Idea Relief Update Underway!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Poised-for-Satellite-Internet-Security-and-Spectrum-Hurdles-Near-Resolution-Vodafone-Idea-Relief-Update-Underway/695126d14342f77179dad13e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Poised-for-Satellite-Internet-Security-and-Spectrum-Hurdles-Near-Resolution-Vodafone-Idea-Relief-Update-Underway/695126d14342f77179dad13e</guid><description>India is set to launch satellite communication services after players like Starlink meet security clearance demands and spectrum pricing is finalized by the Department of Telecom. Meanwhile, the government is actively reviewing relief measures for Vodafone Idea, which faces significant liabilities totaling around ₹2 lakh crore. The DoT is working on a solution to maintain four telecom operators in the robust Indian market.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:37:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695126d14342f77179dad13d_1766926137066.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's NCD Crisis: Experts Propose 'Micro-Hospitals' to Save Lives!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-NCD-Crisis-Experts-Propose-Micro-Hospitals-to-Save-Lives/6951260e4342f77179dad0ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-NCD-Crisis-Experts-Propose-Micro-Hospitals-to-Save-Lives/6951260e4342f77179dad0ac</guid><description>India faces a growing epidemic of non-communicable diseases (NCDs), which cause 63% of deaths. Healthcare experts are recommending the establishment of 'micro-hospitals'. These specialist-led facilities aim to provide coordinated, community-based care, reducing long wait times and fragmentation common in large hospitals. This model seeks to bridge the gap between primary care and tertiary hospitals, offering better diagnostics and treatments closer to home.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:36:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951260e4342f77179dad0ab_1766925905853.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 44,700 Cr Govt Mega-Plan Ignites India's Shipbuilding Future! Massive Boost for Capacity &amp; Jobs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rs-44700-Cr-Govt-Mega-Plan-Ignites-Indias-Shipbuilding-Future-Massive-Boost-for-Capacity-and-Jobs/6951245c4342f77179dace8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rs-44700-Cr-Govt-Mega-Plan-Ignites-Indias-Shipbuilding-Future-Massive-Boost-for-Capacity-and-Jobs/6951245c4342f77179dace8d</guid><description>India's government has launched two major shipbuilding schemes, the Shipbuilding Financial Assistance Scheme (SBFAS) and the Shipbuilding Development Scheme (SbDS), with a combined outlay of over ₹44,700 crore. These initiatives aim to revive the domestic shipbuilding industry, enhance global competitiveness, create long-term capacity, and foster job growth. SBFAS offers financial aid from 15-25%, while SbDS focuses on developing infrastructure, modernizing existing shipyards, and establishing an India Ship Technology Centre. The schemes are expected to support ₹96,000 crore in projects and significantly increase India's shipbuilding capacity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:28:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951245c4342f77179dace8c_1766925724133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Data Guardians Are Coming: New Board Setup Underway, Online Office Ready!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Data-Guardians-Are-Coming-New-Board-Setup-Underway-Online-Office-Ready/695118024342f77179dac5d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Data-Guardians-Are-Coming-New-Board-Setup-Underway-Online-Office-Ready/695118024342f77179dac5d2</guid><description>India's IT Secretary S Krishnan announced that groundwork has begun for appointing members to the new Data Protection Board. The software for its fully online office is developed. Consultations with industry stakeholders are ongoing to assess preparedness for the Digital Personal Data Protection Act (DPDP Act), with a priority on avoiding ecosystem disruption. The board will monitor compliance, inquire into breaches, and impose penalties.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:36:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695118024342f77179dac5d1_1766922545520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Unicorn Fractal's Massive ₹4,900 Cr IPO Nears: Book-Building Starts Next Week!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Unicorn-Fractals-Massive-4900-Cr-IPO-Nears-Book-Building-Starts-Next-Week/6951171f4342f77179dac4db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Unicorn-Fractals-Massive-4900-Cr-IPO-Nears-Book-Building-Starts-Next-Week/6951171f4342f77179dac4db</guid><description>Artificial intelligence leader Fractal Analytics is set to begin its ₹4,900 crore IPO book-building process next week. Having received regulatory approval, the company is nearing its market debut. Fractal is also considering a pre-IPO placement of up to ₹256 crore for institutional investors, which could adjust the final issue size. The company provides advanced analytics and AI solutions to global clients across finance, health, and retail.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:32:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951171f4342f77179dac4da_1766922202684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Financial Revolution: Embedded Finance Set to Explode!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Financial-Revolution-Embedded-Finance-Set-to-Explode/6951160d4342f77179dac359</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Financial-Revolution-Embedded-Finance-Set-to-Explode/6951160d4342f77179dac359</guid><description>India's financial sector is rapidly embracing Embedded Finance (EmFi), integrating financial services seamlessly into non-financial platforms. Fueled by massive mobile penetration and the UPI ecosystem, EmFi is projected to surge from around $6 billion to over $29 billion by 2030. While offering immense convenience and expanding market reach, EmFi faces challenges in data privacy, consumer protection, and regulatory compliance, requiring coordinated efforts for responsible growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:27:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951160d4342f77179dac358_1766921804475.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBFCs Bet Big on Trucks &amp; Tractors: India's 2026 Lending Revolution Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFCs-Bet-Big-on-Trucks-and-Tractors-Indias-2026-Lending-Revolution-Unveiled/695116284342f77179dac39a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFCs-Bet-Big-on-Trucks-and-Tractors-Indias-2026-Lending-Revolution-Unveiled/695116284342f77179dac39a</guid><description>Indian Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs) are pivoting strategy for 2026, moving from fast unsecured digital loans to secured lending in the 'real economy.' The focus is shifting to asset-backed financing for trucks, tractors, and small businesses, especially in rural and semi-urban India, driven by an infrastructure boom and resilient consumption. While commercial vehicles show strength, construction equipment faces challenges. NBFCs emphasize collateral and ground-level cash flow understanding, aiming for responsible, sustainable growth rather than rapid unsecured expansion. The RBI's rate cut is expected to improve margins and repayment capacity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:27:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695116284342f77179dac399_1766921837317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sigachi Industries CEO Remanded: Factory Fire Probe Rocks Pharma Giant – Is Your Investment Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sigachi-Industries-CEO-Remanded-Factory-Fire-Probe-Rocks-Pharma-Giant-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/695111334342f77179dabf55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sigachi-Industries-CEO-Remanded-Factory-Fire-Probe-Rocks-Pharma-Giant-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/695111334342f77179dabf55</guid><description>Sigachi Industries Limited announced its Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer, Amit Raj Sinha, has been remanded in connection with an ongoing investigation into a fire incident at its Hyderabad manufacturing unit on June 30, 2025. Deputy Group CEO Lijo Stephen Chacko will oversee operations on an interim basis to ensure business continuity. The company disclosed the development to stock exchanges as per SEBI regulations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:04:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695111334342f77179dabf54_1766920642201.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>East India Real Estate Surprise: Affordable Demand &amp; Mega Infra Projects Fuel Unstoppable Growth Into 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/East-India-Real-Estate-Surprise-Affordable-Demand-and-Mega-Infra-Projects-Fuel-Unstoppable-Growth-Into-2026/69510ed44342f77179dabc09</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/East-India-Real-Estate-Surprise-Affordable-Demand-and-Mega-Infra-Projects-Fuel-Unstoppable-Growth-Into-2026/69510ed44342f77179dabc09</guid><description>East India's real estate market defied expectations in 2025, prioritizing affordable housing and infrastructure development over premium price hikes. Kolkata led with significant launches and sales, while cities like Bhubaneswar, Guwahati, Patna, and Ranchi benefited from road, rail, and PMAY initiatives. This focus on connectivity and accessible pricing created steady demand, maintaining manageable inventory levels and setting a strong foundation for continued growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:54:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69510ed44342f77179dabc08_1766920392306.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Quality Control Orders: Fueling 'Make in India' Growth and Investment Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Quality-Control-Orders-Fueling-Make-in-India-Growth-and-Investment-Surge/69510f884342f77179dabd1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Quality-Control-Orders-Fueling-Make-in-India-Growth-and-Investment-Surge/69510f884342f77179dabd1a</guid><description>India is rapidly implementing Quality Control Orders (QCOs) to boost domestic manufacturing under the 'Make in India' initiative and enhance product quality. These orders, now exceeding 150, have attracted significant foreign investment and driven growth in sectors like air conditioners, footwear, steel, and toys, reshaping India's trade and manufacturing landscape by promoting local production and reducing reliance on imports.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:54:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69510f884342f77179dabd19_1766920202243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Takeover 2026: Indian IT Giants Set for Massive Revenue Boom &amp; Budget Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Takeover-2026-Indian-IT-Giants-Set-for-Massive-Revenue-Boom-and-Budget-Surge/69510e384342f77179dabb3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Takeover-2026-Indian-IT-Giants-Set-for-Massive-Revenue-Boom-and-Budget-Surge/69510e384342f77179dabb3b</guid><description>Artificial Intelligence is set to dominate the IT sector in 2026, with technology firms anticipating increased IT budgets and widespread AI project adoption. Indian IT leaders like TCS and HCL Technologies project nearly $2 billion in annual recurring revenue from advanced AI offerings. The focus is shifting towards practical, scaled AI solutions driving measurable business outcomes, significantly boosting demand for specialized AI talent.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:54:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69510e384342f77179dabb3a_1766919921860.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jefferies Boosts India, Taiwan Bets! Dumps China, Indonesia in Major Asia Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jefferies-Boosts-India-Taiwan-Bets-Dumps-China-Indonesia-in-Major-Asia-Shift/69510d244342f77179daba29</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jefferies-Boosts-India-Taiwan-Bets-Dumps-China-Indonesia-in-Major-Asia-Shift/69510d244342f77179daba29</guid><description>Global investment bank Jefferies has significantly reallocated its Asia Pacific ex-Japan portfolio, raising India and Taiwan's weightings by one percentage point each. This strategic move, funded by reductions in China and Indonesia exposure, reflects Jefferies' confidence in India's robust domestic demand, infrastructure growth, and improving corporate health, while concerns over China's economic recovery influence the trimming of its allocation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:47:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69510d244342f77179daba28_1766919538687.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Crystal Ball: Will 2026 Deliver Equity Riches or AI Bubble Burst? Investors Watch Closely!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AIs-Crystal-Ball-Will-2026-Deliver-Equity-Riches-or-AI-Bubble-Burst-Investors-Watch-Closely/695107884342f77179dab56c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AIs-Crystal-Ball-Will-2026-Deliver-Equity-Riches-or-AI-Bubble-Burst-Investors-Watch-Closely/695107884342f77179dab56c</guid><description>Global fund managers are shifting back to equities in 2026, moving away from gold and silver, with Artificial Intelligence (AI) expected to be a major driver. Despite past underperformance due to high valuations and weak earnings, India is anticipated to see an earnings recovery driven by interest rate cuts and tax reforms. However, investors must watch for AI bubble risks and compare India's 'growth play' valuation against China's 'value play'.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:25:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695107884342f77179dab56b_1766918100344.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Insurance FDI to 100%! But Who's Protecting You?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Boosts-Insurance-FDI-to-100percent-But-Whos-Protecting-You/695107934342f77179dab5a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Boosts-Insurance-FDI-to-100percent-But-Whos-Protecting-You/695107934342f77179dab5a3</guid><description>India's Parliament has passed the Sabka Bima Sabki Raksha (Amendment of Insurance Laws) Bill, 2025, significantly allowing 100% Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) in insurance companies and reducing capital requirements for reinsurers. While this aims to attract foreign capital and expertise, critics highlight the bill's lack of robust consumer protection measures. A proposed policyholder fund may offer limited relief, as core issues of mis-selling and opaque products persist, potentially prioritizing institutional gains over genuine customer welfare.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:25:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695107934342f77179dab5a2_1766918119370.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking Drop! Private Equity Flees Indian Real Estate, Investments Plummet 29%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Shocking-Drop-Private-Equity-Flees-Indian-Real-Estate-Investments-Plummet-29percent/695107124342f77179dab4ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Shocking-Drop-Private-Equity-Flees-Indian-Real-Estate-Investments-Plummet-29percent/695107124342f77179dab4ac</guid><description>Private equity investments in Indian real estate have plunged 29% this year to $3.46 billion, down from $4.9 billion last year. Knight Frank India reports a cautious investor sentiment, with significant drops in housing and warehousing funds, though office and retail sectors saw modest increases. The slowdown occurred despite improved macro-economic conditions, with experts citing cost of capital, exit visibility, and valuation alignment as key issues. An expected recovery to $4.4 billion in 2026 is projected to be selective.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:23:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695107124342f77179dab4ab_1766917983306.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>