<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:55:02 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Inc Titans: AI Hype vs. Enduring Profit; Banking &amp; IT Valuations Scrutinized</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Inc-Titans-AI-Hype-vs-Enduring-Profit-Banking-and-IT-Valuations-Scrutinized/699feb9ecd95b9dc08f9bbba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Inc-Titans-AI-Hype-vs-Enduring-Profit-Banking-and-IT-Valuations-Scrutinized/699feb9ecd95b9dc08f9bbba</guid><description>Two of India's most influential business leaders, NR Narayana Murthy and Aditya Puri, have delivered a dose of institutional realism, urging entrepreneurs to prioritize long-term profitability and stakeholder fairness over speculative metrics and AI-driven hype. Their commentary surfaces amidst a complex market where the Indian IT sector faces disruption concerns from AI coding agents, while banking valuations are under scrutiny despite underlying sector growth. The discourse highlights a strategic imperative for adaptation and fundamental value creation in a rapidly evolving technological and economic landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:43:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699feb9ecd95b9dc08f9bbb9_1772088342036.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE IPO Momentum Builds Amid Regulatory Hurdles and Valuation Debates</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-IPO-Momentum-Builds-Amid-Regulatory-Hurdles-and-Valuation-Debates/699feb8acd95b9dc08f9bb9d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-IPO-Momentum-Builds-Amid-Regulatory-Hurdles-and-Valuation-Debates/699feb8acd95b9dc08f9bb9d</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange of India (NSE) is advancing its long-anticipated Initial Public Offering (IPO), appointing Rothschild &amp; Co. as an independent advisor. The exchange plans an Offer for Sale (OFS) potentially raising $2.5 billion by divesting 4-4.5% of its equity. This move follows years of regulatory scrutiny and legal challenges, including significant settlements related to co-location practices. Despite these historical issues, the NSE's dominant position in the global derivatives market and a robust unlisted valuation underscore the ongoing momentum towards listing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:43:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699feb8acd95b9dc08f9bb9c_1772088342728.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sundaram-Clayton CEO Transition: R Venkatesh to Lead from April 1</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sundaram-Clayton-CEO-Transition-R-Venkatesh-to-Lead-from-April-1/699feb00cd95b9dc08f9baeb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sundaram-Clayton-CEO-Transition-R-Venkatesh-to-Lead-from-April-1/699feb00cd95b9dc08f9baeb</guid><description>Sundaram-Clayton Limited's Board of Directors has approved a significant leadership change. CEO Vivek S Joshi will resign effective March 31, 2026, and R Venkatesh will take over as Director &amp; CEO from April 1, 2026. This transition marks a pivotal moment for the auto component major, as the market watches for strategic direction under new leadership.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:41:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699feb00cd95b9dc08f9baea_1772088164424.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Capital Markets Surge: Record Funds Raised, IPOs Thrive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Capital-Markets-Surge-Record-Funds-Raised-IPOs-Thrive/699fea8fcd95b9dc08f9ba1d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Capital-Markets-Surge-Record-Funds-Raised-IPOs-Thrive/699fea8fcd95b9dc08f9ba1d</guid><description>India's capital markets have achieved remarkable growth, with SEBI Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey reporting approximately $105 trillion raised through equity and debt issuances between FY16 and January FY26. The IPO market has been particularly strong, with FY26 seeing $1.8 trillion raised via 329 offerings, surpassing FY25's $1.7 trillion from 320 IPOs. The corporate bond market expanded at a 12% CAGR since FY15 to ₹58.2 trillion, and Mutual Fund AUM surged from ₹12 trillion to ₹81 trillion. Regulatory enhancements aim to bolster anchor investor participation and market stability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:39:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fea8fcd95b9dc08f9ba1c_1772088029190.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Unit Gets USFDA Nod for Everolimus Tablets; $78M Market Awaits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Unit-Gets-USFDA-Nod-for-Everolimus-Tablets-78M-Market-Awaits/699fe7c4cd95b9dc08f9b7eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Unit-Gets-USFDA-Nod-for-Everolimus-Tablets-78M-Market-Awaits/699fe7c4cd95b9dc08f9b7eb</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma's subsidiary, Eugia Pharma Specialities Limited, secured final USFDA approval for Everolimus Tablets. This expands the company's oncology and specialty product portfolio, targeting a US market estimated at $78 million annually. The approval marks Eugia's 184th ANDA approval, reinforcing its manufacturing capabilities in regulated markets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:27:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe7c4cd95b9dc08f9b7ea_1772087356986.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HEG's Margin Gains Cloud Input Costs; China Policy Key to Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HEGs-Margin-Gains-Cloud-Input-Costs-China-Policy-Key-to-Growth/699fe7bacd95b9dc08f9b7c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HEGs-Margin-Gains-Cloud-Input-Costs-China-Policy-Key-to-Growth/699fe7bacd95b9dc08f9b7c7</guid><description>HEG reported a 37% YoY revenue increase, driven by robust volume and near-full capacity utilization. EBITDA margins climbed 500 bps due to operating leverage, though gross margins contracted by 235 bps from rising input costs. The company is positioned to benefit from global EAF capacity expansion and potential U.S. trade improvements. However, sustained cost management and the timely demerger of HEG Greentech by Q1 FY27 are crucial for future performance and value realization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:27:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe7bacd95b9dc08f9b7c6_1772087422241.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rich Field Financial Services gets in-principle BSE nod for ₹8.6 Cr preferential issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Rich-Field-Financial-Services-gets-in-principle-BSE-nod-for-86-Cr-preferential-issue/699fe740cd95b9dc08f9b6eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Rich-Field-Financial-Services-gets-in-principle-BSE-nod-for-86-Cr-preferential-issue/699fe740cd95b9dc08f9b6eb</guid><description>BSE has granted in-principle approval to Rich Field Financial Services Limited (RFSL) for a preferential issue of 34.42 lakh equity shares at a minimum price of Rs 25 per share, aiming to raise approximately ₹8.6 crore. This move is part of RFSL's strategy to bolster its capital base for business activities and operational expansion. The approval is conditional and requires adherence to SEBI regulations and further listing permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:25:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe740cd95b9dc08f9b6ea_1772087236224.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aksharchem FY25 PAT turns positive; CARE revises outlook to Negative</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aksharchem-FY25-PAT-turns-positive-CARE-revises-outlook-to-Negative/699fe6c8cd95b9dc08f9b609</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aksharchem-FY25-PAT-turns-positive-CARE-revises-outlook-to-Negative/699fe6c8cd95b9dc08f9b609</guid><description>CARE Ratings has revised Aksharchem (India) Limited's outlook to Negative, citing sustained weak performance and potential deterioration in debt coverage metrics. While FY25 PAT turned positive at ₹4.77 crore, a net loss was reported for 9MFY26. Concerns linger over raw material volatility and project returns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:23:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe6c8cd95b9dc08f9b608_1772087127172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Rally on Trade Fears; India Market Diverges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Rally-on-Trade-Fears-India-Market-Diverges/699fe6a4cd95b9dc08f9b5cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Rally-on-Trade-Fears-India-Market-Diverges/699fe6a4cd95b9dc08f9b5cc</guid><description>Global gold and silver prices climbed as heightened US-Iran nuclear talks and the U.S. imposition of new tariffs fueled safe-haven demand. Gold spot prices rose 0.67% to $5,199.81 and silver gained 0.64% to $89.67 on February 26, 2026. Conversely, Indian precious metals markets experienced a downturn, with MCX Gold falling 0.35% and MCX Silver dropping 1.31%. The U.S. dollar's weakening by 0.5% also supported gold's appreciation, while Treasury yields showed mixed signals. Investors are navigating geopolitical anxieties and a protectionist trade stance, seeking refuge in metals despite some analysts cautioning about a potential market peak.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:22:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe6a4cd95b9dc08f9b5cb_1772087233053.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Equities See Tactical FII Return Amid Valuation Reset</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Equities-See-Tactical-FII-Return-Amid-Valuation-Reset/699fe662cd95b9dc08f9b54b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Equities-See-Tactical-FII-Return-Amid-Valuation-Reset/699fe662cd95b9dc08f9b54b</guid><description>After a historic Rs 1.58 lakh crore outflow in 2025, Foreign Institutional Investors (FIIs) shifted to net buying Indian equities in February 2026. This reversal is tactical, driven by cooling valuations and receding U.S. Treasury yields, rather than broad bullish conviction. Domestic Institutional Investors (DIIs) provided significant support throughout the period. The Indian Rupee's depreciation also impacted repatriated returns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:21:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe662cd95b9dc08f9b54a_1772087001037.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cellecor Gadgets Secures Rs 200 Cr Credit Rating Amidst Growth Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cellecor-Gadgets-Secures-Rs-200-Cr-Credit-Rating-Amidst-Growth-Ambitions/699fe650cd95b9dc08f9b516</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cellecor-Gadgets-Secures-Rs-200-Cr-Credit-Rating-Amidst-Growth-Ambitions/699fe650cd95b9dc08f9b516</guid><description>Cellecor Gadgets Limited has secured consolidated credit ratings totaling Rs 200 crore from Infomerics Valuation and Rating Ltd, including an "IVR A-/Stable" for long-term facilities and "IVR A2+" for short-term instruments. This follows substantial H1FY26 and FY25 revenue and profit growth, alongside a notable increase in Foreign Institutional Investor (FII) holdings. The ratings facilitate access to working capital from major banks, supporting the company's strategy to make consumer electronics accessible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:21:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe650cd95b9dc08f9b515_1772086994832.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSE Index Nears Highs: Value Plays or Momentum Trap?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PSE-Index-Nears-Highs-Value-Plays-or-Momentum-Trap/699fe56dcd95b9dc08f9b43a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PSE-Index-Nears-Highs-Value-Plays-or-Momentum-Trap/699fe56dcd95b9dc08f9b43a</guid><description>The Nifty Public Sector Enterprises (PSE) index has surged, outperforming the broader Nifty 50 index in both calendar and fiscal year-to-date metrics. This rally, attributed to improved fundamentals and government reforms, has propelled the PSE index to its 52-week high. However, a closer examination reveals significant valuation disparities among constituents, with some trading at historically high multiples, alongside enduring structural challenges inherent to state-owned entities. The sector faces a critical juncture as it tests previous peaks, prompting scrutiny of the sustainability of its gains.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:17:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe56dcd95b9dc08f9b439_1772086862438.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JPFL Faces Shareholder Lawsuit &amp; SEBI Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/JPFL-Faces-Shareholder-Lawsuit-and-SEBI-Probe/699fe387cd95b9dc08f9b267</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/JPFL-Faces-Shareholder-Lawsuit-and-SEBI-Probe/699fe387cd95b9dc08f9b267</guid><description>Jindal Poly Films (JPFL) faces amplified scrutiny as the National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) upheld a class action lawsuit seeking ₹2,500 crore from minority shareholders. This comes as the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) continues its probe into alleged ₹760 crore in undisclosed write-offs and potential securities law violations. The company, which has seen its stock halve since early 2025, is contesting the claims while the legal actions set a significant precedent for shareholder rights in India.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:09:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe387cd95b9dc08f9b266_1772086292527.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Warehousing Boom: Policy Fuels Growth, Risks Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Warehousing-Boom-Policy-Fuels-Growth-Risks-Emerge/699fe30bcd95b9dc08f9b1b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Warehousing-Boom-Policy-Fuels-Growth-Risks-Emerge/699fe30bcd95b9dc08f9b1b8</guid><description>India's industrial and warehousing sector is undergoing rapid transformation, propelled by robust policy support, infrastructure expansion, and evolving demand. Colliers India identifies 30 high-potential cities categorized as Prime, Emerging, and Nascent hubs. The market is projected to expand significantly, with Grade A warehousing stock potentially reaching 2 billion sq ft by 2047. However, challenges such as rising land costs, regulatory fragmentation, and logistical inefficiencies persist, requiring strategic navigation amidst strong growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:07:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe30bcd95b9dc08f9b1b7_1772086155086.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anil Ambani Faces ED Heat: Asset Seizures Escalate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Anil-Ambani-Faces-ED-Heat-Asset-Seizures-Escalate/699fe309cd95b9dc08f9b1a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Anil-Ambani-Faces-ED-Heat-Asset-Seizures-Escalate/699fe309cd95b9dc08f9b1a1</guid><description>Anil Ambani appeared for a second Enforcement Directorate (ED) questioning regarding an alleged ₹40,000 crore bank fraud by Reliance Communications (RCOM). The ED has attached assets totaling over ₹15,700 crore, including Ambani's Mumbai residence worth ₹3,716 crore. This escalating probe impacts investor confidence, with RCOM facing insolvency and Reliance Power trading at an expensive valuation relative to peers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:07:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe309cd95b9dc08f9b1a0_1772086205257.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Targets 170K, Silver Eyes 280K Amid Technical Strength: Nuvama</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Targets-170K-Silver-Eyes-280K-Amid-Technical-Strength-Nuvama/699fe1aacd95b9dc08f9b0a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Targets-170K-Silver-Eyes-280K-Amid-Technical-Strength-Nuvama/699fe1aacd95b9dc08f9b0a6</guid><description>Nuvama Professional Clients Group projects gold to advance towards ₹170,000 per 10 grams and silver towards ₹280,000 per kilogram, citing a bullish technical setup. Gold's trajectory is supported by a rising trendline base, with ₹157,000 acting as a critical support. Silver, though facing resistance, shows resilience and potential for upside. Both metals are influenced by macroeconomic factors including interest rate expectations and industrial demand, though silver faces higher volatility risks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:01:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fe1aacd95b9dc08f9b0a5_1772085837448.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Laurus Labs: High Capex Fuels Growth Hopes, But Valuation Concerns Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Laurus-Labs-High-Capex-Fuels-Growth-Hopes-But-Valuation-Concerns-Loom/699fdf4bcd95b9dc08f9af14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Laurus-Labs-High-Capex-Fuels-Growth-Hopes-But-Valuation-Concerns-Loom/699fdf4bcd95b9dc08f9af14</guid><description>Laurus Labs is undertaking a substantial ₹390 crore capex program, primarily for CDMO and API expansion, with Motilal Oswal projecting robust PAT growth and reiterating a Buy rating with a ₹1,280 target. However, current valuations are significantly elevated compared to peers, net debt remains substantial, and recent quarterly profits have lagged revenue gains due to ongoing investments. Analyst sentiment shows divergence, with some maintaining 'Hold' or 'Underperform' ratings and lower targets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:51:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdf4bcd95b9dc08f9af13_1772085189274.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>M&amp;M's Auto Strength Buffers Tractor Woes Amid El Nino Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandMs-Auto-Strength-Buffers-Tractor-Woes-Amid-El-Nino-Fears/699fdef2cd95b9dc08f9ae25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandMs-Auto-Strength-Buffers-Tractor-Woes-Amid-El-Nino-Fears/699fdef2cd95b9dc08f9ae25</guid><description>HSBC forecasts muted tractor volume growth (0-2% CAGR FY26-28) due to El Nino and a high base, cutting estimates for M&amp;M and Escorts Kubota. However, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra's strong automotive business is expected to offset farm segment pressures, with HSBC maintaining a 'Buy' rating and a ₹4,150 target. Escorts Kubota retains a 'Hold' at ₹3,600. Despite sector headwinds, positive reservoir levels and replacement demand offer some support. The broader Indian auto sector remains robust, with January 2026 retail sales up 18%. Escorts Kubota's domestic market share is contracting, highlighting competitive challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:49:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdef2cd95b9dc08f9ae24_1772085076771.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pharma &amp; Diagnostics Attract: Rupee Boost Muted by Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-and-Diagnostics-Attract-Rupee-Boost-Muted-by-Risks/699fdeeccd95b9dc08f9ae0d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-and-Diagnostics-Attract-Rupee-Boost-Muted-by-Risks/699fdeeccd95b9dc08f9ae0d</guid><description>Elara Securities sees opportunity in select Indian pharmaceutical and diagnostics stocks, citing reasonable valuations and the depreciated rupee. However, headwinds from global tariffs, US regulatory scrutiny, and high input costs temper these benefits. The diagnostics sector faces intense competition, while hospitals navigate a transition despite positive forecasts. Companies like Zydus Life Sciences and Aurobindo Pharma offer lower P/E multiples compared to peers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:49:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdeeccd95b9dc08f9ae0c_1772085025131.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Murugappa Group Stocks Diverge on Ownership Shuffle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Murugappa-Group-Stocks-Diverge-on-Ownership-Shuffle/699fde5ccd95b9dc08f9ad5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Murugappa-Group-Stocks-Diverge-on-Ownership-Shuffle/699fde5ccd95b9dc08f9ad5c</guid><description>Murugappa Group entities Cholamandalam Investment and Finance, CG Power, and Tube Investments experienced mixed trading on February 26, 2026. Reports suggest Vellayan Subbiah is realigning ownership, divesting from Cholamandalam while consolidating stakes in CG Power and Tube Investments. This internal shift caused Cholamandalam shares to dip significantly, while CG Power and Tube Investments saw modest gains. The market is now assessing the strategic implications of this promoter-level restructuring on future growth and group synergy, especially given previous disputes involving CG Power's turnaround.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:47:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fde5ccd95b9dc08f9ad5b_1772084973834.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apar Industries: Growth Surge Meets Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apar-Industries-Growth-Surge-Meets-Valuation-Scrutiny/699fdd69cd95b9dc08f9ab17</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apar-Industries-Growth-Surge-Meets-Valuation-Scrutiny/699fdd69cd95b9dc08f9ab17</guid><description>ICICI Direct initiates coverage on Apar Industries with a BUY rating, citing strong growth drivers in electricity demand, transmission, and renewables. The company leverages leadership in conductors, cables, and transformer oils, with earnings projected for a 21% CAGR. However, a high P/E ratio of approximately 44x TTM and past export vulnerabilities present a complex investment picture.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:43:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdd69cd95b9dc08f9ab16_1772084766464.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Uniswap Fee Switch Boost: Revenue Up, But L2 Competition Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Uniswap-Fee-Switch-Boost-Revenue-Up-But-L2-Competition-Looms/699fdd69cd95b9dc08f9ab00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Uniswap-Fee-Switch-Boost-Revenue-Up-But-L2-Competition-Looms/699fdd69cd95b9dc08f9ab00</guid><description>Uniswap's native token, UNI, saw a notable increase as a significant governance proposal to expand its protocol fee switch across eight additional chains and all v3 liquidity pools gained traction. This move aims to generate an additional estimated $27 million in annualized revenue, supplementing approximately $34 million currently used for UNI token burns. While this bolsters UNI's value accrual and deflationary mechanics, it intensifies scrutiny on Uniswap's ability to retain liquidity and market share against fee-sensitive competitors on Layer-2 networks. Recent price action shows UNI trading around $3.33-$4.15 with a market cap near $2.5 billion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:43:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdd69cd95b9dc08f9aaff_1772084748864.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EU Pact Fuels India Alcohol Exports, Ignites Fierce Domestic Rivalry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/EU-Pact-Fuels-India-Alcohol-Exports-Ignites-Fierce-Domestic-Rivalry/699fdd03cd95b9dc08f9a9ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/EU-Pact-Fuels-India-Alcohol-Exports-Ignites-Fierce-Domestic-Rivalry/699fdd03cd95b9dc08f9a9ef</guid><description>India's alcohol and beverage industry stands at a critical juncture, propelled by a Free Trade Agreement with the EU that promises significant export growth by slashing import tariffs for European brands into India. This dual-edged development necessitates a swift elevation of domestic product quality, pricing, and brand strategy to survive intensified competition while capitalizing on new international market access. The sector's resilience and strategic planning will determine its global leadership potential amidst this transformative period.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:41:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdd03cd95b9dc08f9a9ee_1772084595715.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC Bank Pivots Infinia Card: Spend Doubled, Relationship Value Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-Bank-Pivots-Infinia-Card-Spend-Doubled-Relationship-Value-Key/699fdcffcd95b9dc08f9a9d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-Bank-Pivots-Infinia-Card-Spend-Doubled-Relationship-Value-Key/699fdcffcd95b9dc08f9a9d8</guid><description>HDFC Bank has significantly tightened its Infinia Credit Card's annual fee waiver criteria, demanding ₹18 lakh in annual spending or a ₹50 lakh Relationship Value (RLV). Existing cardholders retain current benefits until March 2027, offering a transition window. This move aligns with industry-wide trends of recalibrating premium card economics and focusing on high-value, deeply engaged customers. The changes, communicated via email, signal a strategic pivot towards relationship banking for its most affluent clientele.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:41:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdcffcd95b9dc08f9a9d7_1772084593747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JPFL Faces Heightened Legal and Governance Scrutiny Post-NCLAT Ruling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/JPFL-Faces-Heightened-Legal-and-Governance-Scrutiny-Post-NCLAT-Ruling/699fdcf1cd95b9dc08f9a99c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/JPFL-Faces-Heightened-Legal-and-Governance-Scrutiny-Post-NCLAT-Ruling/699fdcf1cd95b9dc08f9a99c</guid><description>The National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) has dismissed Jindal Poly Films Limited's (JPFL) appeal, allowing a shareholder class action lawsuit alleging over ₹2,500 crore in losses due to undervaluation and fund siphoning to proceed. This ruling validates claims related to past transactions, significantly increasing governance scrutiny on the company and potentially impacting its financial standing amidst existing regulatory concerns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:41:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdcf1cd95b9dc08f9a99b_1772084635233.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Rallies on Global Risk; India Premiums Persist</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Rallies-on-Global-Risk-India-Premiums-Persist/699fdc23cd95b9dc08f9a875</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Rallies-on-Global-Risk-India-Premiums-Persist/699fdc23cd95b9dc08f9a875</guid><description>Gold prices are trending upward, driven by escalating geopolitical tensions, a softening U.S. dollar, and anticipation of Federal Reserve rate cuts. Despite minor daily fluctuations, underlying global factors are pushing the commodity higher, with Indian gold premiums persisting above international rates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:37:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdc23cd95b9dc08f9a874_1772084462262.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nissan Gravite MPV Launch: Aggressive Play Amidst Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nissan-Gravite-MPV-Launch-Aggressive-Play-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/699fdba5cd95b9dc08f9a76e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nissan-Gravite-MPV-Launch-Aggressive-Play-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/699fdba5cd95b9dc08f9a76e</guid><description>Nissan Motor India has rolled out the Gravite, a seven-seater MPV priced from ₹5.65 lakh, targeting the high-volume, price-sensitive entry-level segment. This launch is a key part of Nissan's aggressive strategy to expand its presence, which currently holds less than 1% of India's passenger vehicle market. The Gravite enters a segment dominated by Maruti Suzuki's Eeco and faces competition from Renault's Triber and the larger Maruti Ertiga, necessitating strong execution in pricing, network reach, and product appeal to gain traction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:35:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdba5cd95b9dc08f9a76d_1772084514067.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Toyota to Divest $19B in Holdings Amid Governance Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Toyota-to-Divest-19B-in-Holdings-Amid-Governance-Overhaul/699fdb98cd95b9dc08f9a734</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Toyota-to-Divest-19B-in-Holdings-Amid-Governance-Overhaul/699fdb98cd95b9dc08f9a734</guid><description>Toyota Motor is initiating a significant divestment of approximately $19 billion (3 trillion yen) in strategic shareholdings. This move signals a proactive approach to enhancing capital efficiency and aligns with Japan's broader corporate governance reforms pushing for the unwinding of cross-shareholdings. The automaker is exploring share buybacks and secondary sales, with major banks and insurers expected to participate. The initiative aims to demonstrate a firm commitment to improved governance and shareholder value amidst persistent investor scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:35:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdb98cd95b9dc08f9a733_1772084234827.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Mfg Ambition Meets Trade Storm: US Tariffs, WTO Probe Hit PLI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Mfg-Ambition-Meets-Trade-Storm-US-Tariffs-WTO-Probe-Hit-PLI/699fdb16cd95b9dc08f9a62e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Mfg-Ambition-Meets-Trade-Storm-US-Tariffs-WTO-Probe-Hit-PLI/699fdb16cd95b9dc08f9a62e</guid><description>India's drive to become a global manufacturing hub is confronting significant international trade challenges. The U.S. has imposed a preliminary 126% duty on Indian solar panel imports, citing unfair subsidies, while a WTO panel has been established to investigate China's complaint that India's Production-Linked Incentive (PLI) schemes unfairly favor domestic goods. These actions threaten India's export-driven manufacturing ambitions and put pressure on major players like Waaree Energies and Adani Enterprises.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:33:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdb16cd95b9dc08f9a62d_1772084157451.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gokul Refoils: Rajput Ups Stake to 1.25%, PAC Controls 73.05% Post-Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Gokul-Refoils-Rajput-Ups-Stake-to-125percent-PAC-Controls-7305percent-Post-Acquisition/699fdb12cd95b9dc08f9a617</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Gokul-Refoils-Rajput-Ups-Stake-to-125percent-PAC-Controls-7305percent-Post-Acquisition/699fdb12cd95b9dc08f9a617</guid><description>Promoter Arjunsinh Rajput has acquired 96,048 shares in Gokul Refoils &amp; Solvent Limited via open market purchase on February 24, 2026. This transaction increases his direct shareholding to 1.25%. Combined with his Persons Acting in Concert (PAC), the promoter group now controls a substantial 73.05% stake in the company, reinforcing their dominant position. The acquisition is reported under SEBI SAST Regulations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fdb12cd95b9dc08f9a616_1772084124528.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Upsurge Investment &amp; Finance: Promoter Ups Stake Via 10 Lakh Warrant Conversion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Upsurge-Investment-and-Finance-Promoter-Ups-Stake-Via-10-Lakh-Warrant-Conversion/699fda98cd95b9dc08f9a59c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Upsurge-Investment-and-Finance-Promoter-Ups-Stake-Via-10-Lakh-Warrant-Conversion/699fda98cd95b9dc08f9a59c</guid><description>Promoter Pratibha Goyal has boosted her stake in Upsurge Investment &amp; Finance Limited to 14.99% following the conversion of 10,00,000 warrants on February 23, 2026. This capital infusion also led to an expansion of the company's equity share capital. The move signals continued promoter confidence in the NBFC's future prospects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fda98cd95b9dc08f9a59b_1772084030043.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fractal Industries: Fund Acquires 5.98% Stake Via Open Market, QIB</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Fractal-Industries-Fund-Acquires-598percent-Stake-Via-Open-Market-QIB/699fd9adcd95b9dc08f9a4b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Fractal-Industries-Fund-Acquires-598percent-Stake-Via-Open-Market-QIB/699fd9adcd95b9dc08f9a4b7</guid><description>AL MAHA INVESTMENT FUND – ONYX STRATEGY has emerged as a significant shareholder in Fractal Industries Ltd, acquiring 5.9856% of its total and diluted share capital. The shares were purchased through open market transactions and QIB channels, marking a notable change in the company's ownership structure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:27:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fd9adcd95b9dc08f9a4b6_1772083681964.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NTPC Group Tops 88 GW Installed Capacity with 50 MW Wind Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Group-Tops-88-GW-Installed-Capacity-with-50-MW-Wind-Project/699fd8f8cd95b9dc08f9a3ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Group-Tops-88-GW-Installed-Capacity-with-50-MW-Wind-Project/699fd8f8cd95b9dc08f9a3ff</guid><description>NTPC Group has surpassed 88 GW of total installed power capacity with the commissioning of a 50 MW wind project in Gujarat. This latest addition by NTPC Renewable Energy Limited, a subsidiary of NTPC Green Energy, brings the NTPC Group's commercial capacity to 87,102 MW. The move aligns with NTPC's aggressive renewable energy expansion strategy and its target of achieving 60 GW of renewable capacity by 2032.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:24:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fd8f8cd95b9dc08f9a3fe_1772083582972.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alembic Pharma USFDA Nod For Lamotrigine Tablets; $27M Market Opportunity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Alembic-Pharma-USFDA-Nod-For-Lamotrigine-Tablets-27M-Market-Opportunity/699fd84ecd95b9dc08f9a2e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Alembic-Pharma-USFDA-Nod-For-Lamotrigine-Tablets-27M-Market-Opportunity/699fd84ecd95b9dc08f9a2e6</guid><description>Alembic Pharmaceuticals Limited has secured final approval from the US FDA for its Lamotrigine Orally Disintegrating Tablets USP. This approval opens access to an estimated US$ 27 million market. The company now boasts a cumulative total of 235 Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA) approvals from the USFDA, reinforcing its robust pipeline and commitment to the US generics market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:21:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fd84ecd95b9dc08f9a2e5_1772083394066.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hazoor Multi Projects Subsidiary Gets CRISIL Ratings; Tata Steel Order Bolsters Pipeline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hazoor-Multi-Projects-Subsidiary-Gets-CRISIL-Ratings-Tata-Steel-Order-Bolsters-Pipeline/699fd840cd95b9dc08f9a2ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hazoor-Multi-Projects-Subsidiary-Gets-CRISIL-Ratings-Tata-Steel-Order-Bolsters-Pipeline/699fd840cd95b9dc08f9a2ce</guid><description>Hazoor Multi Projects Limited (HMPL) subsidiary, Hazoor Infra Projects Limited (HIPPL), has received 'CRISIL BBB+/Stable' long-term and 'CRISIL A2' short-term ratings for its Rs 476 crore bank facilities. Concurrently, HMPL secured a Rs 182.95 crore work order from Tata Steel. These developments come as the company reports mixed financial results, with consolidated revenue declining but profit rising due to tax credits, while standalone revenue grew but profit dipped. The company's stock has seen significant historical appreciation but faces valuation concerns with a high P/E ratio.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:21:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fd840cd95b9dc08f9a2cd_1772083404598.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Financials Eye AI Capex Shift Amidst Tech Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Financials-Eye-AI-Capex-Shift-Amidst-Tech-Caution/699fd6eacd95b9dc08f9a035</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Financials-Eye-AI-Capex-Shift-Amidst-Tech-Caution/699fd6eacd95b9dc08f9a035</guid><description>The global artificial intelligence capital expenditure cycle appears to be reaching a turning point, potentially redirecting investor focus toward India. While the Indian Information Technology services sector faces headwinds, prompting a cautious outlook, its financial sector is emerging as a strategic buy. Analysts anticipate significant foreign capital inflows into India by 2026, driven by consistent earnings growth and more attractive valuations compared to peak tech spending regions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:15:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fd6eacd95b9dc08f9a034_1772083177717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BoB Hits Record High Amidst PSU Rally, But Margin Pressures Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/BoB-Hits-Record-High-Amidst-PSU-Rally-But-Margin-Pressures-Loom/699fd6e9cd95b9dc08f9a01e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/BoB-Hits-Record-High-Amidst-PSU-Rally-But-Margin-Pressures-Loom/699fd6e9cd95b9dc08f9a01e</guid><description>Bank of Baroda shares surged to a new all-time high of ₹323, buoyed by 'AAA' ratings on its green bonds and the broader rally in public sector banks, which have seen significant gains over the past year. Despite strong asset quality metrics and improved profitability, concerns are mounting regarding Net Interest Margin (NIM) compression and the upcoming transition to Expected Credit Loss (ECL) accounting standards, which could present near-term challenges. While analysts maintain a positive outlook, price targets suggest limited immediate upside from current levels.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:15:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fd6e9cd95b9dc08f9a01d_1772083124403.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd. Stock Slides Amidst Block Deal, Analyst Optimism Falters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eternal-Ltd-Stock-Slides-Amidst-Block-Deal-Analyst-Optimism-Falters/699fd6ddcd95b9dc08f9a004</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Eternal-Ltd-Stock-Slides-Amidst-Block-Deal-Analyst-Optimism-Falters/699fd6ddcd95b9dc08f9a004</guid><description>Eternal Ltd., the parent company of Zomato and Blinkit, is experiencing significant selling pressure, marking its longest losing streak in over two years. An eight-day decline has pushed the stock to its lowest point since June 2025. This persistent downward movement occurs despite a majority of analysts maintaining 'buy' ratings and setting ambitious price targets. A substantial ₹2,403 crore block deal, involving nearly 1% of outstanding equity, further adds to the uncertainty, with the identities of the transacting parties undisclosed. The stock's performance contrasts sharply with the generally constructive outlook for the Indian quick commerce sector, signaling potential investor concerns beyond headline fundamentals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:15:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fd6ddcd95b9dc08f9a003_1772083083947.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Tightens Mutual Fund Rules: New Clarity, Operational Hurdles Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SEBI-Tightens-Mutual-Fund-Rules-New-Clarity-Operational-Hurdles-Emerge/699fd6dccd95b9dc08f99fed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SEBI-Tightens-Mutual-Fund-Rules-New-Clarity-Operational-Hurdles-Emerge/699fd6dccd95b9dc08f99fed</guid><description>India's Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has issued a new framework for mutual fund scheme classification, effective February 26, 2026. This mandates stricter allocation bands for equity funds, including multi-cap, large-cap, and large &amp; mid-cap categories, and introduces uniform descriptions to boost investor comparability. While the move aims to standardize offerings and clarify investment strategies, it presents significant operational and strategic challenges for Asset Management Companies (AMCs) as they navigate new compliance requirements and potential product rationalization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:15:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fd6dccd95b9dc08f99fec_1772083007388.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Laurus Labs Surges on CDMO Momentum, But Valuation Concerns Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Laurus-Labs-Surges-on-CDMO-Momentum-But-Valuation-Concerns-Linger/699fd6dccd95b9dc08f99fd6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Laurus-Labs-Surges-on-CDMO-Momentum-But-Valuation-Concerns-Linger/699fd6dccd95b9dc08f99fd6</guid><description>Laurus Labs saw its shares rally nearly 3% to ₹1,103.35 on February 26, 2026, nearing its all-time high. The surge follows robust Q3 FY26 performance, with revenue up 26% and EBITDA margins expanding to over 27%, driven by strong generics and Contract Development and Manufacturing Organization (CDMO) segment growth. Analysts are divided, with some reiterating 'Buy' ratings and high targets, while others signal 'Hold' or 'Sell' with lower consensus price targets, citing valuation concerns and sector pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:15:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fd6dccd95b9dc08f99fd5_1772083081674.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>