<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:35:55 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Mukesh Ambani's Bold AI Vision: Reliance to Become AI-Native, Targeting 10x Productivity and India's Economic Leap!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mukesh-Ambanis-Bold-AI-Vision-Reliance-to-Become-AI-Native-Targeting-10x-Productivity-and-Indias-Economic-Leap/6953c5ef4342f77179e6907a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mukesh-Ambanis-Bold-AI-Vision-Reliance-to-Become-AI-Native-Targeting-10x-Productivity-and-Indias-Economic-Leap/6953c5ef4342f77179e6907a</guid><description>Reliance Industries Chairman Mukesh Ambani has unveiled a draft AI Manifesto, charting a course to transform the conglomerate into an AI-native deep-tech enterprise. The plan aims for a tenfold increase in employee productivity and a significant impact on India's economy and society. AI will be embedded across all businesses, focusing on outcomes, efficiency, and safety, while ensuring 'Affordable AI for Every Indian'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr Reddy's Srikakulam Plant Faces USFDA Scrutiny: 5 Critical Observations Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Srikakulam-Plant-Faces-USFDA-Scrutiny-5-Critical-Observations-Revealed/6953c5794342f77179e68e98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Srikakulam-Plant-Faces-USFDA-Scrutiny-5-Critical-Observations-Revealed/6953c5794342f77179e68e98</guid><description>Dr. Reddy's Laboratories' Srikakulam facility in Andhra Pradesh received a Form 483 with five observations from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) after a recent inspection. The observations relate to manufacturing practices, quality control, and data integrity. Dr. Reddy's has committed to addressing these findings within the stipulated timeline.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:12:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c5794342f77179e68e97_1767097868886.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Close Flat: Unpacking the Negative Sentiment Dragging Stocks Down!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Close-Flat-Unpacking-the-Negative-Sentiment-Dragging-Stocks-Down/6953c5984342f77179e68ef8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Close-Flat-Unpacking-the-Negative-Sentiment-Dragging-Stocks-Down/6953c5984342f77179e68ef8</guid><description>India's benchmark stock indices, Sensex and Nifty, ended Tuesday flat with minor losses. The BSE Sensex closed down 20.46 points at 84,675.08, and the NSE Nifty50 settled 3.25 points lower at 25,938.85. Market sentiment was influenced by monthly F&amp;O expiry, profit-booking after recent gains, weak global cues, and continued Foreign Institutional Investor (FII) selling. Muted trading volumes due to year-end holidays were also a factor. Despite these headwinds, strong domestic fundamentals and steady local inflows provided some support.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:12:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c5984342f77179e68ef7_1767097837210.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RVNL Analyst's Top Railway Pick: Rs 400 Target Set as Stock Consolidates Ahead of Budget Buzz!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RVNL-Analysts-Top-Railway-Pick-Rs-400-Target-Set-as-Stock-Consolidates-Ahead-of-Budget-Buzz/6953c5004342f77179e68d26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RVNL-Analysts-Top-Railway-Pick-Rs-400-Target-Set-as-Stock-Consolidates-Ahead-of-Budget-Buzz/6953c5004342f77179e68d26</guid><description>Analyst Pradip Halder names Rail Vikas Nigam Limited (RVNL) as a top investment pick in the railway sector, setting a target price of over ₹400. Despite recent rallies leading to profit booking and consolidation around ₹320, investor interest in railway stocks like RVNL remains strong ahead of the Union Budget, which historically causes sector volatility.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:12:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c5004342f77179e68d25_1767097952356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SRF Hit with ₹16 Crore Tax Demand: Company Vows to Fight Back!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/SRF-Hit-with-16-Crore-Tax-Demand-Company-Vows-to-Fight-Back/6953c4ac4342f77179e68ba2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/SRF-Hit-with-16-Crore-Tax-Demand-Company-Vows-to-Fight-Back/6953c4ac4342f77179e68ba2</guid><description>SRF Ltd received a ₹15.76 crore demand from CGST Dehradun for input tax credit reversal concerning a slump sale and supplier compliance issues, plus interest and penalty. The company, confident in its legal standing, plans to contest the demand, expecting no material financial impact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bitcoin's 2025 Rollercoaster: $12,000 Crash Erases Predictions, Wipes $500 Billion! Did ANYONE Get It Right?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoins-2025-Rollercoaster-12000-Crash-Erases-Predictions-Wipes-500-Billion-Did-ANYONE-Get-It-Right/6953c4424342f77179e689b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoins-2025-Rollercoaster-12000-Crash-Erases-Predictions-Wipes-500-Billion-Did-ANYONE-Get-It-Right/6953c4424342f77179e689b0</guid><description>Bitcoin experienced a dramatic 'flash crash' in October 2025, plunging $12,000 in minutes, triggering over $19 billion in liquidations and erasing $500 billion from the total crypto market cap. This event highlighted the spectacular failure of numerous optimistic price predictions made throughout the year by analysts and industry leaders, many of whom had forecast prices reaching $1 million or $500,000. The year is now set to post its first full-year loss since 2022, underscoring the extreme difficulty of forecasting cryptocurrency markets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:09:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c4424342f77179e689af_1767097989133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks Tap Record ₹13 Lakh Crore via CDs as Deposits Dry Up – What it Means for Your Money!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Tap-Record-13-Lakh-Crore-via-CDs-as-Deposits-Dry-Up-What-it-Means-for-Your-Money/6953c3944342f77179e68702</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Tap-Record-13-Lakh-Crore-via-CDs-as-Deposits-Dry-Up-What-it-Means-for-Your-Money/6953c3944342f77179e68702</guid><description>Indian banks have raised a record ₹13.17 lakh crore through Certificates of Deposit (CDs) in 2025, driven by sluggish deposit growth and pressure on low-cost CASA funds. This marks a significant increase and highlights banks' growing reliance on wholesale funding to support credit expansion. Major banks like Bank of Baroda and HDFC Bank are leading these issuances. CD rates have eased but show signs of firming up.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:08:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c3944342f77179e68701_1767097629835.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Credit Card Rewards Get a MAJOR Makeover! BOBCARD CEO Reveals New Focus on Everyday Value &amp; Discipline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Credit-Card-Rewards-Get-a-MAJOR-Makeover-BOBCARD-CEO-Reveals-New-Focus-on-Everyday-Value-and-Discipline/6953c3584342f77179e685f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Credit-Card-Rewards-Get-a-MAJOR-Makeover-BOBCARD-CEO-Reveals-New-Focus-on-Everyday-Value-and-Discipline/6953c3584342f77179e685f9</guid><description>Credit cards are shifting focus from aspirational travel perks to everyday value and responsible usage, according to BOBCARD MD &amp; CEO Ravindra Rai. He explains that evolving consumer habits and innovations like UPI integration are transforming credit cards into more personalized, disciplined payment tools that reward consistent, timely repayment over interest dependence. This marks a reset towards sustainable benefits relevant to daily spending.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:08:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c3584342f77179e685f8_1767097449888.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pilot Crisis Erupts: IndiGo &amp; Air India in Fierce Hiring War Amidst New Rule Chaos!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Pilot-Crisis-Erupts-IndiGo-and-Air-India-in-Fierce-Hiring-War-Amidst-New-Rule-Chaos/6953c2cc4342f77179e683a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Pilot-Crisis-Erupts-IndiGo-and-Air-India-in-Fierce-Hiring-War-Amidst-New-Rule-Chaos/6953c2cc4342f77179e683a1</guid><description>A critical shortage of airline captains is fueling an intense hiring battle between IndiGo and the Air India group. New Flight Duty Time Limitation (FDTL) rules have led to disruptions and a scramble for pilots, with airlines offering joining bonuses up to ₹50 lakh. Both carriers are hiring rapidly, often just to replace departing pilots who are moving between domestic airlines or joining foreign carriers. This competition highlights the urgent need for airlines to improve working conditions and pay to retain experienced aviators.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:06:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c2cc4342f77179e683a0_1767097391300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerages Reveal 2026 Stock Stars: Unlock Massive Gains with These High-Conviction Picks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokerages-Reveal-2026-Stock-Stars-Unlock-Massive-Gains-with-These-High-Conviction-Picks/6953c2634342f77179e68218</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokerages-Reveal-2026-Stock-Stars-Unlock-Massive-Gains-with-These-High-Conviction-Picks/6953c2634342f77179e68218</guid><description>Leading brokerages like Jefferies, Motilal Oswal, Religare, and Elara Securities have unveiled their top stock recommendations for 2026, targeting a 12-18 month horizon. Their high-conviction picks focus on sectors benefiting from strong domestic savings, scaling quick commerce models, key pharmaceutical plays, and IT services. Stocks like Zomato (Blinkit), HCL Technologies, Groww, and Zydus Lifesciences are highlighted for their potential upside driven by strategic business model transitions and market leadership.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:03:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c2634342f77179e68217_1767097264372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Poised to Revolutionize India: $1.7 Trillion Economic Boom by 2035!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Poised-to-Revolutionize-India-17-Trillion-Economic-Boom-by-2035/6953c0d54342f77179e67d10</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Poised-to-Revolutionize-India-17-Trillion-Economic-Boom-by-2035/6953c0d54342f77179e67d10</guid><description>The Indian government forecasts that Artificial Intelligence (AI) could inject $1.7 trillion into the nation's economy by 2035, identifying it as a primary growth driver. Initiatives like the IndiaAI Mission, backed by over ₹10,300 crore, aim to boost computing infrastructure, support startups, develop indigenous AI models, and enhance skilling programs. AI adoption is expected to transform sectors such as healthcare, agriculture, and manufacturing, creating new job categories and expanding India's AI talent pool significantly.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c0d54342f77179e67d0f_1767096720938.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US RELIANCE ON INDIA SOLAR FACES MAJOR THREAT: 97% Exports Under Fire From New Tariffs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/US-RELIANCE-ON-INDIA-SOLAR-FACES-MAJOR-THREAT-97percent-Exports-Under-Fire-From-New-Tariffs/6953c1324342f77179e67e4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/US-RELIANCE-ON-INDIA-SOLAR-FACES-MAJOR-THREAT-97percent-Exports-Under-Fire-From-New-Tariffs/6953c1324342f77179e67e4c</guid><description>India's solar module exports are overwhelmingly reliant on the United States, with approximately 97% of shipments directed there between 2023 and 2025. This surge is driven by US restrictions on Chinese imports and the lower cost of Indian solar panels. However, Indian exporters face significant challenges, including a US investigation into alleged dumping margins of 123% and a potential 50% tariff from August 2025, as the US aims to boost domestic production.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c1324342f77179e67e4b_1767096816830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economy Set for $1.7 Trillion AI Boom by 2035: Government Unveils Massive Growth Plan!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Economy-Set-for-17-Trillion-AI-Boom-by-2035-Government-Unveils-Massive-Growth-Plan/6953c0084342f77179e67b10</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Economy-Set-for-17-Trillion-AI-Boom-by-2035-Government-Unveils-Massive-Growth-Plan/6953c0084342f77179e67b10</guid><description>Government estimates predict Artificial Intelligence (AI) could inject $1.7 trillion into India's economy by 2035, positioning it as a key growth driver. The IndiaAI Mission, backed by over ₹10,300 crore, aims to build computing infrastructure, support startups, and develop indigenous AI models. This initiative is expected to boost productivity across sectors like healthcare, agriculture, and finance, creating new jobs and enhancing skills. The strategy includes developing affordable AI infrastructure, expanding GPU capacity, and promoting AI tools in Indian languages for broader accessibility.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:57:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953c0084342f77179e67b0f_1767096434709.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Shocked: ₹458 Crore GST Blow! Airline Vows Fierce Fight Against Tax Order!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Shocked-458-Crore-GST-Blow-Airline-Vows-Fierce-Fight-Against-Tax-Order/6953bbea4342f77179e6717a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Shocked-458-Crore-GST-Blow-Airline-Vows-Fierce-Fight-Against-Tax-Order/6953bbea4342f77179e6717a</guid><description>InterGlobe Aviation, the parent of IndiGo, has disclosed receiving a ₹458.3 crore Goods and Services Tax (GST) demand for financial years 2018-19 to 2022-23. The airline company considers the order erroneous and intends to contest it through the appellate process, stating it expects no material financial impact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:39:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953bbea4342f77179e67179_1767095590585.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Rate Cuts Fail: Indian Corporates Shun Bonds Despite 125 Bps Cuts; Rising Yields Dampen Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Rate-Cuts-Fail-Indian-Corporates-Shun-Bonds-Despite-125-Bps-Cuts-Rising-Yields-Dampen-Demand/6953bb724342f77179e6702f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Rate-Cuts-Fail-Indian-Corporates-Shun-Bonds-Despite-125-Bps-Cuts-Rising-Yields-Dampen-Demand/6953bb724342f77179e6702f</guid><description>Indian corporates and financial institutions raised nearly the same amount via domestic bonds in 2025 as in 2024, at ₹10.84 lakh crore, despite the Reserve Bank of India cutting rates by 125 basis points. Rising government bond yields and cautious investor demand, particularly in the second half of the year, offset the benefits of lower borrowing costs. Major issuers like NABARD and Power Finance Corporation became more cautious, with some withdrawing issuances due to high yields.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:36:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953bb724342f77179e6702e_1767095224030.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Investment Blueprint: Experts Reveal Must-Have Strategy for Wealth Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/2026-Investment-Blueprint-Experts-Reveal-Must-Have-Strategy-for-Wealth-Growth/6953bd2a4342f77179e673fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/2026-Investment-Blueprint-Experts-Reveal-Must-Have-Strategy-for-Wealth-Growth/6953bd2a4342f77179e673fb</guid><description>Financial experts are guiding investors for 2026, emphasizing quality stock selection over momentum, and advocating for balanced portfolios. Key strategies include diversifying across stocks, bonds, and 5-10% in gold/silver, strengthening emergency funds, reducing debt, and utilizing tax-efficient government schemes. This approach aims to build resilience, ensure liquidity, and achieve sustainable wealth growth amid evolving global and domestic economic trends.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:36:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953bd2a4342f77179e673fa_1767095781412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Boom or Bust? India's State Firms Automate as Orders Surge, Workforce Shrinks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Boom-or-Bust-Indias-State-Firms-Automate-as-Orders-Surge-Workforce-Shrinks/6953bae54342f77179e66ee5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Boom-or-Bust-Indias-State-Firms-Automate-as-Orders-Surge-Workforce-Shrinks/6953bae54342f77179e66ee5</guid><description>India's defence Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs) are undergoing a major transformation. Despite securing approved defence orders worth ₹79,000 crore, companies like Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd (HAL) are reducing staff by up to 24% as they shift towards automation and advanced engineering. This contrasts with growth at firms like MIDHANI and shipyards, while the private sector's contribution to defence output is set to reach 23.5% in FY25, signalling a new era of public-private collaboration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:36:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953bae54342f77179e66ee4_1767095074008.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Prudential Fund: The ONLY Large-Cap Champion Beating Benchmarks for 10 Years!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/ICICI-Prudential-Fund-The-ONLY-Large-Cap-Champion-Beating-Benchmarks-for-10-Years/6953ba0a4342f77179e66c82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/ICICI-Prudential-Fund-The-ONLY-Large-Cap-Champion-Beating-Benchmarks-for-10-Years/6953ba0a4342f77179e66c82</guid><description>ICICI Prudential Large Cap Fund has uniquely outperformed the Nifty 100 TRI benchmark across 1-year, 5-year, and 10-year periods. Despite a volatile year for equities, the fund demonstrated resilience and delivered strong risk-adjusted returns. With an Assets Under Management (AUM) exceeding ₹78,000 crore, it stands as the largest in its category, reflecting significant investor confidence in its strategy, which focuses on market leaders.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:31:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ba0a4342f77179e66c81_1767094899657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crude Oil Prices Stuck? Expert Narendra Taneja Reveals Natural Gas's Impending Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Crude-Oil-Prices-Stuck-Expert-Narendra-Taneja-Reveals-Natural-Gass-Impending-Surge/6953b6df4342f77179e66504</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Crude-Oil-Prices-Stuck-Expert-Narendra-Taneja-Reveals-Natural-Gass-Impending-Surge/6953b6df4342f77179e66504</guid><description>Energy expert Narendra Taneja forecasts crude oil prices will likely remain range-bound through Q1 2026, barring geopolitical shocks. Surplus supply and moderate demand, driven partly by India, are key factors, with US policy supporting prices around $60 a barrel. Conversely, natural gas demand is expected to see a structural rise due to the global shift towards cleaner energy and the expansion of LNG, particularly in Asia.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:08:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b6df4342f77179e66503_1767094261056.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Healthcare M&amp;A Boom Hits Snag: Quality Deals Drying Up!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Healthcare-MandA-Boom-Hits-Snag-Quality-Deals-Drying-Up/6953b6704342f77179e662ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Healthcare-MandA-Boom-Hits-Snag-Quality-Deals-Drying-Up/6953b6704342f77179e662ef</guid><description>India's healthcare sector is experiencing robust merger and acquisition (M&amp;A) activity, fueled by changing consumer preferences and strong investor interest. Despite nearly 135 deals worth $5.5 billion in the past year, industry experts warn that the availability of prime acquisition targets is diminishing. This is leading companies like KIMS Hospitals to adopt more selective strategies, focusing on multi-speciality hospitals and greenfield projects, while PE interest grows in niche segments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:08:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b6704342f77179e662ee_1767094263228.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>B L Kashyap Secures ₹364 Cr Chennai Order: Construction Giant's Big Win!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/B-L-Kashyap-Secures-364-Cr-Chennai-Order-Construction-Giants-Big-Win/6953b6914342f77179e66356</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/B-L-Kashyap-Secures-364-Cr-Chennai-Order-Construction-Giants-Big-Win/6953b6914342f77179e66356</guid><description>B L Kashyap and Sons Ltd has secured a substantial order worth ₹364.07 crore for civil and structural works in Chennai. The contract is for the 'Embassy Splendid Tech Zone – Block' project, boosting the company's commercial real estate portfolio. This follows a recent ₹615.69 crore order, highlighting a strong period for the firm. The company's shares ended Tuesday trading 1.59% higher at ₹55.50 on the NSE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:08:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b6914342f77179e66355_1767094394364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Deepa Jewellers Files IPO Papers: Rs 250 Crore Plan to Sparkle on Dalal Street!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Deepa-Jewellers-Files-IPO-Papers-Rs-250-Crore-Plan-to-Sparkle-on-Dalal-Street/6953b57d4342f77179e65fc4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Deepa-Jewellers-Files-IPO-Papers-Rs-250-Crore-Plan-to-Sparkle-on-Dalal-Street/6953b57d4342f77179e65fc4</guid><description>Deepa Jewellers, a Hyderabad-based B2B jewellery supplier, has filed preliminary IPO papers with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi). The company aims to raise ₹250 crore through a fresh issue of shares, with promoters also planning an offer for sale. Proceeds will fund long-term working capital and inventory procurement, supporting the company's growth in the organised jewellery market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:08:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b57d4342f77179e65fc3_1767093840140.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Gears Up for PM-KUSUM 2.0: Massive Solar Push for Farmers on the Horizon!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Gears-Up-for-PM-KUSUM-20-Massive-Solar-Push-for-Farmers-on-the-Horizon/6953b5664342f77179e65f44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Gears-Up-for-PM-KUSUM-20-Massive-Solar-Push-for-Farmers-on-the-Horizon/6953b5664342f77179e65f44</guid><description>The Indian government is planning PM-KUSUM 2.0, a successor to the successful PM-KUSUM scheme, to boost decentralized solar energy in agriculture. The new phase will build on previous efforts, focusing on feeder-level solarization and potentially introducing new features like agro-photovoltaic models to overcome land constraints and improve farmer access to reliable daytime power. This initiative aims to reduce reliance on grid electricity and ease discoms' subsidy burdens, signalling a continued strong commitment to renewable energy in the agricultural sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:05:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b5664342f77179e65f43_1767094173633.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki Soars to Record High! Auto Stocks Surge on Exciting Sales Data &amp; Strong IIP Boost – What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Soars-to-Record-High-Auto-Stocks-Surge-on-Exciting-Sales-Data-and-Strong-IIP-Boost-Whats-Next/6953b53b4342f77179e65ea5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Soars-to-Record-High-Auto-Stocks-Surge-on-Exciting-Sales-Data-and-Strong-IIP-Boost-Whats-Next/6953b53b4342f77179e65ea5</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki shares reached a fresh all-time high as auto stocks rallied ahead of December sales data. Analysts anticipate double-digit sales volume growth across categories, driven by factors like GST cuts and new products. Strong industrial production (IIP) data, which hit a 25-month high in November, further boosted sentiment for the auto sector. Geojit Investments noted the sales numbers' significance for economic growth. Several auto majors like Hero MotoCorp, Bajaj Auto, and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra also saw significant gains.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:05:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b53b4342f77179e65ea4_1767093685651.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shock Drop: India Primary Dealers' Bond Commission Plummets 65% - RBI Report Reveals Why!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shock-Drop-India-Primary-Dealers-Bond-Commission-Plummets-65percent-RBI-Report-Reveals-Why/6953b4af4342f77179e65c80</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shock-Drop-India-Primary-Dealers-Bond-Commission-Plummets-65percent-RBI-Report-Reveals-Why/6953b4af4342f77179e65c80</guid><description>Primary Dealers' underwriting commissions in India plummeted 65% to ₹14.5 crore in FY25 from ₹43.1 crore in FY24. This steep fall, driven by strong demand for government securities and minimal devolvement, led to lower average commission rates. While PD participation remained strong, the Reserve Bank of India's latest report indicates early signs of a recovery in commission rates during the first half of FY26.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:05:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b4af4342f77179e65c7f_1767094058480.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jewellery Giant Deepa Jewellers Files for Mega IPO: Rs 250 Crore Fundraise Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Jewellery-Giant-Deepa-Jewellers-Files-for-Mega-IPO-Rs-250-Crore-Fundraise-Revealed/6953b41f4342f77179e65ad6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Jewellery-Giant-Deepa-Jewellers-Files-for-Mega-IPO-Rs-250-Crore-Fundraise-Revealed/6953b41f4342f77179e65ad6</guid><description>Telangana-based Deepa Jewellers, a leading processor and supplier of hallmarked gold jewellery, has submitted preliminary documents to SEBI for an Initial Public Offering (IPO). The company plans to raise Rs 250 crore through a fresh issue, primarily for long-term working capital and inventory expansion. Promoters Ashish Agarwal and his wife will also sell up to 1.18 crore equity shares via an offer-for-sale. Deepa Jewellers has shown robust financial growth, with profits soaring 66.7% in the year ended March 2025.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:05:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b41f4342f77179e65ad5_1767093531577.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Festive Season Fizzle: Consumption Goods Output Hits 3-Year Low Despite GST Cuts!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Festive-Season-Fizzle-Consumption-Goods-Output-Hits-3-Year-Low-Despite-GST-Cuts/6953b3434342f77179e657f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Festive-Season-Fizzle-Consumption-Goods-Output-Hits-3-Year-Low-Despite-GST-Cuts/6953b3434342f77179e657f8</guid><description>India's festive season from September to November saw a muted boost for consumption goods output. Production of everyday essentials, known as non-durables, fell to a three-year low, while big-ticket items like electronics, known as durables, reached a two-year trough. This indicates a lack of strong consumer spending despite recent GST rate reductions. Economists remain cautiously optimistic, anticipating future support from lower interest rates and tax reliefs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:04:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b3434342f77179e657f7_1767093146371.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai Airport Freighter Shutdown: Exporters Warn of Massive Disruption, Cargo May Shift to Delhi &amp; Bengaluru!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbai-Airport-Freighter-Shutdown-Exporters-Warn-of-Massive-Disruption-Cargo-May-Shift-to-Delhi-and-Bengaluru/6953b4234342f77179e65b06</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbai-Airport-Freighter-Shutdown-Exporters-Warn-of-Massive-Disruption-Cargo-May-Shift-to-Delhi-and-Bengaluru/6953b4234342f77179e65b06</guid><description>Maharashtra exporters may reroute air cargo to Delhi or Bengaluru following a proposed 10-month freighter shutdown at Mumbai airport for repairs. Industry body Air Cargo Agents Association of India (ACAAI) warns this will increase operating expenses for exporters already facing pressure and that Navi Mumbai airport is not yet a viable alternative due to limited international passenger flights for belly cargo.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:04:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b4234342f77179e65b05_1767093552986.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cement Boom Ahead? ICRA Predicts 7% Growth &amp; Massive Capacity Expansion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Boom-Ahead-ICRA-Predicts-7percent-Growth-and-Massive-Capacity-Expansion/6953b3644342f77179e6585a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Boom-Ahead-ICRA-Predicts-7percent-Growth-and-Massive-Capacity-Expansion/6953b3644342f77179e6585a</guid><description>India's cement industry is set for robust growth, with ICRA forecasting volumes to rise 6-7% in FY27, driven by housing and infrastructure demand. The sector plans significant capacity expansion, adding 85-90 million tonnes per annum by FY27. Profitability is expected to improve in FY26 due to better pricing and volumes, though FY27 may see a slight moderation from rising input costs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:01:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b3644342f77179e65859_1767093212455.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rebel Foods IPO Dream: Cloud Kitchen Giant Shrinks Losses, Boosts Revenue Ahead of Public Listing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Rebel-Foods-IPO-Dream-Cloud-Kitchen-Giant-Shrinks-Losses-Boosts-Revenue-Ahead-of-Public-Listing/6953b25d4342f77179e65541</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Rebel-Foods-IPO-Dream-Cloud-Kitchen-Giant-Shrinks-Losses-Boosts-Revenue-Ahead-of-Public-Listing/6953b25d4342f77179e65541</guid><description>Rebel Foods, a leading Indian cloud kitchen operator, is strategically recalibrating for a potential IPO in 2026. The company narrowed its net loss to INR 336.6 Cr in FY25 while growing revenue by 14% to INR 1,617.4 Cr. It also launched QuickiES, a 15-minute delivery service, and secured $25 Mn funding, valuing it at $1.4 Bn, as it expands its hybrid model beyond cloud kitchens.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:56:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b25d4342f77179e65540_1767093016134.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economic Juggernaut: Surpasses Japan to Become World's 4th Largest Economy! What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Juggernaut-Surpasses-Japan-to-Become-Worlds-4th-Largest-Economy-Whats-Next/6953b10d4342f77179e6522b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Juggernaut-Surpasses-Japan-to-Become-Worlds-4th-Largest-Economy-Whats-Next/6953b10d4342f77179e6522b</guid><description>India has achieved a historic milestone, officially becoming the world's fourth-largest economy by nominal GDP, surpassing Japan. This significant feat underscores India's position as the fastest-growing major economy, with projections indicating it will soon overtake Germany to become the third largest. The nation is currently experiencing a favourable 'Goldilocks period' characterized by strong growth and low inflation, signalling robust economic momentum.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:53:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953b10d4342f77179e6522a_1767092563138.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stock Split Mania Incoming! 4 Indian Firms Announce January 2026 Splits – Get Ready to Own More Shares!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Stock-Split-Mania-Incoming-4-Indian-Firms-Announce-January-2026-Splits-Get-Ready-to-Own-More-Shares/6953ad3e4342f77179e64998</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Stock-Split-Mania-Incoming-4-Indian-Firms-Announce-January-2026-Splits-Get-Ready-to-Own-More-Shares/6953ad3e4342f77179e64998</guid><description>Four Indian companies, including Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd (MCX), A-1 Ltd, SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd, and Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd, have announced stock splits with record dates in January 2026. These corporate actions aim to increase share liquidity and accessibility. Splits range from 2:1 to 10:1, with face values adjusted accordingly. Investors must own shares before the ex-split date to be eligible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ad3e4342f77179e64997_1767091874527.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market Closes Flat: Auto &amp; Metal Stocks Surge Amid Mixed Trading Session</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Market-Closes-Flat-Auto-and-Metal-Stocks-Surge-Amid-Mixed-Trading-Session/6953ad7c4342f77179e64a50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Market-Closes-Flat-Auto-and-Metal-Stocks-Surge-Amid-Mixed-Trading-Session/6953ad7c4342f77179e64a50</guid><description>Indian equity markets closed nearly flat on Tuesday, December 30, with the BSE Sensex slipping 20 points to 84,675 and the NSE Nifty settling at 25,939. While banking stocks, especially PSU banks, saw strong gains ahead of earnings, the auto and metal sectors also rallied nearly 2% each, supported by monthly sales data expectations and higher global metal prices. However, a negative market breadth and pressure in midcap stocks indicated broader weakness, with the midcap index declining. Individual stocks like Eternal and Max Healthcare faced losses, while Shriram Finance and Timex Group India saw significant gains.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:36:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ad7c4342f77179e64a4f_1767091942788.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Property Puzzle: Is Your Dream Home a Wealth Machine or a Financial Burden?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Property-Puzzle-Is-Your-Dream-Home-a-Wealth-Machine-or-a-Financial-Burden/6953ae194342f77179e64bc7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Property-Puzzle-Is-Your-Dream-Home-a-Wealth-Machine-or-a-Financial-Burden/6953ae194342f77179e64bc7</guid><description>Buying a home in India is now significantly more expensive due to record high prices and elevated interest rates. Experts advise that a home becomes a wealth-building asset when it offers long-term financial value beyond lifestyle. Key factors for success include a stable income, a holding period of 7-10 years, keeping Equated Monthly Instalments (EMIs) within 35-40% of income, and strategic location choice, especially areas with future infrastructure development. While rental income provides cash flow support, long-term price appreciation is the primary driver of wealth creation in real estate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:34:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ae194342f77179e64bc6_1767091981048.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VC Pullback Hits Climate Tech, But Zerodha's Rainmatter DOUBLES DOWN! Their 15-Year Secret Strategy Revealed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/VC-Pullback-Hits-Climate-Tech-But-Zerodhas-Rainmatter-DOUBLES-DOWN-Their-15-Year-Secret-Strategy-Revealed/6953acae4342f77179e6480d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/VC-Pullback-Hits-Climate-Tech-But-Zerodhas-Rainmatter-DOUBLES-DOWN-Their-15-Year-Secret-Strategy-Revealed/6953acae4342f77179e6480d</guid><description>Rainmatter Capital, Zerodha's investment arm, is increasing its focus on climate technology investments despite a general slowdown by other Indian venture capital funds in the sector. Company officials state they are focused on a 10-15 year investment horizon, unaffected by short-term market trends. Rainmatter has invested ₹350 crore in 43 climate tech companies since 2016, prioritizing areas like waste recycling and controlled farming over heavily funded EV ventures. This contrarian approach aims to support entrepreneurs tackling critical problems who may not attract capital from traditional growth-focused VCs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:32:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953acae4342f77179e6480c_1767091508588.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai Motor India Ventures into Commercial Mobility with New Prime Taxi Range!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-Motor-India-Ventures-into-Commercial-Mobility-with-New-Prime-Taxi-Range/6953abe34342f77179e64617</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-Motor-India-Ventures-into-Commercial-Mobility-with-New-Prime-Taxi-Range/6953abe34342f77179e64617</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India has launched its dedicated taxi offerings, the Prime HB hatchback and Prime SD sedan, targeting fleet operators and taxi entrepreneurs. These models focus on low operating costs, reliability, and higher earning potential, powered by 1.2-litre petrol and CNG engines. Priced from ₹5.99 lakh (Prime HB) and ₹6.89 lakh (Prime SD), they offer extended warranty options and a claimed total cost of ownership of about 47 paise per km.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:28:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953abe34342f77179e64616_1767091240346.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's IPO Boom Masks 18% Fundraising Crash: What Every Investor Needs to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-IPO-Boom-Masks-18percent-Fundraising-Crash-What-Every-Investor-Needs-to-Know/6953ab744342f77179e6449e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-IPO-Boom-Masks-18percent-Fundraising-Crash-What-Every-Investor-Needs-to-Know/6953ab744342f77179e6449e</guid><description>Despite a record year for Initial Public Offerings (IPOs) in India, overall public equity fundraising saw an 18% decline in 2025, dropping to ₹3.06 lakh crore. This fall is attributed to significantly lower mobilization through follow-on public offers (FPOs), offer-for-sale routes (OFS), and qualified institutional placements (QIPs), according to PRIME Database. While 103 companies raised a record ₹1.76 lakh crore via mainboard IPOs, the decrease in other capital-raising avenues raises concerns about future funding for corporates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:27:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953ab744342f77179e6449d_1767091392487.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Laurus Labs Stock Explodes 82% in 2025! Best Year in 5 Years - What's Driving the Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Laurus-Labs-Stock-Explodes-82percent-in-2025-Best-Year-in-5-Years-Whats-Driving-the-Surge/6953a6e14342f77179e63a1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Laurus-Labs-Stock-Explodes-82percent-in-2025-Best-Year-in-5-Years-Whats-Driving-the-Surge/6953a6e14342f77179e63a1a</guid><description>Laurus Labs shares hit a new high of ₹1,095, rallying 82% year-to-date in 2025, marking its best annual performance in five years. This surge is driven by robust growth in its Contract Development and Manufacturing Organisation (CDMO) and Generics divisions. Revenue grew 33% year-on-year in H1FY26, with net profit soaring to ₹358 crore. Analysts are optimistic, with Motilal Oswal Financial Services setting a target price of ₹1,110 based on strong future earnings growth expectations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:06:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953a6e14342f77179e63a19_1767090146353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia's Rs 45,000 Crore AI Bet on Intel: Chip Giant's Future Secured?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidias-Rs-45000-Crore-AI-Bet-on-Intel-Chip-Giants-Future-Secured/6953a69f4342f77179e63971</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidias-Rs-45000-Crore-AI-Bet-on-Intel-Chip-Giants-Future-Secured/6953a69f4342f77179e63971</guid><description>Nvidia has finalized a $5 billion (approximately ₹44,955 crore) investment in Intel, acquiring over 214.7 million shares. This deal provides crucial financial support to Intel and establishes a technology partnership. Intel will design custom data-center processors to be packaged with Nvidia's AI chips, enhancing chip communication speeds. The strategic move could reshape the competitive landscape for rivals like Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company and Advanced Micro Devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:05:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953a69f4342f77179e63970_1767090571272.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Stocks Cautioned: Quest's CIO Rakesh Vyas Turns Bullish on Banks, Consumption Ahead of Earnings!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/IT-Stocks-Cautioned-Quests-CIO-Rakesh-Vyas-Turns-Bullish-on-Banks-Consumption-Ahead-of-Earnings/6953a6f64342f77179e63a6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/IT-Stocks-Cautioned-Quests-CIO-Rakesh-Vyas-Turns-Bullish-on-Banks-Consumption-Ahead-of-Earnings/6953a6f64342f77179e63a6e</guid><description>Quest Investment Managers CIO Rakesh Vyas is cautious on IT stocks due to slowing growth but sees limited downside. He is positive on banking, financial services, and select consumption platforms like Zomato and Swiggy, expecting improving margins and visibility. Vyas anticipates a broader earnings recovery in Q3, driven by BFSI and consumption, favoring smaller private and PSU banks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:05:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953a6f64342f77179e63a6d_1767090067869.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>