<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:18:25 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Brigade Enterprises Bets Big on Hyderabad: Growth Engine or Concentrated Risk?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Brigade-Enterprises-Bets-Big-on-Hyderabad-Growth-Engine-or-Concentrated-Risk/6999f3cf84b7d0fe3ee3cd85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Brigade-Enterprises-Bets-Big-on-Hyderabad-Growth-Engine-or-Concentrated-Risk/6999f3cf84b7d0fe3ee3cd85</guid><description>Brigade Enterprises is doubling down on Hyderabad, planning a massive 10.5 million sq ft development footprint by FY27 across residential, office, retail, and hospitality. While the city shows strong economic growth and infrastructure development, this aggressive, singular focus raises questions about portfolio diversification and competitive pressures within a rapidly evolving market. The company's strategy hinges on Hyderabad's sustained boom, a risk factor in itselff3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 18:05:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6999f3cf84b7d0fe3ee3cd84.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UFlex Q3 FY26 PAT Swings To Profit; Revenue Down 3.8%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UFlex-Q3-FY26-PAT-Swings-To-Profit-Revenue-Down-38percent/6999f32084b7d0fe3ee3ccbc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UFlex-Q3-FY26-PAT-Swings-To-Profit-Revenue-Down-38percent/6999f32084b7d0fe3ee3ccbc</guid><description>UFlex reported a Q3 FY26 PAT of ₹121 crore against a loss last year, driven by aseptic packaging growth and film price recovery. However, revenue dipped 3.8% YoY due to US tariffs impacting international sales. The company expects leverage to peak as new projects in Egypt, Mexico, and India near commissioning by Q1 FY27.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 18:02:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999f32084b7d0fe3ee3ccbb_1771697036726.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DeFi Security Arms Race: Specialized AI Detects 92% of Exploits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/DeFi-Security-Arms-Race-Specialized-AI-Detects-92percent-of-Exploits/6999ec8fccd2a5b8cdc4ce66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/DeFi-Security-Arms-Race-Specialized-AI-Detects-92percent-of-Exploits/6999ec8fccd2a5b8cdc4ce66</guid><description>A new benchmark reveals purpose-built AI security agents detect 92% of exploited DeFi smart contract vulnerabilities, vastly outperforming general-purpose models like GPT-5.1. This specialized approach, leveraging domain-specific methodologies, flagged vulnerabilities representing $96.8 million in potential losses, contrasting with $7.5 million from baseline agents. The findings underscore a widening gap between AI-driven offensive and defensive capabilities in decentralized finance, as exploit costs plummet and exploit sophistication escalates12.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:34:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999ec8fccd2a5b8cdc4ce65_1771695373370.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Brazil Forge Pharma &amp; Resources Pacts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Brazil-Forge-Pharma-and-Resources-Pacts/6999eba0ccd2a5b8cdc4cd7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Brazil-Forge-Pharma-and-Resources-Pacts/6999eba0ccd2a5b8cdc4cd7a</guid><description>India and Brazil solidified key economic ties through multiple Memoranda of Understanding (MoUs), primarily targeting advancements in pharmaceuticals and iron ore trade. Biocon Biologics is set to co-develop Pertuzumab for metastatic breast cancer, while NMDC Ltd, Vale SA, and Adani Gangavaram Port will collaborate on an iron ore blending facility. These agreements, inked during Brazilian President Lula da Silva's visit, underscore a strategic push to enhance bilateral trade, R&amp;D, and supply chain capabilities in critical sectors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:30:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999eba0ccd2a5b8cdc4cd79_1771695178438.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Disruption: Indian IT Faces Execution Risk, Not Extinction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Disruption-Indian-IT-Faces-Execution-Risk-Not-Extinction/6999eb78ccd2a5b8cdc4cd40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Disruption-Indian-IT-Faces-Execution-Risk-Not-Extinction/6999eb78ccd2a5b8cdc4cd40</guid><description>The Indian IT sector, valued at $300 billion, faces existential questions amid rapid AI advancements. While some predict sector disappearance within five years, established players like Infosys and TCS are aggressively integrating AI, now contributing significant revenue. Analysts are divided, with some seeing AI as a tool that will expand IT services rather than replace them, emphasizing execution as the critical factor for future growth and resilience.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:29:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999eb78ccd2a5b8cdc4cd3f_1771695075816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Uni Abex Completes Thane Land Sale For ₹257.88 Cr; Boosts Cash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Uni-Abex-Completes-Thane-Land-Sale-For-25788-Cr-Boosts-Cash/6999e88fccd2a5b8cdc4cc24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Uni-Abex-Completes-Thane-Land-Sale-For-25788-Cr-Boosts-Cash/6999e88fccd2a5b8cdc4cc24</guid><description>Uni Abex Alloy Products Limited has announced the full completion of its land sale in Thane, Maharashtra, for approximately ₹257.88 crore. The transaction with M/s RSVM Hospitality Private Limited injects significant cash into the company, bolstering its financial position. This strategic divestment reduces the company's land holding in Thane to a marginal area.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999e88fccd2a5b8cdc4cc23_1771694358255.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Ventures into Startups: A Calculated Risk for MSME Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/SBI-Ventures-into-Startups-A-Calculated-Risk-for-MSME-Growth/6999e45fccd2a5b8cdc4cadb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/SBI-Ventures-into-Startups-A-Calculated-Risk-for-MSME-Growth/6999e45fccd2a5b8cdc4cadb</guid><description>State Bank of India is strategically investing in startup-focused funds and financial market infrastructure as part of an expanded MSME strategy. Managing Director Ravi Ranjan indicated direct equity participation and partnership schemes aim to accelerate MSME credit through innovation and employment generation. This pivot into the venture capital space, while aligned with a strong banking sector outlook and growing startup ecosystem, introduces inherent risks that SBI must manage alongside its commitment to stringent regulatory compliance. Analysts maintain a 'Buy' rating on SBI, anticipating continued growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:59:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999e45fccd2a5b8cdc4cada_1771693309249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HEG Promoter Group Faces SEBI Penalties for Insider Trading Violations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HEG-Promoter-Group-Faces-SEBI-Penalties-for-Insider-Trading-Violations/6999dfa6ccd2a5b8cdc4c9b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HEG-Promoter-Group-Faces-SEBI-Penalties-for-Insider-Trading-Violations/6999dfa6ccd2a5b8cdc4c9b5</guid><description>HEG Limited has disclosed violations of SEBI's insider trading regulations and its own code of conduct by designated promoter group members. Mr. Nivedan Churiwal, Ms. Shubha Churiwal, and Ms. Sudha Churiwal traded shares without mandatory clearance and failed to disclose transactions. Corrective actions include depositing a total of ₹33.87 lakh with SEBI as penalties, reinforcing the company's commitment to market integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:39:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999dfa6ccd2a5b8cdc4c9b4_1771692054209.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vadilal Director Resigns Citing Wage Violations; Company Reviews Compliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Vadilal-Director-Resigns-Citing-Wage-Violations-Company-Reviews-Compliance/6999d990730b6847a517874a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Vadilal-Director-Resigns-Citing-Wage-Violations-Company-Reviews-Compliance/6999d990730b6847a517874a</guid><description>Vadilal Industries faces a governance challenge after Independent Director Shivakumar Dega resigned, citing serious concerns over alleged minimum wage non-payment and statutory violations. The company has initiated a compliance review by forming a sub-committee and appointing independent advisors. This development raises questions about the company's adherence to regulations and its impact on workers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:13:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999d990730b6847a5178749_1771690498324.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eraaya Lifespaces Posts Profit; Faces Auditor Qual, ED Penalty, Legal Fight</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Eraaya-Lifespaces-Posts-Profit-Faces-Auditor-Qual-ED-Penalty-Legal-Fight/6999d8db730b6847a51786bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Eraaya-Lifespaces-Posts-Profit-Faces-Auditor-Qual-ED-Penalty-Legal-Fight/6999d8db730b6847a51786bf</guid><description>Eraaya Lifespaces reported a Q3 FY26 consolidated profit of ₹0.40 Cr on ₹72.06 Cr revenue, driven by Ebix acquisition. However, severe auditor qualifications regarding a ₹33.75 Cr parent loan, a ₹32.91 Cr ED penalty for FEMA non-compliance, and ongoing litigation over management control cast a dark shadow. Standalone revenue also declined 31%.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:10:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999d8db730b6847a51786be_1771690350711.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani's JAL Takeover Fuels F1 Return Ambitions for Buddh Circuit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adanis-JAL-Takeover-Fuels-F1-Return-Ambitions-for-Buddh-Circuit/6999d55a730b6847a517858f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adanis-JAL-Takeover-Fuels-F1-Return-Ambitions-for-Buddh-Circuit/6999d55a730b6847a517858f</guid><description>The Adani Group is reportedly exploring the reintroduction of Formula 1 racing at the Buddh International Circuit, a move intrinsically linked to its acquisition of debt-laden Jaiprakash Associates Ltd. (JAL). Karan Adani's personal engagement highlights the potential for India to re-establish itself on the global motorsport calendar. This strategic play leverages the circuit's infrastructure, acquired as part of a larger distressed asset consolidation effort, to tap into India's growing motorsport following and infrastructure development agenda. However, past tax disputes and financial viability concerns present significant hurdles.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:55:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999d55a730b6847a517858e_1771689448443.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Bets Big on Defense, Infra Amid Governance Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Bets-Big-on-Defense-Infra-Amid-Governance-Scrutiny/6999cc85730b6847a51782ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Bets-Big-on-Defense-Infra-Amid-Governance-Scrutiny/6999cc85730b6847a51782ee</guid><description>The Adani Group is doubling down on national infrastructure and defense manufacturing, bolstered by a $100 billion investment pledge focused on energy, logistics, and core materials, with AI integration as a key driver. Karan Adani highlighted strategic goals in defense indigenization, including a partnership with Embraer. However, the conglomerate continues to navigate significant regulatory scrutiny, including fresh allegations of secret offshore investments and ongoing probes from US authorities, casting a shadow over its ambitious expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:17:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999cc85730b6847a51782ed_1771687186198.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani-Embraer Jet Deal: India's Aerospace Ambition Meets Order Book Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Adani-Embraer-Jet-Deal-Indias-Aerospace-Ambition-Meets-Order-Book-Reality/6999cc3d730b6847a51782c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Adani-Embraer-Jet-Deal-Indias-Aerospace-Ambition-Meets-Order-Book-Reality/6999cc3d730b6847a51782c4</guid><description>Adani Defence &amp; Aerospace and Embraer have signed an MoU to establish a Final Assembly Line (FAL) for the E175 regional jet in India. This strategic move aligns with India's 'Aatmanirbhar Bharat' initiative and the UDAN scheme, seeking to bolster domestic aerospace capabilities and regional air connectivity. However, the venture's success hinges on Embraer securing over 200 firm orders, a substantial challenge given intense global competition and the nascent state of India's aerospace supply chain.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:16:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999cc3d730b6847a51782c3_1771687193489.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pharma Exports Surge 9.4%, Trade Deals Boost Global Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Exports-Surge-94percent-Trade-Deals-Boost-Global-Ambitions/6999c73f730b6847a5178108</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Exports-Surge-94percent-Trade-Deals-Boost-Global-Ambitions/6999c73f730b6847a5178108</guid><description>India's pharmaceutical exports reached $30.47 billion in fiscal year 2024-25, a 9.4% increase, reinforcing its position as a global generic leader. While the US and Europe remain dominant markets, new trade agreements with the EU and US are poised to improve market access and price competitiveness. The sector, valued at approximately $60 billion, is targeting double-digit export growth by 2026-27, supported by government initiatives and strategic investments in high-value segments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:54:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999c73f730b6847a5178107_1771685795110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SER Industries EGM Greenlights Name Change, Acquisitions &amp; Borrowing Powers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/SER-Industries-EGM-Greenlights-Name-Change-Acquisitions-and-Borrowing-Powers/6999c56b730b6847a5178058</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/SER-Industries-EGM-Greenlights-Name-Change-Acquisitions-and-Borrowing-Powers/6999c56b730b6847a5178058</guid><description>SER Industries Limited's Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) on February 20, 2026, concluded with shareholders unanimously approving all 13 resolutions. This includes a name change to 'Desi Farms India Limited', enhanced borrowing powers, and crucial approvals for preferential share and debenture issuances. These measures facilitate the company's strategic pivot into the food and dairy sector through the acquisition of SNA Milk and Milk Products Ltd. and DFSU Farmer Connect Private Ltd., signaling a major corporate restructuring.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:47:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999c56b730b6847a5178057_1771685372435.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Taylormade Renewables Board to Consider Fundraising on Feb 24</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Taylormade-Renewables-Board-to-Consider-Fundraising-on-Feb-24/6999c400730b6847a5177f9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Taylormade-Renewables-Board-to-Consider-Fundraising-on-Feb-24/6999c400730b6847a5177f9e</guid><description>Taylormade Renewables has scheduled a board meeting for February 24, 2026, to evaluate a proposal for raising funds. The company may opt for equity shares, debt securities, or other instruments, subject to necessary regulatory and shareholder approvals. This comes amid recent financial headwinds and a shift towards a recurring revenue model.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:41:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6999c400730b6847a5177f9d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Equities poised to reclaim leadership over precious metals in 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Equities-poised-to-reclaim-leadership-over-precious-metals-in-2026/6999bfd7730b6847a5177e20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Equities-poised-to-reclaim-leadership-over-precious-metals-in-2026/6999bfd7730b6847a5177e20</guid><description>Following a year where gold and silver significantly outpaced Indian equities, analysts predict a reversal in 2026. Precious metals benefited from geopolitical uncertainty and central bank buying, but Indian equity valuations are now presenting a more compelling case for growth. While gold and silver will remain important portfolio hedges, equities are expected to drive long-term wealth creation. Diversification and disciplined rebalancing are key.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:23:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6999bfd7730b6847a5177e1f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prestige Group Signs ₹115 Cr Deal for Bellandur Metro Station Co-Branding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Prestige-Group-Signs-115-Cr-Deal-for-Bellandur-Metro-Station-Co-Branding/6999b9b1730b6847a5177c38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Prestige-Group-Signs-115-Cr-Deal-for-Bellandur-Metro-Station-Co-Branding/6999b9b1730b6847a5177c38</guid><description>Prestige Group has entered a significant public-private partnership with BMRCL to adopt and co-brand the Bellandur Metro Station in Bengaluru for ₹115 crore. The 30-year agreement grants exclusive naming rights, commercial, and advertising entitlements, aiming to enhance brand visibility and integrate with urban transport infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:57:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b9b1730b6847a5177c37_1771682361957.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's CAG to Convene Power Sector Audit Conference</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-CAG-to-Convene-Power-Sector-Audit-Conference/6999b760730b6847a5177b2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-CAG-to-Convene-Power-Sector-Audit-Conference/6999b760730b6847a5177b2a</guid><description>India's Comptroller and Auditor General (CAG) is convening a national conference on February 23 to address evolving trends in the nation's power sector. The event will gather central and state government officials, alongside public sector power companies, to discuss emerging challenges and guide future audit strategies for generation, transmission, and distribution. Key areas for deliberation include digitalization, renewable energy integration, and the financial health of distribution companies (DISCOMs).</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:47:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b760730b6847a5177b29_1771681751751.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Life Board to Decide Interim Dividend Feb 25; Record Date March 6</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/SBI-Life-Board-to-Decide-Interim-Dividend-Feb-25-Record-Date-March-6/6999b675730b6847a5177a82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/SBI-Life-Board-to-Decide-Interim-Dividend-Feb-25-Record-Date-March-6/6999b675730b6847a5177a82</guid><description>SBI Life Insurance's Board of Directors will convene on February 25, 2026, to consider declaring an interim dividend for the Financial Year 2025-26. The record date for determining dividend eligibility is set for March 06, 2026. The company also tightened its insider trading window for designated persons from February 21 to February 27, 2026.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:43:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b675730b6847a5177a81_1771681531692.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Growth Pivot: Opportunity hinges on execution amid structural gaps</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Pivot-Opportunity-hinges-on-execution-amid-structural-gaps/6999b490730b6847a51779bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Pivot-Opportunity-hinges-on-execution-amid-structural-gaps/6999b490730b6847a51779bc</guid><description>India is positioned for economic growth, leveraging a demographic dividend until approximately 2047. However, realizing this potential requires focused investment in human capital, advanced manufacturing, and bridging deep-rooted regional economic disparities. The nation targets substantial foreign direct investment, even as global trends favor developed economies, and faces the dual challenge of attracting AI-driven innovation while potentially disrupting its established IT services sector. Success hinges on effective state-level execution and skilled workforce development.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:35:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b490730b6847a51779bb_1771681074485.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fusion Finance Promoters Seek Reclassification to Public Shareholder Status</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fusion-Finance-Promoters-Seek-Reclassification-to-Public-Shareholder-Status/6999b2a8730b6847a51778e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fusion-Finance-Promoters-Seek-Reclassification-to-Public-Shareholder-Status/6999b2a8730b6847a51778e6</guid><description>Fusion Finance Limited is processing requests from key shareholders, including Devesh Sachdev and Mini Sachdev, to reclassify their shares from 'Promoter/Promoter Group' to 'Public' shareholder category. This move involves 45,34,863 shares and requires approvals from the company's Board, shareholders, and stock exchanges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:27:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b2a8730b6847a51778e5_1771680538953.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE goes nanosecond: Speed race intensifies globally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-goes-nanosecond-Speed-race-intensifies-globally/6999b17f730b6847a51777fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-goes-nanosecond-Speed-race-intensifies-globally/6999b17f730b6847a51777fa</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange of India is set to achieve nanosecond trading response times for equities and derivatives by April 2026, a move that propels it to the forefront of global market speed. This upgrade significantly boosts order handling capacity and expands co-location infrastructure, aiming to accommodate escalating high-frequency trading volumes. However, the pursuit of extreme speed intensifies the competitive race among exchanges and amplifies concerns regarding market volatility and systemic risks, particularly for retail investors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:22:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b17f730b6847a51777f9_1771680277261.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Life Board to Consider Interim Dividend for FY26 on Feb 25</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/SBI-Life-Board-to-Consider-Interim-Dividend-for-FY26-on-Feb-25/6999b147730b6847a5177786</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/SBI-Life-Board-to-Consider-Interim-Dividend-for-FY26-on-Feb-25/6999b147730b6847a5177786</guid><description>SBI Life Insurance's Board of Directors will convene on February 25, 2026, to deliberate on declaring an interim dividend for the Financial Year 2025-26. The company has also set March 06, 2026, as the record date for this potential payout. This announcement signals a potential return of capital to shareholders, contingent on the board's approval.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:21:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b147730b6847a5177785_1771680223496.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Peptris Lands $7.7M Series A for AI Drug Discovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Peptris-Lands-77M-Series-A-for-AI-Drug-Discovery/6999b105730b6847a5177752</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Peptris-Lands-77M-Series-A-for-AI-Drug-Discovery/6999b105730b6847a5177752</guid><description>Bengaluru-based Peptris has closed a Rs 70 crore ($7.7 million) Series A funding round, co-led by IAN Alpha Fund and Speciale Invest. The capital will accelerate its AI-powered drug discovery programs towards clinical readiness. Peptris targets critical bottlenecks in the early stages of drug development, aiming to reduce failure rates and costs. This funding aligns with a significant global surge in AI adoption within the pharmaceutical R&amp;D sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:20:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999b105730b6847a5177751_1771680131950.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Raymond Realty Shareholders Greenlight ESOP 2025 with Overwhelming 99.71% Approval</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Raymond-Realty-Shareholders-Greenlight-ESOP-2025-with-Overwhelming-9971percent-Approval/6999ad45730b6847a5177618</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Raymond-Realty-Shareholders-Greenlight-ESOP-2025-with-Overwhelming-9971percent-Approval/6999ad45730b6847a5177618</guid><description>Raymond Realty Limited shareholders have overwhelmingly approved the 'Raymond Realty Employees Stock Option Plan 2025' and related resolutions via postal ballot, with the primary ESOP approval receiving 99.71% in favour. This move facilitates employee incentives and aligns with the company's strategy as it prepares for an independent listing, reinforcing its commitment to retaining talent.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:04:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999ad45730b6847a5177617_1771679198572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Foxconn-HCL Chip Fab: India's Hardware Ambition Ignites</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Foxconn-HCL-Chip-Fab-Indias-Hardware-Ambition-Ignites/6999aab6730b6847a517748e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Foxconn-HCL-Chip-Fab-Indias-Hardware-Ambition-Ignites/6999aab6730b6847a517748e</guid><description>In Jewar, Uttar Pradesh, Foxconn and HCL Technologies have initiated a joint venture semiconductor manufacturing plant. This project, blessed by Prime Minister Narendra Modi, signifies India's accelerated push into sophisticated hardware production, aiming to bolster 'Make in India' and national self-reliance amidst evolving global supply chains. The venture underscores a strategic pivot, leveraging India's strengths in software and design to conquer complex chip fabrication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:53:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999aab6730b6847a517748d_1771678547828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bizotic Commercial Approves ₹364 Cr Promoter Warrant Allotment; Upfront ₹91 Cr Received</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Bizotic-Commercial-Approves-364-Cr-Promoter-Warrant-Allotment-Upfront-91-Cr-Received/6999aaaf730b6847a5177477</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Bizotic-Commercial-Approves-364-Cr-Promoter-Warrant-Allotment-Upfront-91-Cr-Received/6999aaaf730b6847a5177477</guid><description>Bizotic Commercial Limited's board approved a preferential allotment of 12.58 lakh convertible warrants to promoters, potentially raising ₹364.82 crore. The company has received an upfront payment of ₹91.21 crore. This move signals future capital infusion, though it comes with compliance requirements and a risk of dilution for existing shareholders if warrants are exercised.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:53:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999aaaf730b6847a5177476_1771678504000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mawana Sugars Shareholders Greenlight Mawana Foods Amalgamation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Mawana-Sugars-Shareholders-Greenlight-Mawana-Foods-Amalgamation/6999a7a4730b6847a517730d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Mawana-Sugars-Shareholders-Greenlight-Mawana-Foods-Amalgamation/6999a7a4730b6847a517730d</guid><description>Mawana Sugars Limited shareholders have overwhelmingly approved a scheme of amalgamation to merge Mawana Foods Private Limited into the company. The resolution passed with over 99.99% in favour, signalling strong support for the consolidation. The move now awaits final approval from the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT).</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:40:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a7a4730b6847a517730c_1771677722941.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cipla Faces USFDA OAI at Supplier; Lanreotide Injection Supply Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cipla-Faces-USFDA-OAI-at-Supplier-Lanreotide-Injection-Supply-Risk/6999a49e730b6847a517713e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cipla-Faces-USFDA-OAI-at-Supplier-Lanreotide-Injection-Supply-Risk/6999a49e730b6847a517713e</guid><description>Cipla announced a USFDA inspection at its key supplier Pharmathen International S.A.'s facility in Greece resulted in an 'Official Action Indicated' (OAI) classification. This finding suggests significant regulatory violations, potentially disrupting the supply chain for Lanreotide Injection, a critical product for Cipla USA Inc. The company is awaiting Pharmathen's corrective actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:27:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a49e730b6847a517713d_1771676973131.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rudra Ecovation Shareholders Meet on Shiva Texfabs Amalgamation Scheme</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rudra-Ecovation-Shareholders-Meet-on-Shiva-Texfabs-Amalgamation-Scheme/6999a497730b6847a5177128</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rudra-Ecovation-Shareholders-Meet-on-Shiva-Texfabs-Amalgamation-Scheme/6999a497730b6847a5177128</guid><description>Rudra Ecovation Limited shareholders met virtually on February 21, 2026, to vote on its amalgamation with Shiva Texfabs Limited. The scheme, approved by boards and progressing through regulatory steps including NCLT orders, aims to leverage synergies and strengthen market position in sustainable textiles. E-voting results are awaited, marking a crucial step before final approvals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:27:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a497730b6847a5177127_1771676937551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE IPO Legal Roadblock Cleared, Substantive Claims Unresolved</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NSE-IPO-Legal-Roadblock-Cleared-Substantive-Claims-Unresolved/6999a464730b6847a51770e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NSE-IPO-Legal-Roadblock-Cleared-Substantive-Claims-Unresolved/6999a464730b6847a51770e7</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange's (NSE) long-awaited initial public offering (IPO) has overcome a significant legal hurdle as the Delhi High Court dismissed a petition challenging the Securities and Exchange Board of India's (SEBI) no-objection certificate (NOC). The court's decision, however, was based on territorial jurisdiction rather than the merits of the petitioner's serious allegations concerning corporate action adjustments and potential financial improprieties. This procedural victory clears the path for an Offer for Sale (OFS), but the unaddressed claims introduce a lingering risk profile.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:26:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a464730b6847a51770e6_1771676895106.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exhicon subsidiary UHPL secures DGCA AOP for helicopter operations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Exhicon-subsidiary-UHPL-secures-DGCA-AOP-for-helicopter-operations/6999a420730b6847a517705e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Exhicon-subsidiary-UHPL-secures-DGCA-AOP-for-helicopter-operations/6999a420730b6847a517705e</guid><description>Exhicon Events Media Solutions is expanding into active helicopter flying operations via its subsidiary, United Helicharters Private Limited (UHPL). UHPL has received an Air Operator Permit (AOP) from the DGCA, valid for five years, marking a strategic pivot from aviation support to commercial charter services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:25:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a420730b6847a517705d_1771676858836.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chrome Silicon Q3 Loss Widens as Operations Remain Suspended, Audit Flags Mount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Chrome-Silicon-Q3-Loss-Widens-as-Operations-Remain-Suspended-Audit-Flags-Mount/6999a420730b6847a5177048</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Chrome-Silicon-Q3-Loss-Widens-as-Operations-Remain-Suspended-Audit-Flags-Mount/6999a420730b6847a5177048</guid><description>Chrome Silicon Limited reported a net loss of ₹2.13 crore for the quarter ending December 31, 2025, on a total income of ₹5.34 crore. Total income plummeted 77.32% year-on-year. Crucially, manufacturing operations have been suspended since May 2025 due to market volatility. The company's auditors have raised significant qualifications regarding the accuracy of financial statements, including unverified inventories and assets, unconfirmed liabilities, and uncertain loan recoverability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:25:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a420730b6847a5177047_1771676826623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pharma: Td Vaccine Launch Signals Sector Maturation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Td-Vaccine-Launch-Signals-Sector-Maturation/6999a3aa730b6847a5176f9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Td-Vaccine-Launch-Signals-Sector-Maturation/6999a3aa730b6847a5176f9b</guid><description>Union Health Minister J.P. Nadda launched India's indigenously manufactured Tetanus and adult Diphtheria (Td) vaccine, a significant step for national health security and the 'Atmanirbhar Bharat' vision. The Central Research Institute will supply 55 lakh doses to the Universal Immunization Programme by April 2026, bolstering domestic production capabilities. This event aligns with robust growth projections for India's pharmaceutical sector, driven by strong domestic demand and government incentives, reinforcing its global "pharmacy of the world" status, though challenges in scaling and market competition persist for the broader industry.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a3aa730b6847a5176f9a_1771676717908.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-France Strategic Partnership Deepens: Defense, Tech Deals Signal New Era</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-France-Strategic-Partnership-Deepens-Defense-Tech-Deals-Signal-New-Era/6999a1c5730b6847a5176e53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-France-Strategic-Partnership-Deepens-Defense-Tech-Deals-Signal-New-Era/6999a1c5730b6847a5176e53</guid><description>The India-France relationship has been elevated to a "Special Global Strategic Partnership," marked by significant defense agreements, including a substantial Rafale jet contract and helicopter production, alongside increased cooperation in critical minerals, AI, and innovation. This strategic deepening aims to bolster industrial self-reliance, enhance regional security in the Indo-Pacific, and navigate a complex global order, reflecting a long-term co-development vision.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:15:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a1c5730b6847a5176e52_1771676273656.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Ruling Sparks Volatility; India Rallies AI &amp; Defence Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Ruling-Sparks-Volatility-India-Rallies-AI-and-Defence-Investments/6999a159730b6847a5176df4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Ruling-Sparks-Volatility-India-Rallies-AI-and-Defence-Investments/6999a159730b6847a5176df4</guid><description>Indian equity markets experienced their sharpest decline since Budget Day on February 19, 2026, with the Nifty 50 falling 1.6% and the Sensex dropping 1.5%. This came after a US Supreme Court ruling struck down President Trump's tariffs, though he quickly announced new ones. Simultaneously, India hosted its AI Impact Summit, securing over $360 billion in investment commitments, and advanced talks on the Rafale jet deal, signaling robust domestic growth potential amidst global trade uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:13:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a159730b6847a5176df3_1771676122265.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rishab Special Yarns to become IMPERA WORLDWIDE; approves Rights Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rishab-Special-Yarns-to-become-IMPERA-WORLDWIDE-approves-Rights-Issue/69999fea730b6847a5176d40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rishab-Special-Yarns-to-become-IMPERA-WORLDWIDE-approves-Rights-Issue/69999fea730b6847a5176d40</guid><description>Rishab Special Yarns Limited has announced a significant board resolution to change its name to IMPERA WORLDWIDE LIMITED, subject to shareholder approval. The company also greenlit an increase in its authorised share capital and a proposal for a Rights Issue to raise funds. The board appointed SHRAVAN A. GUPTA &amp; ASSOCIATES as scrutinizer for the upcoming postal ballot process.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:07:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69999fea730b6847a5176d3f_1771675731949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Manufacturing Ambition Meets US Tariff Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Manufacturing-Ambition-Meets-US-Tariff-Volatility/69999e0a730b6847a5176c1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Manufacturing-Ambition-Meets-US-Tariff-Volatility/69999e0a730b6847a5176c1c</guid><description>Despite ongoing volatility from US trade tariff announcements, India's manufacturing sector is poised for significant expansion, driven by government initiatives and a strategic focus on domestic production and global supply chain diversification. Companies like Kirloskar Brothers demonstrate resilience against prior tariff pressures, while financial entities like JM Financial navigate market flux. Current valuations and mixed analyst sentiment for key players underscore the dynamic operational environment as India aims to leverage global shifts into a manufacturing powerhouse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:59:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69999e0a730b6847a5176c1b_1771675282301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Triveni Turbine Faces Tariff Headwinds, Valuation in Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triveni-Turbine-Faces-Tariff-Headwinds-Valuation-in-Focus/69999e07730b6847a5176c05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triveni-Turbine-Faces-Tariff-Headwinds-Valuation-in-Focus/69999e07730b6847a5176c05</guid><description>Triveni Turbine confronts challenges from fluctuating US tariff policies, impacting its global supply chain visibility and cross-border pricing. Despite a 150-day tariff window, long-term planning remains difficult. The company's stock has fallen over 17% in the past year, with a market capitalization of approximately ₹15,608.42 crore. While the Indian manufacturing sector shows resilience, Triveni Turbine's valuation is under review amidst these trade uncertainties and varying analyst outlooks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:59:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69999e07730b6847a5176c04_1771675309036.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>