<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:28:28 +0000</pubDate><item><title>IndusInd Bank: Growth Ambitions vs. Regulatory Shadows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Growth-Ambitions-vs-Regulatory-Shadows/69976485d25eafd9cd033c28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Growth-Ambitions-vs-Regulatory-Shadows/69976485d25eafd9cd033c28</guid><description>IndusInd Bank is pursuing ambitious growth in affordable housing, gold loans, and MSME lending, aiming to bolster its deposit franchise. However, this strategy unfolds against a backdrop of intense regulatory scrutiny, including SEBI and NFRA investigations into past derivative accounting irregularities. Recent reports highlight insider trading allegations against former senior executives linked to these issues, alongside a widening gap between credit expansion and deposit mobilization in the Indian banking sector. Despite management's assurances and forward-looking targets like a 1% RoA by FY27, analyst sentiment remains divided, reflecting market caution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:29:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69976485d25eafd9cd033c27.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Green Building Boom: Mandates Spur Growth Amidst Cost Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Green-Building-Boom-Mandates-Spur-Growth-Amidst-Cost-Hurdles/69975ddad25eafd9cd033a4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Green-Building-Boom-Mandates-Spur-Growth-Amidst-Cost-Hurdles/69975ddad25eafd9cd033a4c</guid><description>India's real estate sector is aggressively adopting green building practices, propelled by national net-zero emission targets and growing tenant demand for sustainable spaces. While this shift promises significant rental premiums and long-term cost savings, developers confront substantial upfront investment costs, a shortage of skilled labor, and the complexities of regulatory compliance. The market is expanding rapidly, projected to reach potentially $70-80 billion by 2030, yet the path to widespread, genuine sustainability faces significant obstacles.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:00:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69975ddad25eafd9cd033a4b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mega-Films Force Release Consolidation, Squeezing Indie Productions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Mega-Films-Force-Release-Consolidation-Squeezing-Indie-Productions/69975d78d25eafd9cd0336b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Mega-Films-Force-Release-Consolidation-Squeezing-Indie-Productions/69975d78d25eafd9cd0336b6</guid><description>The March film release calendar is undergoing a significant reshuffling as at least five domestic and southern language productions postpone their debuts. This strategic retreat is driven by the impending arrival of two high-budget tentpole movies, Ranveer Singh's 'Dhurandhar 2' and Yash's 'Toxic', both slated for March 19. This concentration of releases underscores a market dynamic where blockbuster potential dictates exhibition space, potentially marginalizing mid-tier films and creating significant logistical hurdles for cinema operators.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:59:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69975d78d25eafd9cd0336b5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Shrinks Footprint as Market Share Collapses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Shrinks-Footprint-as-Market-Share-Collapses/69975d07d25eafd9cd033638</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Shrinks-Footprint-as-Market-Share-Collapses/69975d07d25eafd9cd033638</guid><description>Ola Electric is drastically reducing its physical store count to approximately 550 by March-end, marking a stark reversal from its prior expansion. This "structural reset" follows a sharp 55% year-on-year revenue drop to ₹470 crore and a 61% decline in electric two-wheeler deliveries to 32,680 units in Q3 FY26. The company's market share has plummeted to about 4.2% in early February 2026, from over 26% a year ago, as legacy manufacturers dominate the EV two-wheeler segment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69975d07d25eafd9cd033637.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Novartis Exits India, Triggers Mandatory Buyback Offer for Shareholders</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Novartis-Exits-India-Triggers-Mandatory-Buyback-Offer-for-Shareholders/699756ead25eafd9cd0334b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Novartis-Exits-India-Triggers-Mandatory-Buyback-Offer-for-Shareholders/699756ead25eafd9cd0334b6</guid><description>Novartis AG is selling its entire 70.68% stake in Novartis India to a consortium of WaveRise Investments Limited, ChrysCapital Fund X, and Two Infinity Partners. This significant transaction triggers a mandatory open offer to all public shareholders, providing them an opportunity to exit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:31:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699756ead25eafd9cd0334b5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Startups Pause Global Relocation Amidst Market Realignment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indian-Startups-Pause-Global-Relocation-Amidst-Market-Realignment/69975547d25eafd9cd032bb9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indian-Startups-Pause-Global-Relocation-Amidst-Market-Realignment/69975547d25eafd9cd032bb9</guid><description>Several Indian startups are halting plans to re-domicile their headquarters back to India. This pause, driven by moderating global valuations, a downturn in IT stocks, more appealing prospects in the U.S., and persistent tax uncertainties following the Tiger Global verdict, signals a strategic reassessment. Companies previously eyeing domestic listings are now reassessing timelines and viability, prioritizing sustainable growth over immediate market entry. The trend reflects a broader global shift where capital allocation is increasingly scrutinizing business fundamentals and long-term viability. This move also highlights challenges in cross-border tax structures and employee incentive plans, prompting a wait-and-watch approach as market conditions evolve.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:24:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69975547d25eafd9cd032bb8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Labour Codes Squeeze Profit Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Labour-Codes-Squeeze-Profit-Margins/699754b7d25eafd9cd032b1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Labour-Codes-Squeeze-Profit-Margins/699754b7d25eafd9cd032b1e</guid><description>India's implementation of new labour codes has resulted in substantial financial provisioning by major listed companies, directly impacting Q3 FY26 earnings. Mandated changes to basic pay composition and gratuity eligibility have forced one-time charges, with IT services, banking, aviation, and industrial giants like L&amp;T taking significant hits. This represents a structural increase in employee costs, potentially eroding profit margins and competitive advantages across key sectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:21:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699754b7d25eafd9cd032b1d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPFO Data Consolidation: India's Economic Visibility Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFO-Data-Consolidation-Indias-Economic-Visibility-Boost/69975494d25eafd9cd032b04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFO-Data-Consolidation-Indias-Economic-Visibility-Boost/69975494d25eafd9cd032b04</guid><description>The Employees’ Provident Fund Organisation (EPFO) is undertaking a significant data integration drive, connecting its database with numerous central ministries and state governments. This initiative aims to bolster compliance monitoring for employment-linked schemes and provide unprecedented visibility into India's formal and informal economic sectors. By aggregating data streams, the EPFO is paving the way for more precise policy implementation and a clearer picture of national employment trends.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:21:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69975494d25eafd9cd032b03.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zee Ent. Faces SEBI Probe: Governance Questions Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Ent-Faces-SEBI-Probe-Governance-Questions-Linger/69975329d25eafd9cd032a0f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Ent-Faces-SEBI-Probe-Governance-Questions-Linger/69975329d25eafd9cd032a0f</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India has issued a show-cause notice to Zee Entertainment Enterprises (ZEEL) and its top executives, including Subhash Chandra and Punit Goenka, regarding alleged fund diversion and governance failures linked to a 2018 Letter of Comfort for Yes Bank loans. ZEEL denies the charges. This latest regulatory action adds to a series of historical probes and penalties involving the company and its promoters, raising persistent questions about its structural governance and credibility.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:15:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69975329d25eafd9cd032a0e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Switzerland's AI Dual Strategy: Global Standards Amidst Trade Fragmentation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Switzerlands-AI-Dual-Strategy-Global-Standards-Amidst-Trade-Fragmentation/699751ded25eafd9cd032957</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Switzerlands-AI-Dual-Strategy-Global-Standards-Amidst-Trade-Fragmentation/699751ded25eafd9cd032957</guid><description>Swiss President Guy Parmelin champions a nuanced, multi-faceted approach to Artificial Intelligence (AI) governance, eschewing single-instrument regulation. Switzerland actively contributes to global technical standards and supports binding international legal instruments like the Council of Europe framework convention, marking the first such treaty on AI. Concurrently, the nation is bolstering its trade resilience through agreements, acknowledging the volatile global trade environment. This dual strategy positions Switzerland to influence AI's ethical development while safeguarding its economic interests amidst increasing geopolitical and trade fragmentation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:09:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699751ded25eafd9cd032956.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OpenAI's $1T IPO Gamble: Burn Rate Fuels Cash Crunch Amidst AI Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAIs-1T-IPO-Gamble-Burn-Rate-Fuels-Cash-Crunch-Amidst-AI-Race/69974a66d25eafd9cd029aa9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAIs-1T-IPO-Gamble-Burn-Rate-Fuels-Cash-Crunch-Amidst-AI-Race/69974a66d25eafd9cd029aa9</guid><description>OpenAI's rapid growth in users, reaching 800-900 million weekly, is juxtaposed by an escalating $17 billion annual operational burn rate. This financial pressure is intensifying as the company aims for a $1 trillion IPO by 2027. While revenue has surged past $20 billion in 2025, it remains insufficient to cover the immense compute costs. OpenAI is now testing advertisements on its free ChatGPT tiers and making substantial infrastructure investments, all while rivals like Anthropic and Google's Gemini aggressively compete for market share and investor capital. The sustainability of its user-acquisition-heavy model is under scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:37:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69974a66d25eafd9cd029aa8_1771523114667.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata's AI Bet: Infrastructure Scale vs. Execution Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tatas-AI-Bet-Infrastructure-Scale-vs-Execution-Risk/69974955d25eafd9cd026ed1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tatas-AI-Bet-Infrastructure-Scale-vs-Execution-Risk/69974955d25eafd9cd026ed1</guid><description>Tata Group Chairman N. Chandrasekaran has detailed an expansive AI strategy, focusing on infrastructure partnerships with OpenAI and AMD, alongside semiconductor ambitions. While aiming to position India as an AI hub, the sheer capital intensity and competitive landscape in AI data centers and chip design present significant execution risks and potential margin pressures. Tata Consultancy Services (TCS), with its robust financials, is central to this endeavor, but translating grand vision into sustained profitability in these capital-intensive sectors remains a key challenge.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:33:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69974955d25eafd9cd026ed0_1771522522960.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steelco Gujarat Cancels Share Sale Amid 'Fundamental Changes'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steelco-Gujarat-Cancels-Share-Sale-Amid-Fundamental-Changes/69974619d25eafd9cd026d81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steelco-Gujarat-Cancels-Share-Sale-Amid-Fundamental-Changes/69974619d25eafd9cd026d81</guid><description>Steelco Gujarat Limited has cancelled its rights issue, initially set for February 24, 2026. The company cited unspecified 'fundamental changes' as the reason, promising to announce new timelines later. This move comes after a history of financial distress, including insolvency proceedings and a SEBI penalty, raising concerns about its financial stability and future fundraising capabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:19:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69974619d25eafd9cd026d80.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Esab India: Funds Shuffle Amidst Conflicting Analyst Signals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Esab-India-Funds-Shuffle-Amidst-Conflicting-Analyst-Signals/69974596d25eafd9cd026cdc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Esab-India-Funds-Shuffle-Amidst-Conflicting-Analyst-Signals/69974596d25eafd9cd026cdc</guid><description>On February 19, bulk trades involving Nippon India Mutual Fund and SBI Mutual Fund in Esab India underscored divergent institutional perspectives. While Esab India boasts a strong, debt-free balance sheet and operates within a growing industrial sector, its premium valuation and sharply contrasting analyst ratings—ranging from 'Buy' to a significant 'Sell' consensus—present a complex outlook. The stock, trading near ₹5,515, faces investor scrutiny regarding the implications of these fund movements against its fundamental strengths and market sentiment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:17:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69974596d25eafd9cd026cdb_1771521632783.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Tweaks ETF Pricing: T-1 Shift Promises Clarity, Risks New Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Tweaks-ETF-Pricing-T-1-Shift-Promises-Clarity-Risks-New-Volatility/699744c7d25eafd9cd026b5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Tweaks-ETF-Pricing-T-1-Shift-Promises-Clarity-Risks-New-Volatility/699744c7d25eafd9cd026b5f</guid><description>India's SEBI plans to upgrade Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) pricing from T-2 to T-1 Net Asset Value (NAV) to enhance price discovery during market volatility. The move also introduces calibrated price bands, a departure from the flat 20% limit. While intended to reduce price gaps and operational risks, the transition presents logistical challenges for exchanges and may redefine arbitrage opportunities for market participants.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:13:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699744c7d25eafd9cd026b5e_1771521346148.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Air India Bets Big on Fleet Overhaul for Turnaround</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Bets-Big-on-Fleet-Overhaul-for-Turnaround/699744bad25eafd9cd026b47</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Bets-Big-on-Fleet-Overhaul-for-Turnaround/699744bad25eafd9cd026b47</guid><description>Air India is accelerating its fleet modernization and enhancing operational resilience, according to CEO Campbell Wilson. The airline has increased its inventory of spares and components to mitigate past issues with legacy Boeing wide-body aircraft, which caused delays and cancellations. Over half of the wide-body fleet is slated for modernization by the end of 2026, with completion by December 2028. This aggressive upgrade program supports a broader vision to grow the Air India group’s fleet from approximately 300 to over 500 aircraft by 2030, a critical component of its post-privatization transformation strategy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:13:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699744bad25eafd9cd026b46.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Federal Bank Secures ₹686 Cr Tax Payout After Decade-Long Dispute</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Federal-Bank-Secures-686-Cr-Tax-Payout-After-Decade-Long-Dispute/699744a1d25eafd9cd026b29</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Federal-Bank-Secures-686-Cr-Tax-Payout-After-Decade-Long-Dispute/699744a1d25eafd9cd026b29</guid><description>Federal Bank announced it will receive a ₹686 crore tax refund, including accrued interest, concluding a tax dispute spanning assessment years 2012-13 and 2013-14. This significant one-off inflow, which is nearly two-thirds of the bank's third-quarter profit of ₹1,041 crore, is expected to bolster its upcoming quarterly earnings. The resolution follows tribunal orders and subsequent official confirmations received in early 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:13:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699744a1d25eafd9cd026b28.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Valuation Fears Spark Tech Selloff; Retail, Energy Stand Firm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Valuation-Fears-Spark-Tech-Selloff-Retail-Energy-Stand-Firm/69974430d25eafd9cd026a2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Valuation-Fears-Spark-Tech-Selloff-Retail-Energy-Stand-Firm/69974430d25eafd9cd026a2a</guid><description>Wall Street indexes dipped as heavyweight technology stocks retreated, driven by concerns over high AI valuations and potential business model disruptions. Walmart shares rose following a conservative fiscal 2027 forecast and a $30 billion buyback plan. The energy sector also advanced amid geopolitical tensions. Meanwhile, the Federal Reserve's uncertain rate path and upcoming inflation data continue to fuel investor nervousness.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69974430d25eafd9cd026a29_1771521542844.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axis MF's Growth Push: SIFs, Credit Funds to Fuel Top-Six Ambition?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Axis-MFs-Growth-Push-SIFs-Credit-Funds-to-Fuel-Top-Six-Ambition/6997440bd25eafd9cd0269de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Axis-MFs-Growth-Push-SIFs-Credit-Funds-to-Fuel-Top-Six-Ambition/6997440bd25eafd9cd0269de</guid><description>Axis Mutual Fund aims for top-tier AUM by FY29, targeting over 20% annual growth. The strategy hinges on new offerings like Specialised Investment Funds (SIFs) and private credit, alongside a bullish equity outlook. Currently managing ₹3.85 lakh crore, the fund house seeks to expand its 5.6% market share against industry leaders. This aggressive push occurs amid robust industry growth, strong SIP inflows, and a positive Indian economic outlook, but also faces persistent geopolitical risks and competitive pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:10:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997440bd25eafd9cd0269dd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Fears Propel Gold &amp; Silver to Highs; Macro Data Key Ahead</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Geopolitical-Fears-Propel-Gold-and-Silver-to-Highs-Macro-Data-Key-Ahead/69974355d25eafd9cd024d5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Geopolitical-Fears-Propel-Gold-and-Silver-to-Highs-Macro-Data-Key-Ahead/69974355d25eafd9cd024d5a</guid><description>Precious metals experienced a significant rally, with silver prices surging 7.32% and gold advancing 1.24% on Thursday, driven by escalating geopolitical risks and a potent wave of safe-haven demand amid increased speculation over potential U.S. military action against Iran and stalled Russia-Ukraine negotiations. Analysts emphasize that upcoming U.S. GDP and PCE inflation data, alongside Federal Reserve commentary, will be crucial in shaping the market's next move, introducing a layer of volatility for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:07:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69974355d25eafd9cd024d59_1771521088240.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Qualcomm Bets on India for Global Auto Chips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Bets-on-India-for-Global-Auto-Chips/6997433bd25eafd9cd024737</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Bets-on-India-for-Global-Auto-Chips/6997433bd25eafd9cd024737</guid><description>Qualcomm is set to establish contract manufacturing for automotive module products in India, with a significant portion destined for global export. This move aligns with India's push to become a semiconductor manufacturing hub and supports Qualcomm's strategy to diversify its supply chain and capitalize on the growing automotive and AI sectors. The initiative leverages India's expanding electronics manufacturing ecosystem and its substantial R&amp;D presence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:07:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997433bd25eafd9cd024736_1771521026288.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Poonawalla Fincorp Gets Shareholder Nod for Fund Raise, New Director</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Poonawalla-Fincorp-Gets-Shareholder-Nod-for-Fund-Raise-New-Director/6997415bd25eafd9cd022b1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Poonawalla-Fincorp-Gets-Shareholder-Nod-for-Fund-Raise-New-Director/6997415bd25eafd9cd022b1f</guid><description>Poonawalla Fincorp Limited's shareholders have given a strong go-ahead for crucial resolutions in a postal ballot. Investors overwhelmingly approved raising funds through equity shares via Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) and appointed Mr. Vikas Pandey as a Whole-time Director (Executive Director). These decisions signal the company's intent for expansion and strengthening its leadership.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997415bd25eafd9cd022b1e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Heritage Foods Files Rs 100 Cr Defamation Suit Against Sakshi Media</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Heritage-Foods-Files-Rs-100-Cr-Defamation-Suit-Against-Sakshi-Media/69973f78d25eafd9cd022a2f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Heritage-Foods-Files-Rs-100-Cr-Defamation-Suit-Against-Sakshi-Media/69973f78d25eafd9cd022a2f</guid><description>Heritage Foods Limited has launched a ₹100 Crore civil defamation suit against Sakshi Media House, including its newspaper and TV channel. Filed on February 19, 2026, in the Delhi High Court, the suit seeks damages for alleged false, baseless, and malicious publications. The court has granted interim directions restraining further defamatory content and ordering takedowns, marking a significant legal clash over the company's reputation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:51:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69973f78d25eafd9cd022a2e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rail Fractures Surge: Safety Spending Climbs, Analysts Eye Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Rail-Fractures-Surge-Safety-Spending-Climbs-Analysts-Eye-Valuations/69973907d25eafd9cd019643</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Rail-Fractures-Surge-Safety-Spending-Climbs-Analysts-Eye-Valuations/69973907d25eafd9cd019643</guid><description>The Indian Railway Ministry has mandated thorough investigations into a surge in rail fractures, particularly those originating from bolt holes. This escalation coincides with a significant increase in government safety expenditure, which has nearly tripled over the past decade, reaching over ₹1.17 lakh crore in FY26. While this spending aims to bolster infrastructure, concerns persist regarding systemic vulnerabilities, slow technology deployment, and company valuations within the railway infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:23:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69973907d25eafd9cd019642_1771518618740.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: MSMEs Shift to Capability, Not Just Access</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-MSMEs-Shift-to-Capability-Not-Just-Access/6997370ed25eafd9cd00d382</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-MSMEs-Shift-to-Capability-Not-Just-Access/6997370ed25eafd9cd00d382</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 marks a strategic evolution, moving India's focus from merely granting access to developing sustained enterprise capability within Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs). This pivot is crucial for achieving the Viksit Bharat 2047 vision. MSMEs, contributing significantly to India's GDP and exports, are positioned as anchors for productive job creation, particularly in Tier II and III cities. New funding mechanisms, ecosystem-driven models, and aligned skilling initiatives aim to unlock systemic growth, shifting the metric from scheme launches to measurable enterprise confidence and competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:15:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997370ed25eafd9cd00d381.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Star Bazaar's Profit Slump: Neville Tata Faces Uphill Battle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Star-Bazaars-Profit-Slump-Neville-Tata-Faces-Uphill-Battle/6997370bd25eafd9cd00d36b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Star-Bazaars-Profit-Slump-Neville-Tata-Faces-Uphill-Battle/6997370bd25eafd9cd00d36b</guid><description>Star Bazaar's contribution to Trent's profits has fallen significantly, even as the Tata-Tesco joint venture increases its reliance on private labels. Management acknowledges slower-than-expected store expansion, placing Neville Tata at the forefront of a revival strategy. He must now translate private label gains into consistent profitability and accelerate rollout to compete effectively against giants like Reliance Retail, a task proving more challenging than Zudio's rapid growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:15:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997370bd25eafd9cd00d36a_1771517883035.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zaggle Posts Record Quarter, Eyes $1 Billion Revenue Goal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Zaggle-Posts-Record-Quarter-Eyes-1-Billion-Revenue-Goal/6997353bd25eafd9cd00d229</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Zaggle-Posts-Record-Quarter-Eyes-1-Billion-Revenue-Goal/6997353bd25eafd9cd00d229</guid><description>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited announced its best-ever quarterly and nine-month results for Q3 FY26. Revenue jumped 47.9% year-on-year to ₹498 Crores, with profit after tax soaring 77.7% to ₹36 Crores. The company is aggressively integrating AI, expanding through acquisitions, and planning international growth, aiming for $1 billion in revenue within 5-7 years while focusing on achieving positive operating cash flow by FY27.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:07:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997353bd25eafd9cd00d228_1771517369038.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paytm's Profit Boost Questioned Amidst Margin Squeeze, Wallet Revival Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paytms-Profit-Boost-Questioned-Amidst-Margin-Squeeze-Wallet-Revival-Hopes/699734c1d25eafd9cd00d113</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paytms-Profit-Boost-Questioned-Amidst-Margin-Squeeze-Wallet-Revival-Hopes/699734c1d25eafd9cd00d113</guid><description>One 97 Communications, parent of Paytm, reported a net profit of ₹225 crore for Q3, a significant rise from ₹21 crore year-on-year, with revenue growing 6.5% to ₹2,194 crore. This performance was boosted by financial services traction and lower indirect costs. Management has signaled intent to relaunch the Paytm Wallet and highlighted merchant segment growth. However, underlying profitability may be masked by Payment Infrastructure Development Fund (PIDF) incentives, with contribution margins potentially lower without them. Analyst sentiment leans positive, but concerns linger regarding competitive intensity and regulatory dependence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:05:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699734c1d25eafd9cd00d112_1771517240039.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Trade Deficit Widens to $70.3B in December Amid AI Boom and Tariff Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Trade-Deficit-Widens-to-703B-in-December-Amid-AI-Boom-and-Tariff-Shifts/6997349fd25eafd9cd00d08e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Trade-Deficit-Widens-to-703B-in-December-Amid-AI-Boom-and-Tariff-Shifts/6997349fd25eafd9cd00d08e</guid><description>The U.S. trade deficit widened to $70.3 billion in December 2025, as imports rose 3.6% and exports fell 1.7%. The full-year deficit reached $901.5 billion, one of the largest on record, despite fluctuating tariff policies. While the deficit with China narrowed significantly, imbalances grew with Taiwan and Mexico. Massive investments in artificial intelligence drove a surge in computer and accessory imports, underscoring demand-side pressures on trade.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:04:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997349fd25eafd9cd00d08d_1771517206660.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani's $100B AI Push: India's Sovereign Compute Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Adanis-100B-AI-Push-Indias-Sovereign-Compute-Strategy/6997346ed25eafd9cd00d023</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Adanis-100B-AI-Push-Indias-Sovereign-Compute-Strategy/6997346ed25eafd9cd00d023</guid><description>Adani Digital Labs Director Jeet Adani unveiled a $100 billion commitment by Adani Group to build renewable-powered AI data centers by 2035. This massive investment aims to secure India's technological sovereignty, foster domestic AI capabilities, and reduce reliance on foreign infrastructure. The initiative is poised to catalyze an additional $150 billion in ecosystem development, positioning India as a critical player in the global AI race, while Adani Enterprises navigates significant competitive and valuation dynamics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:03:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997346ed25eafd9cd00d022_1771517176595.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Religare Demerger: Market Overreacts? Value Unlock Potential vs. Execution Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Demerger-Market-Overreacts-Value-Unlock-Potential-vs-Execution-Risk/6997343bd25eafd9cd00d000</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Demerger-Market-Overreacts-Value-Unlock-Potential-vs-Execution-Risk/6997343bd25eafd9cd00d000</guid><description>Religare Enterprises' board approved a demerger separating financial services into Religare Finvest (RFL) and retaining Care Health Insurance as a subsidiary. Despite a 10% stock drop triggered by concerns over a holding company discount and regulatory hurdles, analysts point to a substantial valuation gap between reported assets and market capitalization. While execution risks and a 'Strong Sell' rating from MarketsMojo loom, the restructuring aims to unlock shareholder value by creating focused entities, with a potential future merger of Care Health to simplify the structure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:03:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997343bd25eafd9cd00cfff_1771517211090.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Inflation Threatens Savings: India's Market Adapts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Inflation-Threatens-Savings-Indias-Market-Adapts/699733dcd25eafd9cd00cf20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Inflation-Threatens-Savings-Indias-Market-Adapts/699733dcd25eafd9cd00cf20</guid><description>India faces a critical juncture where inflation's silent erosion of savings necessitates a strategic market shift. Beyond traditional savings, investors and financial institutions are increasingly focusing on inflation-hedging assets, dynamic portfolio management, and advanced financial planning to preserve real wealth and meet long-term goals amidst evolving economic conditions. Passive saving is no longer sufficient.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699733dcd25eafd9cd00cf1f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fed Minutes Signal Hawkish Turn Amidst Trump Policy Clash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Fed-Minutes-Signal-Hawkish-Turn-Amidst-Trump-Policy-Clash/699733d7d25eafd9cd00cf04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Fed-Minutes-Signal-Hawkish-Turn-Amidst-Trump-Policy-Clash/699733d7d25eafd9cd00cf04</guid><description>Federal Reserve officials signaled a more hawkish outlook in their January meeting minutes, expressing concern over persistent inflation and a fading labor market weakness. While holding rates steady at 3.5%-3.75%, several officials considered potential rate hikes if inflation remains elevated. This stance creates tension with President Trump's calls for lower rates and the nomination of Kevin Warsh, whose policy philosophy offers a blend of rate cuts and balance sheet normalization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:01:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699733d7d25eafd9cd00cf03_1771517037134.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CIE Auto India Sales Jump 15%, But Margins Dip Amid Rising Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CIE-Auto-India-Sales-Jump-15percent-But-Margins-Dip-Amid-Rising-Debt/69973261d25eafd9cd00cdd8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CIE-Auto-India-Sales-Jump-15percent-But-Margins-Dip-Amid-Rising-Debt/69973261d25eafd9cd00cdd8</guid><description>CIE Automotive India reported a strong 15% year-over-year sales increase for the fourth quarter of CY2025, reaching ₹23,258 million. However, profitability faced headwinds, with consolidated EBITDA margins narrowing to 15.4% from 16.4% a year ago due to new labour codes and restructuring costs. Full-year sales grew 5.7%, but margins compressed to 16.0%. Consolidated net financial debt also rose significantly to ₹18,807 million. Despite these challenges, the company highlighted a positive outlook for the Indian auto market and a strategic focus on expanding its electric vehicle (EV) component offerings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:55:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69973261d25eafd9cd00cdd7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Promoter Sells Jauss Polymers Stake Amidst Severe Financial Distress</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Promoter-Sells-Jauss-Polymers-Stake-Amidst-Severe-Financial-Distress/6997316bd25eafd9cd00cd4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Promoter-Sells-Jauss-Polymers-Stake-Amidst-Severe-Financial-Distress/6997316bd25eafd9cd00cd4f</guid><description>Mr. Ketineni Satish Rao, promoter of Jauss Polymers Limited, has signed an agreement to sell his entire 43.41% stake in the company to Noize Brands And Lifestyle Limited. This stake sale comes at a critical time, as Jauss Polymers is reportedly facing severe financial difficulties, including zero revenue, significant losses, and an auditor's adverse opinion questioning its ability to continue as a going concern. The transaction triggers a mandatory open offer for public shareholders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:51:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997316bd25eafd9cd00cd4e_1771516369343.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Company Posts Strong 9-Month Growth, But Q3 Sees Profit Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Company-Posts-Strong-9-Month-Growth-But-Q3-Sees-Profit-Dip/69972ef8d25eafd9cd00cc7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Company-Posts-Strong-9-Month-Growth-But-Q3-Sees-Profit-Dip/69972ef8d25eafd9cd00cc7c</guid><description>The company has announced its unaudited financial results for the nine months and third quarter ended December 31, 2025. While the nine-month period showed robust growth of over 30% in revenue, EBITDA, and PAT, the third quarter presented a mixed picture. Revenue grew a modest 4.22% year-on-year, but profit after tax (PAT) declined by 4.36%. Sequentially, Q3 revenue and profits saw a significant drop of over 25%. Despite this, margins remained healthy, and a strong order book provides future revenue visibility.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69972ef8d25eafd9cd00cc7b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Black Box Ltd Cuts FY26 Revenue Forecast Amid Supply Chain Snags, Buys Brazil's 2S Inovações</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Black-Box-Ltd-Cuts-FY26-Revenue-Forecast-Amid-Supply-Chain-Snags-Buys-Brazils-2S-Inovações/69972c42d25eafd9cd00cb51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Black-Box-Ltd-Cuts-FY26-Revenue-Forecast-Amid-Supply-Chain-Snags-Buys-Brazils-2S-Inovações/69972c42d25eafd9cd00cb51</guid><description>Black Box Limited reported healthy year-on-year growth in Q3 FY26 revenue and EBITDA, but has revised its full-year FY26 revenue guidance downwards. This cut is due to industry-wide supply chain disruptions delaying project execution and shifting revenue realization into FY27. To counter this and boost future growth, the company announced the acquisition of Brazilian IT firm 2S Inovações Tecnológicas, aiming to expand its Latin American presence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:29:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69972c42d25eafd9cd00cb50_1771515063744.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lancer Container Lines Buys PKMGT by Issuing New Shares</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Lancer-Container-Lines-Buys-PKMGT-by-Issuing-New-Shares/69972c41d25eafd9cd00cb3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Lancer-Container-Lines-Buys-PKMGT-by-Issuing-New-Shares/69972c41d25eafd9cd00cb3b</guid><description>Lancer Container Lines Limited is expanding its reach by acquiring the entire equity of P K M General Trading L.L.C. (PKMGT). The company will issue over 10.28 crore shares at ₹19.77 each on a preferential basis to complete the deal. This move makes PKMGT a wholly owned subsidiary, bringing its subsidiary PT Map Trans Logistic under Lancer's umbrella. Investors should watch how this integration impacts growth and profitability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:29:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69972c41d25eafd9cd00cb3a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo's High Valuation Under Scrutiny Post-Disruption</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-High-Valuation-Under-Scrutiny-Post-Disruption/69972977d25eafd9cd00ca09</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-High-Valuation-Under-Scrutiny-Post-Disruption/69972977d25eafd9cd00ca09</guid><description>IndiGo's operational meltdown in December 2025, stemming from non-compliance with new Flight Duty Time Limitation (FDTL) norms, has triggered a governance debate and intensified market scrutiny. Despite its dominant market share, the airline's stock faces pressure due to its high P/E ratio, recent operational fragility, and a mixed analyst outlook, including 'Sell' ratings and investigations into alleged unfair practices. While the airline claims compliance and is hiring pilots, the market is re-evaluating its premium valuation against demonstrated operational risks and regulatory challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:17:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69972977d25eafd9cd00ca08_1771514361917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Clears USFDA Check, Injectable Business Gets Major Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Clears-USFDA-Check-Injectable-Business-Gets-Major-Boost/6997284ad25eafd9cd00c918</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Clears-USFDA-Check-Injectable-Business-Gets-Major-Boost/6997284ad25eafd9cd00c918</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences has received a major win as its Unit 9 facility in Ahmedabad successfully passed a US FDA inspection for injectable medical devices. The inspection, which concluded on February 19, 2026, had zero observations, signalling strong compliance. This is a significant positive for the company's injectable business, potentially paving the way for smoother market access and approvals for its products manufactured at this site. This development comes after the company has been working to bolster its regulatory standing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:12:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997284ad25eafd9cd00c917_1771514039499.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>