<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:45:28 +0000</pubDate><item><title>GRM Overseas Q3 Profit Soars 43%, Revenue Jumps 29% on Strong Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GRM-Overseas-Q3-Profit-Soars-43percent-Revenue-Jumps-29percent-on-Strong-Demand/69841d5dbf48f011a29b2941</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GRM-Overseas-Q3-Profit-Soars-43percent-Revenue-Jumps-29percent-on-Strong-Demand/69841d5dbf48f011a29b2941</guid><description>GRM Overseas reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 28.9% YoY to ₹492.6 Crores and PAT surging 42.8% YoY to ₹19.3 Crores. EBITDA grew 34.1% to ₹31.3 Crores with margins expanding. For the nine months, revenue rose 11.3% and PAT by 30.3%. Management cited strong demand in international basmati and domestic branded segments, projecting continued growth driven by market expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:32:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841d5dbf48f011a29b2940_1770266131717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aster DM Healthcare, QCIL Merger Forms Top 3 Indian Hospital Chain With Strong Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aster-DM-Healthcare-QCIL-Merger-Forms-Top-3-Indian-Hospital-Chain-With-Strong-Growth/69841d4abf48f011a29b2897</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aster-DM-Healthcare-QCIL-Merger-Forms-Top-3-Indian-Hospital-Chain-With-Strong-Growth/69841d4abf48f011a29b2897</guid><description>Aster DM Healthcare and Quality Care India Limited (QCIL) have announced merger progress, creating one of India's top three hospital chains, 'Aster DM Quality Care Limited', with over 10,625 beds. The proforma combined entity reported a robust 15% year-on-year revenue growth to INR 2,366 crore and a 22% jump in Operating EBITDA to INR 503 crore in Q3FY26, with margins improving to 21%. The transaction is cash neutral and projected to be EPS accretive.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:32:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841d4abf48f011a29b2896_1770266070232.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Westlife Foodworld, Shriram Pistons Surge on BSE Pre-Open Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Westlife-Foodworld-Shriram-Pistons-Surge-on-BSE-Pre-Open-Demand/69841a93bf48f011a29b20e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Westlife-Foodworld-Shriram-Pistons-Surge-on-BSE-Pre-Open-Demand/69841a93bf48f011a29b20e9</guid><description>Westlife Foodworld, Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings, and Eris Lifesciences led gains in the BSE pre-opening session. Westlife Foodworld jumped 6.92% on sustained Q3 FY26 profitability and expansion, while the other two surged on market forces alone. Metals, power, and auto sectors also showed upward movement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:20:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841a93bf48f011a29b20e8_1770265458829.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent: Zudio Fuels Growth, But Fashion Woes Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Zudio-Fuels-Growth-But-Fashion-Woes-Linger/69841a7bbf48f011a29b204d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Zudio-Fuels-Growth-But-Fashion-Woes-Linger/69841a7bbf48f011a29b204d</guid><description>Trent's third-quarter FY26 performance saw a 3.1% rise in net profit to ₹512.8 crore on a 14.8% revenue increase to ₹5,345.1 crore. Analysts are split: Antique Stock Broking maintains a Buy rating, citing cost efficiencies and lifestyle brand momentum, while Centrum Broking retains a Neutral rating, flagging concerns over fashion portfolio demand and the Star format. Despite differing views on near-term demand, both acknowledge Trent's steady store network expansion and profitability improvements.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:20:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841a7bbf48f011a29b204c_1770265344514.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian ETFs Plunge: Silver Hit Hardest by Fed Speculation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indian-ETFs-Plunge-Silver-Hit-Hardest-by-Fed-Speculation/69841a1dbf48f011a29b1f7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indian-ETFs-Plunge-Silver-Hit-Hardest-by-Fed-Speculation/69841a1dbf48f011a29b1f7f</guid><description>Indian silver and gold exchange-traded funds (ETFs) experienced a sharp downturn on Thursday, Feb 5, 2026, halting a brief two-day recovery. Silver ETFs plunged between 15% and 20%, with Axis Silver ETF and Kotak Silver ETF leading the decline. Gold ETFs fared slightly better, dropping 4.5% to 6%. The sell-off mirrored weakness in underlying bullion prices on the MCX, with gold futures down 1.58% and silver futures off 9%. This renewed pressure follows extreme volatility last week, amplifying concerns over speculative trading and US monetary policy uncertainty. The disproportionate impact on silver ETFs highlights its heightened sensitivity to such market swings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:18:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841a1dbf48f011a29b1f7e_1770265862846.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Plunges 9% on MCX, ETFs Hit as Volatility Roars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Plunges-9percent-on-MCX-ETFs-Hit-as-Volatility-Roars/69841a09bf48f011a29b1ee7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Plunges-9percent-on-MCX-ETFs-Hit-as-Volatility-Roars/69841a09bf48f011a29b1ee7</guid><description>Silver experienced a dramatic price collapse on Thursday, February 5, 2026, with MCX prices dropping 9% and global spot rates plummeting over 13%. This severe volatility sent Silver Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) spiraling, with losses ranging from 13% to 20%. The rout highlights amplified investor risk in leveraged commodity plays, especially as silver's price swings drastically from recent record highs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:18:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841a09bf48f011a29b1ee6_1770265230368.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks Split: Trade Hopes Lift Indices, Tech Sell-Off Bites IT</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Stocks-Split-Trade-Hopes-Lift-Indices-Tech-Sell-Off-Bites-IT/6984189abf48f011a29b1ccc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Stocks-Split-Trade-Hopes-Lift-Indices-Tech-Sell-Off-Bites-IT/6984189abf48f011a29b1ccc</guid><description>Indian equities opened with cautious optimism Thursday, driven by hopes of a U.S. trade deal easing tariffs and renewed foreign institutional investor (FII) inflows totaling Rs 29.79 crore. However, the broader market mood contrasts sharply with the technology sector, which experienced a significant downturn mirroring global trends. The Nifty IT index plunged 6% on Wednesday, its steepest fall in six years. Key company earnings and an impending Reserve Bank of India policy decision are also on investors' radar.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:12:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984189abf48f011a29b1ccb_1770264840790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Private Sector Push: Strategic Autonomy Amid Global Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Private-Sector-Push-Strategic-Autonomy-Amid-Global-Shifts/69841648bf48f011a29b1a7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Private-Sector-Push-Strategic-Autonomy-Amid-Global-Shifts/69841648bf48f011a29b1a7c</guid><description>Rajiv Kumar, former NITI Aayog vice-chairman, asserts that India must significantly boost its economic strength and global trade participation to command international respect. He emphasizes empowering the private sector as the primary engine for achieving 'real strategic autonomy' and increasing India's share in global merchandise trade from below 2% to a more influential level. This strategic realignment aims to leverage economic power for geopolitical influence and national interest amidst evolving global policies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:02:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841648bf48f011a29b1a7b_1770264236600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HAL Downgraded by MS Amidst Sector Headwinds; Peers Trade Higher</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/HAL-Downgraded-by-MS-Amidst-Sector-Headwinds-Peers-Trade-Higher/69841119bf48f011a29b16ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/HAL-Downgraded-by-MS-Amidst-Sector-Headwinds-Peers-Trade-Higher/69841119bf48f011a29b16ce</guid><description>Morgan Stanley has downgraded Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL) to 'underweight,' slashing its price target by 34% to ₹3,355. This move signals concerns over increasing private sector competition and potential execution delays, particularly following reports of HAL being excluded from the Advanced Medium Combat Aircraft (AMCA) project. Despite a majority of analysts maintaining 'buy' ratings, HAL's stock fell 6% on February 4, 2026, to close at ₹4,213.9, wiping out ₹18,000 crore in market capitalization. The company's P/E ratio stands at approximately 33.46x, with a market cap of ₹282,029.6 crore, while key domestic defense peers trade at significantly higher multiples.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 03:40:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69841119bf48f011a29b16cd_1770263813374.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Flash Crash: 16% Plunge as Dollar Surges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Flash-Crash-16percent-Plunge-as-Dollar-Surges/698410a7bf48f011a29b15f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Flash-Crash-16percent-Plunge-as-Dollar-Surges/698410a7bf48f011a29b15f3</guid><description>Silver prices underwent a rapid 16% freefall, plummeting below $75 an ounce and erasing prior session gains. Gold also faced selling pressure. This sharp reversal was primarily driven by a resurgent US Dollar Index nearing 98 and heightened market apprehension regarding Federal Reserve policy following speculation over the new Fed Chair nomination. The extreme price swings highlight the market's sensitivity to macro shifts and potential fragility in recent rallies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 03:38:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698410a7bf48f011a29b15f2_1770262895688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPL Taps Advanta IPO for Debt Reduction Amid Trade Deal Optimism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/UPL-Taps-Advanta-IPO-for-Debt-Reduction-Amid-Trade-Deal-Optimism/69840fbabf48f011a29b0e99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/UPL-Taps-Advanta-IPO-for-Debt-Reduction-Amid-Trade-Deal-Optimism/69840fbabf48f011a29b0e99</guid><description>UPL Ltd. shares climbed as the company reported resilient December quarter earnings and announced its subsidiary Advanta's draft IPO filing, intended to accelerate debt reduction. The recent India-US trade pact is expected to significantly improve UPL's competitive standing in the crucial North American agrochemical market, potentially offsetting past tariff challenges and aiding its deleveraging targets. The company aims to reduce its net debt to EBITDA ratio to 1.6-1.8x by March 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 03:34:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69840fbabf48f011a29b0e98_1770262750302.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Demand Skyrockets PC Component Costs, Shifting Memory Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Demand-Skyrockets-PC-Component-Costs-Shifting-Memory-Market/69840f38bf48f011a29b0410</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Demand-Skyrockets-PC-Component-Costs-Shifting-Memory-Market/69840f38bf48f011a29b0410</guid><description>The AI arms race is fundamentally restructuring the memory chip market, leading to tripling component costs and pushing high-end PC prices from $5,800 to over $7,000. Manufacturers are prioritizing AI-critical High Bandwidth Memory (HBM), creating a sustained shortage for consumer-grade DRAM and NAND. This strategic reallocation is forecast to drive significant price hikes across the PC market, with analysts anticipating elevated costs and supply constraints persisting into 2027.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 03:32:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69840f38bf48f011a29b040f_1770262521607.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Breakouts Amidst Volatility: Nuvama's Picks Eye Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Tech-Breakouts-Amidst-Volatility-Nuvamas-Picks-Eye-Gains/69840d5dbf48f011a29aedac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Tech-Breakouts-Amidst-Volatility-Nuvamas-Picks-Eye-Gains/69840d5dbf48f011a29aedac</guid><description>Nuvama's top stock picks for February 5, 2026, focus on companies exhibiting strong technical signals amidst heightened market volatility. Petronet LNG (PETRONET) has reclaimed key moving averages, MRPL (MRPL) is showing a bullish chart pattern nearing 16-month highs, and CCL Products (CCL) has broken out of consolidation after a period of correction. These selections signal a strategy to capitalize on specific stock-level momentum rather than broad index-driven rallies, even as Nifty navigates resistance levels and Bank Nifty eyes support.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 03:24:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69840d5dbf48f011a29aedab_1770261956209.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dividend Surge Signals Mature Cash Flows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Dividend-Surge-Signals-Mature-Cash-Flows/69840837bf48f011a29aea76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Dividend-Surge-Signals-Mature-Cash-Flows/69840837bf48f011a29aea76</guid><description>A wave of Indian companies is set to go ex-dividend on February 6, 2026, distributing interim payouts as a strategic move to reward shareholders. Accelya Solutions India leads with ₹45 per share, followed by significant announcements from REC, NTPC, Nestle India, and others. This broad distribution reflects mature cash flow generation and a focus on capital returns, potentially signaling confidence in ongoing business performance amidst evolving market conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 03:02:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69840837bf48f011a29aea75_1770261168998.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Memory Crunch Hits Phones: Arm, Qualcomm Stocks Dip Despite AI Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Memory-Crunch-Hits-Phones-Arm-Qualcomm-Stocks-Dip-Despite-AI-Hopes/698407bdbf48f011a29ae917</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Memory-Crunch-Hits-Phones-Arm-Qualcomm-Stocks-Dip-Despite-AI-Hopes/698407bdbf48f011a29ae917</guid><description>Arm Holdings and Qualcomm experienced significant stock declines following their latest earnings reports, pressured by a global memory chip shortage. While AI infrastructure build-outs are driving this scarcity and creating long-term opportunities for both firms in data centers, they are simultaneously crimping near-term smartphone production and revenue growth. Analysts are weighing the immediate headwinds against future AI potential, resulting in mixed sentiment and increased stock volatility.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 03:00:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698407bdbf48f011a29ae916_1770261029703.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alphabet's $185B AI Spend: Dual Boost for Custom Silicon &amp; GPUs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabets-185B-AI-Spend-Dual-Boost-for-Custom-Silicon-and-GPUs/6984076abf48f011a29ae77f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabets-185B-AI-Spend-Dual-Boost-for-Custom-Silicon-and-GPUs/6984076abf48f011a29ae77f</guid><description>Alphabet Inc. will nearly double its capital expenditure to $185 billion in 2026, primarily for artificial intelligence infrastructure. This significant investment is poised to benefit both Broadcom Inc., through its custom TPU designs, and Nvidia Corp., as Alphabet continues to utilize standard GPUs. The move highlights the escalating capital demands of AI and the strategic diversification within hyperscale hardware development, a trend impacting the broader semiconductor sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:58:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984076abf48f011a29ae77e_1770260594210.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Q3 Earnings Loom: Valuations, Competition to Test Indian Sector Leaders</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Q3-Earnings-Loom-Valuations-Competition-to-Test-Indian-Sector-Leaders/69840757bf48f011a29ae6cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Q3-Earnings-Loom-Valuations-Competition-to-Test-Indian-Sector-Leaders/69840757bf48f011a29ae6cd</guid><description>As key Indian firms Trent Limited, Bharti Airtel, and Max Healthcare Institute prepare to report Q3 earnings, investor focus sharpens on sector-specific challenges and valuations. Bharti Airtel faces regulatory scrutiny alongside robust market share gains, while Trent navigates a competitive retail environment. Max Healthcare reports amidst a sector consolidation phase, with differing analyst outlooks shaping future performance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:58:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69840757bf48f011a29ae6cc_1770260436330.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nestle Expands Infant Formula Recall Globally Over Toxin Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nestle-Expands-Infant-Formula-Recall-Globally-Over-Toxin-Fears/698406c8bf48f011a29ae5a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nestle-Expands-Infant-Formula-Recall-Globally-Over-Toxin-Fears/698406c8bf48f011a29ae5a1</guid><description>Nestle is expanding its infant formula recall to include Guigoz batches in France and SMA in the UK. This action follows new European Union methods for detecting the cereulide toxin, a substance that can cause severe nausea and vomiting. The move comes despite analyst expectations that previous withdrawals would suffice. French investigators are also examining a potential link between two infant deaths and the recalled Guigoz formula, though no conclusive evidence has emerged.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:56:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698406c8bf48f011a29ae5a0_1770260282826.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Amnesty Scheme Targets Undeclared Foreign Assets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Amnesty-Scheme-Targets-Undeclared-Foreign-Assets/69840656bf48f011a29ae435</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Amnesty-Scheme-Targets-Undeclared-Foreign-Assets/69840656bf48f011a29ae435</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 has launched a one-time, six-month foreign asset disclosure scheme (FAST-DS 2026) providing a window for individuals to declare previously undisclosed foreign assets or income. This initiative offers relief through lower penalties compared to the Black Money Act, specifically targeting smaller taxpayers like students and young professionals. Category A requires a 60% total payment on undisclosed assets up to ₹1 crore, while Category B allows regularization of unreported assets up to ₹5 crore for a flat ₹1 lakh fee per asset. Non-compliance post-deadline invites severe penalties, including prosecution and substantial fines.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:54:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69840656bf48f011a29ae434_1770260222757.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Noize Brands Acquires 43% Jauss Polymers, Triggers ₹1.93 Cr Open Offer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Noize-Brands-Acquires-43percent-Jauss-Polymers-Triggers-193-Cr-Open-Offer/6984057ebf48f011a29ae23b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Noize-Brands-Acquires-43percent-Jauss-Polymers-Triggers-193-Cr-Open-Offer/6984057ebf48f011a29ae23b</guid><description>Noize Brands and Lifestyle Limited, along with PAC Mr. Aditya Chopra, has acquired a 43.41% stake in Jauss Polymers Limited for ₹3.75 Crores. This substantial acquisition triggers a mandatory open offer under SEBI regulations. The acquirer will offer to buy up to 26.00% of Jauss Polymers' equity shares at ₹16.05 per share, amounting to a total consideration of ₹1.93 Crores. The acquirer intends to keep the target company listed post-offer, providing an exit route for retail investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:50:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984057ebf48f011a29ae23a_1770260041840.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Swan Defence Wins Major Oman Defence Export Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Swan-Defence-Wins-Major-Oman-Defence-Export-Order/69840568bf48f011a29ae154</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Swan-Defence-Wins-Major-Oman-Defence-Export-Order/69840568bf48f011a29ae154</guid><description>Swan Defence and Heavy Industries Limited (SDHI) has landed a crucial defence export contract from the Sultanate of Oman. The company will supply a state-of-the-art training ship to the Royal Navy of Oman, underscoring India's growing capabilities in indigenous shipbuilding and its role as a global maritime exporter. This deal highlights SDHI's advanced technical expertise and strengthens bilateral maritime cooperation between India and Oman.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:50:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69840568bf48f011a29ae153_1770259914941.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Critical Minerals: Geopolitical Scramble Ignites Supply Chain War</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Critical-Minerals-Geopolitical-Scramble-Ignites-Supply-Chain-War/6984030dbf48f011a29ade77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Critical-Minerals-Geopolitical-Scramble-Ignites-Supply-Chain-War/6984030dbf48f011a29ade77</guid><description>The inaugural Critical Minerals Ministerial in Washington marked a significant escalation in the global effort to decouple from China's overwhelming control over essential resources. With Beijing dominating 95% of critical mineral production and refining, nations are forging alliances to de-risk supply chains, driven by demand from clean energy and advanced technology sectors. This strategic realignment highlights critical minerals as the new geopolitical battleground, with profound implications for global markets and national security.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:40:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6984030dbf48f011a29ade76_1770259293005.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Earnings Mixed Amid Global Tech Jitters; NSDL Lock-in Expiry Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indian-Earnings-Mixed-Amid-Global-Tech-Jitters-NSDL-Lock-in-Expiry-Looms/6983ffd5bf48f011a29ad232</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indian-Earnings-Mixed-Amid-Global-Tech-Jitters-NSDL-Lock-in-Expiry-Looms/6983ffd5bf48f011a29ad232</guid><description>India's benchmark indices are poised for a cautious start, influenced by Wall Street's tech-led decline and mixed signals from Asia. Domestically, Q3FY26 corporate results present a divergence: Tata Power's profits fall due to operational issues, while Emami and TMB post strong gains. A key event is the expiry of the lock-in period for 75% of NSDL's shares, potentially unlocking significant trading volume. This comes as many large-cap entities, including Bharti Airtel and LIC, are set to announce their earnings today.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:26:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983ffd5bf48f011a29ad231_1770258590783.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHPC Shares Tumble 5% as Q3 Earnings Miss, EBITDA Plunges 79%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/NHPC-Shares-Tumble-5percent-as-Q3-Earnings-Miss-EBITDA-Plunges-79percent/6983ffc0bf48f011a29ad107</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/NHPC-Shares-Tumble-5percent-as-Q3-Earnings-Miss-EBITDA-Plunges-79percent/6983ffc0bf48f011a29ad107</guid><description>NHPC Ltd. reported a sharp year-on-year decline in third-quarter earnings, with EBITDA slumping 79.2% to ₹210 crore. Revenue dipped 2.9% to ₹2,220 crore. Margins contracted significantly to 9.5% from 44.4%, driven by a 3.2-fold surge in other expenses to ₹1,537 crore and increased tax burdens. The company also cancelled solar project MoUs and is set to withdraw as promoter of PTC India.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:26:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983ffc0bf48f011a29ad106_1770258458350.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Experts Unveil Top 9 Stock Picks for February 5 Trading</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Experts-Unveil-Top-9-Stock-Picks-for-February-5-Trading/6983fde3bf48f011a29acf21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Experts-Unveil-Top-9-Stock-Picks-for-February-5-Trading/6983fde3bf48f011a29acf21</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks extended gains on February 5, with the Nifty 50 climbing 0.2 percent amidst strong market breadth. Experts have identified nine high-conviction stock recommendations for short-term trading. These picks, including Hero MotoCorp, Sarda Energy, Max Financial Services, Hindalco Industries, and Larsen &amp; Toubro, are based on technical breakouts and momentum indicators, with specific price targets and stop-loss levels provided for each.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:18:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983fde3bf48f011a29acf20_1770258079599.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIFT Nifty Firms Up; Global Mix, IT ADR Slump Cast Shadow</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GIFT-Nifty-Firms-Up-Global-Mix-IT-ADR-Slump-Cast-Shadow/6983fc05bf48f011a29acd4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GIFT-Nifty-Firms-Up-Global-Mix-IT-ADR-Slump-Cast-Shadow/6983fc05bf48f011a29acd4c</guid><description>Indian equity markets are poised for a positive start, with GIFT Nifty trading higher in early hours. However, a sharp decline in U.S. tech stocks and their Indian ADRs, coupled with mixed Asian and Wall Street performances, suggests volatility. Investors will also monitor developments in the India-U.S. trade deal and reactions to the recent budget.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:10:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983fc05bf48f011a29acd4b_1770257927956.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Soars, Tech Stocks Tumble: Indian Markets Diverge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Soars-Tech-Stocks-Tumble-Indian-Markets-Diverge/6983fba0bf48f011a29acc6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Soars-Tech-Stocks-Tumble-Indian-Markets-Diverge/6983fba0bf48f011a29acc6e</guid><description>On February 4, 2026, Indian markets displayed a bifurcated trend. Precious metals like gold and silver rebounded sharply, driven by a weaker US dollar and global economic data, with gold futures aiming for higher targets. Concurrently, the Indian equity market navigated a cautious session, closing marginally higher. However, the technology sector experienced a significant downturn, losing approximately ₹2 lakh crore in market capitalization due to fears of AI-driven disruption from new tools like Anthropic's Claude Cowork. This occurred amidst a backdrop of mixed corporate earnings reports from companies like Tata Power and Apollo Tyres, and regulatory scrutiny on IndiGo.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:08:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983fba0bf48f011a29acc6d_1770258962122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSDL Share Unlock, Apollo Tyres Margins, IndiGo Probe Jolt Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/NSDL-Share-Unlock-Apollo-Tyres-Margins-IndiGo-Probe-Jolt-Markets/6983fb8abf48f011a29acb5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/NSDL-Share-Unlock-Apollo-Tyres-Margins-IndiGo-Probe-Jolt-Markets/6983fb8abf48f011a29acb5c</guid><description>February 5, 2026, brings significant market events: National Securities Depository (NSDL) will see 75% of its shares become tradable, a ₹14,875 crore liquidity event. IndiGo faces a Competition Commission of India investigation for unfair practices amid market share shifts. Apollo Tyres posted a 39.6% net profit rise, driven by 15.3% EBITDA margins, though its P/E of ~40.7x is elevated compared to peers. Tata Power reported a flat net profit despite a 9.4% revenue decline, impacted by its non-operational Mundra plant.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 02:08:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983fb8abf48f011a29acb5b_1770257393952.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Diverge: Cyclical Stocks Lead Amidst IT Weakness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Markets-Diverge-Cyclical-Stocks-Lead-Amidst-IT-Weakness/6983ef5fbf48f011a29ac4b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Markets-Diverge-Cyclical-Stocks-Lead-Amidst-IT-Weakness/6983ef5fbf48f011a29ac4b0</guid><description>Indian markets showed cautious consolidation on Wednesday, February 4, 2026, with the Nifty 50 index inching up to 25,779.5. A significant divergence emerged, with auto, metal, and energy sectors attracting buying interest, contrasted by a sharp decline in the IT index due to global tech weakness. Mid and small-cap stocks continued their recovery, bolstering market breadth. Investors are advised to focus on selective stock picking amid mixed global cues and profit-booking pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:16:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983ef5fbf48f011a29ac4af_1770255111637.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent Ltd. Beats EBITDA Estimates, But Fashion Woes Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Ltd-Beats-EBITDA-Estimates-But-Fashion-Woes-Linger/6983eee2bf48f011a29ac3c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Ltd-Beats-EBITDA-Estimates-But-Fashion-Woes-Linger/6983eee2bf48f011a29ac3c2</guid><description>Trent Ltd. posted a robust third-quarter performance, with EBITDA rising 27.6% to ₹1,081 crore, surpassing market expectations. This growth was fueled by contributions from beauty, personal care, innerwear, and footwear segments, which now account for over 21% of the topline. The Star hypermarket business also saw its own brands contributing 74% to its revenue, prompting plans for accelerated expansion. However, the company's fashion portfolio experienced marginally negative like-for-like growth due to a shift in the festive season. Despite a 5% rise in its stock price on Wednesday ahead of the results, Trent shares remain significantly below their October 2024 peak, trading over 40% lower.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:14:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983eee2bf48f011a29ac3c1_1770254234617.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GAIL Battles Regulator Over Tariff: Future Capex Squeeze?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GAIL-Battles-Regulator-Over-Tariff-Future-Capex-Squeeze/6983edf6bf48f011a29ac296</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GAIL-Battles-Regulator-Over-Tariff-Future-Capex-Squeeze/6983edf6bf48f011a29ac296</guid><description>GAIL (India) Limited is contesting the Petroleum and Natural Gas Regulatory Board's (PNGRB) recent tariff order for its integrated pipeline network. The regulator approved a 12% increase to ₹65.69 per mmBtu, falling short of GAIL's requested ₹78. GAIL argues the PNGRB's exclusion of future capital and operational expenditures, coupled with a miscalculation of transmission losses and revenue sharing from capacity utilization, jeopardizes its financial model and could lead to higher consumer costs long-term. This dispute highlights a critical tension between regulatory price control and the substantial investment needed for India's energy infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:10:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983edf6bf48f011a29ac295_1770253975749.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ambani: India to slash energy imports; Reliance eyes AI dominance.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Ambani-India-to-slash-energy-imports-Reliance-eyes-AI-dominance/6983ed89bf48f011a29ac106</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Ambani-India-to-slash-energy-imports-Reliance-eyes-AI-dominance/6983ed89bf48f011a29ac106</guid><description>Reliance Industries Chairman Mukesh Ambani projected India will import less than 20% of its energy within a decade. Addressing a JioBlackRock event, he detailed Reliance's pivot to becoming an AI-native deeptech firm, anticipating a tenfold productivity boost. Ambani also stressed that sustained law and order and social harmony are critical for India's long-term economic expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:08:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983ed89bf48f011a29ac105_1770254401830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI's Rs 10 Lakh SIFs: A New Bridge for Sophisticated Investors?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SEBIs-Rs-10-Lakh-SIFs-A-New-Bridge-for-Sophisticated-Investors/6983ed7cbf48f011a29ac0ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SEBIs-Rs-10-Lakh-SIFs-A-New-Bridge-for-Sophisticated-Investors/6983ed7cbf48f011a29ac0ad</guid><description>SEBI has launched Specialised Investment Funds (SIFs) with a minimum investment of ₹10 lakh, aiming to bridge the gap between mutual funds and Portfolio Management Services (PMS). These funds, operational since April 2025, saw over 20,000 folios by December 2025, with many AMCs adopting long-short strategies. Despite their launch, early performance data indicates SIFs are lagging benchmarks, and liquidity can be more restricted than traditional mutual funds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:08:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983ed7cbf48f011a29ac0ac_1770253807337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: High-Tech Vision Ignores Farmer Income Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Budget-2026-High-Tech-Vision-Ignores-Farmer-Income-Crisis/6983ed05bf48f011a29abf52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Budget-2026-High-Tech-Vision-Ignores-Farmer-Income-Crisis/6983ed05bf48f011a29abf52</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 emphasizes technological advancement in agriculture, focusing on AI-driven development and support for high-value crops like coconut and cashew. While this signals a long-term modernization strategy, it largely sidesteps the immediate income distress faced by farmers grappling with volatile markets, rising input costs, and inadequate procurement mechanisms. The budget's vision for future farming offers little tangible relief for cultivators currently struggling with poor market prices, particularly for nutri-cereals, pulses, and oilseeds, where Minimum Support Price (MSP) realization remains inconsistent.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:06:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983ed05bf48f011a29abf51_1770253685300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pivots to US Energy: Trade Deal Fuels New Supply Chains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Pivots-to-US-Energy-Trade-Deal-Fuels-New-Supply-Chains/6983e23abf48f011a29ab87f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Pivots-to-US-Energy-Trade-Deal-Fuels-New-Supply-Chains/6983e23abf48f011a29ab87f</guid><description>India's energy import strategy is undergoing a significant shift, with state-owned companies preparing to boost purchases from the United States under a new bilateral trade agreement. This pivot comes as crude oil and natural gas imports from Russia are expected to decline sharply. While the trade deal offers India reduced tariffs and enhanced energy security, it introduces potential economic challenges, including increased freight costs and forgone discounts, as New Delhi recalibrates its global energy sourcing to balance geopolitical alignments and market economics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:20:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983e23abf48f011a29ab87e_1770250973049.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>