<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:21:25 +0000</pubDate><item><title>NBFC Stocks Surge! Shriram Finance, IIFL, L&amp;T Finance Hit Record Highs - What's Driving the Rally?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFC-Stocks-Surge-Shriram-Finance-IIFL-LandT-Finance-Hit-Record-Highs-Whats-Driving-the-Rally/695637994342f77179f508ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFC-Stocks-Surge-Shriram-Finance-IIFL-LandT-Finance-Hit-Record-Highs-Whats-Driving-the-Rally/695637994342f77179f508ed</guid><description>Shriram Finance, IIFL Finance, and L&amp;T Finance have reached new all-time highs, with Shriram Finance surging 19% in the last month. This rally is boosted by Shriram Finance's significant proposed investment deal with MUFG Bank, which is expected to enhance its capitalisation and profitability. Analysts maintain positive outlooks for these non-banking financial companies, citing steady growth prospects and favourable funding costs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:47:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695637994342f77179f508ec_1767258211689.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India's Historic Shift: First Indian CEO Takes Helm Amidst Massive ₹45,000 Crore Investment!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-Indias-Historic-Shift-First-Indian-CEO-Takes-Helm-Amidst-Massive-45000-Crore-Investment/6956377c4342f77179f5083e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-Indias-Historic-Shift-First-Indian-CEO-Takes-Helm-Amidst-Massive-45000-Crore-Investment/6956377c4342f77179f5083e</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India has appointed Tarun Garg as its first Indian Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer, a landmark achievement after 29 years. Garg, with over 20 years in the auto sector and a key role in launching popular models, succeeds Unsoo Kim. The company also unveiled a substantial ₹45,000 crore investment plan for FY26-FY30, focusing on expanding manufacturing, boosting R&amp;D, localization, introducing 26 new products including EVs and hybrid models, and launching the Genesis luxury brand in India.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:46:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956377c4342f77179f5083d_1767258055419.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Prudential CIO S Naren's Secret Strategy: Find These Unloved Stocks for Big Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/ICICI-Prudential-CIO-S-Narens-Secret-Strategy-Find-These-Unloved-Stocks-for-Big-Gains/695637354342f77179f50699</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/ICICI-Prudential-CIO-S-Narens-Secret-Strategy-Find-These-Unloved-Stocks-for-Big-Gains/695637354342f77179f50699</guid><description>S Naren, Chief Investment Officer at ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company, believes the market is in a mature bull phase, making careful stock selection crucial. He advises against broad sector bets, instead focusing on researching and investing in specific companies across pharmaceuticals, healthcare, and software that have seen significant price corrections and where risk-reward remains favourable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:46:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695637354342f77179f50698_1767258121798.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Stock CRASH WARNING? Emkay Global Slashes Target to Rs 6 – Is This the End?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Stock-CRASH-WARNING-Emkay-Global-Slashes-Target-to-Rs-6-Is-This-the-End/695636494342f77179f50230</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Stock-CRASH-WARNING-Emkay-Global-Slashes-Target-to-Rs-6-Is-This-the-End/695636494342f77179f50230</guid><description>Emkay Global Financial has issued a strong sell recommendation for Vodafone Idea, setting a target price of just Rs 6. The brokerage's report highlights that while the Union Cabinet granted a 5-year interest-free moratorium on certain AGR dues, no waiver was provided, contrary to market expectations. Vodafone Idea also faces significant deferred payment obligations for spectrum. Emkay Global believes the company needs further relief or funding to manage its challenges, leading to their bearish outlook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:41:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695636494342f77179f5022f_1767257820028.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Modern Diagnostic IPO Ignites Market Buzz! GMP Soars as Investors Flock – Will This SME Debut Skyrocket?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Modern-Diagnostic-IPO-Ignites-Market-Buzz-GMP-Soars-as-Investors-Flock-Will-This-SME-Debut-Skyrocket/6956357e4342f77179f4fdb3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Modern-Diagnostic-IPO-Ignites-Market-Buzz-GMP-Soars-as-Investors-Flock-Will-This-SME-Debut-Skyrocket/6956357e4342f77179f4fdb3</guid><description>Modern Diagnostic IPO is witnessing strong investor interest, subscribed over 15 times by day two. The grey market premium (GMP) is around 14%, suggesting potential listing gains. The company aims to raise ₹37 crore and will list on the BSE SME platform on January 7. Proceeds are for expansion and equipment purchases.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:41:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956357e4342f77179f4fdb2_1767257540001.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Stocks 2026: Goodbye Easy Gains, Hello Fundamentals! Are You Ready for the Shift?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Stocks-2026-Goodbye-Easy-Gains-Hello-Fundamentals-Are-You-Ready-for-the-Shift/6956360a4342f77179f50080</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Stocks-2026-Goodbye-Easy-Gains-Hello-Fundamentals-Are-You-Ready-for-the-Shift/6956360a4342f77179f50080</guid><description>Indian equities are entering a selective phase in 2026, moving from a pandemic-era rally driven by momentum to a market where earnings durability is key. Experts predict fewer easy winners and a greater need for astute stock selection as 'firefly stocks' fade, with market performance now hinging squarely on fundamentals rather than broad market direction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:40:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956360a4342f77179f5007f_1767258303626.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Airport King: GMR Soars While Airlines Tumble! Why Investors Are Betting Big on Infrastructure.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Airport-King-GMR-Soars-While-Airlines-Tumble-Why-Investors-Are-Betting-Big-on-Infrastructure/695634ae4342f77179f4f91f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Airport-King-GMR-Soars-While-Airlines-Tumble-Why-Investors-Are-Betting-Big-on-Infrastructure/695634ae4342f77179f4f91f</guid><description>GMR Airports stock has surged 22% in six months while other aviation players declined significantly. This outperformance is driven by stable, long-term airport concession agreements and recent regulatory changes, particularly a 147% tariff hike at Delhi Airport, boosting revenues. Investors are favoring airports' annuity-like income streams over volatile airline operations, with GMR seen as a pure-play infrastructure bet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:40:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695634ae4342f77179f4f91e_1767257326885.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's First Vande Bharat Sleeper Train Launching Soon! Modi to Flag Off Kolkata-Guwahati Route 🚀</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-First-Vande-Bharat-Sleeper-Train-Launching-Soon-Modi-to-Flag-Off-Kolkata-Guwahati-Route/6956353a4342f77179f4fc5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-First-Vande-Bharat-Sleeper-Train-Launching-Soon-Modi-to-Flag-Off-Kolkata-Guwahati-Route/6956353a4342f77179f4fc5a</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi will soon launch India's first Vande Bharat Sleeper train on the Kolkata-Guwahati route. Railway Minister Ashwini Vaishnaw confirmed that testing is complete, with the launch expected around January 18-19. Fares are set to be significantly lower than air travel, starting at approximately ₹2,300 for 3rd AC, making it accessible for the middle class. The train features advanced safety, comfort amenities, and offers regional cuisine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:38:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956353a4342f77179f4fc59_1767257616323.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KEC International Surges on Massive ₹1,050 Crore Order Bonanza: What Investors Must Know NOW!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Surges-on-Massive-1050-Crore-Order-Bonanza-What-Investors-Must-Know-NOW/695634bd4342f77179f4f99d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Surges-on-Massive-1050-Crore-Order-Bonanza-What-Investors-Must-Know-NOW/695634bd4342f77179f4f99d</guid><description>KEC International, part of the RPG Group, has secured new orders worth ₹1,050 crore across its renewable energy, civil, transmission &amp; distribution (T&amp;D), and cables businesses. Notable wins include a 100+ MW wind project balance of plant package and a downstream project for a leading steel player. Subsidiary SAE Towers also bagged significant orders in Mexico. These wins boost the year-to-date order intake to approximately ₹19,300 crore, reinforcing confidence in growth targets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:36:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695634bd4342f77179f4f99c_1767257369030.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Steel Stocks Set for Massive Surge? Morgan Stanley Reveals Top Picks After Government Duty!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Steel-Stocks-Set-for-Massive-Surge-Morgan-Stanley-Reveals-Top-Picks-After-Government-Duty/695634384342f77179f4f62e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Steel-Stocks-Set-for-Massive-Surge-Morgan-Stanley-Reveals-Top-Picks-After-Government-Duty/695634384342f77179f4f62e</guid><description>Morgan Stanley has turned bullish on Indian steel stocks following the Ministry of Finance's imposition of a three-year safeguard duty on certain steel imports. Analysts predict this move could boost domestic hot rolled coil prices by 10% and lead to significant EBITDA increases (16-43%) for covered companies. JSW Steel and Steel Authority of India (SAIL) are highlighted as top picks, with Tata Steel and Jindal Steel also seen as beneficiaries.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:36:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695634384342f77179f4f62d_1767257213031.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nuvama's Q3 Consumer Forecast: Top Picks &amp; Potential Slump Stocks Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nuvamas-Q3-Consumer-Forecast-Top-Picks-and-Potential-Slump-Stocks-Revealed/695634524342f77179f4f70f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nuvamas-Q3-Consumer-Forecast-Top-Picks-and-Potential-Slump-Stocks-Revealed/695634524342f77179f4f70f</guid><description>Nuvama Institutional Equities predicts a strong Q3 for India's consumer sector, driven by demand recovery, GST benefits, and seasonal factors like a harsh winter. They highlight Marico, Tata Consumer Products, Nestle India, and others for top-line growth. Nuvama's preferred 'Buy' stocks include Nestle, Tata Consumer, Britannia, and Asian Paints, while cautioning about a potential volume decline for Colgate Palmolive India. Rural demand continues to outperform urban markets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:36:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695634524342f77179f4f70e_1767257322454.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Consumer Spending Set for 2026 Boom: Premiumization &amp; Policy Drive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Consumer-Spending-Set-for-2026-Boom-Premiumization-and-Policy-Drive-Growth/695634454342f77179f4f698</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Consumer-Spending-Set-for-2026-Boom-Premiumization-and-Policy-Drive-Growth/695634454342f77179f4f698</guid><description>India's consumer sector is poised for continued growth in 2026, driven by a shift towards premium, quality, and value-driven purchases rather than just volume. Urban demand, economic formalization, and supportive policies like GST collections crossing ₹1.6 lakh crore monthly are underpinning this trend. Companies are focusing on execution and tailored product offerings to meet evolving consumer preferences.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:35:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695634454342f77179f4f697_1767257250974.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cupid Shares Surge 27% in 15 Sessions: Record High Amidst Global Expansion and Strong Earnings!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cupid-Shares-Surge-27percent-in-15-Sessions-Record-High-Amidst-Global-Expansion-and-Strong-Earnings/69562f914342f77179f4e263</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cupid-Shares-Surge-27percent-in-15-Sessions-Record-High-Amidst-Global-Expansion-and-Strong-Earnings/69562f914342f77179f4e263</guid><description>Cupid Limited shares have extended their rally for a 15th consecutive session, hitting a new record high of ₹524.95 and gaining approximately 27% during this period. This surge follows strong Q2FY26 results, which saw net profit jump 140% year-on-year to ₹24.12 crore and revenue rise 91% to ₹90.23 crore. The company is also expanding globally by setting up an FMCG manufacturing facility in Saudi Arabia. Despite analyst recommendations to book profits due to overbought conditions, the stock continues its upward momentum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:13:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69562f914342f77179f4e262_1767256616020.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geojit Turns Bullish on Apollo Tyres: Upgrade to 'Accumulate' with ₹548 Target!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Geojit-Turns-Bullish-on-Apollo-Tyres-Upgrade-to-Accumulate-with-548-Target/69562f114342f77179f4e03c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Geojit-Turns-Bullish-on-Apollo-Tyres-Upgrade-to-Accumulate-with-548-Target/69562f114342f77179f4e03c</guid><description>Geojit Investments upgraded Apollo Tyres to 'Accumulate' with a ₹548 target price, citing expected improved operating performance driven by demand recovery and cost optimisation. The brokerage highlighted a strategic shift towards premium products, stable raw material costs, and growth from GST reforms and exports, despite an exceptional cost for a plant closure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:13:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69562f114342f77179f4e03b_1767255886557.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Karur Vysya Bank Shares Surge to Record Highs on Impressive Q3 Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Karur-Vysya-Bank-Shares-Surge-to-Record-Highs-on-Impressive-Q3-Growth/69562eec4342f77179f4df84</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Karur-Vysya-Bank-Shares-Surge-to-Record-Highs-on-Impressive-Q3-Growth/69562eec4342f77179f4df84</guid><description>Karur Vysya Bank shares hit a fresh record high, jumping nearly 4% after reporting strong business growth for the quarter ended December 2025. Total business grew 16.29% year-on-year to ₹2.12 trillion, with deposits up 15.57% to ₹1.15 trillion and advances rising 17.15% to ₹97,048 crore. The bank also saw improvements in net interest margin and a reduction in operating expenses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:13:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69562eec4342f77179f4df83_1767256269201.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil India Stock Alert: HDFC Securities Slashes Target, Yet Maintains Strong 'Buy' Rating! Discover Why</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-India-Stock-Alert-HDFC-Securities-Slashes-Target-Yet-Maintains-Strong-Buy-Rating-Discover-Why/69562e444342f77179f4dc40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-India-Stock-Alert-HDFC-Securities-Slashes-Target-Yet-Maintains-Strong-Buy-Rating-Discover-Why/69562e444342f77179f4dc40</guid><description>HDFC Securities has lowered its target price for Oil India to ₹495 from ₹509, citing delays in the Numaligarh Refinery expansion. Despite this, the brokerage maintains its 'Buy' rating, anticipating robust growth with a 9% CAGR in gas production and a 4% CAGR in oil production over FY25-27E. The new target implies a potential 16.7% upside.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:13:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69562e444342f77179f4dc3f_1767256145318.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Caplin Point Shocks Market: HUGE US Pharma Deal Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Caplin-Point-Shocks-Market-HUGE-US-Pharma-Deal-Unveiled/69562e1f4342f77179f4db6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Caplin-Point-Shocks-Market-HUGE-US-Pharma-Deal-Unveiled/69562e1f4342f77179f4db6d</guid><description>Caplin Point Laboratories has significantly boosted its US presence by acquiring 10 approved Abbreviated New Drug Applications (ANDAs) for injectable and ophthalmic products from a major multinational firm. This strategic move, executed via subsidiaries Caplin Steriles and Caplin One Labs, targets a substantial $473.2 million addressable market and includes vital oncology injectables for its new dedicated facility. The company aims to accelerate growth in regulated markets, particularly the United States, while also planning expansion into Mexico, Canada, the European Union, and Brazil.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:12:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69562e1f4342f77179f4db6c_1767255661697.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>APL Apollo Tubes SMASHES Q3 Records: Demand Surge Fuels Stunning Sales Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/APL-Apollo-Tubes-SMASHES-Q3-Records-Demand-Surge-Fuels-Stunning-Sales-Growth/69562e004342f77179f4dabc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/APL-Apollo-Tubes-SMASHES-Q3-Records-Demand-Surge-Fuels-Stunning-Sales-Growth/69562e004342f77179f4dabc</guid><description>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd reported record Q3FY26 sales volumes, reaching 9,16,976 tonnes, an 11% year-on-year increase. This growth was driven by strong demand across infrastructure, housing, and industrial sectors. Key product segments like structural tubes and value-added rust-proof ranges also saw significant rises. The company's expanding distribution network and focus on branded products contributed to the performance, with the stock trading higher post-announcement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:12:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69562e004342f77179f4dabb_1767255623575.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian VC Funding Slows, But AI &amp; Deep Tech Explode! Is This India's Next Tech Revolution?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indian-VC-Funding-Slows-But-AI-and-Deep-Tech-Explode-Is-This-Indias-Next-Tech-Revolution/69562cfa4342f77179f4d60b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indian-VC-Funding-Slows-But-AI-and-Deep-Tech-Explode-Is-This-Indias-Next-Tech-Revolution/69562cfa4342f77179f4d60b</guid><description>India's venture capital funding for 2025, reaching $9.6 billion by mid-December, is nearly on par with 2024's total, despite a dip in deal volume to 846 from 973. While e-commerce remains the top sector with $2.35 billion, significant growth is seen in AI/ML, attracting $1.2 billion across 191 deals, and Deep Tech, with $1.04 billion from 128 deals. Looking ahead to 2026, a greater focus is anticipated on late-stage AI funding, sector-specific solutions, and generative AI, potentially boosted by the government's INR 1 Lakh Crore RDI Fund.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:07:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69562cfa4342f77179f4d60a_1767255781556.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>South India Cement Prices PLUMMET! Investors Brace for Profit Shock 📉</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/South-India-Cement-Prices-PLUMMET-Investors-Brace-for-Profit-Shock/69562cdc4342f77179f4d52d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/South-India-Cement-Prices-PLUMMET-Investors-Brace-for-Profit-Shock/69562cdc4342f77179f4d52d</guid><description>Cement prices in South India have seen the steepest quarterly fall in Q3FY26, dropping 3.9% sequentially to ₹304 per bag, according to Elara Securities. Subdued demand, oversupply, and intense competition are key reasons, exacerbating profitability concerns for companies like UltraTech Cement and Ramco Cements. Despite upcoming infrastructure projects, a quick revival is unlikely with significant new capacities expected, potentially delaying price recovery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 08:07:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69562cdc4342f77179f4d52c_1767255326221.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auto Stocks Skyrocket: December Sales Boom Pushes BSE Auto Index to All-Time Highs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Stocks-Skyrocket-December-Sales-Boom-Pushes-BSE-Auto-Index-to-All-Time-Highs/695627154342f77179f4bbed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Stocks-Skyrocket-December-Sales-Boom-Pushes-BSE-Auto-Index-to-All-Time-Highs/695627154342f77179f4bbed</guid><description>The Indian auto sector is buzzing as the BSE Auto index reached a new high, surging 1% intraday, driven by strong December 2025 sales updates from major companies. Ashok Leyland and TVS Motor Company hit all-time highs, while Mahindra &amp; Mahindra also neared its record. Companies like M&amp;M reported significant year-on-year sales growth, fueled by factors such as GST rationalization and robust demand across utility, commercial, and two-wheeler segments, according to brokerage reports.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:39:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695627154342f77179f4bbec_1767255072635.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>United Spirits Shares Plummet 4% on Senior Executive Exit: What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/United-Spirits-Shares-Plummet-4percent-on-Senior-Executive-Exit-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/695626734342f77179f4b8aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/United-Spirits-Shares-Plummet-4percent-on-Senior-Executive-Exit-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/695626734342f77179f4b8aa</guid><description>United Spirits shares fell nearly 4% after announcing the resignation of Diwaker Vij, Vice President - Commercial Finance, effective December 31, 2025. This move occurred despite the company reporting strong financial results for Q2FY26, with a 36.1% increase in consolidated net profit to ₹464 crore and an 11.6% rise in net revenue to ₹3,173 crore.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:39:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695626734342f77179f4b8a9_1767253684190.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Production Trails Target, Offtake Dips; Subsidiary IPOs Loom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Production-Trails-Target-Offtake-Dips-Subsidiary-IPOs-Loom/695626a14342f77179f4b9b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Production-Trails-Target-Offtake-Dips-Subsidiary-IPOs-Loom/695626a14342f77179f4b9b1</guid><description>Coal India's year-to-date production stands at 60% of its full-year target, reaching 529.2 MT, a 2.6% dip from last year. December saw a 4.6% production jump to 75.7 MT, but offtake fell 5.2%, and year-to-date offtake is down 2.2%. The company is also advancing plans, directed by the PMO, to list all subsidiaries by FY30, with IPOs for key units in progress.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:38:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695626a14342f77179f4b9b0_1767254468456.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Karur Vysya Bank: Record High Beckons as Q3 Growth Spikes 17%! Investor Frenzy?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Karur-Vysya-Bank-Record-High-Beckons-as-Q3-Growth-Spikes-17percent-Investor-Frenzy/695626054342f77179f4b660</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Karur-Vysya-Bank-Record-High-Beckons-as-Q3-Growth-Spikes-17percent-Investor-Frenzy/695626054342f77179f4b660</guid><description>Karur Vysya Bank reported strong Q3 results, with deposits growing 15.57% year-on-year to ₹99,155 crore and advances surging 17.15% to ₹82,838 crore. CASA also saw a 10.76% increase. The bank's shares are trading near record highs, up 45% in the past year. Most analysts recommend buying the stock.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:38:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695626054342f77179f4b65f_1767253988181.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks to Manage Your Pension Fund! PFRDA Unlocks New Era for NPS Subscribers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-to-Manage-Your-Pension-Fund-PFRDA-Unlocks-New-Era-for-NPS-Subscribers/695626254342f77179f4b720</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-to-Manage-Your-Pension-Fund-PFRDA-Unlocks-New-Era-for-NPS-Subscribers/695626254342f77179f4b720</guid><description>The Pension Fund Regulatory and Development Authority (PFRDA) has introduced major reforms for the National Pension System (NPS). Scheduled Commercial Banks can now independently sponsor Pension Funds, increasing subscriber choice and competition. Dinesh Kumar Khara, former SBI Chairman, has been appointed as the Chairperson of the NPS Trust Board. Additionally, a new slab-based fee structure for non-government subscribers will lower costs as assets under management grow, effective April 1, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:38:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695626254342f77179f4b71f_1767254342460.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Hospital Sector Set for Massive 11-12% Growth: Medical Tourism &amp; Insurance Fueling Unprecedented Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Hospital-Sector-Set-for-Massive-11-12percent-Growth-Medical-Tourism-and-Insurance-Fueling-Unprecedented-Boom/695624694342f77179f4ae43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Hospital-Sector-Set-for-Massive-11-12percent-Growth-Medical-Tourism-and-Insurance-Fueling-Unprecedented-Boom/695624694342f77179f4ae43</guid><description>India's hospital sector is projected to grow at 11-12% annually, driven by factors like increased insurance coverage, booming medical tourism, and rising healthcare demands. The private sector is expected to lead this growth, benefiting from low treatment costs that attract over 7 lakh medical tourists in 2024. Corporate hospitals have shown strong revenue growth, with projections of 10-12% over the next few years, supported by capacity additions and stable occupancy levels.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:30:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695624694342f77179f4ae42_1767253279079.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Skoda India Records Explosive Growth: Sales More Than Double in 25th Anniversary Year!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Skoda-India-Records-Explosive-Growth-Sales-More-Than-Double-in-25th-Anniversary-Year/695624ac4342f77179f4af70</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Skoda-India-Records-Explosive-Growth-Sales-More-Than-Double-in-25th-Anniversary-Year/695624ac4342f77179f4af70</guid><description>Skoda Auto India celebrated its 25th anniversary by achieving its strongest-ever sales performance, more than doubling its unit sales in 2025 to 72,665 units, up from 35,166 units in 2024. The company credits this success to its enhanced product portfolio and expanded network presence. Looking ahead, Skoda Auto India plans further growth in 2026 with new product launches and strengthened customer initiatives.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:28:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695624ac4342f77179f4af6f_1767253506489.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nykaa Stock Plummets? HDFC Securities Slams 'Sell' Rating with Grim Forecast!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Nykaa-Stock-Plummets-HDFC-Securities-Slams-Sell-Rating-with-Grim-Forecast/69561f7d4342f77179f492b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Nykaa-Stock-Plummets-HDFC-Securities-Slams-Sell-Rating-with-Grim-Forecast/69561f7d4342f77179f492b9</guid><description>HDFC Securities maintains a 'Sell' rating on FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa), setting a target price of ₹200. The brokerage expresses concerns over the core beauty and personal care (BPC) business growth, expecting sub-20% expansion after excluding own brands and eB2B. Fashion segment profitability remains a challenge, with margin improvements attributed to cost-cutting rather than core leverage. Reliance on the Dot &amp; Key brand and rising off-platform sales for own brands are also key worries.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:04:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69561f7d4342f77179f492b8_1767253861097.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Grasim Industries Shakes Up Renewable Energy Game: What It Means For Your Portfolio!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Grasim-Industries-Shakes-Up-Renewable-Energy-Game-What-It-Means-For-Your-Portfolio/69561ead4342f77179f48eda</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Grasim-Industries-Shakes-Up-Renewable-Energy-Game-What-It-Means-For-Your-Portfolio/69561ead4342f77179f48eda</guid><description>Grasim Industries is initiating a significant restructuring of its renewable energy business. The plan involves transferring Essel Mining and Industries Ltd's renewable energy assets to its subsidiary, Aditya Birla Renewables. Additionally, several subsidiaries are being merged into Aditya Birla Renewables to create a unified, more efficient operational platform. This move aims to consolidate and streamline its renewable energy operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:03:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69561ead4342f77179f48ed9_1767251694329.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dipan Mehta's Bold Picks: Why Oil &amp; Power Stocks Are Hot, But Avoid Ola Electric!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dipan-Mehtas-Bold-Picks-Why-Oil-and-Power-Stocks-Are-Hot-But-Avoid-Ola-Electric/69561e944342f77179f48e51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dipan-Mehtas-Bold-Picks-Why-Oil-and-Power-Stocks-Are-Hot-But-Avoid-Ola-Electric/69561e944342f77179f48e51</guid><description>Market expert Dipan Mehta sees significant value in oil marketing companies (OMCs) like BPCL and power finance lenders such as REC, PFC, and IREDA, citing attractive valuations and earnings visibility. He is turning constructive on the IT sector, including TCS, anticipating AI revenue growth and currency benefits. However, Mehta strongly advises investors to avoid Ola Electric due to its weak post-listing performance and uncertain path to profitability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:03:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69561e944342f77179f48e50_1767252781877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Govt Slams New Taxes on Cigarettes &amp; Pan Masala: Is Your Wallet Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Govt-Slams-New-Taxes-on-Cigarettes-and-Pan-Masala-Is-Your-Wallet-Ready/69561f084342f77179f49079</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Govt-Slams-New-Taxes-on-Cigarettes-and-Pan-Masala-Is-Your-Wallet-Ready/69561f084342f77179f49079</guid><description>India's government has significantly increased excise duty on cigarettes and introduced a new machine-based cess on pan masala. These moves aim to prevent revenue leakage, protect public health, and fund national security. The changes recalibrate the 'sin tax' framework following a long freeze on cigarette duties and address evasion in the pan masala sector, ensuring the tax burden remains high despite GST compensation ending.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:03:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69561f084342f77179f49078_1767251931159.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cognizant Hit By US Class-Action Lawsuits Over Massive TriZetto Data Breach: Did They Wait Too Long to Tell You?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cognizant-Hit-By-US-Class-Action-Lawsuits-Over-Massive-TriZetto-Data-Breach-Did-They-Wait-Too-Long-to-Tell-You/69561df84342f77179f48b63</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cognizant-Hit-By-US-Class-Action-Lawsuits-Over-Massive-TriZetto-Data-Breach-Did-They-Wait-Too-Long-to-Tell-You/69561df84342f77179f48b63</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions Corp faces multiple class-action lawsuits in the US over a data breach impacting its TriZetto healthcare unit. Allegations claim TriZetto failed to promptly disclose a cyberattack that compromised personal data for nearly a year, raising investor concerns about delayed disclosures and potential financial harm.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:58:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69561df84342f77179f48b62_1767252576062.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market Woes: How SIP Calculators Can Still Power Your Mutual Fund Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indian-Market-Woes-How-SIP-Calculators-Can-Still-Power-Your-Mutual-Fund-Growth/69561bf14342f77179f48228</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indian-Market-Woes-How-SIP-Calculators-Can-Still-Power-Your-Mutual-Fund-Growth/69561bf14342f77179f48228</guid><description>The Indian stock market faced significant challenges in 2025, marked by substantial Foreign Institutional Investor (FII) selling, high valuations, and many listed companies trading well below their 52-week highs. Amidst this volatility, Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) offer a disciplined approach to building wealth by spreading investments across market cycles. A mutual fund SIP calculator, especially one that uses XIRR, is crucial for investors to accurately track their SIP growth and understand real-world returns generated through staggered investments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:54:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69561bf14342f77179f48227_1767251133178.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto's 2026 Crystal Ball: After Wild Ride, Is a Massive Surge Coming? 🚀</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Cryptos-2026-Crystal-Ball-After-Wild-Ride-Is-a-Massive-Surge-Coming/69561bf94342f77179f4826f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Cryptos-2026-Crystal-Ball-After-Wild-Ride-Is-a-Massive-Surge-Coming/69561bf94342f77179f4826f</guid><description>The crypto market experienced significant volatility in 2025, with valuations fluctuating dramatically. Despite this, institutional adoption grew, and the US moved towards formalization. Bitcoin saw highs and lows, while Ethereum dipped. India's policy progress was slow, but retail participation diversified. Experts predict strong upside potential for 2026, driven by easing liquidity and strong underlying demand, with opportunities in derivatives and tokenization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:53:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69561bf94342f77179f4826e_1767252312898.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking Truth: SBI Fixed Deposits Beat 80% of Indian Stocks in 2025! Are Your Investments Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Shocking-Truth-SBI-Fixed-Deposits-Beat-80percent-of-Indian-Stocks-in-2025-Are-Your-Investments-Safe/69561b9e4342f77179f4805f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Shocking-Truth-SBI-Fixed-Deposits-Beat-80percent-of-Indian-Stocks-in-2025-Are-Your-Investments-Safe/69561b9e4342f77179f4805f</guid><description>Despite the Sensex showing gains in 2025, a surprising trend emerged: State Bank of India's (SBI) fixed deposits offered better returns than 80% of actively traded stocks on the BSE. This stark contrast highlights the concentrated nature of market gains, with large-cap companies faring better than mid and small-cap stocks. The year proved challenging for stock picking, as risk-free fixed deposits became unexpectedly competitive against equities, even as household investments shifted towards stocks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:52:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69561b9e4342f77179f4805e_1767251048425.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gabion Technologies IPO Opens Jan 6: Don't Miss This 31% Grey Market Premium Opportunity!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gabion-Technologies-IPO-Opens-Jan-6-Dont-Miss-This-31percent-Grey-Market-Premium-Opportunity/695617894342f77179f46e7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gabion-Technologies-IPO-Opens-Jan-6-Dont-Miss-This-31percent-Grey-Market-Premium-Opportunity/695617894342f77179f46e7f</guid><description>Gabion Technologies' IPO opens on January 6, 2026, aiming to raise ₹29.16 crore with shares priced at ₹76-₹81. The company, a steel gabion manufacturer, has seen its unlisted shares trade at a significant Grey Market Premium (GMP) of ₹106, reflecting a 31% surge. Funds will be used for working capital and machinery. The IPO closes on January 8, with listing expected on the BSE SME platform on January 13, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:30:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695617894342f77179f46e7e_1767249868704.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kotak Mahindra Bank Splits Shares! Rs 5 Becomes Rs 1 - Record Date Jan 14! Will This Boost Your Investment?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kotak-Mahindra-Bank-Splits-Shares-Rs-5-Becomes-Rs-1-Record-Date-Jan-14-Will-This-Boost-Your-Investment/695616ba4342f77179f46aad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kotak-Mahindra-Bank-Splits-Shares-Rs-5-Becomes-Rs-1-Record-Date-Jan-14-Will-This-Boost-Your-Investment/695616ba4342f77179f46aad</guid><description>Kotak Mahindra Bank announced a 5-for-1 stock split, turning each Rs 5 face value share into five Rs 1 face value shares. The record date for this corporate action is set for January 14, 2026. This move aims to increase share accessibility for retail investors, with the bank's last stock split occurring over 15 years ago. Recent Q2 financial results showed a slight decline in revenues and net profit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:30:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695616ba4342f77179f46aac_1767253292031.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹37,000 Crore HDB Financial Shares Set to Flood Market: What Investors MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/37000-Crore-HDB-Financial-Shares-Set-to-Flood-Market-What-Investors-MUST-Know/695616214342f77179f46758</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/37000-Crore-HDB-Financial-Shares-Set-to-Flood-Market-What-Investors-MUST-Know/695616214342f77179f46758</guid><description>HDB Financial Services is seeing its six-month lock-in period expire on Friday, January 2, freeing up approximately 481.5 million shares, valued at nearly ₹37,000 crore at current prices. While these shares are now tradable, their sale is not guaranteed. The company's stock is trading above its IPO price, and three global brokers have initiated coverage with mixed ratings and price targets between ₹780 and ₹808. Allied Blenders and Distillers also faces a significant lock-in expiry.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:30:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695616214342f77179f46757_1767249512073.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Stock CRASHES 85% From December Peak, Halved Since IPO - Investors Panicked!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vishnu-Prakash-R-Punglia-Stock-CRASHES-85percent-From-December-Peak-Halved-Since-IPO-Investors-Panicked/695616274342f77179f467a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vishnu-Prakash-R-Punglia-Stock-CRASHES-85percent-From-December-Peak-Halved-Since-IPO-Investors-Panicked/695616274342f77179f467a9</guid><description>Shares of Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd. are in sharp decline, down 85% from their December 2024 peak of ₹345 and trading at half their IPO price of ₹99. The stock saw heavy trading volumes today, extending a trend of losses that saw it drop for eight consecutive months. While retail investor numbers have significantly increased, promoters and some institutional investors have reduced their stakes, raising concerns among shareholders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695616274342f77179f467a8_1767250741979.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Sparking Global Growth: Is India Ready to Capture the AI Revolution?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Sparking-Global-Growth-Is-India-Ready-to-Capture-the-AI-Revolution/695616584342f77179f468d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Sparking-Global-Growth-Is-India-Ready-to-Capture-the-AI-Revolution/695616584342f77179f468d0</guid><description>William Lee, Chief Economist and Managing Director at Global Economic Advisors, predicts AI will drive the next global growth phase, shifting focus from trade wars to productivity. He believes India can be a major beneficiary by attracting capital flows, but needs to address "political risk" by welcoming foreign investment and opening markets to fully capitalize on this shift.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:30:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695616584342f77179f468cf_1767252070441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>