<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:23:06 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Unlock Potential Gains: Ankush Bajaj Reveals 3 Top Stocks to Buy NOW as Nifty Faces Crucial Test!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Unlock-Potential-Gains-Ankush-Bajaj-Reveals-3-Top-Stocks-to-Buy-NOW-as-Nifty-Faces-Crucial-Test/6951d3e94342f77179db9da4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Unlock-Potential-Gains-Ankush-Bajaj-Reveals-3-Top-Stocks-to-Buy-NOW-as-Nifty-Faces-Crucial-Test/6951d3e94342f77179db9da4</guid><description>SEBI-registered analyst Ankush Bajaj recommends buying National Aluminium Co. Ltd. (NALCO), NMDC Ltd, and Vedanta Ltd, citing strong bullish technicals and uptrends. NALCO shows robust momentum (ADX 52), NMDC exhibits accumulation, and Vedanta is in a broad uptrend. Meanwhile, the Nifty 50 faces overhead pressure, struggling above key trendlines and hourly moving averages, with resistance around 26,100-26,200, though a mildly bullish medium-term bias remains. Option data suggests short-term bearishness.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:52:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951d3e94342f77179db9da3_1766970438571.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Trade Stalls? Sunil Singhania Sees Foreign Money Flooding India Next!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Trade-Stalls-Sunil-Singhania-Sees-Foreign-Money-Flooding-India-Next/6951d3d04342f77179db9d56</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Trade-Stalls-Sunil-Singhania-Sees-Foreign-Money-Flooding-India-Next/6951d3d04342f77179db9d56</guid><description>Sunil Singhania, founder of Abakkus Asset Manager, believes India's market, showing healthy 7-8% Nifty returns despite challenges and strong SIPs, is consolidating. He suggests foreign investors might shift focus to India if the AI-driven rally in other markets cools, seeing significant opportunities for 2026-27. Singhania also details Abakkus's expansion into mutual funds, launching a FlexiCap fund to cater to a growing investor base.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:52:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951d3d04342f77179db9d55_1766970451275.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>3 Expert Stock Picks: Buy NMDC, Oberoi Realty? Sell LTIMindtree! Market Update</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/3-Expert-Stock-Picks-Buy-NMDC-Oberoi-Realty-Sell-LTIMindtree-Market-Update/6951d3834342f77179db9d0e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/3-Expert-Stock-Picks-Buy-NMDC-Oberoi-Realty-Sell-LTIMindtree-Market-Update/6951d3834342f77179db9d0e</guid><description>On December 26, 2025, Indian stock markets saw a dip with the Sensex falling 367 points and Nifty declining 99.8 points amid profit-booking and foreign fund outflows. Despite the cautious sentiment, analyst Raja Venkatraman of NeoTrader recommended three stocks: Buy NMDC Ltd above ₹83, Buy Oberoi Realty Ltd above ₹1,690, and Sell LTIMindtree Ltd below ₹6,020, providing specific stop-loss and target prices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:52:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951d3834342f77179db9d0d_1766970437799.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bearish Bets Surge! Indian Markets on Cautious Alert Ahead of Year-End Expiry - What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Bearish-Bets-Surge-Indian-Markets-on-Cautious-Alert-Ahead-of-Year-End-Expiry-What-You-Need-to-Know/6951d2e04342f77179db9bfd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Bearish-Bets-Surge-Indian-Markets-on-Cautious-Alert-Ahead-of-Year-End-Expiry-What-You-Need-to-Know/6951d2e04342f77179db9bfd</guid><description>Indian stock markets are poised for a cautious final trading week of 2025, with proprietary traders and Foreign Portfolio Investors (FPIs) significantly increasing bearish derivative bets. Ahead of the Nifty and Bank Nifty year-end expiry, these investors have built substantial short call and long put positions, signaling expectations of a flat to downward market movement. Analysts anticipate a sideways trading range with a bearish bias, citing expensive valuations and slower earnings growth as key concerns, despite strong domestic institutional buying.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:52:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951d2e04342f77179db9bfc_1766970157080.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Dips Friday, But 2 Stocks Get Bullish Stamp! MarketSmith India's Secret Picks Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Market-Dips-Friday-But-2-Stocks-Get-Bullish-Stamp-MarketSmith-Indias-Secret-Picks-Revealed/6951d3084342f77179db9c2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Market-Dips-Friday-But-2-Stocks-Get-Bullish-Stamp-MarketSmith-Indias-Secret-Picks-Revealed/6951d3084342f77179db9c2c</guid><description>Indian stock markets ended lower on Friday, December 26, amid year-end caution. However, MarketSmith India has issued two buy recommendations for December 29: Steel Authority of India Ltd (SAIL) at ₹132, citing PSU backing and infrastructure benefits, and Capital India Finance Ltd at ₹38.50, highlighting its expanding lending franchise. The recommendations come as the broader market maintains a 'Confirmed Uptrend' despite Friday's dip.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:52:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951d3084342f77179db9c2b_1766970318452.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's BIG Policy U-Turn: Populist Capitalism Takes Over - Will It Create Jobs?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-BIG-Policy-U-Turn-Populist-Capitalism-Takes-Over-Will-It-Create-Jobs/6951d0d74342f77179db9a82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-BIG-Policy-U-Turn-Populist-Capitalism-Takes-Over-Will-It-Create-Jobs/6951d0d74342f77179db9a82</guid><description>India is shifting from 'populist socialism' to 'populist capitalism' in a move likened to the 1991 reforms. The government is now prioritizing capital and private sector investment to generate jobs, a significant change from previous policies favouring labour. However, the article warns that entrenched bureaucratic hurdles, stemming from a colonial-era mindset, could significantly undermine the effectiveness of these pro-business reforms, hindering India's development goals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:46:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951d0d74342f77179db9a81_1766969626877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRFC Stock EXPLODES Ahead of Budget 2026! Railway Rally Fueled by Fare Hike – Expert Reveals Top Trading Strategy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRFC-Stock-EXPLODES-Ahead-of-Budget-2026-Railway-Rally-Fueled-by-Fare-Hike-Expert-Reveals-Top-Trading-Strategy/6951cd9a4342f77179db98c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRFC-Stock-EXPLODES-Ahead-of-Budget-2026-Railway-Rally-Fueled-by-Fare-Hike-Expert-Reveals-Top-Trading-Strategy/6951cd9a4342f77179db98c0</guid><description>Shares of Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) and other railway stocks surged up to 13% on December 26, 2025, following a passenger fare hike by Indian Railways. With the Union Budget 2026-27 approaching, the sector is buzzing with potential gains. Analysts suggest holding IRFC until the budget provides clarity on government allocations, offering a favourable risk-reward profile.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:31:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951cd9a4342f77179db98bf_1766968809828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's M&amp;A Surge: Bigger Deals, Global Ambitions Fuel 2026 Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-MandA-Surge-Bigger-Deals-Global-Ambitions-Fuel-2026-Boom/6951cd2f4342f77179db9836</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-MandA-Surge-Bigger-Deals-Global-Ambitions-Fuel-2026-Boom/6951cd2f4342f77179db9836</guid><description>Cross-border merger and acquisition (M&amp;A) activity in India is accelerating, with deals becoming larger and more strategic. Driven by India's economic resilience and strong investor interest, both inbound and outbound transactions have surpassed previous years' values. Industry executives anticipate this trend will continue strongly into 2026, with key sectors like finance, manufacturing, technology, healthcare, and infrastructure leading the charge. Government support and a favorable regulatory environment are further bolstering this M&amp;A momentum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:25:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951cd2f4342f77179db9835_1766968695711.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Giants Unleash Record $4.3 Billion Acquisition Spree: AI &amp; Cloud Capabilities Drive Strategic Shift!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Giants-Unleash-Record-43-Billion-Acquisition-Spree-AI-and-Cloud-Capabilities-Drive-Strategic-Shift/6951ccd44342f77179db9789</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Giants-Unleash-Record-43-Billion-Acquisition-Spree-AI-and-Cloud-Capabilities-Drive-Strategic-Shift/6951ccd44342f77179db9789</guid><description>India's top 10 IT firms are investing a record $4.3 billion in acquisitions this fiscal year, the highest since 2000. This strategic shift targets critical AI and cloud capabilities amid rapid technological change, with some companies prioritizing M&amp;A over dividends and share buybacks to boost growth and competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:25:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ccd44342f77179db9788_1766968610701.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's EV Crisis: Makers Scramble for China's Rare Earth Magnets Amidst Supply Chaos!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Crisis-Makers-Scramble-for-Chinas-Rare-Earth-Magnets-Amidst-Supply-Chaos/6951ccdb4342f77179db97b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Crisis-Makers-Scramble-for-Chinas-Rare-Earth-Magnets-Amidst-Supply-Chaos/6951ccdb4342f77179db97b8</guid><description>Leading Indian electric bus and truck manufacturers are planning to request a one-year extension until March 2027 for importing critical rare earth magnet motors under the ₹10,900-crore PM-E Drive scheme. This is due to ongoing supply disruptions from China and delays in developing local production. Companies like Tata Motors and Ashok Leyland are part of these discussions, aiming to ensure continuity for recent large tender orders and avoid increased operational costs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:25:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ccdb4342f77179db97b7_1766968982394.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apple's iPhone 16 Shatters Records: India's Top-Selling Smartphone Amidst Premium Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apples-iPhone-16-Shatters-Records-Indias-Top-Selling-Smartphone-Amidst-Premium-Surge/6951cc554342f77179db970c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apples-iPhone-16-Shatters-Records-Indias-Top-Selling-Smartphone-Amidst-Premium-Surge/6951cc554342f77179db970c</guid><description>Apple Inc.'s iPhone 16 series has become India's highest-selling smartphone, surpassing budget models from Chinese competitors. Driven by easy credit, cashbacks, and aspirational demand, the iPhone 16 series sold 6.5 million units in the first 11 months of 2025, while Vivo's Y29 5G ranked second. This premiumization trend is reshaping India's smartphone market, with iPhones, starting at ₹47,000, outselling devices priced at ₹14,000.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:25:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951cc554342f77179db970b_1766968477545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fortum's India EV Charging Exit: JBM Group in Exclusive Talks for Massive Network Deal!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fortums-India-EV-Charging-Exit-JBM-Group-in-Exclusive-Talks-for-Massive-Network-Deal/6951cc434342f77179db96d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fortums-India-EV-Charging-Exit-JBM-Group-in-Exclusive-Talks-for-Massive-Network-Deal/6951cc434342f77179db96d1</guid><description>JBM Group is in exclusive talks to acquire a majority stake in Fortum Oyj's Indian EV charging business, GLIDA. This deal would mark Fortum's full exit from India and bolster JBM Group's presence in the rapidly expanding Indian EV charging market, adding GLIDA's 850 charging points across the country.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:25:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951cc434342f77179db96d0_1766968621499.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Year-End Bargain Alert! 5 Stocks Like Vedanta, DLF Entering Rare 'Buy Zone' Amidst Market Slump - What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Year-End-Bargain-Alert-5-Stocks-Like-Vedanta-DLF-Entering-Rare-Buy-Zone-Amidst-Market-Slump-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6951cbe04342f77179db9609</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Year-End-Bargain-Alert-5-Stocks-Like-Vedanta-DLF-Entering-Rare-Buy-Zone-Amidst-Market-Slump-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6951cbe04342f77179db9609</guid><description>Indian stock markets saw a broad decline last week, with the Nifty pausing near record highs. However, this pullback has created a 'bargain zone' for select stocks, especially as participation typically dips towards year-end. The Nifty Metal Index hit a fresh all-time high, showing strong buying interest, while the Nifty Realty Index stabilizes near support, signaling potential for a rebound. Foreign Institutional Investors (FIIs) show a subtle easing of their negative stance despite reduced long positions in index futures. Investors are advised to watch stocks like Vedanta, DLF, and others in the Metal and Realty sectors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:21:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951cbe04342f77179db9608_1766968373536.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DIIs Go Big on IT Stocks Despite Slump: Is This the Smartest Bet on AI's Future?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/DIIs-Go-Big-on-IT-Stocks-Despite-Slump-Is-This-the-Smartest-Bet-on-AIs-Future/6951cb924342f77179db95b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/DIIs-Go-Big-on-IT-Stocks-Despite-Slump-Is-This-the-Smartest-Bet-on-AIs-Future/6951cb924342f77179db95b4</guid><description>Despite the Nifty IT index falling 11.67% over the past year due to AI disruption, geopolitical tensions, and visa fee hikes, Domestic Institutional Investors (DIIs) are aggressively increasing their stakes in top IT companies. DIIs boosted holdings by over 2% points in Persistent Systems, Coforge, Tech Mahindra, and Infosys during Q2FY26, signaling a strong belief in the long-term potential of AI-driven growth and digital transformation. These companies are actively developing AI platforms and securing significant deals, suggesting DIIs are looking past near-term challenges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:21:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951cb924342f77179db95b3_1766968395099.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Birla Scion's Small-Cap: Quietly Dominating India's Electronics Surge - Is This Hidden Gem Poised for Explosive Growth?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Birla-Scions-Small-Cap-Quietly-Dominating-Indias-Electronics-Surge-Is-This-Hidden-Gem-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/6951cb6c4342f77179db954c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Birla-Scions-Small-Cap-Quietly-Dominating-Indias-Electronics-Surge-Is-This-Hidden-Gem-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/6951cb6c4342f77179db954c</guid><description>Xpro India, a small-cap company with Birla lineage, is undergoing a strategic shift from commodity processing to specialized manufacturing, focusing on high-tech dielectric films for the electronics and energy sectors. Despite current financial pressures from capacity expansion and a new UAE facility, its strong governance and niche focus present potential long-term benefits. However, its high valuation demands timely execution and profitability recovery.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:21:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951cb6c4342f77179db954b_1766968252797.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>