<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:47:33 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Sparks Market Optimism, Reverses Outflows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Market-Optimism-Reverses-Outflows/69814e4369d815649b720f93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Market-Optimism-Reverses-Outflows/69814e4369d815649b720f93</guid><description>The finalization of a significant trade agreement between the United States and India is injecting optimism into the Indian equity market. The accord lowers reciprocal tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25% and eliminates duties on Russian oil imports. This development is seen by fund managers as a catalyst to attract global investors back to Indian equities, which suffered their worst January since 2016. The move also provides crucial support to the Indian rupee, which had recently touched record lows. Early market reactions included a surge in Nifty 50 futures, signaling positive sentiment ahead of trading sessions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69814e4369d815649b720f92_1770081951773.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godrej Properties Hits ₹1,000 Crore Sales Milestone For Panipat Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-Hits-1000-Crore-Sales-Milestone-For-Panipat-Project/69814b6d69d815649b720d19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-Hits-1000-Crore-Sales-Milestone-For-Panipat-Project/69814b6d69d815649b720d19</guid><description>Godrej Properties (GPL) announces a record INR 1,000 Crore in plot sales for its new Panipat project, Evora Estate. The luxury development sold over 600 plots, marking GPL's most successful plotted launch by value. This achievement underscores GPL's market leadership and successful expansion into emerging residential hubs like Panipat, driven by infrastructure growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:19:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69814b6d69d815649b720d18_1770081548657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Defence Surge: Explosives Sector Poised for Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Defence-Surge-Explosives-Sector-Poised-for-Growth/698148a269d815649b7209bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Defence-Surge-Explosives-Sector-Poised-for-Growth/698148a269d815649b7209bd</guid><description>India's defense production hit an all-time high of ₹1.50 lakh crore in FY2024-25, signaling a strong push for self-reliance. The explosives and propellants segment, projected to grow to $144.74 million by 2030 at a 6.9% CAGR, presents significant opportunities. Solar Industries India Limited, with its substantial order book and innovative products, is well-positioned. However, Premier Explosives faces headwinds from regulatory scrutiny and operational disruptions following safety incidents.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dividend Stocks: Nirlon, MSTC, PTC India Offer Income Plays</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dividend-Stocks-Nirlon-MSTC-PTC-India-Offer-Income-Plays/6981482869d815649b720864</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Dividend-Stocks-Nirlon-MSTC-PTC-India-Offer-Income-Plays/6981482869d815649b720864</guid><description>Nirlon, MSTC, and PTC India, small-cap entities focused on real estate, PSU e-commerce/trading, and power trading respectively, are highlighted for their dividend payouts. Nirlon offers a ~5% yield supported by strong occupancy and rental escalations. MSTC provides a ~9.1% yield via its PSU status, navigating scrap market headwinds with e-commerce diversification. PTC India yields ~6.8% while pivoting to integrated energy solutions. Valuations and return metrics show varied attractiveness, but all demonstrate cash return to shareholders.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:59:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981482869d815649b720863_1770080370500.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>