<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:36:22 +0000</pubDate><item><title>RBI's Banking Watchdog Overwhelmed: Loans, Cards &amp; Digital Issues Fuel Complaint Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Banking-Watchdog-Overwhelmed-Loans-Cards-and-Digital-Issues-Fuel-Complaint-Surge/6952758a4342f77179dcd6df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Banking-Watchdog-Overwhelmed-Loans-Cards-and-Digital-Issues-Fuel-Complaint-Surge/6952758a4342f77179dcd6df</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Ombudsman offices handled approximately 29.6 lakh complaints in the financial year 2024-25, marking a slight 0.8 percent increase from the previous year. A significant portion of these grievances, nearly four-fifths, pertained to loans and advances, credit cards, and digital banking services. Public and private sector banks together accounted for over 72 percent of the total complaints received.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Banking Fraud Bill Skyrockets 30% Amidst Falling Incident Numbers: RBI Report Reveals Alarming Trend!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Banking-Fraud-Bill-Skyrockets-30percent-Amidst-Falling-Incident-Numbers-RBI-Report-Reveals-Alarming-Trend/695275994342f77179dcd71a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Banking-Fraud-Bill-Skyrockets-30percent-Amidst-Falling-Incident-Numbers-RBI-Report-Reveals-Alarming-Trend/695275994342f77179dcd71a</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India reports a significant 30 percent year-on-year increase in the amount involved in banking fraud cases during the first half of FY26 (April-September). While the total number of fraud incidents fell sharply, the value of losses escalated to ₹21,515 crore from ₹16,569 crore in the same period last year. This surge is primarily driven by a rise in fraud amounts related to advances. Private banks reported more cases, while PSBs accounted for a larger share of the total fraud value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Report Shocker: IBC Dominates Loan Recoveries, Surging to 52.4%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Report-Shocker-IBC-Dominates-Loan-Recoveries-Surging-to-524percent/695275204342f77179dcd5e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Report-Shocker-IBC-Dominates-Loan-Recoveries-Surging-to-524percent/695275204342f77179dcd5e9</guid><description>A Reserve Bank of India report reveals the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC) now accounts for 52.4% of total loan recoveries in FY25, up from 49.5% last year. While case referrals decreased under both IBC and SARFAESI Acts, recovery rates improved for both mechanisms. Banks are actively cleaning balance sheets by selling NPAs to ARCs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Foreign Banks Scale Back India Operations: RBI Report Reveals Global Strategy Shifts!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Foreign-Banks-Scale-Back-India-Operations-RBI-Report-Reveals-Global-Strategy-Shifts/695274dc4342f77179dcd518</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Foreign-Banks-Scale-Back-India-Operations-RBI-Report-Reveals-Global-Strategy-Shifts/695274dc4342f77179dcd518</guid><description>A Reserve Bank of India report indicates a slight reduction in the presence of foreign banks in India for 2024-25. The number of foreign banks operating via branches or wholly-owned subsidiaries decreased to 44, with branches falling to 755. This trend is attributed to global business strategy realignments and value optimization by foreign lenders, while Indian banks maintain a stable overseas footprint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Probate Mandatory No More! India Scraps Crucial Will Rule - What This Means For Your Inheritance!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Probate-Mandatory-No-More-India-Scraps-Crucial-Will-Rule-What-This-Means-For-Your-Inheritance/695274ba4342f77179dcd495</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Probate-Mandatory-No-More-India-Scraps-Crucial-Will-Rule-What-This-Means-For-Your-Inheritance/695274ba4342f77179dcd495</guid><description>The Indian government has eliminated the mandatory probate requirement for wills in Mumbai, Chennai, and Kolkata under the Repealing and Amending Act, 2025. This move aims to simplify asset inheritance and create legal uniformity. While it promises a smoother process for beneficiaries, experts warn of a potential rise in will disputes and advise taking necessary safeguards.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:23:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695274ba4342f77179dcd494_1767011631832.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian School Fees: The Silent Budget Killer! Are Parents Prepared for This Shocking Reality?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indian-School-Fees-The-Silent-Budget-Killer-Are-Parents-Prepared-for-This-Shocking-Reality/6952743a4342f77179dcd32b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indian-School-Fees-The-Silent-Budget-Killer-Are-Parents-Prepared-for-This-Shocking-Reality/6952743a4342f77179dcd32b</guid><description>Education costs in Indian metros are soaring, with tuition, coaching, transport, and hidden expenses rising faster than inflation. Experts advise parents to cap education spending at 10-15% of household income and plan finances seriously. Strategies like building a 2-3 year fee corpus using hybrid funds and systematic withdrawal plans (SWPs) are recommended to manage rising costs and avoid derailing other financial goals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ola's Triple Unicorn Dream Crumbles: AI, EV, and Cab Ventures Hit Execution Crisis!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Olas-Triple-Unicorn-Dream-Crumbles-AI-EV-and-Cab-Ventures-Hit-Execution-Crisis/695274834342f77179dcd3f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Olas-Triple-Unicorn-Dream-Crumbles-AI-EV-and-Cab-Ventures-Hit-Execution-Crisis/695274834342f77179dcd3f8</guid><description>Ola's ambitious run with three unicorns – Krutrim (AI), Ola Electric, and Ola Consumer (Cabs) – is facing severe execution stress in 2024-2025. Challenges include scaling capital-intensive manufacturing, a cash-burning ride-hailing platform, and an ambitious AI program simultaneously. Krutrim's progress has slowed, Ola Electric lost significant market share, and Ola Consumer's valuation has fallen. Funding constraints and rising investor scrutiny are key concerns.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:17:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695274834342f77179dcd3f7_1767011607834.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive Salary Hike Ahead! 8th Pay Commission Arrears to Start From Jan 1, 2026 - HUGE Impact for Millions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Massive-Salary-Hike-Ahead-8th-Pay-Commission-Arrears-to-Start-From-Jan-1-2026-HUGE-Impact-for-Millions/695271f54342f77179dcce90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Massive-Salary-Hike-Ahead-8th-Pay-Commission-Arrears-to-Start-From-Jan-1-2026-HUGE-Impact-for-Millions/695271f54342f77179dcce90</guid><description>The 8th Pay Commission's formation has been approved, with its recommendations likely to be implemented retrospectively from January 1, 2026. This means central government employees and pensioners could receive arrears for a period of 1.5 to 2 years, potentially totaling 1.5 to 2 years of back pay. The overhaul is set to impact approximately 50 lakh employees and 69 lakh pensioners, with an estimated fiscal implication of ₹2.4-3.2 lakh crore for the government.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Cities Face CRISIS: Top PM Advisor Issues Stark Warning!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Cities-Face-CRISIS-Top-PM-Advisor-Issues-Stark-Warning/695272804342f77179dccfac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Cities-Face-CRISIS-Top-PM-Advisor-Issues-Stark-Warning/695272804342f77179dccfac</guid><description>Economist Sanjeev Sanyal, a member of Prime Minister's Economic Advisory Council, warns that India's cities are on the brink of a major crisis. He states that despite economic progress, urban quality of life has stagnated, and the excuse of poverty is no longer valid. Sanyal advocates for managing urban transitions over rigid master plans and stresses the critical need for improved walkability and basic services like waste management, which are essential for sustained national growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:09:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695272804342f77179dccfab_1767011028941.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PM Modi Gathers Top Economists: Unlocking India's FY27 Fiscal Roadmap Secrets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PM-Modi-Gathers-Top-Economists-Unlocking-Indias-FY27-Fiscal-Roadmap-Secrets/695271364342f77179dccd4f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PM-Modi-Gathers-Top-Economists-Unlocking-Indias-FY27-Fiscal-Roadmap-Secrets/695271364342f77179dccd4f</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi is convening a crucial meeting with leading economists and sectoral experts to gather insights for the upcoming Union Budget 2026-27. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman is slated to present the budget on February 1st, facing a backdrop of global economic uncertainties and trade challenges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 India Spending Secret: Experience &amp; Digital Payments Dominate! Big Shift Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/2025-India-Spending-Secret-Experience-and-Digital-Payments-Dominate-Big-Shift-Revealed/69526e7a4342f77179dcc8bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/2025-India-Spending-Secret-Experience-and-Digital-Payments-Dominate-Big-Shift-Revealed/69526e7a4342f77179dcc8bf</guid><description>In 2025, Indian consumers are increasingly prioritizing spending on experiences like travel and dining over material goods, opting for shorter, frequent breaks. Digital payments have surged, transforming personal finance. The hospitality sector saw approximately 6% revenue growth, supported by strong domestic demand and a 20% rise in digital bookings, signaling durable consumer engagement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:54:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69526e7a4342f77179dcc8be_1767010012261.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Shock Tariff Cut: What It Means for Global Markets &amp; Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Chinas-Shock-Tariff-Cut-What-It-Means-for-Global-Markets-and-Your-Investments/69526dcf4342f77179dcc75a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Chinas-Shock-Tariff-Cut-What-It-Means-for-Global-Markets-and-Your-Investments/69526dcf4342f77179dcc75a</guid><description>China announced it will slash import tariffs on hundreds of products starting in 2026. This includes key commodities like recycled black powder for lithium-ion batteries and essential medical supplies such as artificial blood vessels and diagnostic kits. The move aims to support strategic industries, lower import costs, and boost trade as China reshapes its future tariff policies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blackstone's Horizon Bags $200M Pre-IPO Deal! India's Logistics Powerhouse Eyes Stock Market Debut!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Blackstones-Horizon-Bags-200M-Pre-IPO-Deal-Indias-Logistics-Powerhouse-Eyes-Stock-Market-Debut/69526d624342f77179dcc636</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Blackstones-Horizon-Bags-200M-Pre-IPO-Deal-Indias-Logistics-Powerhouse-Eyes-Stock-Market-Debut/69526d624342f77179dcc636</guid><description>Blackstone's Indian warehousing platform, Horizon Industrial Parks, has successfully raised $200 million in a pre-IPO funding round. Key investors included SBI group, Radhakishan Damani, Hemendra Kothari, and 360 One. The company, India's largest industrial and logistics infrastructure developer with a vast warehousing network, plans to file its draft IPO papers soon to raise an additional $300 million, targeting a total fundraising of $500 million.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:50:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69526d624342f77179dcc635_1767009947546.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's TV Secret: How It's Beating Streaming Giants &amp; Skyrocketing to $18 Billion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-TV-Secret-How-Its-Beating-Streaming-Giants-and-Skyrocketing-to-18-Billion/69526cef4342f77179dcc520</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Indias-TV-Secret-How-Its-Beating-Streaming-Giants-and-Skyrocketing-to-18-Billion/69526cef4342f77179dcc520</guid><description>India's television market is projected to grow from $14 billion in 2024 to $18.1 billion by 2029. Despite the rise of Over-The-Top (OTT) streaming, traditional TV is thriving due to the nation's strong shared-screen culture, where OTT is seen as an addition, not a replacement. Broadcasters are boosting regional content and using smart pricing. Middle-income households find cable/DTH more economical for family viewing than multiple OTT subscriptions. Bundling services and a focus on local content further solidify TV's dominant position as a cultural anchor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Compass Group India Surges Ahead: 51% CAGR in Corporate Growth Fuels Global Strategy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Compass-Group-India-Surges-Ahead-51percent-CAGR-in-Corporate-Growth-Fuels-Global-Strategy/69526c4b4342f77179dcc39b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Compass-Group-India-Surges-Ahead-51percent-CAGR-in-Corporate-Growth-Fuels-Global-Strategy/69526c4b4342f77179dcc39b</guid><description>Compass Group India is rapidly expanding, driven by a booming corporate and Global Capability Centre (GCC) segment which has achieved a 51% CAGR from FY22 to FY25. The company is doubling down on India as a key strategic market, aiming to double its business every three years, outpacing the industry average growth rate.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69526c4b4342f77179dcc39a_1767009677748.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian NBFCs Ditch Banks: Massive $750 Billion Capital Market Pivot Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-NBFCs-Ditch-Banks-Massive-750-Billion-Capital-Market-Pivot-Unveiled/69526c0e4342f77179dcc2de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-NBFCs-Ditch-Banks-Massive-750-Billion-Capital-Market-Pivot-Unveiled/69526c0e4342f77179dcc2de</guid><description>India's Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs) are significantly reducing their reliance on traditional bank borrowings, which accounted for about 42% of their funding as of March 2025. Facing rising costs and tightening liquidity from banks, NBFCs are strategically pivoting towards capital markets. This shift is projected to propel the sector's total borrowings to $750 billion by FY27E, driven by a 13% compound annual growth rate. Regulatory frameworks like RBI's Scale-Based Regulations and improved access to instruments such as Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) are facilitating this diversification, aiming to enhance sector resilience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:44:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69526c0e4342f77179dcc2dd_1767009668678.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Prices Under Siege! India's Import Crisis Threatens Local Producers – What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Steel-Prices-Under-Siege-Indias-Import-Crisis-Threatens-Local-Producers-Whats-Next/69526ba94342f77179dcc206</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Steel-Prices-Under-Siege-Indias-Import-Crisis-Threatens-Local-Producers-Whats-Next/69526ba94342f77179dcc206</guid><description>Indian steel prices are facing pressure from high imports, particularly from China and other Asian nations. Despite government efforts like safeguard and anti-dumping duties, India remains a net importer. While domestic demand is expected to rise, low-priced imports and potential expiry of duties pose risks to local producers' margins. Analysts suggest import duties are key to supporting domestic realisations and stability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:44:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69526ba94342f77179dcc205_1767009265557.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Broker's Bullish Call: IRCTC Stock Poised for Major Surge to ₹825! Why Analysts Are Buying</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokers-Bullish-Call-IRCTC-Stock-Poised-for-Major-Surge-to-825-Why-Analysts-Are-Buying/69526acd4342f77179dcc04c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokers-Bullish-Call-IRCTC-Stock-Poised-for-Major-Surge-to-825-Why-Analysts-Are-Buying/69526acd4342f77179dcc04c</guid><description>Analysts have issued a 'Buy' recommendation for Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation (IRCTC) with a target price of ₹825 over the next 9-12 months. Positive factors include resilient demand across ticketing, catering, and tourism, alongside the recent railway fare hike. IRCTC anticipates robust EBITDA margins exceeding 35%, supported by cost management and digital efficiencies. The company's monopoly in ticketing and its new role as an approved online payment aggregator further bolster its growth outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Copper Price EXPLODES to Record Highs Near $13,000 Amidst Global Supply Crisis!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Copper-Price-EXPLODES-to-Record-Highs-Near-13000-Amidst-Global-Supply-Crisis/69526a2e4342f77179dcbef2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Copper-Price-EXPLODES-to-Record-Highs-Near-13000-Amidst-Global-Supply-Crisis/69526a2e4342f77179dcbef2</guid><description>Copper has surged to a record near $13,000 a ton on the London Metal Exchange, extending a stunning year-end rally driven by tight supply fears and U.S. trade policy uncertainties. Despite mine outages and smelter pressures, some analysts warn prices may have outpaced weakening demand in China, with potential tariffs looming.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69526a2e4342f77179dcbef1_1767009032952.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quantum Advisors Makes Big Move: Dumps Autos &amp; Metals, Bets Big on IT &amp; Banks for 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Quantum-Advisors-Makes-Big-Move-Dumps-Autos-and-Metals-Bets-Big-on-IT-and-Banks-for-2026/695267334342f77179dcba30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Quantum-Advisors-Makes-Big-Move-Dumps-Autos-and-Metals-Bets-Big-on-IT-and-Banks-for-2026/695267334342f77179dcba30</guid><description>Quantum Advisors is adopting a selective strategy for 2026, increasing its stake in the Information Technology (IT) sector and top-tier private banks while reducing exposure to metals, autos, and engineering stocks. Portfolio Manager Nilesh Shetty cited valuation concerns as the primary driver for these shifts, noting that while earnings are improving, some sectors have become expensive. The firm is boosting IT allocation by 300-400 basis points, focusing on large-cap stocks with lower valuations, and sees potential for Foreign Institutional Investor (FII) inflows to resume.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mamaearth Promoter Varun Alagh Buys ₹50 Crore Shares: Is This a Bullish Signal?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mamaearth-Promoter-Varun-Alagh-Buys-50-Crore-Shares-Is-This-a-Bullish-Signal/695267114342f77179dcb9c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mamaearth-Promoter-Varun-Alagh-Buys-50-Crore-Shares-Is-This-a-Bullish-Signal/695267114342f77179dcb9c0</guid><description>Honasa Consumer, the parent company of brands like Mamaearth and The Derma Co, announced that its promoter, Varun Alagh, has increased his stake. He acquired 18.52 lakh equity shares for approximately ₹50 crore through a block deal on December 29. This move raises his total holding to 32.45% of the company's capital, signaling strong promoter confidence amidst recent positive quarterly results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:21:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695267114342f77179dcb9bf_1767011776081.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titan Dives into Diamonds! Record Highs as 'beYon' Brand Launches – What This Means for Your Portfolio!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Dives-into-Diamonds-Record-Highs-as-beYon-Brand-Launches-What-This-Means-for-Your-Portfolio/695266db4342f77179dcb8f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Dives-into-Diamonds-Record-Highs-as-beYon-Brand-Launches-What-This-Means-for-Your-Portfolio/695266db4342f77179dcb8f3</guid><description>Titan Company, a Tata group firm, has entered the lab-grown diamond market with its new brand 'beYon'. This strategic move aims to tap the affordable segment, with the first store opening in Mumbai on December 29. While brokerages like ICICI Securities and Morgan Stanley are optimistic about Titan's scaling potential, Citi flags intense competition and uncertain profitability in the LGD space. The news propelled Titan shares to a record high before settling slightly lower.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Pumps ₹50,000 Crore Into Banks! Is This a Game Changer for India's Economy?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Pumps-50000-Crore-Into-Banks-Is-This-a-Game-Changer-for-Indias-Economy/6952664d4342f77179dcb779</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Pumps-50000-Crore-Into-Banks-Is-This-a-Game-Changer-for-Indias-Economy/6952664d4342f77179dcb779</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) injected ₹50,000 crore into the banking system on December 29 through Open Market Operation (OMO) purchases of government securities. This move aims to provide durable liquidity following a deficit caused by advance tax and GST payments. The RBI plans further injections, totaling ₹2 lakh crore, and also announced a USD 10 billion swap auction to maintain financial stability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:17:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952664d4342f77179dcb778_1767011513872.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Rate Cuts Mystery: Why Indian Bond Yields Barely Moved Despite Massive Easing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Rate-Cuts-Mystery-Why-Indian-Bond-Yields-Barely-Moved-Despite-Massive-Easing/695266454342f77179dcb711</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Rate-Cuts-Mystery-Why-Indian-Bond-Yields-Barely-Moved-Despite-Massive-Easing/695266454342f77179dcb711</guid><description>Indian government bond yields saw only a 30 basis points drop in 2025, despite the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) implementing cumulative repo rate cuts of 125 basis points. This divergence highlights how market movements often precede policy actions and are influenced by global and domestic factors beyond just rate changes. Investors anticipated cuts early in the year, causing a rally before the RBI acted. A surprise 50 bps cut in June led to profit-booking, while stronger GDP growth, rupee depreciation linked to US tariffs, and rising global yields further pressured bond prices. Future yield movements are expected to hinge on global trends and domestic fiscal dynamics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:17:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695266454342f77179dcb710_1767008088447.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways' HUGE Safety Leap: First Kavach System LIVE in Vadodara! 🚂✨</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indian-Railways-HUGE-Safety-Leap-First-Kavach-System-LIVE-in-Vadodara/695265d64342f77179dcb62c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indian-Railways-HUGE-Safety-Leap-First-Kavach-System-LIVE-in-Vadodara/695265d64342f77179dcb62c</guid><description>Western Railway's Vadodara Division has commissioned the Kavach automatic train protection system on the 96-km Bajwa-Ahmedabad route. This marks a significant milestone for Indian Railways in adopting indigenous technology to prevent accidents, featuring real-time tracking, automatic speed control, and collision prevention. The system aims to drastically enhance passenger safety.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:14:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695265d64342f77179dcb62b_1767011112163.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Banks Hit Record Low Bad Loans! RBI Report Reveals Stunning Resilience – What It Means for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Hit-Record-Low-Bad-Loans-RBI-Report-Reveals-Stunning-Resilience-What-It-Means-for-Your-Investments/6952657b4342f77179dcb53c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Hit-Record-Low-Bad-Loans-RBI-Report-Reveals-Stunning-Resilience-What-It-Means-for-Your-Investments/6952657b4342f77179dcb53c</guid><description>Indian banks have achieved a remarkable improvement in asset quality, reaching a multi-decade low for bad loans. According to a Reserve Bank of India report, the gross non-performing assets (GNPA) ratio fell to 2.1% by September 2025, down from 2.2% in March 2025. While deposits and credit growth showed double-digit figures, they moderated from the previous year. The report also noted improved asset quality for non-bank finance companies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:13:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952657b4342f77179dcb53b_1767011001146.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Real Estate Set for Massive $4.4 Billion Rebound? Knight Frank Predicts 2026 Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Real-Estate-Set-for-Massive-44-Billion-Rebound-Knight-Frank-Predicts-2026-Boom/695264ef4342f77179dcb3b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Real-Estate-Set-for-Massive-44-Billion-Rebound-Knight-Frank-Predicts-2026-Boom/695264ef4342f77179dcb3b5</guid><description>Private equity investment in Indian real estate dropped 29% in 2025, but is poised for a significant rebound. Knight Frank India projects a 28% increase to $4.4 billion in 2026, driven by stabilizing capital costs and aligning valuations. Office assets remain the top recipient, followed by residential, warehousing, and retail, though investments are becoming more selective and structured.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:12:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695264ef4342f77179dcb3b4_1767010525768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock Huge Gains? Motilal Oswal Reveals 4 Stocks with Up to 52% Upside Potential!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Unlock-Huge-Gains-Motilal-Oswal-Reveals-4-Stocks-with-Up-to-52percent-Upside-Potential/6952650e4342f77179dcb40b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Unlock-Huge-Gains-Motilal-Oswal-Reveals-4-Stocks-with-Up-to-52percent-Upside-Potential/6952650e4342f77179dcb40b</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services has identified four Indian stocks poised for significant growth, offering up to 52% upside. These include Coforge, Brigade Enterprises, Apollo Tyres, and Midwest Granites. The brokerage highlights strategic acquisitions, expanding real estate pipelines, operational enhancements, and diversification into new segments as key drivers for these companies. Investors are focusing on these individual growth stories amid limited index movement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:12:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952650e4342f77179dcb40a_1767010741544.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking D2C Turnaround? The Souled Store's Profit Plummets 38% Despite Stellar Revenue Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shocking-D2C-Turnaround-The-Souled-Stores-Profit-Plummets-38percent-Despite-Stellar-Revenue-Surge/695263294342f77179dcaf66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shocking-D2C-Turnaround-The-Souled-Stores-Profit-Plummets-38percent-Despite-Stellar-Revenue-Surge/695263294342f77179dcaf66</guid><description>D2C fashion brand The Souled Store reported a 38% decline in net profit to ₹11 Cr for FY25, down from ₹17.7 Cr in FY24. This dip is attributed to the absence of a significant tax credit booked in the previous fiscal year. Despite the profit drop, the company achieved a robust 37% year-on-year revenue growth, reaching ₹492.4 Cr in FY25 from ₹360.2 Cr in FY24. Total expenses rose by 36%.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:09:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695263294342f77179dcaf65_1767010275437.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Delivery Strike Alert! Zomato, Swiggy, Zepto Partners Vow Nationwide Shutdown Dec 31 – Can India's Gig Economy Handle It?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Delivery-Strike-Alert-Zomato-Swiggy-Zepto-Partners-Vow-Nationwide-Shutdown-Dec-31-Can-Indias-Gig-Economy-Handle-It/6952637e4342f77179dcb026</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Delivery-Strike-Alert-Zomato-Swiggy-Zepto-Partners-Vow-Nationwide-Shutdown-Dec-31-Can-Indias-Gig-Economy-Handle-It/6952637e4342f77179dcb026</guid><description>Delivery partners for major platforms including Zomato, Swiggy, Zepto, Blinkit, Amazon, and Flipkart will go on a nationwide strike on December 31, 2025. This action follows a December 25th protest and aims to pressure companies for fair wages, improved safety, dignity, and social security, protesting against algorithmic control and ID blocking.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:08:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952637e4342f77179dcb025_1767007297617.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Premium Homes Skyrocket, Affordable Housing Vanishes: Lenders Forced to Rethink Strategy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Premium-Homes-Skyrocket-Affordable-Housing-Vanishes-Lenders-Forced-to-Rethink-Strategy/6952624b4342f77179dcad7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Premium-Homes-Skyrocket-Affordable-Housing-Vanishes-Lenders-Forced-to-Rethink-Strategy/6952624b4342f77179dcad7c</guid><description>Developers are rapidly shifting focus from affordable housing projects (under ₹50 lakh) to high-end luxury homes, driven by high land costs, low profits, and lack of incentives. This strategic pivot compels lenders and Housing Finance Companies to reconsider their home loan market approaches, potentially increasing focus on co-lending and higher-yield, non-salaried customers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:06:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952624b4342f77179dcad7b_1767010056984.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Skyrockets to Record Highs, Gold Nears Peak! Is This a Gold Rush 2.0?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-to-Record-Highs-Gold-Nears-Peak-Is-This-a-Gold-Rush-20/695262594342f77179dcadc9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-to-Record-Highs-Gold-Nears-Peak-Is-This-a-Gold-Rush-20/695262594342f77179dcadc9</guid><description>Precious metals are shining bright as silver futures surged to an all-time high of ₹2,54,174 per kg on the MCX, extending its rally for the sixth consecutive session. Gold prices also hovered near record levels, trading at ₹1,40,230 per 10 grams. Strong investor demand and supportive global cues are driving these significant gains in the commodities market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:05:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695262594342f77179dcadc8_1767010863793.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRFC's Rs 9,821 Crore Deal: CEO Manoj Dubey Unveils Strategy to Skyrocket Profits and AUM!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IRFCs-Rs-9821-Crore-Deal-CEO-Manoj-Dubey-Unveils-Strategy-to-Skyrocket-Profits-and-AUM/695260254342f77179dca966</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IRFCs-Rs-9821-Crore-Deal-CEO-Manoj-Dubey-Unveils-Strategy-to-Skyrocket-Profits-and-AUM/695260254342f77179dca966</guid><description>Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) anticipates a significant boost to its Assets Under Management (AUM) and margins following a Rs 9,821 crore refinancing deal with Dedicated Freight Corridor Corporation of India Ltd (DFCCIL). CEO Manoj Kumar Dubey stated this unique transaction, which refinances a World Bank loan, allows DFCCIL to save approximately ₹2,700 crore and substantially enhances IRFC's net interest margins (NIM). This strategic move is a key component of IRFC's diversification initiative, 'IRFC 2.0', aiming to expand beyond core railway lending.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:47:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695260254342f77179dca965_1767009472877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2025: Massive Reforms Unveiled to Supercharge Economy &amp; Boost Growth! See What Changed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-Massive-Reforms-Unveiled-to-Supercharge-Economy-and-Boost-Growth-See-What-Changed/69525f4d4342f77179dca74f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2025-Massive-Reforms-Unveiled-to-Supercharge-Economy-and-Boost-Growth-See-What-Changed/69525f4d4342f77179dca74f</guid><description>In 2025, India's National Democratic Alliance government, led by Prime Minister Narendra Modi, enacted sweeping reforms across taxation, labour laws, MSMEs, and foreign investment to bolster economic resilience. Key changes include a simplified Goods and Services Tax (GST) with fewer rates, significant income tax relief for middle-class individuals, consolidation of labour laws into four codes, revised MSME definitions to boost growth, and 100% Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) in insurance. These measures aim to simplify business, attract capital, and support economic expansion, building on the 8.2% GDP growth recorded in Q2 2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:46:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69525f4d4342f77179dca74e_1767009353680.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharat Electronics Secures Massive ₹569 Crore Defence Deals, Stock Edges Higher!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Electronics-Secures-Massive-569-Crore-Defence-Deals-Stock-Edges-Higher/69525f534342f77179dca782</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Electronics-Secures-Massive-569-Crore-Defence-Deals-Stock-Edges-Higher/69525f534342f77179dca782</guid><description>Bharat Electronics Limited (BEL) has announced securing new orders worth ₹569 crore for a diverse range of defence and non-defence products. These include radars, communication equipment, and security software, bolstering its already strong order book. This follows previous wins totalling ₹776 crore. The company also reported robust Q2 financial results, with net profit up 18% year-on-year to ₹1,286 crore, driving investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:46:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69525f534342f77179dca781_1767009207359.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver's Shocking Rally: Is a Physical Shortage Driving Prices to Unseen Heights?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silvers-Shocking-Rally-Is-a-Physical-Shortage-Driving-Prices-to-Unseen-Heights/69525e764342f77179dca4df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silvers-Shocking-Rally-Is-a-Physical-Shortage-Driving-Prices-to-Unseen-Heights/69525e764342f77179dca4df</guid><description>Silver prices are surging, outperforming gold, but not due to normal market sentiment. Analysts point to a severe, persistent physical shortage driven by years of underinvestment, declining mine grades, and booming industrial demand, especially from solar and EVs. Visible inventories are depleted globally, and China's potential export curbs add pressure, widening the gap between paper and physical markets. This brittle rally warns of potential sharp corrections despite strong structural demand.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:44:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69525e764342f77179dca4de_1767008264439.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Plummets Below $88,000! Nasdaq Futures Wilt, Sparking Crypto Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Plummets-Below-88000-Nasdaq-Futures-Wilt-Sparking-Crypto-Sell-Off/69525e964342f77179dca546</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Plummets-Below-88000-Nasdaq-Futures-Wilt-Sparking-Crypto-Sell-Off/69525e964342f77179dca546</guid><description>Bitcoin has reversed earlier gains, dropping below $88,000 after failing to hold above $90,000. Major cryptocurrencies like Ether and Solana followed suit. This decline mirrors weakness in Nasdaq futures, which are trading lower, suggesting a cautious start to the US stock market. Analysts note a strong correlation between Bitcoin and the Nasdaq, especially during downtrends, and point to potential year-end tax selling as a factor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:44:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69525e964342f77179dca545_1767005988004.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Set to Block Cheap Chinese Penicillin Imports? Big Win for Domestic Drug Makers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Set-to-Block-Cheap-Chinese-Penicillin-Imports-Big-Win-for-Domestic-Drug-Makers/69525e014342f77179dca388</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Set-to-Block-Cheap-Chinese-Penicillin-Imports-Big-Win-for-Domestic-Drug-Makers/69525e014342f77179dca388</guid><description>The Indian government is finalizing a Minimum Import Price (MIP) for Penicillin-G, a crucial raw material for antibiotics. This move aims to protect domestic manufacturers from price undercutting by Chinese suppliers and make investments under the Production-Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme, like Aurobindo Pharma's, viable. The MIP is expected to be time-bound and apply only to domestic consumption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:43:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69525e014342f77179dca387_1767005759206.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IPO Star Corona Remedies Unleashes Massive Gujarat Plant Expansion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/IPO-Star-Corona-Remedies-Unleashes-Massive-Gujarat-Plant-Expansion/69525d744342f77179dca273</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/IPO-Star-Corona-Remedies-Unleashes-Massive-Gujarat-Plant-Expansion/69525d744342f77179dca273</guid><description>Newly listed Corona Remedies, fresh off a successful IPO subscribed 137 times, has announced a significant capacity expansion at its Bhayla manufacturing facility in Gujarat. The expansion, funded by internal accruals, will boost annual production capacity by 240 million units to 1.09 billion units, aiming to meet growing market demand and optimize operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:43:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69525d744342f77179dca272_1767008391449.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IPO Boom: Fairly Priced or Overvalued? Expert Reveals Shocking Truth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-IPO-Boom-Fairly-Priced-or-Overvalued-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-Truth/69525d694342f77179dca23f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-IPO-Boom-Fairly-Priced-or-Overvalued-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-Truth/69525d694342f77179dca23f</guid><description>Despite record IPO fundraising of ₹1.75 lakh crore in 2025, average listing gains have moderated. Suraj Krishnaswamy, MD at Axis Capital, argues that Indian IPOs are now more fairly valued than in 2020-2022, dispelling perceptions of aggressive pricing. He anticipates IPO fundraising to remain strong, with ₹1.5 lakh crore as a baseline for 2026, driven by technology, renewable energy, healthcare, BFSI, and consumer sectors, alongside growing interest in InvITs and REITs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:43:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69525d694342f77179dca23e_1767007388508.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>