<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:26:11 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Garment Mantra Eyes Export Boom on India-EU Trade Deal, US Tariffs Clarity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Garment-Mantra-Eyes-Export-Boom-on-India-EU-Trade-Deal-US-Tariffs-Clarity/6982c53cf5a3f0ebac98b157</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Garment-Mantra-Eyes-Export-Boom-on-India-EU-Trade-Deal-US-Tariffs-Clarity/6982c53cf5a3f0ebac98b157</guid><description>Garment Mantra Lifestyle Limited is poised for export growth following the India-European Union Free Trade Agreement and clearer US tariff structures. The company has already achieved over ₹100 crore in export sales this financial year. A recent Rights Issue has significantly bolstered its working capital, positioning Garment Mantra to capitalize on enhanced global competitiveness and market access for Indian textile manufacturers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:05:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982c53cf5a3f0ebac98b156_1770177926790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asia Navigates AI Bifurcation: Hardware Resilience, Software Woes Amid Geopolitical Crosscurrents</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Asia-Navigates-AI-Bifurcation-Hardware-Resilience-Software-Woes-Amid-Geopolitical-Crosscurrents/6982c4c7f5a3f0ebac98b028</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Asia-Navigates-AI-Bifurcation-Hardware-Resilience-Software-Woes-Amid-Geopolitical-Crosscurrents/6982c4c7f5a3f0ebac98b028</guid><description>Asian equities traded with caution on February 4, 2026, as AI advancements spurred fears of software disruption while bolstering regional hardware manufacturers. The MSCI Asia-Pacific index eased 0.2%, and Japan's Nikkei fell 1.2%. Geopolitical tensions bolstered oil prices, with Brent crude reaching $67.78 per barrel. Gold and silver prices recovered from a recent Fed-induced slump, signaling a bifurcated market response to technological shifts and global instability. The yen weakened ahead of Japanese elections, reflecting domestic political drivers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:05:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982c4c7f5a3f0ebac98b027_1770177898750.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anthropic Pursues $350B Valuation for Funding &amp; Employee Liquidity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-Pursues-350B-Valuation-for-Funding-and-Employee-Liquidity/6982c2faf5a3f0ebac98ad1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-Pursues-350B-Valuation-for-Funding-and-Employee-Liquidity/6982c2faf5a3f0ebac98ad1c</guid><description>Artificial intelligence firm Anthropic is reportedly pursuing a $20 billion funding round alongside a substantial employee tender offer. This dual strategy targets a $350 billion pre-money valuation, reflecting intense investor demand and a critical need for talent liquidity in the hyper-competitive AI sector. The move positions Anthropic to further solidify its standing against major rivals like OpenAI amidst unprecedented market valuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982c2faf5a3f0ebac98ad1b_1770177727007.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AB Capital Surges on Strong Q3, Advent Deal Boosts Housing Arm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AB-Capital-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Advent-Deal-Boosts-Housing-Arm/6982c3d4f5a3f0ebac98aec8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AB-Capital-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Advent-Deal-Boosts-Housing-Arm/6982c3d4f5a3f0ebac98aec8</guid><description>Aditya Birla Capital's shares climbed following a strong third quarter, marked by a 28.7% profit surge to ₹772 crore and 24% AUM growth to ₹1.48 lakh crore. A strategic ₹2,750 crore capital infusion into its housing finance subsidiary from Advent International further bolsters its expansion plans. The company's diversified business segments, including life and health insurance, also demonstrated healthy performance metrics, positioning it favorably within the buoyant Indian financial services sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:00:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982c3d4f5a3f0ebac98aec7_1770177613091.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Solar Exports Gain US Foothold Amid Capacity Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/India-Solar-Exports-Gain-US-Foothold-Amid-Capacity-Boom/6982ba89f5a3f0ebac98985f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/India-Solar-Exports-Gain-US-Foothold-Amid-Capacity-Boom/6982ba89f5a3f0ebac98985f</guid><description>Indian solar manufacturers are poised for a revival in US exports following a new bilateral trade agreement. A headline tariff of 18 percent offers competitive relief, crucial as domestic production capacity is set to vastly outstrip demand by fiscal year 2028. Vikram Solar, which has seen its stock climb on the news, benefits from this renewed access to the lucrative US market, though lingering anti-dumping investigations present a significant overhang. Jefferies India forecasts capacities reaching 143GW/226GW for cells/modules by FY28, far exceeding the 65GWdc domestic demand.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:58:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982ba89f5a3f0ebac98985e_1770177402262.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Rallies 4% on Comex Amidst Extreme Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Rallies-4percent-on-Comex-Amidst-Extreme-Volatility/6982c2e8f5a3f0ebac98ac64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Rallies-4percent-on-Comex-Amidst-Extreme-Volatility/6982c2e8f5a3f0ebac98ac64</guid><description>Silver prices rallied 4.27% on Comex to $86.85, following a severe 45% correction from recent highs. This surge contrasts with a 0.38% dip on India's MCX, where Tuesday's session closed at Rs 2,67,000 per kilogram, highlighting divergent market dynamics. The rebound occurred amidst extreme price swings, with prices previously plummeting as much as 40% in two days and hitting lows around $71. Geopolitical tensions and a nomination for a hawkish Fed chair are influencing sentiment. Analysts forecast continued volatility within a broad $72–$87 range, with some projecting significant upside potential for 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:55:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982c2e8f5a3f0ebac98ac63_1770177328366.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Crude Switch: $3B Savings Potential Faces Logistical Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Crude-Switch-3B-Savings-Potential-Faces-Logistical-Hurdles/6982c17ff5a3f0ebac98a9ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Crude-Switch-3B-Savings-Potential-Faces-Logistical-Hurdles/6982c17ff5a3f0ebac98a9ac</guid><description>India's crude oil import bill could see an annual reduction of up to $3 billion by diverting supply from Russia to Venezuelan heavy crude. This potential saving hinges on Venezuelan crude being priced with a $10-12 per barrel discount to offset increased shipping and handling costs. However, significant logistical hurdles, including Venezuela's greater geographical distance, and the necessity for domestic refineries to process heavier crude grades, introduce complexities to this strategy. Geopolitical shifts impacting Russian crude prices and refinery capabilities will ultimately shape the viability of this import recalibration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982c17ff5a3f0ebac98a9ab_1770177014361.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Varun Beverages' Premium Valuation Faces Margin, Growth Tests</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Varun-Beverages-Premium-Valuation-Faces-Margin-Growth-Tests/6982c1f6f5a3f0ebac98aaeb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Varun-Beverages-Premium-Valuation-Faces-Margin-Growth-Tests/6982c1f6f5a3f0ebac98aaeb</guid><description>Varun Beverages reported a 10% volume increase in India and internationally for Q4CY25, alongside a 3.4% rise in net realization. While achieving an all-time high India EBITDA margin of approximately 26% in CY25, the company faces sustained margin compression due to competition. VBL is pursuing significant inorganic growth, including the Twizza acquisition, aiming for international margin convergence. The company currently trades at a premium valuation, with its current P/E ratio around 85x, reflecting high market expectations for future earnings growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:51:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982c1f6f5a3f0ebac98aaea_1770177073910.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks Face Valuation Test Amid AI Disruption Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Face-Valuation-Test-Amid-AI-Disruption-Fears/6982bbeff5a3f0ebac989b45</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Face-Valuation-Test-Amid-AI-Disruption-Fears/6982bbeff5a3f0ebac989b45</guid><description>The release of Anthropic's advanced AI automation tools triggered a sharp market sell-off, dubbed 'SaaSpocalypse,' pressuring Indian IT giants Infosys, Wipro, and TCS. While fears of AI replacing core services are rampant, this report dissects the valuation implications and the companies' strategic positioning against this evolving threat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:34:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982bbeff5a3f0ebac989b44_1770175953742.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pawar Family Rift Deepens: Sunetra Pawar's Elevation Stirs Maharashtra Politics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Pawar-Family-Rift-Deepens-Sunetra-Pawars-Elevation-Stirs-Maharashtra-Politics/6982bc05f5a3f0ebac989c5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Pawar-Family-Rift-Deepens-Sunetra-Pawars-Elevation-Stirs-Maharashtra-Politics/6982bc05f5a3f0ebac989c5b</guid><description>Sunetra Pawar has assumed the post of Maharashtra Deputy Chief Minister, widening fissures within the Pawar family. The swift appointment, reportedly without patriarch Sharad Pawar's full knowledge, signals an effort to consolidate the Ajit Pawar faction's leadership following the late Ajit Pawar's death. This move, potentially influenced by the Bharatiya Janata Party, introduces new complexities into the state's coalition government, requiring Sunetra Pawar to navigate the dominant BJP and the Eknath Shinde-led Shiv Sena. The elevation also raises questions about dynastic politics versus democratic processes, with critics pointing to the need for transparent party leadership selection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:29:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982bc05f5a3f0ebac989c5a_1770175764939.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jefferies' Wood Pivots: India Sales Fund Mining &amp; Asian Tech Bets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Jefferies-Wood-Pivots-India-Sales-Fund-Mining-and-Asian-Tech-Bets/6982bc4ff5a3f0ebac989d27</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Jefferies-Wood-Pivots-India-Sales-Fund-Mining-and-Asian-Tech-Bets/6982bc4ff5a3f0ebac989d27</guid><description>Jefferies' Chris Wood has made significant shifts in his GREED &amp; fear long-only portfolios. ICICI Bank, DLF, and MakeMyTrip have been divested, replaced by mining giants Anglo American and Zijin Mining, alongside Samsung Life Insurance and Eternal (Zomato parent). This strategic reallocation suggests a turn from Indian financials and real estate towards global commodities and Asian growth narratives, particularly notable given the recent sharp correction in Zomato's parent company. The moves reflect a nuanced view on inflation, industrial demand, and digital sector valuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:28:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982bc4ff5a3f0ebac989d26_1770175679094.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Households Face Healthcare Cost Peril Amid Insurance Gaps</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indian-Households-Face-Healthcare-Cost-Peril-Amid-Insurance-Gaps/6982bbdff5a3f0ebac989ac5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indian-Households-Face-Healthcare-Cost-Peril-Amid-Insurance-Gaps/6982bbdff5a3f0ebac989ac5</guid><description>A recent nationwide survey indicates that 82% of Indian households perceive rising healthcare costs as a significant future financial threat, with an equal percentage fearing sudden medical emergencies. The Nishchit Index 2.0, commissioned by Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance, also found that 79% of respondents lack confidence in their existing insurance coverage, and 80% are unsure about their emergency savings adequacy. Environmental concerns, particularly pollution, are further amplifying these financial anxieties, with 81% believing pollution will worsen and directly impact future medical expenses and health risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:26:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982bbdff5a3f0ebac989ac4_1770175562835.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>3i Infotech Files Fraud Complaint, Alleges ₹128 Cr Misappropriation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/3i-Infotech-Files-Fraud-Complaint-Alleges-128-Cr-Misappropriation/6982ba71f5a3f0ebac9897df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/3i-Infotech-Files-Fraud-Complaint-Alleges-128-Cr-Misappropriation/6982ba71f5a3f0ebac9897df</guid><description>3i Infotech has filed a police complaint with Navi Mumbai EOW alleging large-scale corporate financial fraud, criminal breach of trust, and cheating amounting to over ₹128 crore. The complaint targets eMudhra Limited, Mr. Venkatraman Srinivasan (former 3i Infotech MD), and Mr. Ravi Jagannathan (former eMudhra MD) over the fraudulent disinvestment of 3i Consumer Services Limited and wrongful redemption of preference shares. SEBI complaint is also being prepared.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:20:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982ba71f5a3f0ebac9897de_1770175216638.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US-India Strategic Minerals Pact: Beyond Trade Tariffs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-India-Strategic-Minerals-Pact-Beyond-Trade-Tariffs/6982b819f5a3f0ebac98947a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-India-Strategic-Minerals-Pact-Beyond-Trade-Tariffs/6982b819f5a3f0ebac98947a</guid><description>External Affairs Minister S. Jaishankar's meeting with US Secretary of State Marco Rubio solidified a burgeoning strategic alliance, extending beyond a recently finalized trade deal that reduced US tariffs on Indian goods to 18%. The discussions prioritized formalizing cooperation on critical minerals, a move reflecting a global push to secure vital supply chains amid increasing geopolitical competition and China's dominant market share. This strategic alignment is amplified by the upcoming Critical Minerals Ministerial, underscoring a concerted effort to diversify resource access and bolster national security through robust bilateral and multilateral initiatives, including the Quad.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:12:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982b819f5a3f0ebac989479_1770174635618.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Buy IOC, Tata Elxsi, IFCI: Top Stock Picks for Feb 4 Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Buy-IOC-Tata-Elxsi-IFCI-Top-Stock-Picks-for-Feb-4-Rally/6982b893f5a3f0ebac98959b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Buy-IOC-Tata-Elxsi-IFCI-Top-Stock-Picks-for-Feb-4-Rally/6982b893f5a3f0ebac98959b</guid><description>Anand Rathi Shares and Stock Brokers has pinpointed Indian Oil Corporation (IOC), Tata Elxsi, and IFCI as top stock picks for February 4, 2026. Analysts highlight trendline and Alligator breakouts, supported by bullish technical indicators like MACD and DMI, suggesting significant upside potential. Specific buy zones, stop-loss levels, and price targets are provided for each stock, guiding investors on potential entry and exit points.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:11:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982b893f5a3f0ebac98959a_1770174716273.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-China Trade Hits Record $155B Amid Deepening Deficit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-China-Trade-Hits-Record-155B-Amid-Deepening-Deficit/6982afbff5a3f0ebac988176</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-China-Trade-Hits-Record-155B-Amid-Deepening-Deficit/6982afbff5a3f0ebac988176</guid><description>India and China achieved a record bilateral trade volume of $155.6 billion in 2025, marking a 12% year-on-year increase, according to Chinese Ambassador Xu Feihong. This surge follows a diplomatic reset after the 2020 Galwan Valley clashes and includes Chinese support for India's BRICS presidency and Global South initiatives. However, India's trade deficit with China expanded to a record $116 billion in 2025, highlighting persistent economic imbalances and strategic vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:54:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982afbff5a3f0ebac988175_1770173607790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Surge on Trade Deal; Global Slump Ignored</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Surge-on-Trade-Deal-Global-Slump-Ignored/6982b18cf5a3f0ebac989081</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Surge-on-Trade-Deal-Global-Slump-Ignored/6982b18cf5a3f0ebac989081</guid><description>Indian equity markets surged on February 4, 2026, driven by a landmark India-US trade deal that slashed tariffs to 18%. This development, coupled with a strengthening rupee and robust foreign institutional investor inflows totaling ₹5,236 crore, propelled broad-based gains. Despite a tech-led sell-off in US markets and mixed Asian performance, Indian benchmarks closed significantly higher, signaling resilience and unlocking export potential for key sectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:42:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982b18cf5a3f0ebac989080_1770172973052.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Q3 Earnings Deluge: Divergence Amidst Macro Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Q3-Earnings-Deluge-Divergence-Amidst-Macro-Shifts/6982afabf5a3f0ebac987fab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Q3-Earnings-Deluge-Divergence-Amidst-Macro-Shifts/6982afabf5a3f0ebac987fab</guid><description>India's market faces an earnings avalanche today, with over 140 companies, including Bajaj Finserv, Tata Power, and Cummins India, reporting Q3 FY26 results. Performances are diverging significantly, impacted by sector-specific pressures like cement price declines and robust industrial demand. The backdrop includes positive shifts from the India-US trade deal, but concerns linger over elevated valuations for some entities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:34:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982afabf5a3f0ebac987faa_1770172441299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Angel One Hits 15-Month Highs in Platform Activity, Client Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Angel-One-Hits-15-Month-Highs-in-Platform-Activity-Client-Growth/6982ae43f5a3f0ebac986a87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Angel-One-Hits-15-Month-Highs-in-Platform-Activity-Client-Growth/6982ae43f5a3f0ebac986a87</guid><description>Angel One's January 2026 business update reveals a 15-month high in platform activity, fueled by a 20.8% YoY client base increase to 36.39 million and a 45.7% surge in average client funding book. Trading volumes soared, with total orders up 16.4% YoY and average daily orders jumping 33.9%. Overall Average Daily Turnover (ADTO) more than doubled YoY, reaching ₹64,075 billion. While market share in equity and F&amp;O options improved, commodity share saw a decline. The update noted fewer trading days in January impacting daily metrics.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982ae43f5a3f0ebac986a86_1770172155631.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Surges on Bullish Reversal; HDFC Securities Recommends Two Stocks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nifty-Surges-on-Bullish-Reversal-HDFC-Securities-Recommends-Two-Stocks/6982add9f5a3f0ebac98691c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nifty-Surges-on-Bullish-Reversal-HDFC-Securities-Recommends-Two-Stocks/6982add9f5a3f0ebac98691c</guid><description>The Indian benchmark Nifty 50 index has signaled a bullish trend reversal, recovering 1,770 points from its recent low. It has reclaimed crucial Exponential Moving Averages, suggesting sustained upward momentum. HDFC Securities has recommended buying Samvardhana Motherson and Bharat Forge, outlining specific price targets and stop-loss levels for both counter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982add9f5a3f0ebac98691b_1770172053802.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yes Bank Taps New CEO Amid Financial Recovery and Sector Evolution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Bank-Taps-New-CEO-Amid-Financial-Recovery-and-Sector-Evolution/6982adc7f5a3f0ebac98685d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Bank-Taps-New-CEO-Amid-Financial-Recovery-and-Sector-Evolution/6982adc7f5a3f0ebac98685d</guid><description>Yes Bank shares are under the spotlight following the Reserve Bank of India's approval for Vinay Muralidhar Tonse's appointment as Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer for a three-year term. This leadership transition coincides with the bank's robust third-quarter earnings, which saw a 55.4% surge in net profit to ₹951.6 crore. Despite a positive operational outlook, analyst sentiment remains cautious, with a prevailing 'Sell' consensus and an average price target indicating potential downside.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:26:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982adc7f5a3f0ebac98685c_1770171965129.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance's Profit Hit by Provisions; Long-Term Strategy Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finances-Profit-Hit-by-Provisions-Long-Term-Strategy-Focus/6982ad6df5a3f0ebac986706</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finances-Profit-Hit-by-Provisions-Long-Term-Strategy-Focus/6982ad6df5a3f0ebac986706</guid><description>Bajaj Finance reported a 6% year-on-year decline in profit after tax for Q3 FY26, missing consensus estimates by 21%, primarily due to accelerated expected credit loss (ECL) provisions totaling approximately ₹1,406 crore. Despite strong net interest income growth near 20%, provisions surged, pushing credit costs to 3.06%. A ₹1,416 crore one-time gain from a Bajaj Housing Finance stake sale was recognized in net worth, not P&amp;L. Management highlighted strategic provisioning for balance sheet resilience and outlined an AI-led strategy to improve future credit costs and productivity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982ad6df5a3f0ebac986705_1770171956222.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IREDA Eyes ₹2,994 Cr QIP Amidst Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Eyes-2994-Cr-QIP-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/6982ad59f5a3f0ebac98665f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Eyes-2994-Cr-QIP-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/6982ad59f5a3f0ebac98665f</guid><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency (IREDA) Ltd. has announced its board will convene to approve a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) aimed at raising up to ₹2,994 crore. This move, intended to fuel expansion in the green energy sector, occurs against a backdrop of the stock's year-to-date decline and significantly higher valuation multiples compared to peers like PFC and REC. Historical QIPs have previously pressured IREDA's share price.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982ad59f5a3f0ebac98665e_1770171852832.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Rally: Trade Deal Boost Meets Macro Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rally-Trade-Deal-Boost-Meets-Macro-Uncertainty/6982ad6bf5a3f0ebac9866ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rally-Trade-Deal-Boost-Meets-Macro-Uncertainty/6982ad6bf5a3f0ebac9866ca</guid><description>Precious metals extended a sharp rebound on February 4, 2026, with gold holding above $5,000 and silver around $86 per ounce. This recovery follows significant volatility, driven by a weaker US dollar and bargain buying. A recent US-India trade deal, slashing tariffs, improved global sentiment, while persistent macroeconomic uncertainty and industrial demand continue to underpin precious metals. Investors now await critical US labor data, which will shape Federal Reserve policy expectations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:24:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982ad6bf5a3f0ebac9866c9_1770171836082.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Sparks Rally, Sectors Eye Tariff Relief</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Rally-Sectors-Eye-Tariff-Relief/6982abedf5a3f0ebac986493</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Rally-Sectors-Eye-Tariff-Relief/6982abedf5a3f0ebac986493</guid><description>Indian equities rallied significantly on February 3, 2026, driven by the announcement of a trade agreement with the United States. This pact reduces reciprocal tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from as high as 50%, removing a major market overhang. Benchmark indices like the Nifty and Sensex saw substantial gains, reflecting renewed investor optimism. Sectors poised for direct benefits include chemicals, auto ancillaries, textiles, and IT services, due to enhanced export competitiveness and improved business confidence. The deal is also anticipated to attract foreign investment and strengthen the Indian rupee.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:18:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982abedf5a3f0ebac986492_1770171473740.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apple Deepens India Ties: Skills Investment Fuels Supply Chain and Market Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apple-Deepens-India-Ties-Skills-Investment-Fuels-Supply-Chain-and-Market-Growth/6982aa81f5a3f0ebac9862c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apple-Deepens-India-Ties-Skills-Investment-Fuels-Supply-Chain-and-Market-Growth/6982aa81f5a3f0ebac9862c3</guid><description>Apple is intensifying its India strategy by launching a new education hub in Bengaluru to bolster supply chain workforce skills. This initiative, backed by a $50 million global fund, aims to deliver over 100 training programs across more than 25 supplier facilities by 2026. The move supports India's rising importance as both a critical manufacturing base and a rapidly expanding high-value market, complementing Apple's significant gains in smartphone market share within the country.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:12:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982aa81f5a3f0ebac9862c2_1770171114574.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 14,000 Cr IPO Rush: Will Investor Appetite Hold?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Rs-14000-Cr-IPO-Rush-Will-Investor-Appetite-Hold/6982a997f5a3f0ebac98610b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Rs-14000-Cr-IPO-Rush-Will-Investor-Appetite-Hold/6982a997f5a3f0ebac98610b</guid><description>Seven companies are poised to launch Initial Public Offerings (IPOs) by the end of February, seeking to collectively raise approximately ₹14,000 crore. This significant influx comes after a subdued start to 2026 for the primary market, which has seen only three listings to date, raising a total of ₹4,765 crore. Key issuers include Fractal Analytics and Aye Finance, alongside larger offerings from Indo MIM and Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions. This wave represents a critical gauge of renewed investor appetite amidst lingering trade uncertainties and follows a record-setting fundraising year in 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982a997f5a3f0ebac98610a_1770170903940.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Surges 7% as US Slashes India Tariffs, Safe Havens Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-7percent-as-US-Slashes-India-Tariffs-Safe-Havens-Boost/6982a7b3f5a3f0ebac985ee0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-7percent-as-US-Slashes-India-Tariffs-Safe-Havens-Boost/6982a7b3f5a3f0ebac985ee0</guid><description>Gold prices saw a sharp rebound, surging over 7% on February 3rd. This recovery followed a significant tariff reduction by US President Donald Trump, who lowered levies on Indian goods to 18% from 50%. Analysts point to strong buying from central banks and increased demand for safe-haven assets, alongside geopolitical tensions, as key drivers for the yellow metal's resurgence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 02:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982a7b3f5a3f0ebac985edf_1770170396849.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Diverges: AI Strength Seen Amid Software Sell-off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tech-Diverges-AI-Strength-Seen-Amid-Software-Sell-off/6982a2aaf5a3f0ebac985916</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tech-Diverges-AI-Strength-Seen-Amid-Software-Sell-off/6982a2aaf5a3f0ebac985916</guid><description>Asian equities declined Wednesday, mirroring a US tech sell-off triggered by Advanced Micro Devices Inc.'s weak sales forecast. This overshadowed gains in economic barometers like FedEx Corp. and Walmart Inc., which neared $1 trillion market cap. A stark divergence emerged: while broader software stocks plunged and the iShares Expanded Tech-Software Sector ETF dropped 4.5%, Palantir Technologies Inc. posted a strong 'beat-and-raise' in AI, signaling selective investor appetite amidst a rotation into value sectors. Oil prices climbed on geopolitical tensions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:57:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982a2aaf5a3f0ebac985915_1770170270680.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apple Rebounds on Bullish Signals; Expert Options Strategy Revealed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apple-Rebounds-on-Bullish-Signals-Expert-Options-Strategy-Revealed/6982a314f5a3f0ebac985b4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apple-Rebounds-on-Bullish-Signals-Expert-Options-Strategy-Revealed/6982a314f5a3f0ebac985b4d</guid><description>Apple shares are staging a comeback after a significant slide driven by concerns over iPhone demand. Management's outlook for the March quarter and resilient Asian market performance are fueling a rebound. This recovery aligns with improving sentiment for mega-cap technology stocks, supported by AI investments, cooling inflation, and anticipated interest rate adjustments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:40:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982a314f5a3f0ebac985b4c_1770169245828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Flares Ignite Oil Prices Amid Supply Fragility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitical-Flares-Ignite-Oil-Prices-Amid-Supply-Fragility/6982a304f5a3f0ebac985aae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Geopolitical-Flares-Ignite-Oil-Prices-Amid-Supply-Fragility/6982a304f5a3f0ebac985aae</guid><description>Oil prices climbed for a second consecutive day as geopolitical tensions resurfaced following the U.S. downing of an Iranian drone and harassment of a U.S.-flagged tanker. West Texas Intermediate approached $64 a barrel, while Brent crude settled above $67. These gains were supported by a reported decrease in U.S. crude inventories, though the exact figure awaits official confirmation. The market remains acutely sensitive to disruptions in the Middle East, a crucial supply region, while OPEC+ anticipates gradual demand growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:40:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982a304f5a3f0ebac985aad_1770169173980.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US-India Trade Deal: Geopolitical Gambit or Economic Boon?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-India-Trade-Deal-Geopolitical-Gambit-or-Economic-Boon/6982a28ef5a3f0ebac985889</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-India-Trade-Deal-Geopolitical-Gambit-or-Economic-Boon/6982a28ef5a3f0ebac985889</guid><description>Washington has announced a trade agreement with New Delhi, a move seen by analysts as a strategic reaction to the recently concluded comprehensive EU-India free trade pact. This US-India deal aims to offer immediate tariff relief and improve bilateral ties, but its timing implies an effort to reassert US influence amidst a rapidly shifting global trade map. While promising bilateral benefits, its reactive nature poses questions for India regarding genuine progress versus competitive pressure from deeper European engagement. Market reactions have been mixed, with some sectors showing initial optimism while broader economic implications are still under scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:38:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982a28ef5a3f0ebac985888_1770169134037.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Copper Breakout Signals Long-Term Demand Amidst Commodity Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Copper-Breakout-Signals-Long-Term-Demand-Amidst-Commodity-Volatility/6982a130f5a3f0ebac9856b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Copper-Breakout-Signals-Long-Term-Demand-Amidst-Commodity-Volatility/6982a130f5a3f0ebac9856b4</guid><description>COMEX Copper's multi-decade price channel breakout signals robust demand driven by electrification and infrastructure, positioning it as a "growth haven." Despite recent silver price volatility and a dip in the Nifty Metal Index, underlying demand trends offer support for key metal stocks. However, analyst sentiment for Hindustan Copper presents a cautious outlook, contrasting with the prevailing bullish technical narrative.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982a130f5a3f0ebac9856b3_1770168756957.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Finance's MUFG Deal Fuels Bajaj Finance Rivalry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finances-MUFG-Deal-Fuels-Bajaj-Finance-Rivalry/6982a0adf5a3f0ebac98552b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finances-MUFG-Deal-Fuels-Bajaj-Finance-Rivalry/6982a0adf5a3f0ebac98552b</guid><description>Shriram Finance has secured a pivotal Rs 39,617 crore investment from MUFG Bank, significantly bolstering its competitive position against market leader Bajaj Finance. Both non-banking financial companies (NBFCs) demonstrated robust loan book expansion in the December 2025 quarter. Shriram Finance's retail lending strategy enhanced its Net Interest Margin (NIM), while Bajaj Finance managed higher provisions to reveal strong underlying profit growth, intensifying their market rivalry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:30:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982a0adf5a3f0ebac98552a_1770168608156.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tech Talent Gap: Industry Apathy Risks Future Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tech-Talent-Gap-Industry-Apathy-Risks-Future-Dominance/69829b10f5a3f0ebac9851aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tech-Talent-Gap-Industry-Apathy-Risks-Future-Dominance/69829b10f5a3f0ebac9851aa</guid><description>India's tech sector confronts a persistent skill gap, exacerbated by industry's abandonment of historical talent development models for 'day-one productivity.' Despite the National Education Policy (NEP) 2020's call for partnerships, corporate engagement remains superficial. This strategic shift, driven by complex new roles and attrition fears, risks undermining India's competitive advantage in the global technology arena, necessitating urgent policy intervention and genuine industry commitment to human capital investment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:06:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69829b10f5a3f0ebac9851a9_1770167172727.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alphabet Bets Big on India for AI Talent</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Bets-Big-on-India-for-AI-Talent/69829135f5a3f0ebac984cd3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Alphabet-Bets-Big-on-India-for-AI-Talent/69829135f5a3f0ebac984cd3</guid><description>Alphabet Inc. is dramatically expanding its presence in India, leasing and optioning millions of square feet of office space in Bengaluru. This strategic move aims to capture critical artificial intelligence talent and bolster its Global Capability Centers (GCCs) as India emerges as a key hub for AI development. The expansion could more than double its India workforce, signaling a major push in the global race for AI expertise against rivals like Microsoft and OpenAI.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:24:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69829135f5a3f0ebac984cd2_1770164647102.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>