<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:36:16 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Everest Industries Plummets: Revenue Drops 27%, Losses Widen Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Everest-Industries-Plummets-Revenue-Drops-27percent-Losses-Widen-Sharply/6986080be769d12df1d83a54</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Everest-Industries-Plummets-Revenue-Drops-27percent-Losses-Widen-Sharply/6986080be769d12df1d83a54</guid><description>Everest Industries' Q3 FY26 results reveal a sharp 26.85% YoY revenue decline to ₹26,883.42 L, with standalone PBT losses widening to ₹4,059.67 L. Consolidated figures mirror this distress, with revenue down 23.74% YoY and losses escalating. Earnings Per Share (EPS) has seen a severe drop. Both Building Products and Steel Buildings segments reported revenue decreases.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ram Ratna Wires Hits Record Highs on Revenue, EBITDA, PAT Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ram-Ratna-Wires-Hits-Record-Highs-on-Revenue-EBITDA-PAT-Surge/698607b6e769d12df1d835d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ram-Ratna-Wires-Hits-Record-Highs-on-Revenue-EBITDA-PAT-Surge/698607b6e769d12df1d835d3</guid><description>Ram Ratna Wires Limited posted record-breaking results for Q3 FY26, with revenue soaring 43.8% year-on-year to ₹1,277.9 crore. Operating EBITDA jumped 84.9% to ₹72.0 crore, and Profit After Tax (PAT) climbed 72.5% to ₹31.6 crore. Margins also saw significant improvement. The company attributes this exceptional performance to robust demand in the HVAC sector for copper tubes and continued growth in copper winding wires driven by India's electrification efforts. Management expressed confidence in sustained growth fueled by industry tailwinds and ongoing capacity additions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Diffusion Engineers Surges on Strong Earnings, Defence Deal; CEO Exits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diffusion-Engineers-Surges-on-Strong-Earnings-Defence-Deal-CEO-Exits/698607a0e769d12df1d834d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diffusion-Engineers-Surges-on-Strong-Earnings-Defence-Deal-CEO-Exits/698607a0e769d12df1d834d7</guid><description>Diffusion Engineers reported a robust Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue up 27.31% YoY to ₹1,008.24 Crores and net profit surging 69.15% to ₹120.11 Crores. The company also approved acquiring a 10% stake in defence solutions firm Tejorup Sunmay Systems for ₹4.4 Crores. However, CEO Ramesh Kumar N resigned, citing personal reasons.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SRG Housing Finance Posts Strong 33% AUM Growth, Profit Jumps 43% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SRG-Housing-Finance-Posts-Strong-33percent-AUM-Growth-Profit-Jumps-43percent-YoY/6986049fe769d12df1d818ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SRG-Housing-Finance-Posts-Strong-33percent-AUM-Growth-Profit-Jumps-43percent-YoY/6986049fe769d12df1d818ca</guid><description>SRG Housing Finance reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with Gross Loan Assets (AUM) surging 33.42% YoY to ₹943.93 crore. Profit After Tax (PAT) climbed 43.03% to ₹8.21 crore. Net Interest Income (NII) rose 40.87%, boosting Net Interest Margins. The company maintains asset quality and eyes ₹1,000 crore AUM target.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rapido's Ownly Enters Bengaluru Food Delivery Arena</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Rapidos-Ownly-Enters-Bengaluru-Food-Delivery-Arena/69860415e769d12df1d813f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Rapidos-Ownly-Enters-Bengaluru-Food-Delivery-Arena/69860415e769d12df1d813f4</guid><description>Ownly, Rapido's food delivery service, has officially launched across Bengaluru following a six-month pilot. The platform operates on a zero-commission model for restaurants, positioning itself as a challenger to market leaders Swiggy and Zomato. While aiming to address restaurant pain points like high commissions, Ownly faces intense competition in a market where incumbents leverage significant scale and marketing budgets. The company plans to train its existing ride-hailing 'captains' to handle deliveries and expand to other cities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:09:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India REITs Poised for Growth as RBI Opens Bank Lending</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-REITs-Poised-for-Growth-as-RBI-Opens-Bank-Lending/69860406e769d12df1d8136e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-REITs-Poised-for-Growth-as-RBI-Opens-Bank-Lending/69860406e769d12df1d8136e</guid><description>India's Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs) are set for accelerated expansion following the Reserve Bank of India's (RBI) proposal to permit direct bank lending. This regulatory shift aims to bypass previous funding hurdles, such as reliance on special purpose vehicles (SPVs) and volatile capital markets, offering trusts access to more stable, long-term capital. Industry executives anticipate this will enable faster retail and office asset growth, bolster financial flexibility, and improve distributable cash flows, contributing to the formalization of commercial real estate. Crucially, the effectiveness hinges on accompanying regulatory safeguards.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI's ₹25k Fraud Cap: Consumer Shield or Fraudster Incentive?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-25k-Fraud-Cap-Consumer-Shield-or-Fraudster-Incentive/6986014ee769d12df1d7fcf2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-25k-Fraud-Cap-Consumer-Shield-or-Fraudster-Incentive/6986014ee769d12df1d7fcf2</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) announced a new framework to compensate banking customers up to ₹25,000 for small-value digital fraud losses. While intended to bolster trust, the policy's reliance on the Depositor Education and Awareness Fund, coupled with a mandatory 15% customer liability, raises questions about its efficacy and potential for unintended consequences, including a possible moral hazard for fraudsters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JK Tyre Q3 Profit Surges: Margin Expansion &amp; Merger Synergy Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JK-Tyre-Q3-Profit-Surges-Margin-Expansion-and-Merger-Synergy-Focus/698600bee769d12df1d7f8bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JK-Tyre-Q3-Profit-Surges-Margin-Expansion-and-Merger-Synergy-Focus/698600bee769d12df1d7f8bc</guid><description>JK Tyre &amp; Industries Ltd. reported a substantial Q3 FY26 performance, with net profit soaring to ₹207 crore, up from ₹52.6 crore year-on-year. Revenue climbed 15% to ₹4,223 crore, fueled by strong domestic demand and resilient exports. The quarter was marked by an 82% surge in EBITDA to ₹571.3 crore, expanding margins to 13.5% due to product premiumization and favorable raw material costs. The successful merger of Cavendish Industries Limited adds a strategic layer, promising future operational synergies and economies of scale.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sula Vineyards: Destocking Hits Profit, But Tourism &amp; Analyst Optimism Persist</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sula-Vineyards-Destocking-Hits-Profit-But-Tourism-and-Analyst-Optimism-Persist/69860094e769d12df1d7f7cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sula-Vineyards-Destocking-Hits-Profit-But-Tourism-and-Analyst-Optimism-Persist/69860094e769d12df1d7f7cb</guid><description>Sula Vineyards Ltd. announced a 67.5% year-on-year net profit drop to ₹9.1 crore for the quarter ending December 31, 2025. Revenue declined 9.6% to ₹195.7 crore, with EBITDA falling 40.2% to ₹31.8 crore due to one-time tactical destocking in Karnataka. Despite these operational headwinds, wine tourism surged 34%, and the company appointed Gayathri Iyer as Company Secretary. Analysts maintain a positive outlook with a consensus 'Buy' rating and an average price target indicating potential upside.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Purple Finance Plans ₹69 Cr Warrant Issue, Promoter Shift, MF Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Purple-Finance-Plans-69-Cr-Warrant-Issue-Promoter-Shift-MF-Push/6985fe8fe769d12df1d7e57e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Purple-Finance-Plans-69-Cr-Warrant-Issue-Promoter-Shift-MF-Push/6985fe8fe769d12df1d7e57e</guid><description>Purple Finance Limited's board greenlit a ₹69.30 crore preferential issuance of equity warrants at ₹55 each, alongside a ₹12.60 crore increase in authorized share capital. Amendments to the MoA and AoA will enable mutual fund distribution and allow debenture trustee nominee directors in case of defaults. Significantly, an open offer is triggered due to concert parties, proposing Sandeep Jindal's reclassification as a promoter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Avian Flu in Chennai Threatens Poultry Sector Stability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Avian-Flu-in-Chennai-Threatens-Poultry-Sector-Stability/6985fe28e769d12df1d7e10d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Avian-Flu-in-Chennai-Threatens-Poultry-Sector-Stability/6985fe28e769d12df1d7e10d</guid><description>The resurfacing of highly pathogenic H5N1 avian influenza in Tamil Nadu, evidenced by over a thousand crow deaths in Chennai, casts a significant shadow over India's robust poultry sector. While authorities intensify surveillance and containment measures, the incident highlights the economic vulnerabilities within the industry, particularly concerning biosecurity and the potential for widespread disruption to supply chains and consumer prices. The event underscores the delicate balance between public health imperatives and the economic stability of a sector vital for food security and rural livelihoods.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dai-ichi Karkaria Sees PAT Slump into Loss, Revenue Declines 7.4%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Dai-ichi-Karkaria-Sees-PAT-Slump-into-Loss-Revenue-Declines-74percent/6985fe10e769d12df1d7e025</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Dai-ichi-Karkaria-Sees-PAT-Slump-into-Loss-Revenue-Declines-74percent/6985fe10e769d12df1d7e025</guid><description>Dai-ichi Karkaria reported a significant profit decline for Q3 FY26, swinging to a standalone PAT loss of ₹150 lakh from a profit of ₹191 lakh a year ago. Revenue from operations fell 7.4% YoY to ₹3,781 lakh. For the nine-month period, PAT plummeted 72.4% YoY to ₹35 lakh, despite a 7.8% revenue increase. Consolidated results mirrored the trend with a Q3 FY26 loss of ₹86 lakh.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Swarnsarita Jewels: Open Offer at ₹32.15 Per Share to Boost Promoter Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Swarnsarita-Jewels-Open-Offer-at-3215-Per-Share-to-Boost-Promoter-Stake/6985fc0be769d12df1d7ceb1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Swarnsarita-Jewels-Open-Offer-at-3215-Per-Share-to-Boost-Promoter-Stake/6985fc0be769d12df1d7ceb1</guid><description>The Cordia family and SJPL are launching a ₹15.42 crore open offer for Swarnsarita Jewels India Limited, seeking to acquire 22.97% stake at ₹32.15 per share. This voluntary offer, running from March 20 to April 07, 2026, aims to consolidate promoter holding to 75% and provides an exit opportunity for shareholders at a premium. Adequate financial arrangements are confirmed, though the offer managers have faced prior administrative warnings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Le Lavoir Consolidated Revenue Skyrockets 400%+, Standalone Sales Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Le-Lavoir-Consolidated-Revenue-Skyrockets-400percent-Standalone-Sales-Dip/6985fba4e769d12df1d7ca24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Le-Lavoir-Consolidated-Revenue-Skyrockets-400percent-Standalone-Sales-Dip/6985fba4e769d12df1d7ca24</guid><description>Le Lavoir Limited posted a significant Q3 FY26 consolidated revenue leap of over 400% YoY to ₹350.29 Lakhs, with consolidated PAT surging 118.6% to ₹70.02 Lakhs, largely due to its subsidiaries. Standalone revenue, however, contracted 5.6% YoY to ₹55.99 Lakhs, though standalone PAT rose 23.3%. The company confirmed no deviation in fund utilization from a recent preferential issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GACL Eyes Growth with ₹1029 Cr Capex, but Q3 FY26 Reports Net Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/GACL-Eyes-Growth-with-1029-Cr-Capex-but-Q3-FY26-Reports-Net-Loss/6985fb90e769d12df1d7c942</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/GACL-Eyes-Growth-with-1029-Cr-Capex-but-Q3-FY26-Reports-Net-Loss/6985fb90e769d12df1d7c942</guid><description>Gujarat Alkalies and Chemicals Ltd (GACL) posted a Q3 FY26 standalone revenue of ₹1044.46 Cr, up 1.46% YoY, with EBITDA rising 19% to ₹135 Cr. Despite a positive standalone PBT of ₹12.62 Cr, the company reported a net loss of ₹11.16 Cr. The Board approved a significant ₹1029 Cr capital expenditure for new projects, including a phosphoric acid plant and KOH capacity expansion, aiming to boost future revenues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Steel: India Surge Masks UK Slump Amid Global Oversupply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-India-Surge-Masks-UK-Slump-Amid-Global-Oversupply/6985f9c6e769d12df1d7b77f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-India-Surge-Masks-UK-Slump-Amid-Global-Oversupply/6985f9c6e769d12df1d7b77f</guid><description>Tata Steel posted a robust ₹2,730 crore net profit for Q3 FY26, fueled by strong sales volumes and improved realizations in India. This domestic success contrasts sharply with a significant EBITDA loss in the UK, underscoring regional performance disparities. Despite global steel oversupply pressures, particularly from China, and weak European demand, the company's strategic capacity expansions and cost efficiencies signal a focus on future growth, though current market dynamics present a mixed operational picture. Consolidated deliveries reached approximately 6.04 million tons, supported by strong performance in India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JK Lakshmi Cement: Volume Up, Margins Squeeze Amid Debt-Fueled Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/JK-Lakshmi-Cement-Volume-Up-Margins-Squeeze-Amid-Debt-Fueled-Expansion/6985f94ce769d12df1d7b34d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/JK-Lakshmi-Cement-Volume-Up-Margins-Squeeze-Amid-Debt-Fueled-Expansion/6985f94ce769d12df1d7b34d</guid><description>JK Lakshmi Cement's Q3FY26 saw standalone revenue climb 6.1% on 8.2% volume growth, reaching 3.3 million tonnes. However, a 2% dip in realisations, driven by higher non-trade sales, tempered profitability. Cost efficiencies per tonne saved 4.3%. The company is advancing a ₹3,000 crore capacity expansion to 22.6 mtpa by FY28, financed 70% by debt, while integrating subsidiaries. Analysts maintain a Buy rating with a ₹930 target, balancing medium-term growth prospects against near-term challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>LIC's Margin Leap Fuels Rally on Renewed Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LICs-Margin-Leap-Fuels-Rally-on-Renewed-Growth/6985f927e769d12df1d7b21e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LICs-Margin-Leap-Fuels-Rally-on-Renewed-Growth/6985f927e769d12df1d7b21e</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) posted a robust 15.9% year-on-year growth in Annual Premium Equivalent (APE) and a 28% increase in Value of New Business (VNB) for the first nine months of FY26. A strategic shift towards non-participating products boosted the VNB margin to 18.8%, a significant improvement. This performance has spurred a substantial rally in its stock price, with analysts maintaining 'BUY' ratings and revising price targets upwards, even as new FDI regulations loom.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:22:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Solarworld Energy Files ₹92 Cr Claim Against SGEL in Delhi HC Over Project Delays</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Solarworld-Energy-Files-92-Cr-Claim-Against-SGEL-in-Delhi-HC-Over-Project-Delays/6985f728e769d12df1d7a00b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Solarworld-Energy-Files-92-Cr-Claim-Against-SGEL-in-Delhi-HC-Over-Project-Delays/6985f728e769d12df1d7a00b</guid><description>Solarworld Energy Solutions Limited has initiated arbitration proceedings against SJVN Green Energy Limited (SGEL) by filing a petition in the Delhi High Court. The company claims approximately ₹92.4 crore in dues and bank guarantee amounts, citing delays caused by SGEL's failure to meet contractual obligations for two solar projects (100 MW and 260 MW). Solarworld is seeking the release of retention amounts and other dues, and has opted not to extend Performance Bank Guarantees, leading to SGEL conditionally involving them.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Medi Assist Restructures Paramount TPA, Merges Residual Entity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Medi-Assist-Restructures-Paramount-TPA-Merges-Residual-Entity/6985f705e769d12df1d79f25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Medi-Assist-Restructures-Paramount-TPA-Merges-Residual-Entity/6985f705e769d12df1d79f25</guid><description>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Limited is executing a comprehensive three-step restructuring for its subsidiary, Paramount Health Services &amp; Insurance TPA Private Limited (Paramount TPA), following its acquisition. The plan involves a slump transfer of Paramount TPA's licensed business to Medi Assist Insurance TPA, followed by the surrender of Paramount TPA's license. The residual Paramount entity will then merge with the holding company, Medi Assist Healthcare Services Limited. This strategic move aims for greater economies of scale, enhanced policyholder experience, and a streamlined corporate structure, while ensuring stronger corporate governance over surplus assets. The restructuring, effective from July 1, 2025, for merger purposes, is not expected to alter the shareholding pattern of the listed entity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bazel International Gets BSE Nod for Bonus Share Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Bazel-International-Gets-BSE-Nod-for-Bonus-Share-Issue/6985f6bce769d12df1d79c03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Bazel-International-Gets-BSE-Nod-for-Bonus-Share-Issue/6985f6bce769d12df1d79c03</guid><description>Bazel International Limited has received in-principle approval from BSE Limited for its proposed bonus equity share issue. The company plans to issue up to 38,55,222 shares, allotting one new share for every one existing share held, in compliance with SEBI regulations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pearl Global Surges on Strong Earnings, ICRA Upgrades Rating to A+</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Pearl-Global-Surges-on-Strong-Earnings-ICRA-Upgrades-Rating-to-A/6985f526e769d12df1d78d12</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Pearl-Global-Surges-on-Strong-Earnings-ICRA-Upgrades-Rating-to-A/6985f526e769d12df1d78d12</guid><description>Pearl Global Industries Limited (PGIL) reported a significant jump in its Q3 and 9M FY26 financial results, with consolidated revenue up 13.2% YoY for 9M FY26 to INR 3,711 crore and PAT rising 14.0% YoY to INR 189 crore. Q3 FY26 saw revenue climb 14.4% YoY to INR 1,170 crore, with PAT growing 6.8% YoY to INR 52 crore. The company's credit profile was bolstered by an upgrade from ICRA to A+ (Stable), reflecting enhanced financial health. Management is optimistic, citing expected benefits from reduced US tariffs and favorable India-EU/UK Free Trade Agreements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:05:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985f526e769d12df1d78d11_1770386967265.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godawari Power Expands into Logistics, Invests in BESS Amidst Revenue Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Expands-into-Logistics-Invests-in-BESS-Amidst-Revenue-Dip/6985f4fce769d12df1d78c53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Expands-into-Logistics-Invests-in-BESS-Amidst-Revenue-Dip/6985f4fce769d12df1d78c53</guid><description>Godawari Power and Ispat (GPIL) board approved un-audited financial results for Q3 FY26. Standalone PAT rose 9.42% YoY to ₹148.54 Cr on reduced expenses and higher other income, despite a 7.65% YoY revenue dip. However, consolidated PAT fell 4.27% YoY. Key strategic approvals include a ₹120 Cr railway wagon purchase, diversification into logistics, divestment of associate Ardent Steels for ₹90.87 Cr, and a ₹200 Cr investment in a Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) plant via its subsidiary GNEPL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:04:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985f4fce769d12df1d78c52_1770387128246.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sastasundar Ventures Posts Profit Turnaround on Exceptional Items, Faces Subsidiary Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sastasundar-Ventures-Posts-Profit-Turnaround-on-Exceptional-Items-Faces-Subsidiary-Concerns/6985f471e769d12df1d78909</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sastasundar-Ventures-Posts-Profit-Turnaround-on-Exceptional-Items-Faces-Subsidiary-Concerns/6985f471e769d12df1d78909</guid><description>Sastasundar Ventures Limited reported a consolidated net profit of ₹35.87 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, a stark turnaround from losses in the prior year, fueled by a significant positive swing in exceptional items. Consolidated revenue grew 23% YoY to ₹34,573.70 Lakhs. However, the standalone entity reported widened net losses, and a material uncertainty concerning the going concern status of a step-down subsidiary, Genu Path Labs Limited, was highlighted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:02:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985f471e769d12df1d78908_1770386795275.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Premier Ltd Faces Insolvency as Auditors Flag Going Concern Doubts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Premier-Ltd-Faces-Insolvency-as-Auditors-Flag-Going-Concern-Doubts/6985f350e769d12df1d77fe5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Premier-Ltd-Faces-Insolvency-as-Auditors-Flag-Going-Concern-Doubts/6985f350e769d12df1d77fe5</guid><description>Premier Limited, under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), reported a consolidated net loss of ₹175 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, with operations suspended due to lack of working capital. Auditors issued a qualified review report, highlighting erosion of net worth, material uncertainty about the company's ability to continue as a going concern, and significant compliance violations. The company's future hinges on NCLT approval of a resolution plan.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:57:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985f350e769d12df1d77fe4_1770386670191.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godawari Power Posts Mixed Results, Eyes Logistics Expansion and BESS Investment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Posts-Mixed-Results-Eyes-Logistics-Expansion-and-BESS-Investment/6985f2f2e769d12df1d77afa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Posts-Mixed-Results-Eyes-Logistics-Expansion-and-BESS-Investment/6985f2f2e769d12df1d77afa</guid><description>Godawari Power and Ispat Limited reported mixed financial results for Q3 FY26. Standalone revenue fell 8.57% YoY to ₹1,001.47 Cr, with net profit down 40.21% to ₹148.54 Cr. Consolidated revenue dropped 12.19% to ₹1,139.45 Cr, though net profit rose 3.60% to ₹145.04 Cr. The company approved purchasing 40 railway wagons for ₹120 Cr, is divesting its stake in Ardent Steels for ₹90.87 Cr, and plans a ₹200 Cr investment in a BESS plant. A new pellet plant was also commissioned.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:56:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985f2f2e769d12df1d77af9_1770386323811.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Hits Record 9-Month Performance, Eyes Critical Minerals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindustan-Copper-Hits-Record-9-Month-Performance-Eyes-Critical-Minerals/6985f295e769d12df1d7771f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindustan-Copper-Hits-Record-9-Month-Performance-Eyes-Critical-Minerals/6985f295e769d12df1d7771f</guid><description>Hindustan Copper Limited (HCL) announced its strongest-ever financial performance for the nine months ending December 31, 2025. Revenue surged 43% year-on-year to ₹1921.84 crore, while Profit After Tax (PAT) jumped 71% to ₹474.27 crore. EBITDA margins improved to over 40%. The company declared an interim dividend of Re 1 per share and signaled strategic entry into the critical minerals sector to support India's technology advancements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:54:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985f295e769d12df1d7771e_1770386529740.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Everest Industries Q3 Loss Surges 167% on Sharp Revenue Decline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Everest-Industries-Q3-Loss-Surges-167percent-on-Sharp-Revenue-Decline/6985f1dce769d12df1d771ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Everest-Industries-Q3-Loss-Surges-167percent-on-Sharp-Revenue-Decline/6985f1dce769d12df1d771ed</guid><description>Everest Industries reported a stark financial deterioration for Q3 FY26, with standalone revenue plunging 26.84% YoY to ₹268.83 crore and net loss widening significantly to ₹317.24 crore. Consolidated figures mirrored this trend, showing a 23.74% revenue drop and a net loss of ₹379.78 crore. The nine-month performance also saw significant revenue declines and surging losses, exacerbated by a ₹132.96 crore exceptional charge for gratuity under new Labour Codes. The company provided no forward-looking guidance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pearl Global Q3 Revenue Jumps 14.4%, FTAs Fuel Bright Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pearl-Global-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-144percent-FTAs-Fuel-Bright-Outlook/6985f148e769d12df1d76d6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pearl-Global-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-144percent-FTAs-Fuel-Bright-Outlook/6985f148e769d12df1d76d6b</guid><description>Pearl Global Industries reported a strong Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue climbing 14.4% year-on-year to ₹1,170 crore and 9MFY26 revenue growing 13.2% to ₹3,711 crore. Adjusted EBITDA saw a robust 14.0% jump in 9MFY26. The company anticipates significant growth driven by strategic advantages from evolving trade agreements like India-UK FTA and reduced US tariffs, alongside capacity expansions in Bangladesh. A credit rating upgrade to [ICRA] A+ underscores this positive trajectory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:48:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985f148e769d12df1d76d6a_1770386159817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nitin Spinners: Q3 Profit Dips Marginally, Eyes Recovery with Major Capex Plan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Nitin-Spinners-Q3-Profit-Dips-Marginally-Eyes-Recovery-with-Major-Capex-Plan/6985f0fbe769d12df1d76942</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Nitin-Spinners-Q3-Profit-Dips-Marginally-Eyes-Recovery-with-Major-Capex-Plan/6985f0fbe769d12df1d76942</guid><description>Nitin Spinners Limited reported a mixed Q3 FY'26 performance. Revenue dipped 4.5% YoY to INR 800.68 Cr but grew 5.3% QoQ. PAT saw a marginal 0.8% YoY decline to INR 44.41 Cr, yet rose 27.7% QoQ. The company is embarking on a significant INR 1,120 Cr expansion and a INR 230 Cr solar power project, aiming to boost future growth and efficiency amidst positive long-term textile sector outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:47:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985f0fbe769d12df1d76941_1770385992015.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KIMS Boosts Sunshine Hospital Stake with ₹100 Cr Investment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/KIMS-Boosts-Sunshine-Hospital-Stake-with-100-Cr-Investment/6985f090e769d12df1d7649c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/KIMS-Boosts-Sunshine-Hospital-Stake-with-100-Cr-Investment/6985f090e769d12df1d7649c</guid><description>Krishna Institute of Medical Sciences Limited (KIMS) has approved a strategic plan to invest up to ₹100 Crores in its material subsidiary, Sarvejana Healthcare Private Limited (Sunshine Hospital). This move aims to enhance KIMS's shareholding in Sunshine Hospital, which reported a robust turnover of ₹597.00 Cr in FY25, up from ₹464.20 Cr in FY24. The board also approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 and 9 months ended December 31st, 2025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blackstone's Aadhar Housing Offer Sees Zero Bids on Feb 6</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Blackstones-Aadhar-Housing-Offer-Sees-Zero-Bids-on-Feb-6/6985eff0e769d12df1d75ff3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Blackstones-Aadhar-Housing-Offer-Sees-Zero-Bids-on-Feb-6/6985eff0e769d12df1d75ff3</guid><description>JM Financial disclosed that zero equity shares were tendered into the Aadhar Housing Finance open offer on February 6, 2026. This represents a complete absence of participation from public shareholders, raising immediate questions about the offer's attractiveness and the potential success of the acquisition by Blackstone-linked entities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SEBI Penalizes 17 in Unison Metals Stock Scam, Bans Market Access</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Penalizes-17-in-Unison-Metals-Stock-Scam-Bans-Market-Access/6985ef73e769d12df1d75b22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Penalizes-17-in-Unison-Metals-Stock-Scam-Bans-Market-Access/6985ef73e769d12df1d75b22</guid><description>SEBI has finalized its probe into Unison Metals Ltd., penalizing 17 individuals and entities for a stock manipulation scheme. The regulator imposed market bans for 1-3 years and ordered disgorgement of ₹3.87 crore, plus ₹1.37 crore in penalties, totaling over ₹5.24 crore. The fraudulent practice involved using Telegram channels to inflate stock prices and offload shares, violating market integrity rules.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sastasundar Ventures Reports Consolidated Profit Turnaround, Standalone Operations Lag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sastasundar-Ventures-Reports-Consolidated-Profit-Turnaround-Standalone-Operations-Lag/6985eeefe769d12df1d7569a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sastasundar-Ventures-Reports-Consolidated-Profit-Turnaround-Standalone-Operations-Lag/6985eeefe769d12df1d7569a</guid><description>Sastasundar Ventures achieved a significant consolidated profit turnaround in Q3 FY26, posting ₹35.87 Lakhs net profit against a prior year loss, driven by a 22.9% YoY revenue jump. However, standalone operations continued to report net losses, though narrowed to ₹10.49 Lakhs. Key subsidiary actions, including a ₹10,000 Lakhs buy-back by Sastasundar Healthbuddy Limited, influenced consolidated results, while concerns persist over Genu Path Labs' going concern status.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Ltd Faces Insolvency, Q3 Losses Mount Amid Audit Red Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premier-Ltd-Faces-Insolvency-Q3-Losses-Mount-Amid-Audit-Red-Flags/6985ee6ee769d12df1d75254</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premier-Ltd-Faces-Insolvency-Q3-Losses-Mount-Amid-Audit-Red-Flags/6985ee6ee769d12df1d75254</guid><description>Premier Limited remains in severe financial distress, reporting a Net Loss of Rs 175 Lakhs for Q3 FY26 and Rs 411 Lakhs for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, with its net worth completely eroded. Manufacturing operations are suspended due to a lack of working capital. Statutory auditors issued a qualified limited review report, highlighting material uncertainty about the company's ability to continue as a going concern and raising concerns about asset impairment and expense verification. The company's future is contingent on NCLT approval of a resolution plan.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:36:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985ee6ee769d12df1d75253_1770385373747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prime Fresh Surges 37% Revenue; Unveils Vision 2031 Expansion Plan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Prime-Fresh-Surges-37percent-Revenue-Unveils-Vision-2031-Expansion-Plan/6985edeae769d12df1d74dbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Prime-Fresh-Surges-37percent-Revenue-Unveils-Vision-2031-Expansion-Plan/6985edeae769d12df1d74dbb</guid><description>Prime Fresh Limited posted a robust Q3FY26 with revenue up 37% YoY to ₹743 Mn and PAT soaring 156% YoY to ₹47 Mn, driven by significant volume growth. The company also outlined its long-term 'Vision 2031' strategy, focusing on premium, organic, and value-added segments, alongside a major greenfield expansion in Nashik, Maharashtra. This marks a strategic shift towards enhanced margins and diversified product offerings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ram Ratna Wires Posts Strong Q3 Growth, But 9-Month Profit Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ram-Ratna-Wires-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-But-9-Month-Profit-Dips/6985edc7e769d12df1d74c48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ram-Ratna-Wires-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-But-9-Month-Profit-Dips/6985edc7e769d12df1d74c48</guid><description>Ram Ratna Wires Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 results with standalone revenue up 42.1% YoY to ₹1,24,961.76 Lakhs and consolidated revenue at ₹1,27,793.64 Lakhs (+43.7% YoY). Standalone Profit Before Tax (PBT) surged 84.5% YoY. However, consolidated profit for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, saw a marginal decrease to ₹6,936.86 Lakhs from ₹7,020.37 Lakhs in the prior year. The company also announced the appointment of Shri Iqbal Singh Saggu as the new CFO, effective April 1, 2026, replacing Shri Rajeev Maheshwari.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sudeep Pharma Posts 49% Revenue Jump on Acquisition, Lists Successfully</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Sudeep-Pharma-Posts-49percent-Revenue-Jump-on-Acquisition-Lists-Successfully/6985ed02e769d12df1d74072</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Sudeep-Pharma-Posts-49percent-Revenue-Jump-on-Acquisition-Lists-Successfully/6985ed02e769d12df1d74072</guid><description>Sudeep Pharma Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue soaring 49.15% year-on-year to ₹17,233.56 Lakhs, boosted by the acquisition of Nutrition Supplies &amp; Services (Ireland) Limited. Consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) surged 66.13% to ₹4,769.91 Lakhs, and diluted EPS rose to ₹4.29. Standalone PAT also grew 30.21% YoY. The company successfully completed its IPO in November 2025, listing on NSE and BSE, with ₹7,581.40 Lakhs of net proceeds remaining unutilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:30:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985ed02e769d12df1d74071_1770385046504.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Shields Digital Finance Trust With Fraud Payouts, Sales Rules</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/RBI/RBI-Shields-Digital-Finance-Trust-With-Fraud-Payouts-Sales-Rules/6985ecbbe769d12df1d73edd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/RBI/RBI-Shields-Digital-Finance-Trust-With-Fraud-Payouts-Sales-Rules/6985ecbbe769d12df1d73edd</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India will compensate victims of small-value digital fraud up to ₹25,000, covering 85% of losses for a first-time, unintended fraud. This initiative aims to stabilize consumer trust amidst rising digital transaction volumes and increasing fraud incidents. Concurrently, the RBI is introducing stringent guidelines to curb mis-selling of financial products and harmonize loan recovery practices, targeting product suitability, customer consent, and fair conduct across the banking system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Anand Rathi Faces Rs 13 Cr Fraud Probe, IT Vulnerability Under Fire</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Anand-Rathi-Faces-Rs-13-Cr-Fraud-Probe-IT-Vulnerability-Under-Fire/6985ec85e769d12df1d73cfd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Anand-Rathi-Faces-Rs-13-Cr-Fraud-Probe-IT-Vulnerability-Under-Fire/6985ec85e769d12df1d73cfd</guid><description>Anand Rathi Share and Stock Brokers reported a suspected Rs 13 crore fraud involving off-market share transfers from a client's demat account. The incident, occurring February 6, implicates unidentified individuals and certain IT employees in document fabrication and cheating, separate from the firm's broking arm. The company is initiating legal action, including an FIR, and bolstering internal controls to prevent recurrence, sparking scrutiny over its operational integrity and IT safeguards.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>