<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:55:00 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Textile Stocks Tumble on Export Incentive Cuts Amid EU Trade Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Textile-Stocks-Tumble-on-Export-Incentive-Cuts-Amid-EU-Trade-Hopes/699d456504a25a58c84e993d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Textile-Stocks-Tumble-on-Export-Incentive-Cuts-Amid-EU-Trade-Hopes/699d456504a25a58c84e993d</guid><description>Shares of major Indian textile manufacturers like Gokaldas Exports, Arvind, Trident, and Pearl Global Industries experienced significant declines today, following the government's decision to halve benefits under the Remission of Duties and Taxes on Exported Products (RoDTEP) scheme. This policy shift, effective immediately, is projected to increase export costs by 1-2%, impacting profitability. The move comes despite optimistic projections for the sector driven by the recently concluded India-European Union Free Trade Agreement (FTA), which promises tariff-free access to the EU market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:29:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d456504a25a58c84e993c_1771915188623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KEC International: Data Centers Spark Growth Amidst Water Segment Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Data-Centers-Spark-Growth-Amidst-Water-Segment-Woes/699d44bd04a25a58c84e9815</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Data-Centers-Spark-Growth-Amidst-Water-Segment-Woes/699d44bd04a25a58c84e9815</guid><description>KEC International aims for ₹1,000 crore annual revenue from data center civil works within two years, leveraging successful project execution and a robust bidding pipeline. The company forecasts substantial order book growth to over ₹25,000 crore for FY26 and expects FY27 inflows above ₹30,000 crore, aligning with India's infrastructure expansion. However, the water segment remains a drag with ₹800-900 crore in receivables and persistent execution challenges, compounded by labor shortages. Despite these headwinds, analysts maintain a 'Strong Buy' consensus with an average price target suggesting significant upside.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:27:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d44bd04a25a58c84e9814_1771914589828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shilpa Medicare Stock Dips Despite LatAm Biosimilar Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Shilpa-Medicare-Stock-Dips-Despite-LatAm-Biosimilar-Deal/699d44b804a25a58c84e97fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Shilpa-Medicare-Stock-Dips-Despite-LatAm-Biosimilar-Deal/699d44b804a25a58c84e97fe</guid><description>Shilpa Medicare Ltd's subsidiary, Shilpa Biologicals Pvt. Ltd., has secured an exclusive licensing agreement with SteinCares to commercialize a biosimilar across Latin America. The deal positions Shilpa Biologicals for product development and long-term manufacturing, marking its entry into a new regional market. Despite this strategic expansion and a generally optimistic analyst outlook, Shilpa Medicare's stock saw a fractional decline, suggesting market skepticism or the prioritization of other factors over territorial gains.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:27:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d44b804a25a58c84e97fd_1771914943838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank: Fraud Hits Stock, But Proactive Disclosure Cautions Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Hits-Stock-But-Proactive-Disclosure-Cautions-Investors/699d446104a25a58c84e9700</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Hits-Stock-But-Proactive-Disclosure-Cautions-Investors/699d446104a25a58c84e9700</guid><description>IDFC First Bank disclosed INR 5.9 billion in fraudulent withdrawals from Haryana state government accounts, leading to a 16% stock drop. While KPMG investigates, analysts noted the incident's isolated nature and potential for recovery, though near-term PBT could fall 56%. Despite this, the bank's proactive disclosure and existing capital buffers mitigate systemic risk, prompting a range of analyst ratings from Neutral to Add with revised price targets, focusing on long-term potential amidst evolving governance scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:25:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d446104a25a58c84e96ff_1771914602563.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Clean Max IPO: Institutional Bets on Debt Cut Amidst Retail Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Clean-Max-IPO-Institutional-Bets-on-Debt-Cut-Amidst-Retail-Caution/699d444c04a25a58c84e96d9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Clean-Max-IPO-Institutional-Bets-on-Debt-Cut-Amidst-Retail-Caution/699d444c04a25a58c84e96d9</guid><description>Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions' ₹3,100 crore IPO is experiencing a subscription dichotomy: Qualified Institutional Buyers (QIBs) fully committed, yet retail and Non-Institutional Investors (NIIs) show subdued interest. The company, a leader in commercial and industrial renewable energy, plans to use over 90% of its fresh issue proceeds to repay significant debt, a move critical for its leveraged balance sheet. Despite strong revenue growth and expanding EBITDA margins, the IPO's steep valuation and a nearly flat grey market premium (GMP) suggest muted listing expectations, prompting caution among discerning investors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:25:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d444c04a25a58c84e96d8_1771914450606.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PC Jeweller Bets on Chad Mining; Retail Strength Lags Cautious Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/PC-Jeweller-Bets-on-Chad-Mining-Retail-Strength-Lags-Cautious-Market/699d444704a25a58c84e96c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/PC-Jeweller-Bets-on-Chad-Mining-Retail-Strength-Lags-Cautious-Market/699d444704a25a58c84e96c2</guid><description>PC Jeweller is diversifying into mining via a new entity, PCJ Mining SARL, in the Republic of Chad, a significant strategic pivot. This move complements a strong Q3 FY26 performance, which saw standalone revenue jump 37% year-on-year to ₹875 crore, driven by festive and wedding season demand. Despite the core business resilience and improved financial health, the market's response to the international mining venture is cautious, reflecting the inherent risks and execution challenges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:25:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d444704a25a58c84e96c1_1771914425211.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indoco Remedies Gets USFDA Nod for Brivaracetam Oral Solution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indoco-Remedies-Gets-USFDA-Nod-for-Brivaracetam-Oral-Solution/699d437404a25a58c84e95a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indoco-Remedies-Gets-USFDA-Nod-for-Brivaracetam-Oral-Solution/699d437404a25a58c84e95a3</guid><description>Indoco Remedies Limited secured final USFDA approval for its Brivaracetam Oral Solution on February 24, 2026. This greenlights the marketing of a generic version of UCB Inc.'s Briviact, an antiepileptic drug, in the US. Manufactured at its Goa facility, this approval strengthens Indoco's regulated market presence and commitment to accessible healthcare globally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:21:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d437404a25a58c84e95a2_1771914167807.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Israel Defense Ties Deepen for Tech Autonomy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Israel-Defense-Ties-Deepen-for-Tech-Autonomy/699d42f204a25a58c84e94b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Israel-Defense-Ties-Deepen-for-Tech-Autonomy/699d42f204a25a58c84e94b8</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi's visit to Israel marks a strategic acceleration in defense and technology cooperation, prioritizing joint development of advanced systems and AI. This move significantly bolsters India's 'Atmanirbhar Bharat' (self-reliant India) agenda, aiming to foster indigenous manufacturing and technological independence. While India diversifies its defense partnerships away from historical reliance on Russia, Israel emerges as a critical enabler for high-tech capabilities, embedding advanced Israeli systems into Indian platforms and exploring collaborative R&amp;D. This collaboration addresses India's modernization needs while navigating complex geopolitical dynamics and enhancing its strategic autonomy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:19:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d42f204a25a58c84e94b7_1771914080645.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Surges Amidst Tariff Chaos and Economic Crosscurrents</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-Amidst-Tariff-Chaos-and-Economic-Crosscurrents/699d417a04a25a58c84e938b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-Amidst-Tariff-Chaos-and-Economic-Crosscurrents/699d417a04a25a58c84e938b</guid><description>Gold prices advanced significantly, breaching $5182, driven by escalating policy uncertainty following a Supreme Court ruling that nullified existing tariffs. This decision prompted the administration to announce new, temporary tariffs under a less-used trade provision, casting a shadow over the US economic outlook. The precious metal benefits from a weaker US dollar and ongoing geopolitical risks, while mixed economic data points to persistent inflation challenges and slowing growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:13:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d417a04a25a58c84e938a_1771913904907.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sejal Glass Targets ₹400 Cr FY26 Revenue; New Products Drive Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sejal-Glass-Targets-400-Cr-FY26-Revenue-New-Products-Drive-Growth/699d3f1804a25a58c84e9210</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sejal-Glass-Targets-400-Cr-FY26-Revenue-New-Products-Drive-Growth/699d3f1804a25a58c84e9210</guid><description>Sejal Glass aims for ₹400 crore revenue in FY26 and 25% growth thereafter, banking on new high-value product segments like fire-rated and bulletproof glass. The company reported consolidated income of ₹284.51 crore for the nine months ended December 2025, with ongoing integration of its Glasstech acquisition and plans for another potential acquisition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:03:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3f1804a25a58c84e920f_1771913094014.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABB India's Order Surge Meets Valuation Hurdles Amidst Mixed Analyst Views</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-Indias-Order-Surge-Meets-Valuation-Hurdles-Amidst-Mixed-Analyst-Views/699d3d7804a25a58c84e8f94</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-Indias-Order-Surge-Meets-Valuation-Hurdles-Amidst-Mixed-Analyst-Views/699d3d7804a25a58c84e8f94</guid><description>ABB India reported a robust 52% year-over-year surge in order inflows for Q4CY25, driven by emerging sectors like renewables and data centers. Motilal Oswal initiated a 'Buy' rating with a INR 6,600 target, citing an end to earnings cuts and expected margin improvements. However, the company's high trailing Price-to-Earnings (P/E) ratio of approximately 72-76x, significantly above industry averages and some peers, contrasts with a 'Hold' consensus from other analysts and lower price targets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:56:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3d7804a25a58c84e8f93_1771912735266.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fears &amp; Macro Shocks Trigger Crypto Selloff</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fears-and-Macro-Shocks-Trigger-Crypto-Selloff/699d3d7104a25a58c84e8f60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fears-and-Macro-Shocks-Trigger-Crypto-Selloff/699d3d7104a25a58c84e8f60</guid><description>Cryptocurrencies are experiencing significant weekly losses, with Bitcoin trading within a tight $60k-$70k range and altcoins underperforming severely. This downturn is amplified by emerging "AI scare trade" anxieties impacting risk assets, alongside broader macroeconomic headwinds. Sell-side pressure among altcoins is at five-year highs, indicating holders are distributing positions, while buyers remain scarce. Technical indicators suggest a bearish outlook, with a potential for further downside.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:56:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3d7104a25a58c84e8f5f_1771913356587.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Home First Finance: Tech Edge vs. Credit Cost Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Home-First-Finance-Tech-Edge-vs-Credit-Cost-Headwinds/699d3d5004a25a58c84e8efa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Home-First-Finance-Tech-Edge-vs-Credit-Cost-Headwinds/699d3d5004a25a58c84e8efa</guid><description>Prabhudas Lilladher initiated coverage on Home First Finance Company India (HOMEFIRS) with a 'BUY' rating and a price target of ₹1,375. The brokerage highlights the company's technology-driven model and robust AUM growth projections. However, concerns persist regarding elevated credit costs in the MFI/MSME segment and a valuation premium compared to some peers, despite a recent stock correction. The company's recent QIP and strong capital adequacy provide a buffer, but sustainability of growth amidst evolving sector dynamics warrants scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:55:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3d5004a25a58c84e8ef9_1771912833922.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Stalls Post-SCOTUS Ruling Amid Lingering US Trade Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Stalls-Post-SCOTUS-Ruling-Amid-Lingering-US-Trade-Uncertainty/699d3d0604a25a58c84e8e44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Stalls-Post-SCOTUS-Ruling-Amid-Lingering-US-Trade-Uncertainty/699d3d0604a25a58c84e8e44</guid><description>The Indian Rupee faces headwinds as a US Supreme Court ruling invalidating Trump-era tariffs introduces renewed policy uncertainty. Despite immediate dollar weakness and a potential drop in India's effective tariff rate to 11-13%, the currency remains under pressure. Persistent foreign investor outflows in early 2026 and the US administration's pivot to alternative tariff mechanisms underscore ongoing volatility, overshadowing short-term relief and limiting sustained rupee appreciation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:54:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3d0604a25a58c84e8e43_1771912660066.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NPS Tier I Funds Show Wide Return Gaps, Manager Consistency Lacking</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NPS-Tier-I-Funds-Show-Wide-Return-Gaps-Manager-Consistency-Lacking/699d3cf404a25a58c84e8dcd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NPS-Tier-I-Funds-Show-Wide-Return-Gaps-Manager-Consistency-Lacking/699d3cf404a25a58c84e8dcd</guid><description>National Pension System (NPS) Tier I returns as of February 20, 2026, present a bifurcated picture. Equity funds achieved strong gains, peaking at 17.38 percent, while corporate bonds yielded 8.63 percent and government bonds 8.88 percent. Crucially, performance varied sharply among the ten available pension fund managers, with no single entity consistently leading across all asset classes and tenures, indicating a challenging environment for identifying perennial top performers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:53:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3cf404a25a58c84e8dcc_1771912699860.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nexome Capital Markets ₹22.04 Cr Rights Issue Approved at ₹75/Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nexome-Capital-Markets-2204-Cr-Rights-Issue-Approved-at-75Share/699d3cb604a25a58c84e8d28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nexome-Capital-Markets-2204-Cr-Rights-Issue-Approved-at-75Share/699d3cb604a25a58c84e8d28</guid><description>Nexome Capital Markets has received board approval for a ₹22.04 crore rights issue, offering 29,38,500 shares at ₹75 each. The record date is March 5, 2026. This capital infusion comes amidst recent financial headwinds and a significant decline in revenue and profitability, potentially leading to shareholder dilution upon successful completion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:52:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3cb604a25a58c84e8d27_1771912485159.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Navigates Profit-Taking Amid Geopolitical Storm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Navigates-Profit-Taking-Amid-Geopolitical-Storm/699d3bf904a25a58c84e8b70</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Navigates-Profit-Taking-Amid-Geopolitical-Storm/699d3bf904a25a58c84e8b70</guid><description>Gold prices in India experienced a slight pullback on February 24, 2026, with 24K gold trading at ₹160,800 per 10 grams. This movement reflects a delicate balance between investor profit-taking and a strengthening US dollar, which historically weighs on the precious metal. However, underlying geopolitical uncertainties and the complex Federal Reserve rate outlook continue to provide a robust floor, preventing steeper declines and underscoring gold's role as a safe-haven asset amidst global instability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:49:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3bf904a25a58c84e8b6f_1771912912732.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IBM Plunges 13% on AI COBOL Threat; Market Reassesses Legacy Systems</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IBM-Plunges-13percent-on-AI-COBOL-Threat-Market-Reassesses-Legacy-Systems/699d3bab04a25a58c84e8ac6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IBM-Plunges-13percent-on-AI-COBOL-Threat-Market-Reassesses-Legacy-Systems/699d3bab04a25a58c84e8ac6</guid><description>International Business Machines (IBM) experienced a sharp 13.15% stock decline on February 23, 2026, wiping out over $31 billion in market value. The sell-off was triggered by AI research firm Anthropic's announcement of a tool capable of automating COBOL software modernization, directly challenging IBM's lucrative mainframe and consulting business. Despite this significant market reaction, IBM's recent financial reports indicate strong operational performance, creating a valuation dichotomy for investors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:48:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3bab04a25a58c84e8ac5_1771912641781.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MOFSL's Bullish Call: Six Indian Stocks With Upside Potential</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/MOFSLs-Bullish-Call-Six-Indian-Stocks-With-Upside-Potential/699d3b9e04a25a58c84e8aae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/MOFSLs-Bullish-Call-Six-Indian-Stocks-With-Upside-Potential/699d3b9e04a25a58c84e8aae</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services (MOFSL) maintains a 'Buy' stance on six Indian companies across technology, auto, consumer, and industrial sectors, projecting significant upside from robust domestic demand and company-specific growth drivers like AI adoption, EV push, and international expansion. However, a deeper analysis reveals varying sector headwinds, competitive pressures, and cautionary analyst sentiment, particularly for IT stocks facing AI-induced disruption risks. While some firms exhibit strong fundamentals, others trade at stretched valuations, necessitating a balanced risk assessment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:48:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3b9e04a25a58c84e8aad_1771912220225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Suzlon's Renewable Pivot: New CEO Faces Steep Climb</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Suzlons-Renewable-Pivot-New-CEO-Faces-Steep-Climb/699d3b5a04a25a58c84e8a61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Suzlons-Renewable-Pivot-New-CEO-Faces-Steep-Climb/699d3b5a04a25a58c84e8a61</guid><description>Suzlon Energy appointed Ajay Kapur as Group CEO as part of its 'Suzlon 2.0' strategy to become a full-stack renewable solutions provider. While the company shows signs of financial recovery and sector tailwinds, Kapur inherits challenges including intense competition, past execution risks, and a complex transition from traditional industries. The company's market position and recent analyst upgrades are tempered by the need for successful strategic execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3b5a04a25a58c84e8a60_1771912399845.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India GDP Surge Meets Forecast Divergence: Banks Navigate Credit-Deposit Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Surge-Meets-Forecast-Divergence-Banks-Navigate-Credit-Deposit-Gap/699d3b0204a25a58c84e899c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Surge-Meets-Forecast-Divergence-Banks-Navigate-Credit-Deposit-Gap/699d3b0204a25a58c84e899c</guid><description>India's economy is poised for robust Q3 FY26 growth, potentially exceeding 8.1%, fueled by strong consumption. However, forecasts vary significantly, and a new GDP base year introduces revision uncertainty. Public sector banks reported stronger profit growth than private counterparts. Concurrently, the banking sector's credit-to-deposit ratio has hit record highs, signaling potential liquidity pressures amidst robust credit demand.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:45:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d3b0204a25a58c84e899b_1771912226615.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stripe, PayPal Back Xflow's AI-Driven Assault on India's B2B Payment Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Stripe-PayPal-Back-Xflows-AI-Driven-Assault-on-Indias-B2B-Payment-Gap/699d391204a25a58c84e8828</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Stripe-PayPal-Back-Xflows-AI-Driven-Assault-on-Indias-B2B-Payment-Gap/699d391204a25a58c84e8828</guid><description>Indian fintech Xflow has secured $16.6 million in a Series A funding round led by General Catalyst, with strategic participation from major players like Stripe and PayPal Ventures. This capital infusion, valuing the company at $85 million post-investment, will fuel Xflow's mission to streamline complex cross-border B2B payments for Indian businesses. Leveraging AI for foreign exchange optimization and an API-first approach, Xflow targets a market rife with bank-dominated inefficiencies and aims for greater transparency and speed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:37:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d391204a25a58c84e8827_1771912308563.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pharma Sector: US Slowdown, gRevlimid Patent Loss Hit Earnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-Sector-US-Slowdown-gRevlimid-Patent-Loss-Hit-Earnings/699d372604a25a58c84e865f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-Sector-US-Slowdown-gRevlimid-Patent-Loss-Hit-Earnings/699d372604a25a58c84e865f</guid><description>Aggregate revenue for covered Indian pharmaceutical firms rose 11.6% in Q3 FY26, largely driven by a 12.1% surge in domestic sales. However, US market growth was a mere 1.4% on a constant currency basis, potentially boosted by currency tailwinds. The loss of gRevlimid patent exclusivity in January 2026 is projected to impact growth and margins for exposed companies. Reflecting these pressures, ICICI Securities revised FY27 earnings per share downwards by up to 49% for 13 out of 24 covered entities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:29:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d372604a25a58c84e865e_1771911357799.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KSH International Rating Upgraded to 'A' by CARE; Revenue Nears ₹2000 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Rating-Upgraded-to-A-by-CARE-Revenue-Nears-2000-Cr/699d366f04a25a58c84e8535</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Rating-Upgraded-to-A-by-CARE-Revenue-Nears-2000-Cr/699d366f04a25a58c84e8535</guid><description>CARE Ratings has upgraded KSH International's long-term credit rating to 'A' from 'A-' with a 'Stable' outlook. The upgrade reflects significant improvements in operational scale and profitability for FY25 and the nine-month period ending FY26. Key drivers include a strengthened capital structure post-IPO and successful commissioning of the Supa greenfield project. The agency expects sustained revenue growth and profitability due to enhanced capacity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:26:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d366f04a25a58c84e8534_1771910868684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pace Digitek Rallies on RIL Order Amid Margin Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pace-Digitek-Rallies-on-RIL-Order-Amid-Margin-Concerns/699d364804a25a58c84e84b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pace-Digitek-Rallies-on-RIL-Order-Amid-Margin-Concerns/699d364804a25a58c84e84b6</guid><description>Pace Digitek's stock surged over 4% following a substantial ₹158.71 crore purchase order from Reliance Industries for lithium-ion battery packs. The company's subsidiary, Lineage Power, secured this deal for delivery by August 2026. However, recent quarterly results reveal expenses are outpacing revenue growth, signaling potential margin compression. This order comes as Pace Digitek faces scrutiny over its working capital management and accounts receivable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:25:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d364804a25a58c84e84b5_1771911200196.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Credent Global Finance Equity Boosted By Minerva Ventures' 6.51% QIP Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Credent-Global-Finance-Equity-Boosted-By-Minerva-Ventures-651percent-QIP-Acquisition/699d363104a25a58c84e848c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Credent-Global-Finance-Equity-Boosted-By-Minerva-Ventures-651percent-QIP-Acquisition/699d363104a25a58c84e848c</guid><description>Minerva Ventures Fund has acquired a 6.51% stake in Credent Global Finance Limited, purchasing 4,000,000 shares through a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) on February 19, 2026. This transaction increases the company's total equity share capital and voting capital. The move signals institutional confidence and expands the company's capital base.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:25:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d363104a25a58c84e848b_1771910840533.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Plunges Below $63K Amid Tariff Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Plunges-Below-63K-Amid-Tariff-Jitters/699d355904a25a58c84e835b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Plunges-Below-63K-Amid-Tariff-Jitters/699d355904a25a58c84e835b</guid><description>Bitcoin's price has fallen below $63,000, extending its weekly decline amid heightened global trade uncertainty stemming from President Trump's tariff escalations. The cryptocurrency's slide is compounded by a sell-off in AI-focused stocks, signaling a broader risk-off sentiment. Key support at $60,000 is under intense scrutiny, with analysts warning of potential declines into the $50,000 range should this level falter. This downturn occurs against a backdrop of shifting macroeconomics, with gold showing strength as a traditional safe haven.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:21:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d355904a25a58c84e835a_1771910912183.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABB India: High P/E Meets Margin Squeeze Amidst Capex Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-India-High-PE-Meets-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Capex-Hopes/699d34cc04a25a58c84e82a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-India-High-PE-Meets-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Capex-Hopes/699d34cc04a25a58c84e82a3</guid><description>ABB India's Q4CY25 saw revenue rise 5.7% YoY, but margins contracted significantly due to commodity inflation. Despite a strong order pipeline and guidance for double-digit CY26 growth, the company trades at a P/E of ~75x, far exceeding industry peers and the broader sector average. Analyst sentiment is bifurcated, with several rating the stock 'Neutral' or 'Hold' and some price targets suggesting downside, casting doubt on the sustainability of its premium valuation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:19:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d34cc04a25a58c84e82a2_1771910475977.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T Bags ₹1000-2500 Cr Order for LIGO India Observatory</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-Bags-1000-2500-Cr-Order-for-LIGO-India-Observatory/699d31fe04a25a58c84e80b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-Bags-1000-2500-Cr-Order-for-LIGO-India-Observatory/699d31fe04a25a58c84e80b0</guid><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro's Heavy Civil Infrastructure and Heavy Engineering verticals have secured a significant order valued between ₹1,000-2,500 crore to establish India's LIGO Observatory in Maharashtra. This project, part of the nation's 'Mega Science' initiative, involves complex civil infrastructure, an 8km beam tube, and advanced vacuum systems, with a 48-month completion deadline. The win underscores L&amp;T's expertise in large-scale, technologically advanced projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:07:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d31fe04a25a58c84e80af_1771911589160.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brahmaputra Infra JV L-1 for ₹397 Cr NH Project; Order Book Surpasses ₹1,500 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Brahmaputra-Infra-JV-L-1-for-397-Cr-NH-Project-Order-Book-Surpasses-1500-Cr/699d314404a25a58c84e7ffa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Brahmaputra-Infra-JV-L-1-for-397-Cr-NH-Project-Order-Book-Surpasses-1500-Cr/699d314404a25a58c84e7ffa</guid><description>Brahmaputra Infrastructure Ltd's joint venture has become the L-1 bidder for a significant national highway widening project in Rajasthan. The ₹397 Crore EPC contract for NH-458 will extend the company's execution presence and push its total order book, including joint operations, to approximately ₹1,500 Crores, signalling continued growth in its core civil infrastructure business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:04:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d314404a25a58c84e7ff9_1771909618986.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Base Metals Rally on Tariff Hopes Amidst Rising Inventories</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Base-Metals-Rally-on-Tariff-Hopes-Amidst-Rising-Inventories/699d2f0504a25a58c84e7d70</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Base-Metals-Rally-on-Tariff-Hopes-Amidst-Rising-Inventories/699d2f0504a25a58c84e7d70</guid><description>Global base metals, led by copper and aluminum, advanced sharply as China's markets reopened following the Lunar New Year. Investors reacted positively to signals that the U.S. may reduce tariffs on Chinese goods, a development estimated by Morgan Stanley to lower the average tariff rate. However, despite this speculative rally, exchange-monitored inventories of copper and nickel are at record highs for this time of year, indicating a disconnect between anticipated trade policy shifts and current physical demand. Analyst sentiment remains cautiously optimistic, anticipating a recovery in manufacturing demand, yet the build-up of stockpiles suggests potential headwinds for sustained price appreciation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:54:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d2f0504a25a58c84e7d6f_1771909191348.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's ITDC to Monetise Iconic Hotels Under NMP 2.0</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indias-ITDC-to-Monetise-Iconic-Hotels-Under-NMP-20/699d2ec904a25a58c84e7d10</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indias-ITDC-to-Monetise-Iconic-Hotels-Under-NMP-20/699d2ec904a25a58c84e7d10</guid><description>India Tourism Development Corporation (ITDC) is set to redevelop its flagship hotels, The Ashok and Hotel Samrat, under the National Monetisation Pipeline (NMP) 2.0. The government aims to raise ₹1,200 crore through a public-private partnership model, with The Ashok slated for FY27 and Hotel Samrat for FY30. This initiative aligns with NMP 2.0's broader goal of monetising ₹16.72 trillion in assets to fund infrastructure development.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:53:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d2ec904a25a58c84e7d0f_1771909503623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Morepen Labs: ₹825 Cr CDMO Deal Fuels Rally, But Execution is Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Morepen-Labs-825-Cr-CDMO-Deal-Fuels-Rally-But-Execution-is-Key/699d2eb804a25a58c84e7cf3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Morepen-Labs-825-Cr-CDMO-Deal-Fuels-Rally-But-Execution-is-Key/699d2eb804a25a58c84e7cf3</guid><description>Morepen Laboratories shares are trading higher after announcing an ₹825 crore multi-year CDMO contract with an undisclosed global pharmaceutical firm. The deal marks a significant expansion beyond its core API business, with execution planned through Q1 FY27. This follows a modest 3% year-on-year profit increase to ₹27.5 crore in Q3 FY26, on revenue growth of 6.9% to ₹484.16 crore. The stock's recent 34% monthly gain contrasts with the broader market's flat performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:53:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d2eb804a25a58c84e7cf2_1771909027289.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Market Divergence: Secondary Surge, Primary Pause</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Market-Divergence-Secondary-Surge-Primary-Pause/699d2c6104a25a58c84e7a59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Market-Divergence-Secondary-Surge-Primary-Pause/699d2c6104a25a58c84e7a59</guid><description>India's secondary market surged in January 2026, with equity cash turnover reaching ₹23.9 lakh crore, a 16-month peak. Exchange-traded funds and gold bonds saw substantial increases, fueled by global uncertainty and domestic price volatility. Conversely, primary market fundraising plummeted to a 21-month low, with IPO capital raised down 78% MoM and mixed listing debuts, reflecting a broader investor hesitancy and preference for liquid, safe-haven assets. Inflation remains within the RBI's target band, and the repo rate holds steady at 5.25%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:43:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d2c6104a25a58c84e7a58_1771909031886.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Seed Bill Tightens Grip on Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Seed-Bill-Tightens-Grip-on-Market/699d2bfc04a25a58c84e79ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Seed-Bill-Tightens-Grip-on-Market/699d2bfc04a25a58c84e79ca</guid><description>The Indian Parliament is set to debate a new Seeds Bill, replacing the 1966 Act with mandatory registration and steep penalties, including up to Rs 30 lakh fines and three years imprisonment for major offenses. This regulatory overhaul aims to formalize the Rs 40,000 crore market, address decades-old gaps, and potentially shift competitive advantages, impacting both public and private sector players. The move anticipates a more structured, compliant, and potentially innovative agricultural input sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:41:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d2bfc04a25a58c84e79c9_1771908377049.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reva's IPO: Margin Risk Looms in COCO Store Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Revas-IPO-Margin-Risk-Looms-in-COCO-Store-Shift/699d298b04a25a58c84e775b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Revas-IPO-Margin-Risk-Looms-in-COCO-Store-Shift/699d298b04a25a58c84e775b</guid><description>PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery's upcoming IPO is marked by a strategic shift from a cost-efficient shop-in-shop model to capital-intensive Company-Owned Company-Operated (COCO) stores. This transition, while aimed at brand building, introduces significant economic risks including higher overheads and longer stabilization periods. The company's sharp focus on diamond jewellery, a differentiator, also presents vulnerability due to discretionary demand sensitivity and the escalating threat from lab-grown diamonds, unlike its diversified peers. Valuations appear demanding, pricing in a smooth execution of this operational pivot.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:31:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d298b04a25a58c84e775a_1771908047441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Flair Writing Expands Pencil Output by 84M Units at Subsidiary</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Flair-Writing-Expands-Pencil-Output-by-84M-Units-at-Subsidiary/699d298804a25a58c84e7744</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Flair-Writing-Expands-Pencil-Output-by-84M-Units-at-Subsidiary/699d298804a25a58c84e7744</guid><description>Flair Writing Industries has commenced manufacturing wooden pencils at its subsidiary, Flomaxe Stationery Private Limited in Surat, adding an estimated annual capacity of 84 million pieces. This strategic move bolsters its creative product portfolio and backward integration, aiming to capture a larger share of the substantial wooden pencil market. The facility will also produce complementary items like erasers and sharpeners, enhancing the company's stationery offerings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d298804a25a58c84e7743_1771907566625.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Creative Newtech Partners Kaspersky to Expand India Cybersecurity Offerings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Creative-Newtech-Partners-Kaspersky-to-Expand-India-Cybersecurity-Offerings/699d298804a25a58c84e772e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Creative-Newtech-Partners-Kaspersky-to-Expand-India-Cybersecurity-Offerings/699d298804a25a58c84e772e</guid><description>Creative Newtech Limited has teamed up with global cybersecurity firm Kaspersky to distribute its product suite across North, West, and East India. The move leverages the rapidly expanding Indian cybersecurity market, projected to reach $20.5 billion by 2030, and aims to enhance Creative Newtech's technology solutions portfolio.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d298804a25a58c84e772d_1771907578167.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>D&amp;H India: Indo Thai Securities Ups Stake to 9.43% via Rights Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DandH-India-Indo-Thai-Securities-Ups-Stake-to-943percent-via-Rights-Issue/699d298704a25a58c84e7718</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DandH-India-Indo-Thai-Securities-Ups-Stake-to-943percent-via-Rights-Issue/699d298704a25a58c84e7718</guid><description>Indo Thai Securities Ltd and its Persons Acting in Concert (PACs) have significantly increased their stake in D&amp;H India Ltd to 9.43% by acquiring 8,84,186 equity shares through a recent rights issue. This move surpasses the 5% regulatory disclosure threshold, marking a substantial shift in D&amp;H India's ownership structure and signalling increased investor interest in the industrial fan and blower manufacturer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d298704a25a58c84e7717_1771908832841.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Plunge: Tariffs, AI Fears Spark Steep Opening Drop</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Plunge-Tariffs-AI-Fears-Spark-Steep-Opening-Drop/699d27cb04a25a58c84e748a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Plunge-Tariffs-AI-Fears-Spark-Steep-Opening-Drop/699d27cb04a25a58c84e748a</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks experienced a sharp downturn Tuesday morning, with the Sensex falling over 500 points and the Nifty down over 140. This selloff was triggered by escalating US tariff uncertainties and growing concerns over artificial intelligence impacting traditional IT services. IT stocks were significant laggards, exacerbating the broader market decline amidst a cautious global outlook.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:23:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d27cb04a25a58c84e7489_1771907518353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>