<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:21:45 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Silver Skyrockets Over ₹9,000! Experts Predict Astonishing ₹3 Lakh Target by March 2026 - What's Driving the Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-Over-9000-Experts-Predict-Astonishing-3-Lakh-Target-by-March-2026-Whats-Driving-the-Surge/695397144342f77179e610e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-Over-9000-Experts-Predict-Astonishing-3-Lakh-Target-by-March-2026-Whats-Driving-the-Surge/695397144342f77179e610e9</guid><description>Silver prices surged by over 4%, or ₹9,661, to trade at ₹2,34,090, driven by persistent supply concerns and strong industrial demand, especially from electric vehicles. Analysts predict silver could reach ₹3 lakh by March 31, 2026, as battery demand is expected to consume a significant portion of annual production. Gold also saw a modest rise amid geopolitical tensions and rate cut hopes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:02:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695397144342f77179e610e8_1767086027363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RVNL Stock Skyrockets Post Fare Hikes! Is the Rally Built on Hype or Real Numbers? Investors Watch Closely!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RVNL-Stock-Skyrockets-Post-Fare-Hikes-Is-the-Rally-Built-on-Hype-or-Real-Numbers-Investors-Watch-Closely/695396264342f77179e60e40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RVNL-Stock-Skyrockets-Post-Fare-Hikes-Is-the-Rally-Built-on-Hype-or-Real-Numbers-Investors-Watch-Closely/695396264342f77179e60e40</guid><description>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL) shares surged over 6% following the second railway passenger fare revision in December. While the fare hikes aim to bolster Indian Railways' finances, the stock's sharp rise and increased market capitalization appear disproportionate to the estimated incremental revenue gain. Analysts question if the rally is driven by short-term sentiment or sustainable fundamentals, especially given RVNL's recent underwhelming financial performance and current rich valuation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:57:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695396264342f77179e60e3f_1767085789006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unlocks Next-Gen Connectivity: New Spectrum Plan for 5G, 6G and Satellite Era Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Unlocks-Next-Gen-Connectivity-New-Spectrum-Plan-for-5G-6G-and-Satellite-Era-Revealed/6953951e4342f77179e60b59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Unlocks-Next-Gen-Connectivity-New-Spectrum-Plan-for-5G-6G-and-Satellite-Era-Revealed/6953951e4342f77179e60b59</guid><description>India's Department of Telecommunications has launched the National Frequency Allocation Plan 2025 (NFAP-2025), a vital policy document guiding radio-frequency spectrum management. Effective immediately, it allocates spectrum across 8.3 kHz to 3000 GHz, crucial for upcoming technologies. Key updates include assigning the 6425-7125 MHz band for future mobile services like 5G, 5G Advanced, and 6G, alongside allocating Ka, Q, and V bands for advanced satellite services. The plan also enhances spectrum for in-flight and maritime connectivity, V2X communication, and LEO/MEO satellite services, aiming to boost India's digital ecosystem and align with global standards.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:56:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953951e4342f77179e60b58_1767085562017.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Beauty Market Matures: Nykaa Reveals Smart Shoppers Drive Growth with Focus on Performance &amp; Ingredients!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Beauty-Market-Matures-Nykaa-Reveals-Smart-Shoppers-Drive-Growth-with-Focus-on-Performance-and-Ingredients/695395154342f77179e60b22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Beauty-Market-Matures-Nykaa-Reveals-Smart-Shoppers-Drive-Growth-with-Focus-on-Performance-and-Ingredients/695395154342f77179e60b22</guid><description>Nykaa's Beauty Rewind 2025 report indicates India's beauty market has matured, shifting from trend-led splurges to informed, ingredient-focused choices. Consumers now prioritize performance and convenience, with high-volume categories like lipsticks and essential skincare driving growth, signaling a more stable, data-driven consumer business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:52:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695395154342f77179e60b21_1767085487964.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dhara Rail Projects IPO: Grey Market Signals HUGE Listing Gains! Will Investors Hit the Jackpot?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Dhara-Rail-Projects-IPO-Grey-Market-Signals-HUGE-Listing-Gains-Will-Investors-Hit-the-Jackpot/695391a64342f77179e603cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Dhara-Rail-Projects-IPO-Grey-Market-Signals-HUGE-Listing-Gains-Will-Investors-Hit-the-Jackpot/695391a64342f77179e603cf</guid><description>Dhara Rail Projects, a provider of railway rolling stock systems, is set to list on December 31, 2025. The ₹50.20 crore SME IPO was massively oversubscribed, garnering bids over 111 times its offer size. Investors are anticipating a strong debut as the grey market premium (GMP) indicates unlisted shares trading at ₹140.5, an 11.5% premium over the ₹126 upper price band. If this trend holds, shares could list around ₹140.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695391a64342f77179e603ce_1767084627218.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SoftBank Unleashes $3 Billion AI Blitz: Acquires Digital Infrastructure Giant DigitalBridge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SoftBank-Unleashes-3-Billion-AI-Blitz-Acquires-Digital-Infrastructure-Giant-DigitalBridge/6953910f4342f77179e601b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SoftBank-Unleashes-3-Billion-AI-Blitz-Acquires-Digital-Infrastructure-Giant-DigitalBridge/6953910f4342f77179e601b5</guid><description>SoftBank Group is acquiring US-based DigitalBridge Group Inc. for approximately $3 billion (around ₹26,000 crore) in an all-cash deal. DigitalBridge, a private equity firm specializing in data centers and digital infrastructure crucial for the AI boom, is being bought at a premium. This strategic move signals SoftBank's aggressive expansion in digital infrastructure to meet soaring AI-driven demand.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953910f4342f77179e601b4_1767084559816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IREDA Stock in Freefall: Analyst Unlocks Crucial Pre-Budget Trading Plan – Will Rs 130 Support Hold?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Stock-in-Freefall-Analyst-Unlocks-Crucial-Pre-Budget-Trading-Plan-Will-Rs-130-Support-Hold/695390ac4342f77179e60063</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Stock-in-Freefall-Analyst-Unlocks-Crucial-Pre-Budget-Trading-Plan-Will-Rs-130-Support-Hold/695390ac4342f77179e60063</guid><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency (IREDA) shares have significantly underperformed, dropping nearly 40% in 2025. Analyst Swati Hotkar notes the weak trend but sees a potential short-term pullback to Rs 160-165 if the Rs 130 support level holds. Investors are advised to consider booking profits in this range ahead of the budget. The PSU stock, which had previously hit an all-time high of Rs 310 after its IPO, is currently trading well below key moving averages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:30:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695390ac4342f77179e60062_1767084395353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godawari Power Surges 2% on Major ESG Upgrade: Is This India's Next Green Champion?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Surges-2percent-on-Major-ESG-Upgrade-Is-This-Indias-Next-Green-Champion/6953905f4342f77179e5ff7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Surges-2percent-on-Major-ESG-Upgrade-Is-This-Indias-Next-Green-Champion/6953905f4342f77179e5ff7b</guid><description>Godawari Power and Ispat shares climbed over 2% following a significant upgrade in its Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) rating by CareEdge. The company's ESG score dramatically improved from 51 to 76.6, and its rating was elevated from CareEdge ESG 3 to CareEdge ESG 1. This upgrade highlights the company's enhanced performance in sustainability and governance factors, boosting investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:30:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953905f4342f77179e5ff7a_1767084416279.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Oil's Rs 5 Dividend Alert! Record Date Set - Get Paid by Jan 11, 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Oils-Rs-5-Dividend-Alert-Record-Date-Set-Get-Paid-by-Jan-11-2026/695390414342f77179e5ff1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Oils-Rs-5-Dividend-Alert-Record-Date-Set-Get-Paid-by-Jan-11-2026/695390414342f77179e5ff1a</guid><description>Indian Oil Corporation, a Maharatna PSU, has declared an interim dividend of ₹5 per equity share for FY2025-26. The company has fixed December 18, 2025, as the record date for determining eligible shareholders. Payments are scheduled to be made on or before January 11, 2026. This announcement follows strong Q2 results driven by improved refining margins.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:30:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695390414342f77179e5ff19_1767084201584.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mamaearth CEO Bets Big! Varun Alagh Buys ₹50 Cr Stake, Honasa Consumer Shares Skyrocket 8%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mamaearth-CEO-Bets-Big-Varun-Alagh-Buys-50-Cr-Stake-Honasa-Consumer-Shares-Skyrocket-8percent/69538fd94342f77179e5fd30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mamaearth-CEO-Bets-Big-Varun-Alagh-Buys-50-Cr-Stake-Honasa-Consumer-Shares-Skyrocket-8percent/69538fd94342f77179e5fd30</guid><description>Honasa Consumer, the parent company of Mamaearth, saw its shares surge over 8 percent on December 30 following a significant move by its CEO and promoter, Varun Alagh. He acquired approximately 0.57% stake for nearly ₹50 crore through a block deal with Fireside Ventures Investment Fund I, increasing his total shareholding to 32.45%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:26:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69538fd94342f77179e5fd2f_1767084152013.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Stocks Plunge 3 Days Straight! Profit-Booking Hits Sector Despite Massive ₹80,000 Cr Approvals - What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stocks-Plunge-3-Days-Straight-Profit-Booking-Hits-Sector-Despite-Massive-80000-Cr-Approvals-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/69538f9c4342f77179e5fc8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stocks-Plunge-3-Days-Straight-Profit-Booking-Hits-Sector-Despite-Massive-80000-Cr-Approvals-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/69538f9c4342f77179e5fc8e</guid><description>Indian defence shares extended a three-day decline, with the Nifty Defence index falling 1.5% on Tuesday amid broad sector selling. This occurred despite the Defence Acquisition Council (DAC) recently approving procurement proposals worth over ₹79,000 crore. Analysts remain positive on the medium-term outlook, citing strong multi-year order visibility and support for domestic manufacturers from these approvals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:26:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69538f9c4342f77179e5fc8d_1767084329993.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blackstone-Backed Bagmane REIT Eyes Rs 4,000 Cr IPO: Filing Soon!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Blackstone-Backed-Bagmane-REIT-Eyes-Rs-4000-Cr-IPO-Filing-Soon/69538f754342f77179e5fbdd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Blackstone-Backed-Bagmane-REIT-Eyes-Rs-4000-Cr-IPO-Filing-Soon/69538f754342f77179e5fbdd</guid><description>Blackstone-backed Bagmane Group is set to file draft papers this week for a Rs 4,000 crore Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT) IPO. The REIT comprises 20 million square feet of office properties in Bengaluru, valued at Rs 40,000 crore gross asset value. This would be India's fifth office REIT.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:26:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69538f754342f77179e5fbdc_1767084181514.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABS Mandate Clash: India's Top Bike Makers V. Government Deadline!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/ABS-Mandate-Clash-Indias-Top-Bike-Makers-V-Government-Deadline/69538ee44342f77179e5f9dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/ABS-Mandate-Clash-Indias-Top-Bike-Makers-V-Government-Deadline/69538ee44342f77179e5f9dd</guid><description>India's largest two-wheeler manufacturers, including Hero MotoCorp Ltd., Bajaj Auto Ltd., and TVS Motor Company Ltd., are strongly opposing a government mandate for mandatory Anti-lock Braking Systems (ABS) on all bikes from January 1. They cite supply chain constraints, increased costs for consumers, and a lack of clear evidence that ABS significantly reduces accidents, urging for a phased rollout instead of the strict deadline. The government is currently reconsidering its position.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:25:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69538ee44342f77179e5f9dc_1767083939383.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Real Estate Booms: Private Equity Surges 59% to $6.7 Billion, Foreign Capital Dominates!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Real-Estate-Booms-Private-Equity-Surges-59percent-to-67-Billion-Foreign-Capital-Dominates/69538e7e4342f77179e5f8d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indian-Real-Estate-Booms-Private-Equity-Surges-59percent-to-67-Billion-Foreign-Capital-Dominates/69538e7e4342f77179e5f8d2</guid><description>Private equity capital injected into Indian real estate surged 59% year-over-year to $6.7 billion in 2025, with foreign investors accounting for 76% of inflows. The office sector led investments, followed by data centers and residential properties. This marks a strong recovery to pre-pandemic levels, driven by improved regulatory clarity and developer stability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:23:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69538e7e4342f77179e5f8d1_1767083794263.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Skyrocket: Experts Predict Massive Gains Through 2026! Will You Profit?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Skyrocket-Experts-Predict-Massive-Gains-Through-2026-Will-You-Profit/69538c3b4342f77179e5f1f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Skyrocket-Experts-Predict-Massive-Gains-Through-2026-Will-You-Profit/69538c3b4342f77179e5f1f9</guid><description>Gold and silver have seen extraordinary gains in 2025, with gold up 71% and silver up 150%. Analysts predict this bullish trend will continue into 2026 and beyond, driven by geopolitical tensions, inflation concerns, US dollar weakness, and central bank buying. Strong fundamentals and demand, especially for silver in green energy, suggest sustained strength, with gold potentially reaching $5000 and silver $85-$95 in 2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:14:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69538c3b4342f77179e5f1f8_1767083479466.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2026 Inflation Secret Unveiled: New CPI Series &amp; Rate Cut Clues Emerge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Inflation-Secret-Unveiled-New-CPI-Series-and-Rate-Cut-Clues-Emerge/69538bb64342f77179e5ef67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Inflation-Secret-Unveiled-New-CPI-Series-and-Rate-Cut-Clues-Emerge/69538bb64342f77179e5ef67</guid><description>India is preparing to revamp its Consumer Price Index (CPI) methodology and monetary policy mandate by 2026. With inflation remaining low due to subdued food costs and GST cuts, the Reserve Bank of India has room for rate adjustments. A new CPI series, promising greater accuracy, will be released in February, aiming to refine inflation targeting for the next five years.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:12:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69538bb64342f77179e5ef66_1767083188989.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>QSR Sector Slumps: Is Value Demand Killing India's Fast Food Dreams? Experts Reveal What's Next!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/QSR-Sector-Slumps-Is-Value-Demand-Killing-Indias-Fast-Food-Dreams-Experts-Reveal-Whats-Next/69538a074342f77179e5eaef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/QSR-Sector-Slumps-Is-Value-Demand-Killing-Indias-Fast-Food-Dreams-Experts-Reveal-Whats-Next/69538a074342f77179e5eaef</guid><description>India's quick service restaurant (QSR) sector recovery faltered in Q3FY26, with demand remaining uneven and heavily value-driven. Despite the festive season and GST rationalisation, industry footfalls missed expectations, indicating pressure on discretionary spending. Analysts at PL Capital note that while urban areas and specific players like Jubilant FoodWorks show sequential improvements, overall consumption favors value offerings over premium items, affecting companies like Westlife Foodworld and Restaurant Brands Asia.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:58:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69538a074342f77179e5eaee_1767082635590.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metals Maverick: Why Copper &amp; Zinc Soar While Steel Stumbles - Analyst Reveals Top Picks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metals-Maverick-Why-Copper-and-Zinc-Soar-While-Steel-Stumbles-Analyst-Reveals-Top-Picks/695389ac4342f77179e5e9b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metals-Maverick-Why-Copper-and-Zinc-Soar-While-Steel-Stumbles-Analyst-Reveals-Top-Picks/695389ac4342f77179e5e9b0</guid><description>Axis Securities analyst Aditya Welekar notes a divergence in the metals sector. Non-ferrous metals like copper and silver are experiencing a structural rally due to demand and supply issues, boosting stocks like Hindustan Copper (+95% YTD) and Hindustan Zinc (+40% YTD). However, steel lags, facing muted prices and export challenges. While valuations are catching up, some upside remains, particularly for Hindalco.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:58:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695389ac4342f77179e5e9af_1767082489252.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Skyrockets Past Bitcoin: Shocking Volatility Twist Leaves Traders Reeling!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-Past-Bitcoin-Shocking-Volatility-Twist-Leaves-Traders-Reeling/69538a254342f77179e5eb52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-Past-Bitcoin-Shocking-Volatility-Twist-Leaves-Traders-Reeling/69538a254342f77179e5eb52</guid><description>As the year ends, silver's volatility has surged dramatically, outpacing even bitcoin. While silver prices have jumped over 151% driven by demand-supply imbalances and China's export license decision, bitcoin remains range-bound, down nearly 7% amid fading ETF demand and narrative shifts. This stark divergence highlights contrasting market fortunes for the precious metal and the leading cryptocurrency.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:55:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69538a254342f77179e5eb51_1767082633450.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Logistics Boom: Record Leasing Volumes Hit 60 Msf in 2025! What's Driving the Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Logistics-Boom-Record-Leasing-Volumes-Hit-60-Msf-in-2025-Whats-Driving-the-Surge/6953891e4342f77179e5e7d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Logistics-Boom-Record-Leasing-Volumes-Hit-60-Msf-in-2025-Whats-Driving-the-Surge/6953891e4342f77179e5e7d0</guid><description>India's logistics and industrial real estate market is heading for a record year, with leasing volumes expected to touch nearly 60 million square feet in 2025. This marks the fourth consecutive year crossing 50 million sq ft, driven by strong manufacturing, e-commerce, and 3PL expansion. Rental growth is projected at 3-7% for 2026, signaling sustained sector strength.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:54:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953891e4342f77179e5e7cf_1767082573532.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Cracks Down: Social Media Giants Face Legal Fury Over Explicit Content!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Cracks-Down-Social-Media-Giants-Face-Legal-Fury-Over-Explicit-Content/695388d84342f77179e5e713</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Cracks-Down-Social-Media-Giants-Face-Legal-Fury-Over-Explicit-Content/695388d84342f77179e5e713</guid><description>India's Ministry of Electronics and Information Technology (Meity) has issued a stern warning to major social media platforms, demanding an end to 'below par' moderation of sexually explicit material. Platforms like Meta's Facebook and Instagram, and Google's YouTube, are on notice. Failure to comply risks losing 'safe harbour' protection under the IT Act, potentially leading to legal action and criminal charges, impacting India's massive digital user base.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:53:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695388d84342f77179e5e712_1767082445751.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Hidden Power: Businesses Unlocking Massive Productivity Gains in 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Hidden-Power-Businesses-Unlocking-Massive-Productivity-Gains-in-2026/6953885c4342f77179e5e54f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Hidden-Power-Businesses-Unlocking-Massive-Productivity-Gains-in-2026/6953885c4342f77179e5e54f</guid><description>Enterprises are moving beyond AI hype to real-world application, with significant productivity gains emerging. Major companies report widespread AI tool usage among employees, leading to faster software development and problem-solving. Startups are also seeing accelerated demand for AI assistants. This trend is set to become undeniable in 2026, benefiting leading AI developers and potentially reshaping various industries through automation and enhanced efficiency.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:53:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953885c4342f77179e5e54e_1767082176924.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Corporate India Hits Brakes: C-Suite Hiring Freezes as AI &amp; Psychometric Tests Rule 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Corporate-India-Hits-Brakes-C-Suite-Hiring-Freezes-as-AI-and-Psychometric-Tests-Rule-2026/695387f04342f77179e5e422</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Corporate-India-Hits-Brakes-C-Suite-Hiring-Freezes-as-AI-and-Psychometric-Tests-Rule-2026/695387f04342f77179e5e422</guid><description>Corporate India is entering a period of hiring caution for senior and middle management, shifting from rapid poaching to rigorous vetting. With timelines exceeding six months, companies are using psychometric tests, AI assessments, and peer reviews to de-risk appointments. This shift signals a focus on operational resilience and navigating AI disruption, leading to slower growth in executive mandates and a fear of job insecurity among candidates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:53:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695387f04342f77179e5e421_1767082103392.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Telecom Shockwave: Starlink Roars In, Vodafone Idea Fights for Survival, and Data Usage Explodes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Indias-Telecom-Shockwave-Starlink-Roars-In-Vodafone-Idea-Fights-for-Survival-and-Data-Usage-Explodes/695389464342f77179e5e84c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Indias-Telecom-Shockwave-Starlink-Roars-In-Vodafone-Idea-Fights-for-Survival-and-Data-Usage-Explodes/695389464342f77179e5e84c</guid><description>India's telecom sector in 2025 faces a dynamic landscape with Elon Musk's Starlink set to enter the competitive satellite communication market. Meanwhile, Vodafone Idea struggles with significant Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) liabilities, raising concerns about its survival and market duopoly. State-run BSNL shows a revival with profits and subscriber growth, bolstered by government investment in 4G and rural broadband. Domestic manufacturing is booming, with significant export growth driven by PLI schemes, while data usage surges, creating opportunities and challenges like increased online fraud prevention efforts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:52:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695389464342f77179e5e84b_1767082456754.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2026 Two-Wheeler Revolution: Royal Enfield Bullet 650, BMW GS, and More Suzuki!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-2026-Two-Wheeler-Revolution-Royal-Enfield-Bullet-650-BMW-GS-and-More-Suzuki/695387b34342f77179e5e353</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-2026-Two-Wheeler-Revolution-Royal-Enfield-Bullet-650-BMW-GS-and-More-Suzuki/695387b34342f77179e5e353</guid><description>India gears up for an exciting start to 2026 with multiple new two-wheeler launches. Key models include the highly anticipated Royal Enfield Bullet 650, featuring a 647.95cc engine and modern tech. BMW Motorrad is set to introduce the F 450 GS, with TVS handling production, boasting a 420cc engine and advanced features. KTM's 390 Adventure R and Brixton Motorcycles' Storr 500 are also slated for launch, promising diverse options for riders.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:49:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695387b34342f77179e5e352_1767082201677.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Record Rumble! Promoters Cash In ₹2.57 Lakh Crore in 2025, Stocks Soar to New Highs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Record-Rumble-Promoters-Cash-In-257-Lakh-Crore-in-2025-Stocks-Soar-to-New-Highs/695387694342f77179e5e256</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Record-Rumble-Promoters-Cash-In-257-Lakh-Crore-in-2025-Stocks-Soar-to-New-Highs/695387694342f77179e5e256</guid><description>Promoters have sold shares worth a staggering ₹2.57 lakh crore in 2025, the highest in six years, as stock markets rally. Over the past six years since 2020, total promoter stake sales have reached ₹10 lakh crore. The majority of these sales, approximately 70% or ₹7 lakh crore, occurred in the secondary markets, with the remainder coming from IPOs and Offer for Sale (OFS) routes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:49:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695387694342f77179e5e255_1767081895051.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Solar Powerhouse Waaree Renewable Tech Secures Major Order Boost: Capacity &amp; Value Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Solar-Powerhouse-Waaree-Renewable-Tech-Secures-Major-Order-Boost-Capacity-and-Value-Surge/6953870f4342f77179e5e16f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Solar-Powerhouse-Waaree-Renewable-Tech-Secures-Major-Order-Boost-Capacity-and-Value-Surge/6953870f4342f77179e5e16f</guid><description>Waaree Renewable Technologies has received a significant capacity enhancement for a solar project, increasing it from 30 MWp to 35 MWp. The order value has also risen by ₹12.64 crore, now standing at ₹102.93 crore. The company will undertake engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) on a turnkey basis, including operation and maintenance, for this domestic order set to be completed by FY 2026-27. This follows strong Q2FY26 financial results showing a 48% revenue jump and doubled net profit.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:49:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953870f4342f77179e5e16e_1767081948244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks' NPA Recovery Stalls: IBC &amp; SARFAESI Show Mixed Results as Overall Rates Lag!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-NPA-Recovery-Stalls-IBC-and-SARFAESI-Show-Mixed-Results-as-Overall-Rates-Lag/695386ea4342f77179e5e0c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-NPA-Recovery-Stalls-IBC-and-SARFAESI-Show-Mixed-Results-as-Overall-Rates-Lag/695386ea4342f77179e5e0c4</guid><description>Despite the Insolvency &amp; Bankruptcy Code (IBC) and SARFAESI Act showing improved recovery rates in Fiscal Year 2025, the overall recovery rate for banks against stressed assets saw only a marginal improvement, climbing from 17.2% to 18%. The IBC's recovery rate increased to 36.5% and SARFAESI's to 31.5%, with IBC accounting for over half of the total ₹1,04,099 crore recovered. However, recoveries through Debt Recovery Tribunals declined, indicating a mixed picture in asset resolution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:48:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695386ea4342f77179e5e0c3_1767081786617.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Procter &amp; Gamble Home Products' FY25 Profit Skyrockets 19.1% to ₹683 Crore, Revenue Climbs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Procter-and-Gamble-Home-Products-FY25-Profit-Skyrockets-191percent-to-683-Crore-Revenue-Climbs/695386014342f77179e5de36</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Procter-and-Gamble-Home-Products-FY25-Profit-Skyrockets-191percent-to-683-Crore-Revenue-Climbs/695386014342f77179e5de36</guid><description>Procter &amp; Gamble Home Products Ltd (PGHPL) announced a substantial 19.1% increase in net profit for FY25, reaching ₹683.29 crore, while revenue from operations rose 3.4% to ₹9,054.11 crore. The company saw significant savings from a 63% drop in tax expenses. Despite increased advertising costs, PGHPL, an unlisted entity managing brands like Ariel and Tide, demonstrated strong performance. Other P&amp;G entities in India are listed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:48:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695386014342f77179e5de35_1767081587242.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Oil Bill PLUMMETS Despite Higher Imports: What This Means for Your Wallet!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Oil-Bill-PLUMMETS-Despite-Higher-Imports-What-This-Means-for-Your-Wallet/695384ea4342f77179e5db82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Oil-Bill-PLUMMETS-Despite-Higher-Imports-What-This-Means-for-Your-Wallet/695384ea4342f77179e5db82</guid><description>India's oil import bill fell by 12% to $80.9 billion in April-November despite a 2.4% rise in import volumes to 163.4 million tonnes. This is due to lower international crude oil prices, with the Indian basket averaging $67.6 per barrel. However, the country's reliance on imported crude oil increased to 88.6% as domestic production declined.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695384ea4342f77179e5db81_1767081293210.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys &amp; Cera Alert! Stocks Trade BELOW Buyback Price – Is This Your Next Big Opportunity?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Infosys-and-Cera-Alert-Stocks-Trade-BELOW-Buyback-Price-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Opportunity/695381594342f77179e5d294</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Infosys-and-Cera-Alert-Stocks-Trade-BELOW-Buyback-Price-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Opportunity/695381594342f77179e5d294</guid><description>Infosys and Cera Sanitaryware are among several prominent companies whose shares are currently trading below their announced buyback prices. Infosys shares are below its ₹1,800 buyback price, while Cera Sanitaryware is trading a significant 57% below its ₹12,000 buyback price. Share buybacks are a tax-efficient method for companies to return capital to shareholders, reduce share count, and potentially increase stock value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:25:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695381594342f77179e5d293_1767080471155.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Rebalancing Alert: Major Inflow/Outflow Shakeup Rocks Top Stocks - See Who Gains &amp; Loses!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Rebalancing-Alert-Major-InflowOutflow-Shakeup-Rocks-Top-Stocks-See-Who-Gains-and-Loses/6953809b4342f77179e5cd64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Rebalancing-Alert-Major-InflowOutflow-Shakeup-Rocks-Top-Stocks-See-Who-Gains-and-Loses/6953809b4342f77179e5cd64</guid><description>The Nifty indices are undergoing a significant rejig today, December 30, triggering substantial inflows and outflows for key stocks. Nuvama Alternative &amp; Quantitative Research predicts Eicher Motors, Maruti Suzuki, Asian Paints, Hindalco, and State Bank of India could see inflows of $70-80 million each. Conversely, ICICI Bank and HDFC Bank are poised for major outflows, estimated at $152 million and $149 million respectively, due to index adjustments including revised norms for the Nifty Bank index. New entrants like Yes Bank and Union Bank are also expected to attract significant funds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:25:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6953809b4342f77179e5cd63_1767080166495.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Startup Shock: Fewer Failures Hide Deeper Problems!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Shock-Fewer-Failures-Hide-Deeper-Problems/695380e64342f77179e5d0ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Shock-Fewer-Failures-Hide-Deeper-Problems/695380e64342f77179e5d0ee</guid><description>India witnessed a sharp drop in startup shutdowns in 2025, falling to 730 from 3,903 in 2024. However, high-profile failures of companies like Good Glamm Group, Hike, Dunzo, Builder.ai, and BluSmart reveal deeper issues including leverage, delayed profitability, and loss of relevance. The ecosystem is recalibrating towards sustainable growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:25:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695380e64342f77179e5d0ed_1767080401277.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRDAI Prepares to Unveil New Rules on Insurance Commissions: Policyholder Protection in Focus?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/IRDAI-Prepares-to-Unveil-New-Rules-on-Insurance-Commissions-Policyholder-Protection-in-Focus/695380bd4342f77179e5cdbd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/IRDAI-Prepares-to-Unveil-New-Rules-on-Insurance-Commissions-Policyholder-Protection-in-Focus/695380bd4342f77179e5cdbd</guid><description>India's insurance regulator, IRDAI, is set to release draft regulations concerning insurance agent commissions. The Department of Financial Services (DFS) Secretary, M. Nagaraju, indicated the move aims to empower IRDAI to control distribution costs, ensure commissions are reasonable, and prevent higher premiums or reduced Incremental Capital Ratio (ICR) that could harm policyholders.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:25:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695380bd4342f77179e5cdbc_1767080212513.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silent Killers Strike: Heatwaves Reign Supreme in 2025's Deadliest Climate Disasters, Poorest Communities Bear the Brunt!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Silent-Killers-Strike-Heatwaves-Reign-Supreme-in-2025s-Deadliest-Climate-Disasters-Poorest-Communities-Bear-the-Brunt/695380364342f77179e5cc13</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Silent-Killers-Strike-Heatwaves-Reign-Supreme-in-2025s-Deadliest-Climate-Disasters-Poorest-Communities-Bear-the-Brunt/695380364342f77179e5cc13</guid><description>A new report reveals that heatwaves were the deadliest climate-related disasters of 2025, disproportionately impacting impoverished and marginalized communities globally. Despite not breaking temperature records, 2025 was among the hottest years, pushing societies towards adaptation limits. The three-year average global temperature crossed the critical 1.5°C threshold for the first time, signaling increased extreme weather events like floods and storms, exacerbated by continued fossil fuel use.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:21:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695380364342f77179e5cc12_1767080289897.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Chopper Takes Flight! HAL Unveils DHRUV-NG - Global Ambitions Soar!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-New-Chopper-Takes-Flight-HAL-Unveils-DHRUV-NG-Global-Ambitions-Soar/69537ef84342f77179e5c68d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-New-Chopper-Takes-Flight-HAL-Unveils-DHRUV-NG-Global-Ambitions-Soar/69537ef84342f77179e5c68d</guid><description>Union Civil Aviation Minister Ram Mohan Naidu inaugurated HAL's next-generation civil helicopter, DHRUV-NG, in Bengaluru. This 5.5-tonne, twin-engine helicopter is designed for the global market, featuring advanced avionics, a glass cockpit, and enhanced comfort. It marks a significant step for India's indigenous helicopter manufacturing capabilities, offering a cost-effective alternative to imported models.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:19:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69537ef84342f77179e5c68c_1767079742296.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gurugram Housing Prices EXPLODE: 150% Surge Since 2019! Is Your City Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Gurugram-Housing-Prices-EXPLODE-150percent-Surge-Since-2019-Is-Your-City-Next/69537e7f4342f77179e5c514</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Gurugram-Housing-Prices-EXPLODE-150percent-Surge-Since-2019-Is-Your-City-Next/69537e7f4342f77179e5c514</guid><description>Gurugram leads Indian cities with a staggering 150% rise in property prices since 2019, according to Square Yards. Pune, Noida, Greater Noida, Mumbai, and Bengaluru also saw significant price growth. While transaction volumes dipped slightly in 2025, increased average deal sizes indicate a maturing market dominated by demand for premium and luxury housing. Affordability is expected to improve for mid-income buyers in 2026 as markets stabilize.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:18:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69537e7f4342f77179e5c513_1767079624455.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Sentiment Weak, But Fundamentals Strong? Bajaj Finserv CIO Reveals Buying Opportunity!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Sentiment-Weak-But-Fundamentals-Strong-Bajaj-Finserv-CIO-Reveals-Buying-Opportunity/69537ab14342f77179e5bc49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Sentiment-Weak-But-Fundamentals-Strong-Bajaj-Finserv-CIO-Reveals-Buying-Opportunity/69537ab14342f77179e5bc49</guid><description>Bajaj Finserv Asset Management Company's Chief Investment Officer, Nimesh Chandan, believes that despite prevailing weak market sentiment, strong underlying economic fundamentals present a significant buying opportunity for investors. He emphasizes that headlines have driven market movements rather than core economic strength. Chandan identifies consumption-linked sectors, paints, select digital stocks, and construction companies as key areas of focus, viewing potential trade deals mainly as sentiment boosters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:53:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69537ab14342f77179e5bc48_1767078685316.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Commodity Euphoria Over? Fund Manager Exits Metals, Bets Big on These Unexpected Sectors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Commodity-Euphoria-Over-Fund-Manager-Exits-Metals-Bets-Big-on-These-Unexpected-Sectors/69537a564342f77179e5bb3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Commodity-Euphoria-Over-Fund-Manager-Exits-Metals-Bets-Big-on-These-Unexpected-Sectors/69537a564342f77179e5bb3a</guid><description>Parag Thakkar of Fort Capital advises caution on the commodity rally, having exited metal stocks like Hindalco Industries. He sees potential risks from geopolitical easing and FOMO. Instead, he favors a contrarian bet on FMCG and cement sectors, citing improving demand indicators and potential price hikes. He also keeps an eye on select IT and conglomerate stocks like Coforge and Reliance Industries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:53:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69537a564342f77179e5bb39_1767078787116.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Governance Push Ignites Global Stage; Markets Show Mixed Signals: What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-AI-Governance-Push-Ignites-Global-Stage-Markets-Show-Mixed-Signals-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/69537a134342f77179e5b9d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-AI-Governance-Push-Ignites-Global-Stage-Markets-Show-Mixed-Signals-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/69537a134342f77179e5b9d1</guid><description>India is set to host the AI Summit 2026, aiming to build consensus on global AI governance norms. While equity markets appeared 'listless' in 2025, analysts at DBS Group suggest foundations for stronger earnings in 2026 are being laid. In stock-specific news, Dixon Technologies shares are heading for their worst year since 2018, while Shriram Finance shares gained following a credit rating upgrade.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:53:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69537a134342f77179e5b9d0_1767078592710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>