<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India BFSI: AI Surge Meets Governance Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-BFSI-AI-Surge-Meets-Governance-Hurdles/699f172c04a25a58c8555773</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-BFSI-AI-Surge-Meets-Governance-Hurdles/699f172c04a25a58c8555773</guid><description>India's Banking, Financial Services, and Insurance (BFSI) sector is at a critical juncture, driven by rapid artificial intelligence adoption and a shifting investor base towards wealth creation. While AI promises enhanced fraud detection, credit underwriting, and customer service, its widespread deployment hinges on overcoming data quality, talent, and regulatory challenges. Simultaneously, a younger, digitally-savvy investor demographic is reshaping the wealth management landscape and fueling demand for alternative assets, necessitating structural market and policy reforms to sustain growth and ensure operational resilience.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Hype Powers Tech Stocks Amid Earnings Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Hype-Powers-Tech-Stocks-Amid-Earnings-Uncertainty/699f172904a25a58c855575c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Hype-Powers-Tech-Stocks-Amid-Earnings-Uncertainty/699f172904a25a58c855575c</guid><description>US markets opened higher Wednesday, Feb 25, 2026, with technology stocks spearheading the advance. Nvidia's upcoming earnings report is a key focal point for gauging artificial intelligence spending trends, especially after hyperscalers signaled increased capital expenditures. However, geopolitical tensions and varied corporate outlooks, like Workday's softer revenue forecast, introduce caution. Oracle saw a significant boost following an analyst upgrade.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Enbee Trade Finance ₹120 Cr Rights Issue Approved; Price ₹1/Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Enbee-Trade-Finance-120-Cr-Rights-Issue-Approved-Price-1Share/699f163104a25a58c8555639</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Enbee-Trade-Finance-120-Cr-Rights-Issue-Approved-Price-1Share/699f163104a25a58c8555639</guid><description>Enbee Trade and Finance's Board has greenlit terms for a ₹120.05 crore rights issue, offering shares at ₹1 each to existing shareholders on a 21:10 ratio. The record date is March 4, 2026, with the issue opening March 12. This move aims to inject capital but significantly dilutes share count.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's MMF Sector: Tax Woes Hit Global Competitiveness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indias-MMF-Sector-Tax-Woes-Hit-Global-Competitiveness/699f150404a25a58c8555503</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indias-MMF-Sector-Tax-Woes-Hit-Global-Competitiveness/699f150404a25a58c8555503</guid><description>India's man-made fibre industry is grappling with significant cost pressures driven by an inverted Goods and Services Tax (GST) regime. Raw materials essential for polyester and Viscose Staple Fibre (VSF) production face an 18% GST, starkly contrasting with the 5% levied on finished products. This anomaly, combined with duty-free VSF imports from ASEAN and competitors' zero-duty access to vital inputs like sulphur and natural gas, creates substantial cost disadvantages. Logistical fragmentation further exacerbates these issues, undermining India's position in the global market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Zerodha LAS Hits ₹500 Cr Milestone, Touts Cheaper Debt Alternative</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Zerodha-LAS-Hits-500-Cr-Milestone-Touts-Cheaper-Debt-Alternative/699f13f504a25a58c854aafa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Zerodha-LAS-Hits-500-Cr-Milestone-Touts-Cheaper-Debt-Alternative/699f13f504a25a58c854aafa</guid><description>Zerodha Capital's Loan Against Shares (LAS) business has surpassed ₹500 crore, a significant achievement for a less-publicized offering. Co-founder Nithin Kamath champions LAS as a secured, cost-effective alternative to high-interest personal loans and credit cards. This milestone underscores Zerodha's strategic expansion into diversified financial services, leveraging its client base to offer essential liquidity options while navigating an increasingly regulated fintech credit market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gravita India invests ₹49 Cr, boosts Mundra lead recycling capacity by 80,300 MTPA</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Gravita-India-invests-49-Cr-boosts-Mundra-lead-recycling-capacity-by-80300-MTPA/699f136204a25a58c854aa48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Gravita-India-invests-49-Cr-boosts-Mundra-lead-recycling-capacity-by-80300-MTPA/699f136204a25a58c854aa48</guid><description>Gravita India Limited has significantly ramped up its lead recycling operations by investing ₹49 Crore in its Mundra, Gujarat facility. The expansion adds 80,300 MTPA to the unit's capacity, bringing the total at Mundra to 1,45,100 MTPA. This move bolsters the company's global installed recycling capacity to 4,25,959 MTPA, aligning with growing demand for sustainable lead products and enhancing its competitive edge.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBL Bank: SBI MF gets RBI nod to boost stake to 9.99%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBL-Bank-SBI-MF-gets-RBI-nod-to-boost-stake-to-999percent/699f12e804a25a58c854a9a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBL-Bank-SBI-MF-gets-RBI-nod-to-boost-stake-to-999percent/699f12e804a25a58c854a9a2</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has granted approval to SBI Mutual Fund to acquire an aggregate holding of up to 9.99% in RBL Bank Limited. This approval, valid for one year, allows SBI Mutual Fund to significantly increase its current stake of 1.88%, potentially altering the bank's shareholding structure. The move signals growing institutional confidence in RBL Bank.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apollo Ingredients Faces Scrutiny: ₹3 Cr Rights Issue Funds Diverted for Lease</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Apollo-Ingredients-Faces-Scrutiny-3-Cr-Rights-Issue-Funds-Diverted-for-Lease/699f110c04a25a58c854a822</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Apollo-Ingredients-Faces-Scrutiny-3-Cr-Rights-Issue-Funds-Diverted-for-Lease/699f110c04a25a58c854a822</guid><description>Apollo Ingredients Limited has disclosed a significant deviation in the utilisation of its Rights Issue proceeds. The company raised ₹5 crore but used ₹3 crore for lease payments to a related party, deviating from the original stated objective of working capital. While shareholder approval for the specific lease transaction was later obtained, a monitoring agency noted the deviation, raising governance concerns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Endowments Shift to Crypto ETFs Amidst Return Drought</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Endowments-Shift-to-Crypto-ETFs-Amidst-Return-Drought/699f108304a25a58c854a752</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Endowments-Shift-to-Crypto-ETFs-Amidst-Return-Drought/699f108304a25a58c854a752</guid><description>Endowments are confronting diminishing returns from traditional assets, compelling a strategic shift toward higher-risk alternatives like cryptocurrency ETFs to meet fixed payout obligations. Institutions face a challenging environment characterized by stretched valuations and crowded private markets, forcing a re-evaluation of investment playbooks and potentially an increased allocation to digital assets despite inherent volatility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Market Reverses Amid US Tensions; PSU Banks Soar, IT Stocks Crash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Reverses-Amid-US-Tensions-PSU-Banks-Soar-IT-Stocks-Crash/699f0e6e04a25a58c854a11d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Reverses-Amid-US-Tensions-PSU-Banks-Soar-IT-Stocks-Crash/699f0e6e04a25a58c854a11d</guid><description>Indian equity markets experienced significant intraday volatility on February 25, 2026, with the Nifty 50 and Sensex surrendering substantial early gains. Heightened concerns over U.S. trade policy, including new tariffs on Indian solar imports and escalating US-Iran tensions, weighed on sentiment. This external pressure contrasted sharply with robust performance in the PSU Banking sector, which continued its rally on strong earnings, while the IT sector faced a severe downturn amid AI disruption fears and significant foreign investor outflows. Broader market indices, however, showed resilience, outperforming the frontline benchmarks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Exporters Navigate Trade Policy Whac-a-Mole</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indian-Exporters-Navigate-Trade-Policy-Whac-a-Mole/699f0e4604a25a58c854a0fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indian-Exporters-Navigate-Trade-Policy-Whac-a-Mole/699f0e4604a25a58c854a0fe</guid><description>Indian exporters report increased US buyer inquiries following the US Supreme Court's invalidation of reciprocal tariffs and subsequent reduction in duties. However, a new 10% global import surcharge, implemented February 24, 2026, coupled with the administration's unpredictable trade policy, fosters cautious optimism. While recent data shows a recovery from earlier lows, the specter of further tariffs and intense competition from nations like Vietnam casts a shadow over sustained export growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Foseco India FY26 Revenue Up 14%; Q4 Standalone Profit Dips 20% Amid MCIL Buy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Foseco-India-FY26-Revenue-Up-14percent-Q4-Standalone-Profit-Dips-20percent-Amid-MCIL-Buy/699f0cd104a25a58c8549f91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Foseco-India-FY26-Revenue-Up-14percent-Q4-Standalone-Profit-Dips-20percent-Amid-MCIL-Buy/699f0cd104a25a58c8549f91</guid><description>Foseco India reported its Q4 and full-year FY26 results, showcasing 14.32% standalone revenue growth for the year to ₹620.78 Cr. However, standalone net profit for the December quarter fell 20.55% year-on-year to ₹15.53 Cr, despite higher revenue. The company also announced a significant strategic acquisition of a 75% stake in Morganite Crucible (India) Limited for ₹638 Cr.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Capricorn Systems Q4 FY26: Equity Capital Jumps To ₹27.97 Cr Post Rights Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Capricorn-Systems-Q4-FY26-Equity-Capital-Jumps-To-2797-Cr-Post-Rights-Issue/699f0be004a25a58c8549e87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Capricorn-Systems-Q4-FY26-Equity-Capital-Jumps-To-2797-Cr-Post-Rights-Issue/699f0be004a25a58c8549e87</guid><description>Capricorn Systems Global Solutions Limited has approved the allotment of 2,39,76,000 fully paid-up Rights Equity Shares. This move significantly boosts the company's paid-up equity share capital from ₹4.00 crore to ₹27.97 crore. The shares were issued at ₹10 each in a 6:1 ratio, a move aimed at strengthening its financial base.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Precious Metals ETFs Surge: Profit vs. Peril</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-ETFs-Surge-Profit-vs-Peril/699f0a3504a25a58c8549c57</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Precious-Metals-ETFs-Surge-Profit-vs-Peril/699f0a3504a25a58c8549c57</guid><description>Precious metal ETFs have delivered exceptional returns, with silver ETFs surging over 170% and gold ETFs over 80% in the past year. However, significant price volatility, tracking discrepancies, and shifting macroeconomic factors necessitate a strategic approach focused on diversification rather than market timing. Investors must scrutinize expense ratios, tracking errors, and geopolitical influences before committing capital to these high-risk, high-reward assets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Fuels Digital Scams: Fintech Faces Fraud Reckoning</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Fuels-Digital-Scams-Fintech-Faces-Fraud-Reckoning/699f0a3404a25a58c8549c40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Fuels-Digital-Scams-Fintech-Faces-Fraud-Reckoning/699f0a3404a25a58c8549c40</guid><description>Sophisticated AI-driven scams, particularly targeting the elderly, are costing billions globally, pressuring fintechs and banks to enhance security measures. Regulatory bodies like the RBI are increasing oversight, while the cybersecurity market sees robust growth as institutions race to protect customers and maintain trust in the face of evolving threats and operational risks. This shift necessitates a strategic re-evaluation of defenses and customer engagement models across the digital finance ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Insurer Reforms: Value Quest Faces Profit Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurer-Reforms-Value-Quest-Faces-Profit-Pressure/699f08b304a25a58c8549a9f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurer-Reforms-Value-Quest-Faces-Profit-Pressure/699f08b304a25a58c8549a9f</guid><description>The Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority of India (IRDAI) is spearheading a significant reform agenda aimed at making insurance more affordable and value-driven. Key initiatives include rationalizing commission structures, introducing a digital e-marketplace (Bima Sugam), and developing a digital public infrastructure. These changes target the high distribution costs, which stood at Rs 1 lakh crore in FY25, and aim to re-align incentives towards long-term value rather than short-term sales. While the intent is to benefit policyholders, these reforms present a complex transition for insurers, potentially impacting their operational models and profit margins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jane Street SEBI Case Delayed: Regulatory Uncertainty Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Jane-Street-SEBI-Case-Delayed-Regulatory-Uncertainty-Looms/699f082504a25a58c85499bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Jane-Street-SEBI-Case-Delayed-Regulatory-Uncertainty-Looms/699f082504a25a58c85499bd</guid><description>The Securities Appellate Tribunal (SAT) adjourned its hearing on Jane Street's appeal against SEBI's interim order concerning alleged Bank Nifty manipulation. The firm contests SEBI's findings and claims a lack of document access. The adjournment, due to time constraints, leaves the substantial ₹4,843 crore deposit order in limbo, extending regulatory uncertainty for the US-based proprietary trading firm. This delay highlights procedural challenges in high-stakes market integrity investigations and their impact on firm operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance REIL Allots ₹853 Cr Shares; Meta Stake Rises to 30%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Reliance-REIL-Allots-853-Cr-Shares-Meta-Stake-Rises-to-30percent/699f073504a25a58c85498a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Reliance-REIL-Allots-853-Cr-Shares-Meta-Stake-Rises-to-30percent/699f073504a25a58c85498a9</guid><description>Reliance Industries' step-down subsidiary, Reliance Enterprise Intelligence Limited (REIL), has completed a ₹853.2 crore equity share allotment. The transaction saw ₹596.6 crore allocated to RIL's Reliance Intelligence and ₹256.6 crore to Meta's Facebook Overseas, Inc. This changes REIL's ownership to 70% Reliance Intelligence and 30% Facebook Overseas, marking its transition from a wholly owned subsidiary to a step-down subsidiary.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Baba Arts Open Offer: Skybridge Interactive to Acquire 25.32% Stake at ₹6</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Baba-Arts-Open-Offer-Skybridge-Interactive-to-Acquire-2532percent-Stake-at-6/699f03eb04a25a58c85495b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Baba-Arts-Open-Offer-Skybridge-Interactive-to-Acquire-2532percent-Stake-at-6/699f03eb04a25a58c85495b9</guid><description>Skybridge Interactive LLP has launched an open offer to acquire up to 25.32% of Baba Arts Limited for ₹7.98 crore at ₹6 per share. This move signals a potential change of promoter, with Skybridge aiming to take control of the Mumbai-based film production and distribution company. Investors should note that crucial information in the offer document has not been independently verified.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Wildlife Raids Devour Indian Agriculture: ₹40K Cr Losses Threaten Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Wildlife-Raids-Devour-Indian-Agriculture-40K-Cr-Losses-Threaten-Sector/699f03b404a25a58c8549570</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Wildlife-Raids-Devour-Indian-Agriculture-40K-Cr-Losses-Threaten-Sector/699f03b404a25a58c8549570</guid><description>Biologist Dr. Milind Watve highlights that India's agricultural sector suffers annual wildlife-induced losses of up to ₹40,000 crore. Decades of hunting bans have reduced wildlife's fear of humans, leading to crop raids and substantial indirect economic impacts, including farmers abandoning land. Current mitigation strategies and assessment methods are criticized for their inadequacy, failing to quantify damage accurately or address behavioral drivers, creating a systemic economic vulnerability for Indian agriculture.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Defence Stocks Diverge: Strategic Shift Boosts Privates, PSUs Face Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stocks-Diverge-Strategic-Shift-Boosts-Privates-PSUs-Face-Headwinds/699f01a004a25a58c8549239</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stocks-Diverge-Strategic-Shift-Boosts-Privates-PSUs-Face-Headwinds/699f01a004a25a58c8549239</guid><description>India's defence sector is bifurcating. Public sector undertakings (PSUs) like Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL) and Bharat Dynamics (BDL) are under pressure, exhibiting year-to-date declines. Conversely, private manufacturers Data Patterns and Solar Industries India are posting significant gains. This trend reflects a systemic shift in defence procurement favouring private sector efficiency and indigenous capabilities, amplified by geopolitical realities and strong budgetary allocations. While the long-term outlook remains robust, elevated valuations and execution risks present challenges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanofi India FY25 Profit Up 4% to ₹326.7 Cr; Revenue Dips; Dividend ₹48/Share Proposed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sanofi-India-FY25-Profit-Up-4percent-to-3267-Cr-Revenue-Dips-Dividend-48Share-Proposed/699f019704a25a58c8549222</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Sanofi-India-FY25-Profit-Up-4percent-to-3267-Cr-Revenue-Dips-Dividend-48Share-Proposed/699f019704a25a58c8549222</guid><description>Sanofi India's Board approved audited FY25 financial results, reporting a profit after tax of ₹3,267 million, up 4% from ₹3,137 million in FY24. Revenue from operations declined by 8.7% to ₹18,374 million from ₹20,132 million, attributed partly to an anticipated contract cessation with Zentiva. The company recommended a final dividend of ₹48 per share, bringing the total for FY25 to ₹123 per share. Key director appointments and a resignation were also announced.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:05:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India FY25 Profit ₹240 Cr; ₹75 Dividend Declared</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sanofi-Consumer-Healthcare-India-FY25-Profit-240-Cr-75-Dividend-Declared/699f019104a25a58c854920c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sanofi-Consumer-Healthcare-India-FY25-Profit-240-Cr-75-Dividend-Declared/699f019104a25a58c854920c</guid><description>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd reported robust FY2025 results, with revenue at ₹8,784 million and profit at ₹2,401 million. The board recommended a final dividend of ₹75 per equity share, subject to shareholder approval. The company received an unmodified audit opinion for its financial statements. However, it faces potential impacts from new labour codes and a change in its ultimate parent structure following the Opella stake sale.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:05:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Skye Air's Drone-AI Launch: High Tech, High Risk in India's Last Mile</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Skye-Airs-Drone-AI-Launch-High-Tech-High-Risk-in-Indias-Last-Mile/699f005404a25a58c854901f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Skye-Airs-Drone-AI-Launch-High-Tech-High-Risk-in-Indias-Last-Mile/699f005404a25a58c854901f</guid><description>Skye Air Mobility has launched an advanced drone and AI robot delivery service in Gurugram, integrating aerial drones with automated ground systems for last-mile operations. This move signals significant progress in automated logistics, building on the company's substantial delivery volume. However, the venture's future hinges on navigating complex regulations, securing substantial capital for infrastructure expansion, and proving long-term economic viability amidst fierce competition and the financial realities of its key partners.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Union Bank of India's VR upgraded by Fitch; Long-Term IDR affirmed 'BBB-'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Union-Bank-of-Indias-VR-upgraded-by-Fitch-Long-Term-IDR-affirmed-BBB-/699effb304a25a58c8548f44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Union-Bank-of-Indias-VR-upgraded-by-Fitch-Long-Term-IDR-affirmed-BBB-/699effb304a25a58c8548f44</guid><description>Fitch Ratings has upgraded Union Bank of India's Viability Rating (VR) to 'bb' from 'bb-'. The bank's Long-Term Issuer Default Rating (IDR) has been affirmed at 'BBB-' with a Stable Outlook, reflecting strong government support. The upgrade signals improved asset quality, capitalisation, and profitability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:57:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699effb304a25a58c8548f43_1772028233626.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Regency Fincorp Board to Meet Feb 28 for NCD Term Sheet Approval</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Regency-Fincorp-Board-to-Meet-Feb-28-for-NCD-Term-Sheet-Approval/699efe4904a25a58c8548d4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Regency-Fincorp-Board-to-Meet-Feb-28-for-NCD-Term-Sheet-Approval/699efe4904a25a58c8548d4d</guid><description>Regency Fincorp Limited announced its Board of Directors will convene on February 28, 2026, via video conferencing. The primary agenda is to consider and approve a revised term sheet for issuing Listed, Rated, Secured, and Redeemable Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs). This move signifies the company's ongoing efforts to raise debt capital, crucial for its lending operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Granito India: ₹155 Cr Bank Facilities Shift to Rating Watch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Asian-Granito-India-155-Cr-Bank-Facilities-Shift-to-Rating-Watch/699efe4804a25a58c8548d37</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Asian-Granito-India-155-Cr-Bank-Facilities-Shift-to-Rating-Watch/699efe4804a25a58c8548d37</guid><description>Infomerics Valuation and Rating Limited has placed Asian Granito India Limited's (AGIL) ₹155 crore worth of bank loan facilities on 'watch with developing implications'. This move signifies a potential future change in credit rating, moving from a previously stable outlook, indicating closer monitoring by the agency.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:51:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699efe4804a25a58c8548d36_1772027883384.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LT Foods Shares Unmoved by Duty Cut Amidst FMCG Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/LT-Foods-Shares-Unmoved-by-Duty-Cut-Amidst-FMCG-Caution/699efce804a25a58c8548b85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/LT-Foods-Shares-Unmoved-by-Duty-Cut-Amidst-FMCG-Caution/699efce804a25a58c8548b85</guid><description>LT Foods' subsidiary, Ecopure Specialities Limited, secured a significant reduction in US countervailing duties on organic soybean meal, from 340.27% to 75.48%, potentially saving ₹163 crore. This positive trade development coincided with a 9.8% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹157.35 crore and a 23.5% revenue jump to ₹2,809.2 crore in Q3 FY26. Despite these strong results, LT Foods' stock closed nearly unchanged, suggesting market skepticism amidst broader FMCG sector caution and persistent trade risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lodha Bets Big on Ultra-Luxury Malabar Hill Redevelopment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Lodha-Bets-Big-on-Ultra-Luxury-Malabar-Hill-Redevelopment/699efbfa04a25a58c8548a48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Lodha-Bets-Big-on-Ultra-Luxury-Malabar-Hill-Redevelopment/699efbfa04a25a58c8548a48</guid><description>Realty major Lodha Developers has acquired development rights for a 4.3-acre prime land parcel in Mumbai's upscale Malabar Hill for an estimated ₹2,800 crore development potential. The deal with the Sorabji Kanga Charity Trust involves substantial monetary and non-monetary considerations, including a new building for the trust and a significant revenue share. This acquisition underscores Lodha's strategic push into the super-luxury housing segment in established, supply-constrained micro-markets. The transaction highlights the rarity and high value of contiguous land parcels in prime South Mumbai locations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanofi India FY25 Profit ₹240 Cr; Recommends ₹75 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sanofi-India-FY25-Profit-240-Cr-Recommends-75-Dividend/699efb7a04a25a58c8548997</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sanofi-India-FY25-Profit-240-Cr-Recommends-75-Dividend/699efb7a04a25a58c8548997</guid><description>Sanofi India has announced its audited FY2025 standalone financial results, reporting a profit of ₹2,401 million (₹240.1 crore) on revenues of ₹8,784 million (₹878.4 crore). The company's Board of Directors has recommended a final dividend of ₹75 per equity share, subject to shareholder approval. This follows a significant operational period where the company's ultimate parent entity transitioned to Opal JVco S.a.r.l.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Tech Charts Upcycle Strategy: Diversified Capabilities, AI Focus, ES-Tec Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tata-Tech-Charts-Upcycle-Strategy-Diversified-Capabilities-AI-Focus-ES-Tec-Acquisition/699efa8a04a25a58c8548899</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tata-Tech-Charts-Upcycle-Strategy-Diversified-Capabilities-AI-Focus-ES-Tec-Acquisition/699efa8a04a25a58c8548899</guid><description>Tata Technologies unveiled a strategic roadmap to capitalize on market shifts, emphasizing diversified global engineering capabilities, AI integration, and full-vehicle development. Key growth drivers include expansion into China's EV sector and Aerospace. The acquisition of Germany-based ES-Tec Group and focus on margin recovery aim to position the company for future growth and increased financial visibility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kuberan Global Edu Board to Consider Publishing Segment Sale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Kuberan-Global-Edu-Board-to-Consider-Publishing-Segment-Sale/699efa1004a25a58c8548801</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Kuberan-Global-Edu-Board-to-Consider-Publishing-Segment-Sale/699efa1004a25a58c8548801</guid><description>Kuberan Global Edu Solutions Limited will hold a board meeting on March 2, 2026, to evaluate the potential sale of its educational book publishing division. The divestment is proposed to be carried out as a slump sale for a lump-sum consideration, signaling a potential strategic shift for the company.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:33:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699efa1004a25a58c8548800_1772027212847.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences to launch innovative Semaglutide injection in India post-patent expiry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-to-launch-innovative-Semaglutide-injection-in-India-post-patent-expiry/699ef92604a25a58c85486cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-to-launch-innovative-Semaglutide-injection-in-India-post-patent-expiry/699ef92604a25a58c85486cb</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences is set to launch an indigenously developed Semaglutide Injection in India on Day 1 of patent expiry. The drug, targeting Type 2 Diabetes and Obesity, features a novel reusable pen with adjustable doses, enhancing patient convenience and affordability. This move taps into India's large and growing patient base for these conditions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Avanti Feeds Q3 FY26 Profit Jumps 10.5% to ₹149 Cr; Earnings Call Scheduled</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Avanti-Feeds-Q3-FY26-Profit-Jumps-105percent-to-149-Cr-Earnings-Call-Scheduled/699ef7ba04a25a58c854851b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Avanti-Feeds-Q3-FY26-Profit-Jumps-105percent-to-149-Cr-Earnings-Call-Scheduled/699ef7ba04a25a58c854851b</guid><description>Avanti Feeds has reported a strong Q3 FY26 performance, with net profit rising 10.5% year-on-year to ₹149.4 crore, driven by margin expansion. Revenue saw a modest increase to ₹1,383.5 crore. The company will host an investor conference call on March 3, 2026, to discuss these results and future outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank of Baroda Bags CARE AAA for Green Bonds; FY25 Profit ₹19,581 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-Baroda-Bags-CARE-AAA-for-Green-Bonds-FY25-Profit-19581-Cr/699ef74b04a25a58c8548451</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-Baroda-Bags-CARE-AAA-for-Green-Bonds-FY25-Profit-19581-Cr/699ef74b04a25a58c8548451</guid><description>Bank of Baroda's Green Infrastructure bonds have been assigned the highest 'CARE AAA; Stable' rating, signalling strong creditworthiness. The bank achieved a record net profit of ₹19,581 crore in FY25, though it anticipates near-term pressure on its net interest margins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:21:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ef74b04a25a58c8548450_1772025863009.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axis Bank to meet global investors at Daiwa Conference in Tokyo</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-to-meet-global-investors-at-Daiwa-Conference-in-Tokyo/699ef74504a25a58c854843b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-to-meet-global-investors-at-Daiwa-Conference-in-Tokyo/699ef74504a25a58c854843b</guid><description>Axis Bank will participate in the Daiwa Investment Conference in Tokyo, holding in-person group meetings with analysts and institutional investors on March 2-3, 2026. The bank has made a presentation available on its website, underscoring its commitment to transparent communication with stakeholders.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vishnu Prakash R Punglia: CARE Downgrades Rating to BB+; Outlook Negative</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vishnu-Prakash-R-Punglia-CARE-Downgrades-Rating-to-BB-Outlook-Negative/699ef5d804a25a58c8548240</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vishnu-Prakash-R-Punglia-CARE-Downgrades-Rating-to-BB-Outlook-Negative/699ef5d804a25a58c8548240</guid><description>CARE Ratings has downgraded Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Limited's long-term bank facilities to 'CARE BB+; Negative' and short-term facilities to 'CARE A4+'. The outlook revision from Stable to Negative reflects concerns over the company's deteriorating operational performance and stretched liquidity. Key drivers include an operating loss in Q3FY26 and persistent high working capital intensity, primarily due to delays in collections and work certifications from water supply projects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's EV Bet: Industrial Leap Over Hybrid Legacy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Bet-Industrial-Leap-Over-Hybrid-Legacy/699ef49e04a25a58c8547f4b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Bet-Industrial-Leap-Over-Hybrid-Legacy/699ef49e04a25a58c8547f4b</guid><description>India is prioritizing a decisive shift to electric vehicles (EVs) over hybrid technologies, viewing it as a critical industrial restructuring rather than merely an environmental choice. Former G20 Sherpa Amitabh Kant warned that clinging to intermediate solutions risks locking the nation into outdated systems as global supply chains pivot to EVs. This strategic acceleration is designed to fuel ambitious GDP growth targets, bolster manufacturing, and secure a leading role in emerging automotive value chains, supported by government incentives and a focus on export competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank of Baroda's Green Bonds Get 'AAA' Rating; Total Rated Amount Surges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-Barodas-Green-Bonds-Get-AAA-Rating-Total-Rated-Amount-Surges/699ef40804a25a58c8547e15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-Barodas-Green-Bonds-Get-AAA-Rating-Total-Rated-Amount-Surges/699ef40804a25a58c8547e15</guid><description>ICRA has assigned an 'AAA (Stable)' rating to Bank of Baroda's Long-Term Green Infrastructure Bonds worth ₹10,000 crore, significantly boosting its total rated amount to ₹16,500 crore. This upgrade underscores the bank's strong franchise, capitalisation, improving asset quality, and crucial sovereign ownership, supported by competitive funding. The rating action highlights confidence in the bank's financial stability and its commitment to sustainable finance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:07:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Siti Networks FY25 Loss Widens to ₹1954M on Plummeting Revenue Amid CIRP</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Siti-Networks-FY25-Loss-Widens-to-1954M-on-Plummeting-Revenue-Amid-CIRP/699ef3fe04a25a58c8547dfe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Siti-Networks-FY25-Loss-Widens-to-1954M-on-Plummeting-Revenue-Amid-CIRP/699ef3fe04a25a58c8547dfe</guid><description>Siti Networks Limited has submitted its audited FY25 financials, reporting a net loss of ₹1,954.06 million on revenue of ₹3,563.42 million. The company, under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) since February 2023, is facing significant compliance hurdles, including the inability to hold its Annual General Meeting due to regulatory rejections. This filing underscores the precarious operational and governance state of the company.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>