<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:45:17 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Eyes NBFC Bank Shift: Hurdles Outweigh Opportunity?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Eyes-NBFC-Bank-Shift-Hurdles-Outweigh-Opportunity/69a091070e2cce98568b97bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Eyes-NBFC-Bank-Shift-Hurdles-Outweigh-Opportunity/69a091070e2cce98568b97bc</guid><description>The Department of Financial Services is considering a pathway for Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs) to become universal banks, mirroring Small Finance Bank (SFB) transition norms. However, the stringent capital adequacy, asset quality, and operational requirements outlined by the Reserve Bank of India present a formidable barrier, suggesting only a select few NBFCs may realistically achieve this transformation. This regulatory proposal, while signaling potential liberalization, highlights the vast gap between current NBFC operations and universal banking standards, creating significant execution risks for aspiring institutions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:29:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a091070e2cce98568b97bb_1772131141818.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Carbon Market Aims to Unlock Renewables Amid PPA Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Carbon-Market-Aims-to-Unlock-Renewables-Amid-PPA-Woes/69a08e3d0e2cce98568b8dba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Carbon-Market-Aims-to-Unlock-Renewables-Amid-PPA-Woes/69a08e3d0e2cce98568b8dba</guid><description>India is set to launch a carbon trading platform by September to accelerate its renewable energy transition and meet its 500GW target by 2030. This initiative aims to circumvent the critical bottleneck of slow Power Purchase Agreement (PPA) signings. Complementing this, a new incentive scheme for thermal power plants will bolster grid stability, addressing intermittency challenges. This dual strategy signals a significant policy evolution focused on market mechanisms and operational integration to drive clean energy adoption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:17:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a08e3d0e2cce98568b8db9_1772130421727.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Micron Opens India Plant Amid AI Memory Surge, Faces Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Micron-Opens-India-Plant-Amid-AI-Memory-Surge-Faces-Market-Volatility/69a08daa0e2cce98568b8d57</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Micron-Opens-India-Plant-Amid-AI-Memory-Surge-Faces-Market-Volatility/69a08daa0e2cce98568b8d57</guid><description>Micron Technology has inaugurated its Rs 22,516 crore semiconductor assembly and testing plant in Sanand, Gujarat, marking a significant step in India's semiconductor ambitions. The facility will produce DRAM and NAND products crucial for AI applications, aiming to capitalize on soaring global memory demand. Despite robust stock performance and analyst optimism, the memory market faces inherent volatility, intense competition from established OSAT players, and execution challenges within India's developing ecosystem, posing risks alongside significant growth opportunities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:15:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a08daa0e2cce98568b8d56_1772130302060.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zaggle Wins Deals Amidst Rising Costs, Stock Recovers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zaggle-Wins-Deals-Amidst-Rising-Costs-Stock-Recovers/69a08a666e7998eb8432f424</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zaggle-Wins-Deals-Amidst-Rising-Costs-Stock-Recovers/69a08a666e7998eb8432f424</guid><description>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services announced securing new corporate expense solution agreements with Chennai Super Kings Cricket Limited and Saurashtra Cement Limited. This follows a strong third quarter where net profit surged 84.3% to ₹36.3 crore on a 56% revenue increase to ₹525.5 crore. The stock closed up 7.05% at ₹232.95 following the news. However, significant year-on-year increases in redemption and incentive expenses highlight potential margin pressures despite the growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Tax Shift: Direct Taxes Lead, GST Drives Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Shift-Direct-Taxes-Lead-GST-Drives-Revenue/69a088886e7998eb8432f2b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Shift-Direct-Taxes-Lead-GST-Drives-Revenue/69a088886e7998eb8432f2b3</guid><description>India's tax revenue has surged dramatically, with direct taxes now comprising nearly 58.5% of total collections, surpassing indirect taxes. This shift, driven by an expanding tax filer base and policy adjustments, indicates a more progressive tax system. Concurrently, Goods and Services Tax (GST) continues its strong growth, solidifying its position as the primary indirect tax source due to enhanced digital compliance and unified structures. Customs duty collections are moderating as the nation strategically prioritizes domestic manufacturing and consumption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:53:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a088886e7998eb8432f2b2_1772128981987.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sebi Battles Sophisticated Scams Amidst Indian Market Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Battles-Sophisticated-Scams-Amidst-Indian-Market-Growth/69a0871c6e7998eb8432f1e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Battles-Sophisticated-Scams-Amidst-Indian-Market-Growth/69a0871c6e7998eb8432f1e8</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) is confronting an alarming rise in sophisticated financial fraud, including STT demand scams and deceptive 'risk-free' investment schemes. Fraudsters are increasingly employing advanced tactics like impersonation and social engineering, targeting India's burgeoning retail investor base amid rapid digitalization. Despite Sebi's proactive enforcement and investor education efforts, the scale of financial crime, evidenced by substantial losses and evolving fraud typologies, presents a significant challenge to maintaining market integrity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:47:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0871c6e7998eb8432f1e7_1772128682021.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Hardware Obsolescence Risk: Burry Flags Tech Valuation Bubble</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Hardware-Obsolescence-Risk-Burry-Flags-Tech-Valuation-Bubble/69a081fd6e7998eb8432efe2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Hardware-Obsolescence-Risk-Burry-Flags-Tech-Valuation-Bubble/69a081fd6e7998eb8432efe2</guid><description>Investor Michael Burry is raising alarms over AI infrastructure, drawing parallels to historical market manias. His central concern targets the depreciation of critical AI hardware, arguing that rapid technological obsolescence makes GPUs' economic life far shorter than booked useful life. This discrepancy could inflate earnings by billions and distort valuations, particularly for pure-play Nvidia. Coupled with staggering capital expenditures and mounting corporate debt, this presents a significant risk to the AI buildout's sustainability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:25:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a081fd6e7998eb8432efe1_1772126853028.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Smallcap Funds: Liquidity Tests Mask Deeper Capital Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Smallcap-Funds-Liquidity-Tests-Mask-Deeper-Capital-Risk/69a07d566e7998eb8432e941</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Smallcap-Funds-Liquidity-Tests-Mask-Deeper-Capital-Risk/69a07d566e7998eb8432e941</guid><description>Liquidity stress tests reveal smallcap funds require significantly longer periods to liquidate assets, with Quant Small Cap Fund needing over 100 days. While these metrics highlight potential redemptions delays, experts caution that the greater threat to investors lies in capital erosion from market downturns, a risk amplified by high valuations and concentrated strategies in the small-cap segment. Mid-cap funds generally present a better liquidity profile. The outlook for small caps in 2026 remains mixed, contingent on economic growth and rate policies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:05:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a07d566e7998eb8432e940_1772126102101.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Prices Tense: Record Stockpiles vs. Iran Diplomacy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-Prices-Tense-Record-Stockpiles-vs-Iran-Diplomacy/69a07d246e7998eb8432dc9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Oil-Prices-Tense-Record-Stockpiles-vs-Iran-Diplomacy/69a07d246e7998eb8432dc9b</guid><description>Oil prices are navigating a challenging environment marked by a historic 16 million barrel surge in US crude inventories, the largest build in approximately three years. This fundamental bearish signal is being counterbalanced by significant geopolitical risk stemming from ongoing US-Iran nuclear negotiations. Analysts suggest this diplomatic uncertainty has embedded as much as a $10 per barrel premium into crude prices. Concurrently, Saudi Arabia is increasing production as a contingency, and OPEC+ is poised to consider an April output adjustment, further complicating the supply outlook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:04:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a07d246e7998eb8432dc9a_1772126042157.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Exchange India to raise ₹350 crore via securities; shareholder nod awaited</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Exchange-India-to-raise-350-crore-via-securities-shareholder-nod-awaited/69a07c9c6e7998eb8432cebe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Exchange-India-to-raise-350-crore-via-securities-shareholder-nod-awaited/69a07c9c6e7998eb8432cebe</guid><description>Steel Exchange India Limited announced its Board Meeting on March 4, 2026, to consider approving the issuance of securities worth up to ₹350 crore. This move is part of a larger ₹750 crore fundraising limit and requires shareholder approval. The company is looking to strengthen its financial position and fund growth initiatives.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:02:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a07c9c6e7998eb8432cebd_1772125492243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto Enters 401(k)s: A Stability Game Changer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-Enters-401ks-A-Stability-Game-Changer/69a07c5b6e7998eb8432b534</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-Enters-401ks-A-Stability-Game-Changer/69a07c5b6e7998eb8432b534</guid><description>Regulatory shifts in 2026 are propelling crypto integration into the $10 trillion US 401(k) market. This move transforms digital assets from fringe investments into potential stabilizing forces within retirement portfolios, mirroring a global trend of institutional adoption and regulatory clarity. The long-term impact promises a permanent fixture in American retirement savings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:01:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a07c5b6e7998eb8432b533_1772125481813.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UK Shuts Tax-Free Crypto ETN Access for Mainstream ISAs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/UK-Shuts-Tax-Free-Crypto-ETN-Access-for-Mainstream-ISAs/69a07c556e7998eb8432b51a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/UK-Shuts-Tax-Free-Crypto-ETN-Access-for-Mainstream-ISAs/69a07c556e7998eb8432b51a</guid><description>His Majesty's Revenue and Customs (HMRC) will reclassify cryptocurrency Exchange-Traded Notes (ETNs) from mainstream Stocks and Shares ISAs to the more obscure Innovative Finance ISAs (IFISAs) starting April 6, 2026. This regulatory shift significantly curtails tax-free investment opportunities for retail investors in digital assets, positioning the UK as an outlier among major financial markets embracing crypto ETPs. While existing holdings are unaffected, new investments will face substantial accessibility hurdles, raising concerns about market development and investor access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:01:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a07c556e7998eb8432b519_1772125438893.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tejas Networks Soars on NEC Deal; India Inc Faces AI, R&amp;D Gaps</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tejas-Networks-Soars-on-NEC-Deal-India-Inc-Faces-AI-RandD-Gaps/69a076419e91847a1e7b202a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tejas-Networks-Soars-on-NEC-Deal-India-Inc-Faces-AI-RandD-Gaps/69a076419e91847a1e7b202a</guid><description>Tejas Networks surged over 14% following a significant 5G massive MIMO radio agreement with NEC Corporation, contributing to a modest market uptick driven by renewed Foreign Portfolio Investor (FPI) buying. Despite this positive development, discussions persist regarding India Inc.'s critical deficit in research and development investment and the looming threat of "AI colonization." Meanwhile, global AI leader Nvidia's dominance faces escalating competition from rivals such as AMD and Marvell.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:35:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a076419e91847a1e7b2029_1772124362299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zaggle Prepaid inks 5-year employee solutions deal with Saurashtra Cement</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zaggle-Prepaid-inks-5-year-employee-solutions-deal-with-Saurashtra-Cement/69a076399e91847a1e7b1ffc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zaggle-Prepaid-inks-5-year-employee-solutions-deal-with-Saurashtra-Cement/69a076399e91847a1e7b1ffc</guid><description>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited has secured a 5-year agreement with Saurashtra Cement Limited to provide its Zaggle Save Employee Expense Management &amp; Benefits solution. This deal marks an expansion of Zaggle's corporate client base, reinforcing its strategy in the business solutions segment. Saurashtra Cement will leverage Zaggle's platform for enhanced employee benefits and expense management.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:35:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a076399e91847a1e7b1ffb_1772123762663.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Mech Projects: ₹57,811 Cr Backlog Fuels FY26 Target; Expands Renewables, MDO.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Mech-Projects-57811-Cr-Backlog-Fuels-FY26-Target-Expands-Renewables-MDO/69a074cf9e91847a1e7ab52b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Mech-Projects-57811-Cr-Backlog-Fuels-FY26-Target-Expands-Renewables-MDO/69a074cf9e91847a1e7ab52b</guid><description>Power Mech Projects is leveraging its strong ₹57,811 Cr order backlog to target ₹10,000 Cr in fresh order inflows for FY26. The company is strategically pivoting towards integrated EPC delivery, expanding into the high-growth renewables sector (solar, BESS), and scaling up its Mining Development and Operations (MDO) contracts. This diversification aims for higher margins and long-term recurring revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:29:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a074cf9e91847a1e7ab52a_1772123425098.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kabra Drugs plans name change, eyes expansion in Indonesia, Canada.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kabra-Drugs-plans-name-change-eyes-expansion-in-Indonesia-Canada/69a072029e91847a1e79f118</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kabra-Drugs-plans-name-change-eyes-expansion-in-Indonesia-Canada/69a072029e91847a1e79f118</guid><description>Kabra Drugs Limited will hold a board meeting on March 7, 2026, to consider a potential name change and discuss strategic expansion into Indonesia and Canada. These moves signal a significant push for global market presence and a potential rebranding effort for the API manufacturer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a072029e91847a1e79f117_1772122694464.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Addverb Shifts to Humanoid, Defense Robotics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Addverb-Shifts-to-Humanoid-Defense-Robotics/69a070229e91847a1e79c149</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Addverb-Shifts-to-Humanoid-Defense-Robotics/69a070229e91847a1e79c149</guid><description>Noida-based Addverb Technologies is aggressively diversifying beyond warehouse automation into advanced robotics, including AI-powered humanoid robots and specialized defense machines. This strategic pivot, aiming to capture new markets and leverage its manufacturing prowess, is underpinned by a significant ambition to become a global automation leader. The company is reportedly preparing to raise up to $150 million to fuel this expansion, signaling a significant capital commitment to research, development, and international market penetration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:09:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a070229e91847a1e79c148_1772122637864.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Freshworks Backs Stock with $400M Buyback Amidst Decline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Freshworks-Backs-Stock-with-400M-Buyback-Amidst-Decline/69a06f329e91847a1e79c066</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Freshworks-Backs-Stock-with-400M-Buyback-Amidst-Decline/69a06f329e91847a1e79c066</guid><description>Freshworks Inc. authorized a $400 million share repurchase program, signaling management's confidence amidst a severe stock decline. The software company posted 16% revenue growth to $838.8 million in 2025 and achieved GAAP profitability, yet its shares fell over 60%. This strategy aims to counter investor skepticism and a valuation disconnect, even as analyst sentiment leans cautiously optimistic with an average 'Buy' rating and significant price target upside.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:05:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a06f329e91847a1e79c065_1772122501430.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSB Profit Surge: Value Play or Lingering Risks?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSB-Profit-Surge-Value-Play-or-Lingering-Risks/69a06de99e91847a1e7900db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSB-Profit-Surge-Value-Play-or-Lingering-Risks/69a06de99e91847a1e7900db</guid><description>Public sector banks (PSBs) have posted a significant profit surge in the last quarter, driven by asset quality improvements and treasury gains. State Bank of India led the charge, with Canara Bank and Bank of Baroda also showing strong treasury performance. Punjab National Bank and Central Bank of India also contributed to this trend. However, the underlying question remains whether these gains represent a sustainable shift or are supported by transient factors, especially when compared to the agility and customer service efficiency of their private sector counterparts. The government's ambitious ₹80,000 crore disinvestment target for FY27 adds another layer to the fiscal outlook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a06de99e91847a1e7900da_1772121861044.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Edtech Consolidation Accelerates Amidst Valuation Reset</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Edtech-Consolidation-Accelerates-Amidst-Valuation-Reset/69a06dcc9e91847a1e7900c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Edtech-Consolidation-Accelerates-Amidst-Valuation-Reset/69a06dcc9e91847a1e7900c4</guid><description>India's edtech market is consolidating, with upGrad acquiring Internshala for approximately ₹100 crore via stock swap. This move reflects a broader industry shift from hyper-growth to a more disciplined cycle focused on product depth, measurable outcomes, and retention as key valuation drivers. Investor caution, amplified by high-profile sector corrections, now scrutinizes unit economics over rapid scaling, with consolidation becoming a strategic necessity for many players.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:59:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a06dcc9e91847a1e7900c3_1772122202441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Retail Investors Retreat: Active Demat Accounts Plummet</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Retail-Investors-Retreat-Active-Demat-Accounts-Plummet/69a069959e91847a1e78fd86</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Retail-Investors-Retreat-Active-Demat-Accounts-Plummet/69a069959e91847a1e78fd86</guid><description>Active demat accounts in India have fallen significantly, with only about one-third operational by January 2026. This trend marks a retreat from the retail investor boom post-pandemic. Factors like market volatility, substantial losses in derivatives trading, stretched valuations, and FII outflows are contributing to cautious sentiment. Domestic institutional investors (DIIs) are now dominant, absorbing much of the capital that foreign players are exiting, while SEBI tightens oversight on speculative trading and 'finfluencers'. This shift raises concerns over future market liquidity and the sustainability of current valuations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:41:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a069959e91847a1e78fd85_1772121062094.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Regulators Push Stablecoin Rules Amidst Charter Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Regulators-Push-Stablecoin-Rules-Amidst-Charter-Scrutiny/69a0696a9e91847a1e78fd55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Regulators-Push-Stablecoin-Rules-Amidst-Charter-Scrutiny/69a0696a9e91847a1e78fd55</guid><description>U.S. banking regulators are actively shaping the stablecoin landscape, with the OCC proposing rules for the GENIUS Act, aiming for safe industry growth. The Federal Reserve is also developing capital and liquidity standards. This push for clarity follows years of a hesitant stance. However, this evolving regulatory friendliness faces scrutiny, notably from Senator Elizabeth Warren, who is questioning the accelerated charter approval for Erebor Bank, a digital asset-focused institution, citing concerns about political favoritism. The tension between regulatory enablement and oversight scrutiny creates a complex environment for digital asset innovation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0696a9e91847a1e78fd54_1772120485434.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Talent Wars Escalate: Meta &amp; Apple Lose Researchers to OpenAI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Talent-Wars-Escalate-Meta-and-Apple-Lose-Researchers-to-OpenAI/69a069059e91847a1e78fcb0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Talent-Wars-Escalate-Meta-and-Apple-Lose-Researchers-to-OpenAI/69a069059e91847a1e78fcb0</guid><description>OpenAI has recruited Ruoming Pang, a significant AI researcher, from Meta Platforms Inc., who had joined Meta only months prior from Apple. Pang led AI infrastructure at Meta's Superintelligence Labs. This move intensifies the AI talent war, with top researchers commanding packages reportedly exceeding $200 million. The aggressive recruitment by OpenAI and other tech giants raises questions about the financial sustainability of such high compensation and the strategic implications for companies like Meta and Apple, which are losing critical AI expertise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:38:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a069059e91847a1e78fcaf_1772120604956.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Merlin Group Bets Big on Pune with ₹273 Cr Mundhwa Land Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Merlin-Group-Bets-Big-on-Pune-with-273-Cr-Mundhwa-Land-Deal/69a068299e91847a1e78fbae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Merlin-Group-Bets-Big-on-Pune-with-273-Cr-Mundhwa-Land-Deal/69a068299e91847a1e78fbae</guid><description>Kolkata-based Merlin Group has acquired a 3.26-acre land parcel in Pune's Mundhwa locality for ₹273 crore through its subsidiary, Merlin Prime Spaces. The developer plans to invest over ₹1,000 crore to construct an office-led commercial project targeting banking, financial services, insurance (BFSI) companies and Global Capability Centres (GCCs). The project, slated for completion by 2030, is projected to be valued at ₹3,000 crore upon occupation. This strategic acquisition signals Merlin Group's aggressive expansion into the Pune market, aiming to capitalize on the city's burgeoning commercial real estate demand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:35:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a068299e91847a1e78fbad_1772120276005.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel Invests ₹2,401 Cr In Foreign Arm TSHP</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Invests-2401-Cr-In-Foreign-Arm-TSHP/69a067429e91847a1e78fa44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Invests-2401-Cr-In-Foreign-Arm-TSHP/69a067429e91847a1e78fa44</guid><description>Tata Steel Limited has acquired an additional equity stake in its wholly-owned foreign subsidiary, T Steel Holdings Pte. Ltd (TSHP), for ₹2,401.50 crore (USD 264 million). This transaction on February 26, 2026, ensures TSHP continues as a wholly-owned entity and is part of the company's ongoing capital infusions into its international operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:31:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a067429e91847a1e78fa43_1772120582544.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UP Lands Auto Giants Suzuki, Honda for Green Mobility Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/UP-Lands-Auto-Giants-Suzuki-Honda-for-Green-Mobility-Push/69a0673f9e91847a1e78fa2e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/UP-Lands-Auto-Giants-Suzuki-Honda-for-Green-Mobility-Push/69a0673f9e91847a1e78fa2e</guid><description>Uttar Pradesh's Chief Minister secured substantial investment proposals totaling ₹2.5 lakh crore with ₹1.5 lakh crore in MoUs from Suzuki Motor and Honda Motor during Japan and Singapore roadshows. These commitments target green mobility, renewable energy via compressed bio-gas plants, and expanded automotive supply chains. Suzuki indicated potential doubling of Maruti Suzuki's India capacity, solidifying UP's role as a key industrial growth corridor championing sustainable development.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:31:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0673f9e91847a1e78fa2d_1772120033361.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gem Aromatics Secures $1M Export Orders, Launches New Products at Dahej</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Gem-Aromatics-Secures-1M-Export-Orders-Launches-New-Products-at-Dahej/69a067389e91847a1e78fa14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Gem-Aromatics-Secures-1M-Export-Orders-Launches-New-Products-at-Dahej/69a067389e91847a1e78fa14</guid><description>Gem Aromatics is seeing a rebound in international demand, securing USD 1 million in export orders from the US and Europe. The company has also begun commercial production of cooling agents and Safranal at its Dahej facility, diversifying its product portfolio and bolstering manufacturing capabilities. This comes as the company continues planned work on its MEHQ catalyst manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a067389e91847a1e78fa13_1772120369147.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Israel FTA Talks Resume Amid Trade Dip and Geopolitical Currents</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Israel-FTA-Talks-Resume-Amid-Trade-Dip-and-Geopolitical-Currents/69a066219e91847a1e78f84a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Israel-FTA-Talks-Resume-Amid-Trade-Dip-and-Geopolitical-Currents/69a066219e91847a1e78f84a</guid><description>India and Israel have initiated the first round of negotiations for a Free Trade Agreement (FTA), with the next session scheduled for May 2026 in Israel. This marks a renewed effort to boost bilateral trade after previous talks stalled in October 2021. While both nations highlight significant untapped potential in sectors like technology and agriculture, recent trade data reveals a sharp decline in bilateral commerce for FY2024-25, with exports falling 52%. The push for an ambitious pact occurs amidst global geopolitical volatility and India's broader strategy to diversify trade partnerships, including recent FTAs with the EU and other nations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:26:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a066219e91847a1e78f849_1772120032571.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RCOM Legal Onslaught: Assets Seized Amidst Escalating Fraud Allegations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/RCOM-Legal-Onslaught-Assets-Seized-Amidst-Escalating-Fraud-Allegations/69a065d69e91847a1e78f804</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/RCOM-Legal-Onslaught-Assets-Seized-Amidst-Escalating-Fraud-Allegations/69a065d69e91847a1e78f804</guid><description>Anil Ambani was questioned for nine hours by the Enforcement Directorate (ED) and faces a new CBI case for an alleged ₹2,223.17 crore fraud against Bank of Baroda. The ED provisionally attached his ₹3,716 crore Mumbai residence, 'Abode,' as part of a money-laundering probe linked to Reliance Communications (RCOM). These actions compound RCOM's ongoing insolvency proceedings, impacting an already dire financial situation against a backdrop of strong sector growth from competitors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:25:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a065d69e91847a1e78f803_1772119828377.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emergent Industrial Solutions Seeks ₹1650 Cr MRPT Approval for FY26-27</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Emergent-Industrial-Solutions-Seeks-1650-Cr-MRPT-Approval-for-FY26-27/69a064689e91847a1e78f68c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Emergent-Industrial-Solutions-Seeks-1650-Cr-MRPT-Approval-for-FY26-27/69a064689e91847a1e78f68c</guid><description>Emergent Industrial Solutions Limited is seeking shareholder nod for material related party transactions (MRPTs) totalling ₹1650 crore for FY2026-27. These proposed purchases from entities like Indo Resources DMCC and Indo International Trading FZCO, while crucial for operations, cross SEBI's materiality threshold, requiring investor consent. The voting period runs from February 28 to March 29, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:19:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a064689e91847a1e78f68b_1772119255467.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Divide: Nvidia Soars, Salesforce Faces AI Disruption Threat</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Divide-Nvidia-Soars-Salesforce-Faces-AI-Disruption-Threat/69a0631f9e91847a1e78f4b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Divide-Nvidia-Soars-Salesforce-Faces-AI-Disruption-Threat/69a0631f9e91847a1e78f4b9</guid><description>Nvidia posted record fourth-quarter revenue and earnings, driven by strong AI chip demand, with its stock climbing. Conversely, Salesforce shares dipped after issuing fiscal 2027 revenue guidance that fell short of expectations. This stark contrast illuminates the widening chasm in the tech sector, as AI infrastructure providers like Nvidia thrive, while established software giants like Salesforce grapple with the existential threat AI poses to traditional business models. Labor market data and commodity prices showed mixed signals, with jobless claims remaining historically low and oil prices declining on oversupply concerns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:13:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0631f9e91847a1e78f4b8_1772118975318.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lupin CEO Vinita Gupta Named CNBC Changemaker; US Business Ranks 3rd</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-CEO-Vinita-Gupta-Named-CNBC-Changemaker-US-Business-Ranks-3rd/69a0631e9e91847a1e78f4a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-CEO-Vinita-Gupta-Named-CNBC-Changemaker-US-Business-Ranks-3rd/69a0631e9e91847a1e78f4a2</guid><description>Lupin CEO Vinita Gupta has been honored on the 2026 CNBC Changemakers List, recognizing her leadership in transforming industries. This accolade highlights Lupin's robust growth, particularly its U.S. generic business, which ranks as the third-largest supplier, and the company's global standing as the seventh-largest pharmaceutical firm by volume. The recognition underscores strategic achievements like the late-2025 FDA approval for its biosimilar Pegfilgrastim and ongoing expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:13:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0631e9e91847a1e78f4a1_1772119382696.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Review Signals Major Shift in India's Commodity Derivatives</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/SEBI-Review-Signals-Major-Shift-in-Indias-Commodity-Derivatives/69a063019e91847a1e78f46f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/SEBI-Review-Signals-Major-Shift-in-Indias-Commodity-Derivatives/69a063019e91847a1e78f46f</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has received reports from working groups reviewing the agricultural commodity derivatives framework, concurrently planning a similar deep dive into non-agricultural segments. This dual focus signals SEBI's intent to modernize market operations, enhance liquidity, and potentially attract greater institutional investment, aiming for optimized efficiency without compromising market integrity. The move is poised to reshape India's commodity derivatives landscape, aligning it with global best practices and fostering greater price discovery and risk management capabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:13:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a063019e91847a1e78f46e_1772118893511.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Israel FTA: Strategic Trade Pact Faces Geopolitical Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Israel-FTA-Strategic-Trade-Pact-Faces-Geopolitical-Headwinds/69a062939e91847a1e78f3a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Israel-FTA-Strategic-Trade-Pact-Faces-Geopolitical-Headwinds/69a062939e91847a1e78f3a9</guid><description>The inaugural round of India-Israel Free Trade Agreement (FTA) negotiations has concluded in New Delhi, focusing on a 'modern, comprehensive, and future-ready' pact. Discussions covered goods, services, IPR, and digital trade, aiming to leverage bilateral merchandise trade of $3.62 billion (FY25). While optimism prevails for enhanced cooperation in sectors like technology, agriculture, and defense, the agreement must navigate regional geopolitical volatility and intricate economic integration challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:11:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a062939e91847a1e78f3a8_1772118828551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Labor Market Tightens: Claims Rise, Payroll Revisions Signal Slowdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Labor-Market-Tightens-Claims-Rise-Payroll-Revisions-Signal-Slowdown/69a062909e91847a1e78f392</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Labor-Market-Tightens-Claims-Rise-Payroll-Revisions-Signal-Slowdown/69a062909e91847a1e78f392</guid><description>Initial jobless claims rose to 212,000 for the week ending February 21, marking a slight uptick but remaining near historically low levels. However, a significant downward revision to 2024-2025 payroll figures, slashing job creation by hundreds of thousands to just 181,000 last year, points to a structural deceleration in the U.S. labor market. This trend, coupled with job openings falling to a five-year low, reinforces an economic environment characterized by a "low-hire, low-fire" dynamic, where finding new employment is increasingly challenging despite low unemployment rates. Lingering effects from high interest rates and trade uncertainties continue to hamper hiring momentum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:11:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a062909e91847a1e78f391_1772118794188.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>iValue Infosolutions to Host Investor Call on AI Impact March 4</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/iValue-Infosolutions-to-Host-Investor-Call-on-AI-Impact-March-4/69a0628a9e91847a1e78f37b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/iValue-Infosolutions-to-Host-Investor-Call-on-AI-Impact-March-4/69a0628a9e91847a1e78f37b</guid><description>iValue Infosolutions Limited announced it will host a virtual business update call for investors on March 4, 2026. The meeting will focus on the strategic impact of Artificial Intelligence (AI) on the company, featuring management representatives and its Strategic Technology Advisor. The discussion will draw solely from publicly available information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:11:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0628a9e91847a1e78f37a_1772118991041.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fino Payments Bank Seeks Shareholder Nod for CEO Pay &amp; 3-Yr Re-appointment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Payments-Bank-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-CEO-Pay-and-3-Yr-Re-appointment/69a061979e91847a1e78f20e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Payments-Bank-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-CEO-Pay-and-3-Yr-Re-appointment/69a061979e91847a1e78f20e</guid><description>Fino Payments Bank is seeking shareholder approval through a postal ballot for two key resolutions concerning its MD &amp; CEO, Rishi Gupta. The resolutions involve approving his remuneration of ₹5.70 crore for FY 2024-25 and re-appointing him for a three-year term from May 2026. This move ensures leadership continuity as the bank progresses towards its planned conversion into a Small Finance Bank.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:07:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a061979e91847a1e78f20d_1772118569585.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's CAFE 3 Norms Force EV Shift, Auto Sector Faces Cost Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-CAFE-3-Norms-Force-EV-Shift-Auto-Sector-Faces-Cost-Squeeze/69a061379e91847a1e78f197</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-CAFE-3-Norms-Force-EV-Shift-Auto-Sector-Faces-Cost-Squeeze/69a061379e91847a1e78f197</guid><description>India is set to implement its third phase of Corporate Average Fuel Efficiency (CAFE) norms from April 2027, significantly tightening fuel efficiency benchmarks for passenger vehicles. The new regulations will mandate lower fleet-wide CO₂ emissions, encouraging greater adoption of electric and hybrid vehicles. While promoting cleaner mobility, CAFE 3 is anticipated to raise production costs, particularly for entry-level vehicles, and may force strategic recalibrations across the automotive sector, favoring companies with strong investments in sustainable technologies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:05:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a061379e91847a1e78f196_1772118613697.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Ruling Boosts India's Trade Talk Leverage</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Tariff-Ruling-Boosts-Indias-Trade-Talk-Leverage/69a0603f9e91847a1e78f081</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Tariff-Ruling-Boosts-Indias-Trade-Talk-Leverage/69a0603f9e91847a1e78f081</guid><description>US Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnik met Indian Minister Piyush Goyal on February 26, 2026, following the Supreme Court's February 20th ruling invalidating President Trump's tariffs under IEEPA. This decision removed the US's primary unilateral leverage tool, potentially strengthening India's position in ongoing trade deal negotiations. Despite the US imposing new temporary global tariffs under Section 122 of the Trade Act, India has deferred its delegation's visit to reassess terms, seeking greater clarity and safeguards. The framework deal, previously targeting an 18% reciprocal tariff from the US and $500 billion in Indian purchases, now faces recalibration amidst lingering policy uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:01:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0603f9e91847a1e78f080_1772118150606.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AU Small Finance Bank Rating Affirmed 'AA'; Strong Capital, Universal Bank Transition Underway</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AU-Small-Finance-Bank-Rating-Affirmed-AA-Strong-Capital-Universal-Bank-Transition-Underway/69a060359e91847a1e78f067</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AU-Small-Finance-Bank-Rating-Affirmed-AA-Strong-Capital-Universal-Bank-Transition-Underway/69a060359e91847a1e78f067</guid><description>ICRA has reaffirmed AU Small Finance Bank's long-term debt rating at '[ICRA] AA; Stable'. The rating highlights the bank's robust retail asset franchise and adequate capitalization. However, potential deposit outflows due to de-empanelment for government business in Haryana and asset quality management during its transition to a universal bank remain key monitorables.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:01:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a060359e91847a1e78f066_1772118174443.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>