<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:47:19 +0000</pubDate><item><title>EMS Approves ₹300 Cr QIP, Boosts Share Capital for Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EMS-Approves-300-Cr-QIP-Boosts-Share-Capital-for-Growth/69a18f81fa7d0695d1abc1e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EMS-Approves-300-Cr-QIP-Boosts-Share-Capital-for-Growth/69a18f81fa7d0695d1abc1e8</guid><description>EMS Limited's board has greenlit a substantial fundraising plan, approving up to ₹300 Crores via a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP). The company also proposed increasing its authorised share capital to facilitate future growth. This move is subject to regulatory and shareholder approvals, with an EGM scheduled soon.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TIL Ltd Board Okays ₹200 Cr Rights Issue; Details March 5</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TIL-Ltd-Board-Okays-200-Cr-Rights-Issue-Details-March-5/69a18f77fa7d0695d1abc1d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TIL-Ltd-Board-Okays-200-Cr-Rights-Issue-Details-March-5/69a18f77fa7d0695d1abc1d1</guid><description>TIL Limited's Board of Directors has approved a Rights Issue to raise up to ₹200 crore, signalling a move towards capital expansion and funding strategic growth initiatives. The company's Rights Issue Committee will meet on March 05, 2026, to finalise crucial details like the record date and issue price. The fundraising is crucial for its expansion strategy and integration into the Gainwell Group, though it comes amidst existing high debt levels and past regulatory scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:35:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18f77fa7d0695d1abc1d0_1772196063500.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Forex Reserves Fall From Record; RBI Intervenes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Fall-From-Record-RBI-Intervenes/69a18ea2fa7d0695d1abc0dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Fall-From-Record-RBI-Intervenes/69a18ea2fa7d0695d1abc0dc</guid><description>India's foreign exchange reserves decreased by $2.119 billion to $723.608 billion in the week ending February 20, 2026, following a record high of $725.727 billion. This decline, driven by reduced foreign currency assets and gold holdings, suggests the Reserve Bank of India may have intervened to curb rupee depreciation against a strengthening dollar amidst global geopolitical tensions. Investors are now scrutinizing reserve sustainability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:31:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18ea2fa7d0695d1abc0db_1772195786715.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jaiprakash Power Ventures Faces NCLT Insolvency Plea Over ₹511 Cr Default Claim</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jaiprakash-Power-Ventures-Faces-NCLT-Insolvency-Plea-Over-511-Cr-Default-Claim/69a18db8fa7d0695d1abbf43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jaiprakash-Power-Ventures-Faces-NCLT-Insolvency-Plea-Over-511-Cr-Default-Claim/69a18db8fa7d0695d1abbf43</guid><description>Jaiprakash Power Ventures Limited (JPVL) is facing a critical legal challenge as National Asset Reconstruction Company Limited (NARCL) has filed an application with the NCLT Allahabad seeking to initiate Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP). The application alleges a default of ₹511.72 crore, plus interest, stemming from a corporate guarantee JPVL provided for Jaiprakash Associates Limited. This development casts a shadow over the company's financial stability and operational future.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:27:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18db8fa7d0695d1abbf42_1772195371466.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Banks Face Funding Squeeze as Credit Outstrips Deposits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Banks-Face-Funding-Squeeze-as-Credit-Outstrips-Deposits/69a18da0fa7d0695d1abbf22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Banks-Face-Funding-Squeeze-as-Credit-Outstrips-Deposits/69a18da0fa7d0695d1abbf22</guid><description>As of January 2026, India's banking system is experiencing a significant imbalance, with credit growth accelerating to 14.4% year-on-year while deposit expansion lags at 12.5%. This widening gap is pushing the credit-to-deposit ratio to historic highs, pressuring banks to increase funding costs and potentially impacting net interest margins. While economic momentum supports loan demand, the challenge lies in securing stable, cost-effective deposits.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:27:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18da0fa7d0695d1abbf21_1772195377662.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alka India AGM to vote on Name Change, ₹5000 Cr Borrowing, Agro Acquisitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Alka-India-AGM-to-vote-on-Name-Change-5000-Cr-Borrowing-Agro-Acquisitions/69a18bf0fa7d0695d1abbc93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Alka-India-AGM-to-vote-on-Name-Change-5000-Cr-Borrowing-Agro-Acquisitions/69a18bf0fa7d0695d1abbc93</guid><description>Alka India Limited will hold its 31st Annual General Meeting on March 23, 2026, proposing a significant strategic overhaul. Key agenda items include a name change to AUDROC Limited, shifting its registered office to Gujarat, and a substantial increase in borrowing limits to ₹5,000 crore. The company also seeks approval for a preferential share issue to acquire seven agro-product companies and disinvestment in its subsidiary, Vintage FZE.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18bf0fa7d0695d1abbc92_1772195427510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Swojas Foods Converts Warrants, Infuses ₹1.98 Cr Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Swojas-Foods-Converts-Warrants-Infuses-198-Cr-Capital/69a18bb7fa7d0695d1abbc5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Swojas-Foods-Converts-Warrants-Infuses-198-Cr-Capital/69a18bb7fa7d0695d1abbc5d</guid><description>Swojas Foods Limited has successfully converted 1.6 million warrants into equity shares, raising ₹1.98 crore. This move increases the company's paid-up equity share capital to ₹366.63 crore, strengthening its financial base. The conversion follows a larger preferential issue approved by shareholders and regulators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:19:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18bb7fa7d0695d1abbc5c_1772195068193.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki's NEXA Studio Expansion: Premium Reach or Margin Strain?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzukis-NEXA-Studio-Expansion-Premium-Reach-or-Margin-Strain/69a18b6bfa7d0695d1abbbd5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzukis-NEXA-Studio-Expansion-Premium-Reach-or-Margin-Strain/69a18b6bfa7d0695d1abbbd5</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki aims to significantly scale its NEXA Studio network to 600-700 outlets by 2030-31, targeting untapped potential in India's non-urban areas. The company expects these smaller format premium retail points to account for 25-30% of its NEXA channel sales, a substantial increase from the current 8-10%. This strategic push aligns with a broader industry shift towards premium vehicles, even as mass-market affordability becomes a concern.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:17:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18b6bfa7d0695d1abbbd4_1772194749351.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HealthX Platform: SHBL merger approved post-Mitsubishi stake sale; Envision gains rights</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HealthX-Platform-SHBL-merger-approved-post-Mitsubishi-stake-sale-Envision-gains-rights/69a189d9fa7d0695d1abb9fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/HealthX-Platform-SHBL-merger-approved-post-Mitsubishi-stake-sale-Envision-gains-rights/69a189d9fa7d0695d1abb9fe</guid><description>HealthX Platform Limited's subsidiary, Sastasundar Healthbuddy (SHBL), has approved a Tripartite Agreement to merge with its parent company, HealthX. This follows Envision India Fund's acquisition of Mitsubishi Corporation's entire stake in SHBL. Envision India Fund will gain board observer and potential director rights, with the merger's consummation contingent on legal compliance and final valuation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:11:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a189d9fa7d0695d1abb9fd_1772194579243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SIPs: ₹1 Crore Goal Hinges on Time &amp; Inflation, Not Just Returns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SIPs-1-Crore-Goal-Hinges-on-Time-and-Inflation-Not-Just-Returns/69a18970fa7d0695d1abb95d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SIPs-1-Crore-Goal-Hinges-on-Time-and-Inflation-Not-Just-Returns/69a18970fa7d0695d1abb95d</guid><description>Achieving a ₹1 crore corpus through Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) in India faces a significant hurdle: the extended time required for compounding to overcome initial contributions. A standard Rs 40,000 monthly SIP over 10 years at 12% annual returns falls short of the target. While step-up SIPs offer a potential solution, the erosion of real wealth due to inflation remains a critical, often-overlooked, factor, demanding a realistic assessment of future purchasing power and alternative wealth-building strategies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:09:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18970fa7d0695d1abb95c_1772194310495.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motisons Jewellers Board to Consider ₹350 Crore Fundraising on March 6</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Motisons-Jewellers-Board-to-Consider-350-Crore-Fundraising-on-March-6/69a188e7fa7d0695d1abb8cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Motisons-Jewellers-Board-to-Consider-350-Crore-Fundraising-on-March-6/69a188e7fa7d0695d1abb8cf</guid><description>Motisons Jewellers has called a Board meeting for March 6, 2026, to evaluate a significant fundraising proposal of up to ₹350 crore. The capital infusion could fuel future growth, expansion, or debt reduction. The agenda also includes increasing authorized share capital and appointing merchant bankers to manage the process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:07:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a188e7fa7d0695d1abb8ce_1772194311097.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Sector's AI Fears Overshadow Banking Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IT-Sectors-AI-Fears-Overshadow-Banking-Strength/69a18762fa7d0695d1abb709</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/IT-Sectors-AI-Fears-Overshadow-Banking-Strength/69a18762fa7d0695d1abb709</guid><description>Indian benchmark indices concluded February with declines, largely due to a historic sell-off in the information technology sector driven by artificial intelligence disruption fears. This led to the Nifty IT index's worst monthly performance since 2008, wiping out trillions in market cap. However, select sectors like banking and consumer durables posted gains, indicating a bifurcated market. Global geopolitical concerns and a rise in volatility further pressured sentiment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:00:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18762fa7d0695d1abb708_1772193773257.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shanti Spintex Board Approves Rajeshwari Cotspin Resolution, Credit, Trading Account</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Shanti-Spintex-Board-Approves-Rajeshwari-Cotspin-Resolution-Credit-Trading-Account/69a1870afa7d0695d1abb644</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Shanti-Spintex-Board-Approves-Rajeshwari-Cotspin-Resolution-Credit-Trading-Account/69a1870afa7d0695d1abb644</guid><description>Shanti Spintex Limited's board met on February 27, 2026, approving strategic initiatives including joining a consortium for Rajeshwari Cotspin Limited's resolution plan. The company will also leverage new credit facilities, potentially from Tata Capital, and establish a commodity trading account, signaling diversification and expansion efforts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:59:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1870afa7d0695d1abb643_1772193692246.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-EU FTA: Mercedes-Benz Navigates Phased Gains Amidst Cost Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Mercedes-Benz-Navigates-Phased-Gains-Amidst-Cost-Pressures/69a186effa7d0695d1abb5e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Mercedes-Benz-Navigates-Phased-Gains-Amidst-Cost-Pressures/69a186effa7d0695d1abb5e2</guid><description>Santosh Iyer, MD &amp; CEO of Mercedes-Benz India, sees Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) as key catalysts for India's economic integration and automotive competitiveness. While FTAs promise future tariff reductions on premium European vehicles, their phased implementation and quota restrictions mean immediate financial impact for Mercedes-Benz Group AG is limited. The company faces significant investments in electrification and competitive pressures, particularly in China, tempering immediate enthusiasm despite a favorable P/E ratio and positive analyst outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:58:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a186effa7d0695d1abb5e1_1772193792360.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Loans Surge: India's Financial Safety Net Amidst Credit Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Gold-Loans-Surge-Indias-Financial-Safety-Net-Amidst-Credit-Squeeze/69a186adfa7d0695d1abb532</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Gold-Loans-Surge-Indias-Financial-Safety-Net-Amidst-Credit-Squeeze/69a186adfa7d0695d1abb532</guid><description>India's gold loan market is experiencing explosive growth, up 42% year-on-year, as high gold prices and tighter unsecured lending channels drive demand. Banks are rapidly increasing their market share, challenging established NBFCs, especially ahead of new RBI regulations effective April 1, 2026. This surge highlights a growing reliance on gold as a critical financial buffer for a broad segment of the population, indicating a fundamental shift in credit accessibility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:57:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a186adfa7d0695d1abb531_1772193579206.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brijlaxmi Leasing Open Offer: ₹6.53 Cr Bid at ₹10.05/Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Brijlaxmi-Leasing-Open-Offer-653-Cr-Bid-at-1005Share/69a1869dfa7d0695d1abb517</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Brijlaxmi-Leasing-Open-Offer-653-Cr-Bid-at-1005Share/69a1869dfa7d0695d1abb517</guid><description>Brijlaxmi Leasing and Finance Limited has announced an open offer where acquirers, including its promoters and related entities, plan to buy up to 64,99,889 equity shares at ₹10.05 each. The total offer value stands at ₹6.53 crore. This move provides public shareholders an exit opportunity at a fixed price and could lead to a change in the company's shareholding structure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:57:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1869dfa7d0695d1abb516_1772193540845.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Abbott-Novo Nordisk India Launch Bets on Patent Expiry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Abbott-Novo-Nordisk-India-Launch-Bets-on-Patent-Expiry/69a18693fa7d0695d1abb4fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Abbott-Novo-Nordisk-India-Launch-Bets-on-Patent-Expiry/69a18693fa7d0695d1abb4fe</guid><description>Abbott and Novo Nordisk India have joined forces to introduce Extensior, a new semaglutide injection, targeting India's rapidly expanding diabetes market. The collaboration is strategically timed to coincide with the March 20, 2026, expiry of semaglutide's patent in India, aiming to significantly expand access to GLP-1 therapy by offering a potentially more affordable alternative to existing premium brands like Ozempic. This move capitalizes on the country's substantial diabetes burden and the anticipated surge in generic competition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:57:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18693fa7d0695d1abb4fd_1772193590765.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW Energy Secures Rail Infrastructure Amidst Insolvency Proceedings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/JSW-Energy-Secures-Rail-Infrastructure-Amidst-Insolvency-Proceedings/69a185d6fa7d0695d1abb359</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/JSW-Energy-Secures-Rail-Infrastructure-Amidst-Insolvency-Proceedings/69a185d6fa7d0695d1abb359</guid><description>JSW Energy Ltd. has secured approval from the bankruptcy court to acquire Raigarh Champa Rail Infrastructure (RCRIPL) via insolvency resolution. This Rs 700 crore acquisition offers lenders a recovery of approximately 129% on admitted liabilities of ₹543 crore. RCRIPL provides sole rail infrastructure for coal transportation to JSW Energy's subsidiary, KSK Mahanadi Power Company Ltd. (KMPCL), marking a strategic consolidation of critical assets to optimize logistics and costs within JSW Energy's expanding power generation portfolio.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:53:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a185d6fa7d0695d1abb358_1772193359553.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kansai Nerolac Paints Shareholders Approve Nerofix Merger With Overwhelming Majority</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kansai-Nerolac-Paints-Shareholders-Approve-Nerofix-Merger-With-Overwhelming-Majority/69a185c0fa7d0695d1abb338</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kansai-Nerolac-Paints-Shareholders-Approve-Nerofix-Merger-With-Overwhelming-Majority/69a185c0fa7d0695d1abb338</guid><description>Shareholders of Kansai Nerolac Paints Limited gave a near-unanimous approval for the amalgamation with its wholly-owned subsidiary, Nerofix Private Limited, at a meeting on February 27, 2026. This decisive vote marks a crucial step towards merging Nerofix, which specializes in adhesives and construction chemicals, into the parent paint company. The move is set to streamline operations and unlock synergies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:53:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a185c0fa7d0695d1abb337_1772193322337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Leadership Stalls: Finance Demands Clash at the Top</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Leadership-Stalls-Finance-Demands-Clash-at-the-Top/69a18514fa7d0695d1abb1d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Leadership-Stalls-Finance-Demands-Clash-at-the-Top/69a18514fa7d0695d1abb1d6</guid><description>Tata Sons' board postponed a decision on Chairman N Chandrasekaran's third term due to objections from Tata Trusts Chairman Noel Tata. Concerns over Air India losses, heavy capital expenditure in new ventures, and Tata Sons' potential listing status have surfaced. This deferral signals internal friction within the conglomerate's holding structure, raising questions about prior resolutions and future strategic direction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:50:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18514fa7d0695d1abb1d5_1772193198270.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Captures Users, E-commerce Holds Operational Moat in India</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Captures-Users-E-commerce-Holds-Operational-Moat-in-India/69a184cbfa7d0695d1abb19c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Captures-Users-E-commerce-Holds-Operational-Moat-in-India/69a184cbfa7d0695d1abb19c</guid><description>Artificial intelligence applications in India have surpassed e-commerce in daily active users, with platforms like ChatGPT engaging over 100 million users daily. Despite AI's impressive reach, established e-commerce players such as Zomato and Swiggy are leveraging robust operational infrastructure and complex supply chains as a significant competitive moat, rendering them resilient to direct AI-driven disruption. Instead, AI is expected to function as an incremental demand driver and efficiency enhancer within these existing ecosystems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:49:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a184cbfa7d0695d1abb19b_1772193315233.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bhilwara Tech Textiles seeks ₹804cr RPT approval; high dependency risk flagged</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bhilwara-Tech-Textiles-seeks-804cr-RPT-approval-high-dependency-risk-flagged/69a18438fa7d0695d1abb0e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bhilwara-Tech-Textiles-seeks-804cr-RPT-approval-high-dependency-risk-flagged/69a18438fa7d0695d1abb0e1</guid><description>Bhilwara Technical Textiles Limited is initiating a postal ballot to get shareholder approval for related party transactions (RPT) with Maral Overseas Limited. The proposed transaction value of up to ₹8.04 crore for FY 2026-27 is significant, accounting for approximately 98.10% of the company's FY 2024-25 consolidated turnover. This raises concerns about high dependency on a related entity. E-voting is open until March 29, 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:47:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18438fa7d0695d1abb0e0_1772193136117.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Magnum Ventures Demerges Paper Unit; FY25 Turnover ₹397 Cr.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Magnum-Ventures-Demerges-Paper-Unit-FY25-Turnover-397-Cr/69a18257fa7d0695d1abaf64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Magnum-Ventures-Demerges-Paper-Unit-FY25-Turnover-397-Cr/69a18257fa7d0695d1abaf64</guid><description>Magnum Ventures Limited's Board of Directors has approved a scheme to demerge its paper business into a new entity, Magnum Paperz Limited. The paper division contributed a significant 75% of the company's total turnover of ₹397.26 crore in FY24-25. This strategic move aims to unlock focused growth and independent operations for both the paper and hotel businesses, with shareholders set to receive new shares in the demerged paper company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:39:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18257fa7d0695d1abaf63_1772192450958.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JioFinance AI App Launches, Targets Fintech Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/JioFinance-AI-App-Launches-Targets-Fintech-Dominance/69a18003fa7d0695d1abad59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/JioFinance-AI-App-Launches-Targets-Fintech-Dominance/69a18003fa7d0695d1abad59</guid><description>Jio Finance Platform and Service Limited (JFPSL) has launched its JioFinance app, an AI-driven digital marketplace aiming to simplify financial services for Indian consumers. The app aggregates a wide range of products from loans and insurance to investments and UPI, personalized through AI. An 'Finsider' early access program seeks user feedback. This aggressive expansion positions JFSL to challenge established fintech players in India's rapidly growing digital finance sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:29:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a18003fa7d0695d1abad58_1772191903567.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Deficit Hits 63% of Target Amid Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Deficit-Hits-63percent-of-Target-Amid-Revenue-Growth/69a17fb0fa7d0695d1abac99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Deficit-Hits-63percent-of-Target-Amid-Revenue-Growth/69a17fb0fa7d0695d1abac99</guid><description>India's fiscal deficit for the April-January period reached Rs 9.8 lakh crore, equivalent to 63% of the financial year 2025-26 target. This trajectory was supported by robust growth in net tax receipts, which climbed to Rs 20.94 lakh crore, and a substantial increase in non-tax revenue to Rs 5.57 lakh crore. Government expenditure also rose to Rs 36.9 lakh crore, with capital expenditure seeing an increase to Rs 8.4 lakh crore, signaling a continued focus on infrastructure development. Despite rising revenues, the pace of spending places ongoing pressure on fiscal consolidation efforts and borrowing requirements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:27:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17fb0fa7d0695d1abac98_1772192068454.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Essar Pivots to Viable Green Tech &amp; UK Data Centers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Essar-Pivots-to-Viable-Green-Tech-and-UK-Data-Centers/69a17f11fa7d0695d1ababc7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Essar-Pivots-to-Viable-Green-Tech-and-UK-Data-Centers/69a17f11fa7d0695d1ababc7</guid><description>Essar Group is strategically recalibrating its energy transition focus towards commercially viable green technologies, moving beyond policy-driven initiatives. Concurrently, the conglomerate is making a significant push into digital infrastructure, planning a 1-gigawatt data center in the UK to capitalize on surging AI and data demand. This dual-pronged approach balances evolving energy markets with the infrastructure needs of the digital age, underpinned by the group's substantial industrial experience.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:25:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17f11fa7d0695d1ababc6_1772191676501.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sri Lanka's Blue Bond Lists on GIFT City Exchange</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sri-Lankas-Blue-Bond-Lists-on-GIFT-City-Exchange/69a17e53fa7d0695d1abaa7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sri-Lankas-Blue-Bond-Lists-on-GIFT-City-Exchange/69a17e53fa7d0695d1abaa7c</guid><description>Sri Lanka's DFCC Bank has achieved a significant milestone by dual-listing its LKR 3 billion Blue Bond on the NSE International Exchange at GIFT City. This move positions GIFT City as a key international platform for niche sustainable finance instruments, particularly benefiting emerging economies. The listing aims to broaden investor access for critical marine and water resource projects, enhancing Sri Lanka's global profile in green finance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:21:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17e53fa7d0695d1abaa7b_1772191424159.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fiscal Deficit: Path to Target Fraught with Spending Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Deficit-Path-to-Target-Fraught-with-Spending-Risks/69a17dc8fa7d0695d1aba975</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Deficit-Path-to-Target-Fraught-with-Spending-Risks/69a17dc8fa7d0695d1aba975</guid><description>India's fiscal deficit for the April-January period reached ₹9.8 lakh crore, hitting 63% of the government's annual estimate. Revenue streams, including net tax receipts at ₹20.94 lakh crore and non-tax revenue at ₹5.57 lakh crore, saw year-on-year increases. However, total government expenditure climbed to ₹36.9 lakh crore, with capital expenditure at ₹8.4 lakh crore, indicating sustained infrastructure investment. While the deficit is progressing towards its target, the aggressive pace of spending warrants close monitoring.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:19:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17dc8fa7d0695d1aba974_1772191294185.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KRBL Faces SAR 31M &amp; USD 2.15M Arbitral Award; Plans Challenge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/KRBL-Faces-SAR-31M-and-USD-215M-Arbitral-Award-Plans-Challenge/69a17da8fa7d0695d1aba951</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/KRBL-Faces-SAR-31M-and-USD-215M-Arbitral-Award-Plans-Challenge/69a17da8fa7d0695d1aba951</guid><description>KRBL Limited disclosed an arbitral award dated February 26, 2026, ordering the company to pay SAR 30,990,241.25 and USD 21,51,399.15 to Reliable Trading Company (RTC). The basmati rice exporter is seeking legal counsel to challenge the award. This development poses a significant financial risk if KRBL's legal challenge fails.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:19:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17da8fa7d0695d1aba950_1772191455337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>International Combustion India: CRISIL Re-affirms Ratings; Outlook Negative</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/International-Combustion-India-CRISIL-Re-affirms-Ratings-Outlook-Negative/69a17d30fa7d0695d1aba894</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/International-Combustion-India-CRISIL-Re-affirms-Ratings-Outlook-Negative/69a17d30fa7d0695d1aba894</guid><description>CRISIL has re-affirmed International Combustion (India) Limited's long-term rating at BBB and short-term rating at A3+, but maintained a 'Negative' outlook. This indicates stability in current creditworthiness, but the negative outlook signals potential for future downgrades if risks like demand cyclicality, raw material price volatility, and large working capital needs are not effectively managed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17d30fa7d0695d1aba893_1772191716168.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan Acquires US Firm Jayhawk for $150M to Boost Global Specialty Chemicals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Acquires-US-Firm-Jayhawk-for-150M-to-Boost-Global-Specialty-Chemicals/69a17cbafa7d0695d1aba80b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Acquires-US-Firm-Jayhawk-for-150M-to-Boost-Global-Specialty-Chemicals/69a17cbafa7d0695d1aba80b</guid><description>Anupam Rasayan India Ltd. has completed a significant overseas acquisition, purchasing 100% of US-based Jayhawk Fine Chemicals Corporation for approximately $150 million. The deal, financed through a mix of shares and debt, aims to bolster the company's global footprint and strengthen its specialty chemicals platform by moving closer to end-use applications in sectors like electronics and semiconductors. This strategic move is expected to be EPS accretive.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:15:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17cbafa7d0695d1aba80a_1772191212325.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paisalo Digital Fuels Growth with AI Pivot &amp; CP Issuance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digital-Fuels-Growth-with-AI-Pivot-and-CP-Issuance/69a17b64fa7d0695d1aba6d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digital-Fuels-Growth-with-AI-Pivot-and-CP-Issuance/69a17b64fa7d0695d1aba6d5</guid><description>Paisalo Digital Limited has raised approximately ₹29.16 crore through a 91-day commercial paper issuance, signaling a strategic move to fuel its AI-first transformation. This follows a record-breaking quarter ending December 31, 2025, which saw Profit After Tax surge and Assets Under Management grow 16%. The company's expanding touchpoint network, robust asset quality, and a significant increase in promoter stake underscore its resilience and forward-looking strategy, aimed at capitalizing on the expanding MSME sector and supportive government policies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:09:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17b64fa7d0695d1aba6d4_1772190670795.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW Cement ₹50 Cr Equity Fundraise; Borrowing Limit Hike Proposed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Cement-50-Cr-Equity-Fundraise-Borrowing-Limit-Hike-Proposed/69a17ad7fa7d0695d1aba607</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Cement-50-Cr-Equity-Fundraise-Borrowing-Limit-Hike-Proposed/69a17ad7fa7d0695d1aba607</guid><description>JSW Cement Limited is pursuing a dual strategy: a ₹50 crore equity share issuance and an increase in its borrowing limits, pending shareholder approval via postal ballot by March 17, 2026. This move aims to bolster its capital base and financial flexibility for ongoing expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:07:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17ad7fa7d0695d1aba606_1772190580665.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold ETFs Attract Capital Amidst Volatility &amp; Rate Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-ETFs-Attract-Capital-Amidst-Volatility-and-Rate-Hopes/69a17a27fa7d0695d1aba4bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-ETFs-Attract-Capital-Amidst-Volatility-and-Rate-Hopes/69a17a27fa7d0695d1aba4bd</guid><description>Bullion exchange-traded products are experiencing significant investor allocations, fueled by substantial price gains and persistent global macroeconomic uncertainties. While gold and silver ETFs offer a hedge against capital preservation needs, smart investors scrutinize product specifics like expense ratios and assets under management (AUM) to ensure long-term return optimization. Sustained central bank buying provides a structural demand floor, further underpinning interest despite market volatility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:04:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17a27fa7d0695d1aba4bc_1772190555530.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GDP Surge: New Series, Sectoral Gaps, and Global Comparisons</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Surge-New-Series-Sectoral-Gaps-and-Global-Comparisons/69a17a0cfa7d0695d1aba437</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Surge-New-Series-Sectoral-Gaps-and-Global-Comparisons/69a17a0cfa7d0695d1aba437</guid><description>India's economy posted a robust 7.8% real GDP growth in the October-December 2025 quarter (Q3 FY2025-26), driven by a newly implemented GDP series with a 2022-23 base year. Revised full-year estimates for FY2025-26 peg real GDP growth at 7.6% and nominal GDP at 8.6%, surpassing previous projections. While headline figures indicate strong economic momentum, analysis reveals a complex picture involving sectoral performance variations, ongoing global economic competition, and the implications of statistical methodology shifts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:03:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17a0cfa7d0695d1aba436_1772190381616.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Future: Structural Gaps Amplify Disruption Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Future-Structural-Gaps-Amplify-Disruption-Risk/69a1797ffa7d0695d1aba2e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Future-Structural-Gaps-Amplify-Disruption-Risk/69a1797ffa7d0695d1aba2e5</guid><description>Rajiv Memani, EY India's Chairman, highlighted significant challenges for Indian industry, including low R&amp;D spending and inconsistent manufacturing growth. He cautioned that artificial intelligence will sharply divide winners and losers, intensifying competition and potentially exacerbating existing structural vulnerabilities. Prioritizing innovation and strategic R&amp;D investment is presented as crucial for Indian firms to navigate this impending technological churn and maintain global competitiveness. The current economic trajectory suggests a critical juncture where existing industrial weaknesses could magnify the impact of AI-driven market shifts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:01:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1797ffa7d0695d1aba2e4_1772190348829.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCC Ltd Secures Interim Court Relief, But NHAI Dispute Lingers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Ltd-Secures-Interim-Court-Relief-But-NHAI-Dispute-Lingers/69a1797afa7d0695d1aba2ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Ltd-Secures-Interim-Court-Relief-But-NHAI-Dispute-Lingers/69a1797afa7d0695d1aba2ce</guid><description>NCC Ltd received a reprieve as the Telangana High Court granted an interim suspension of the National Highways Authority of India's (NHAI) two-year debarment order. This allows NCC and its subsidiary OB Infrastructure Ltd (OBIL) to participate in future tenders, providing much-needed operational breathing room. However, the core contractual disputes remain unresolved, with arbitration proceedings and NHAI's legal challenges ongoing, casting a shadow over long-term business continuity and growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:01:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1797afa7d0695d1aba2cd_1772190262038.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan Completes $155M Monitchem Kansas Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Completes-155M-Monitchem-Kansas-Acquisition/69a17975fa7d0695d1aba2b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Completes-155M-Monitchem-Kansas-Acquisition/69a17975fa7d0695d1aba2b7</guid><description>Anupam Rasayan India Ltd. has successfully completed the acquisition of Monitchem Kansas S.à r.l. and its subsidiaries for up to US$155 million. The deal, executed via its wholly-owned subsidiary Doriath S.à r.l., marks a significant step to bolster the company's presence and manufacturing capabilities in the United States, gaining access to niche, high-value chemical operations and an established customer base.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:01:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17975fa7d0695d1aba2b6_1772190222090.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Breaches 200-Day EMA Amidst Broad Market Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Breaches-200-Day-EMA-Amidst-Broad-Market-Sell-Off/69a17930fa7d0695d1aba196</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Breaches-200-Day-EMA-Amidst-Broad-Market-Sell-Off/69a17930fa7d0695d1aba196</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks faced widespread selling pressure on February 27, 2026, as the Nifty closed below the 25,200 mark and crucially breached its 200-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA). Subdued global cues and escalating geopolitical tensions fueled investor caution, leading to broad-based declines across sectors, except for pockets of resilience in IT and media. This technical breakdown suggests a shift in market sentiment towards risk aversion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17930fa7d0695d1aba195_1772190327838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Poverty Claims Under Fire Amidst Rising Household Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Poverty-Claims-Under-Fire-Amidst-Rising-Household-Debt/69a17925fa7d0695d1aba178</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Poverty-Claims-Under-Fire-Amidst-Rising-Household-Debt/69a17925fa7d0695d1aba178</guid><description>Development economist Santosh Mehrotra has debunked government claims of India's poverty rate plummeting to 5%, citing flawed methodologies and presenting an alternative estimate of around 26%. His critique points to a severe decline in non-agricultural employment, forcing millions back into agriculture. This economic strain is exacerbated by rising household debt, including record gold loans, as real wages stagnate, raising concerns about underlying economic sustainability and the true state of millions of households.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a17925fa7d0695d1aba177_1772190124952.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>