<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:39:33 +0000</pubDate><item><title>AvenuesAI Revenue Surges 122%, FY26 Guidance Up Amid AI Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AvenuesAI-Revenue-Surges-122percent-FY26-Guidance-Up-Amid-AI-Push/698eeee848d8f5c5fee50fa5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AvenuesAI-Revenue-Surges-122percent-FY26-Guidance-Up-Amid-AI-Push/698eeee848d8f5c5fee50fa5</guid><description>AvenuesAI Limited posted a stellar Q3 FY26 with consolidated gross revenue soaring 122.5% YoY to ₹2,381.2 Cr, fueled by its AI-native strategy. The company raised its full-year FY26 guidance for revenue to ₹7,500-8,000 Cr and PAT to ₹250-275 Cr. However, standalone PAT saw a 25.4% YoY decline, and 9M consolidated profitability metrics lagged revenue growth, raising questions about margin sustainability despite the AI transformation and new product launches.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:29:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eeee848d8f5c5fee50fa4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Punjab Communications Hits Q3 Loss Amid Auditor's Serious Inventory Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Punjab-Communications-Hits-Q3-Loss-Amid-Auditors-Serious-Inventory-Concerns/698eee1348d8f5c5fee50a2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Punjab-Communications-Hits-Q3-Loss-Amid-Auditors-Serious-Inventory-Concerns/698eee1348d8f5c5fee50a2a</guid><description>Punjab Communications Ltd. swung to a net loss of ₹0.25 Cr in Q3 FY26 from a profit of ₹0.55 Cr a year ago. Auditors issued a 'Qualified Conclusion,' citing significant concerns over inventory valuation methods, lack of physical verification, and referencing a prior adverse opinion from predecessor auditors. Revenue from operations grew 15.26% YoY.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:25:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eee1348d8f5c5fee50a29.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Photoquip India Profit Plunges 77% YoY on Revenue Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Photoquip-India-Profit-Plunges-77percent-YoY-on-Revenue-Woes/698eed6548d8f5c5fee5056c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Photoquip-India-Profit-Plunges-77percent-YoY-on-Revenue-Woes/698eed6548d8f5c5fee5056c</guid><description>Photoquip India Limited reported a severe drop in Q3 FY2025-26 profit, plunging 76.98% YoY to ₹0.58 Lakhs. Revenue from operations saw a minor 0.65% YoY dip, but other income declined sharply. The nine-month performance is even more concerning, with net profit down 89.71% YoY. Basic EPS fell to ₹0.02.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:22:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eed6548d8f5c5fee5056b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anna Infra Sees 2281% Revenue Leap Fueled by Real Estate Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Anna-Infra-Sees-2281percent-Revenue-Leap-Fueled-by-Real-Estate-Surge/698eed4848d8f5c5fee50481</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Anna-Infra-Sees-2281percent-Revenue-Leap-Fueled-by-Real-Estate-Surge/698eed4848d8f5c5fee50481</guid><description>Anna Infrastructures Limited delivered stellar Q3 FY26 results, with revenue soaring 2281.7% YoY to ₹173.13 Lakhs, propelled by its Real Estate division. Net profit jumped an astounding 173660% YoY to ₹86.88 Lakhs, with EPS at ₹2.29. Nine-month figures also show robust growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:22:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eed4848d8f5c5fee50480.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alkem Labs to Acquire Swiss Heart Device Firm Occlutech, Targets New Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alkem-Labs-to-Acquire-Swiss-Heart-Device-Firm-Occlutech-Targets-New-Growth/698eed1848d8f5c5fee5024b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alkem-Labs-to-Acquire-Swiss-Heart-Device-Firm-Occlutech-Targets-New-Growth/698eed1848d8f5c5fee5024b</guid><description>Alkem Laboratories, via its subsidiary Alkem Medtech, has made a binding offer to acquire a majority stake (51-55%) in Swiss medical device firm Occlutech Holding AG. This strategic move marks Alkem's entry into the advanced cardiovascular devices segment, aiming to leverage Occlutech's global presence and product portfolio. However, Occlutech reported a significant net loss of EUR 20.52 million (INR 185.73 Cr) and a negative net worth for FY2024, highlighting potential integration challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:21:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eed1848d8f5c5fee5024a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AvenuesAI Posts Record Q3, Hikes FY26 Outlook on AI Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AvenuesAI-Posts-Record-Q3-Hikes-FY26-Outlook-on-AI-Push/698eecec48d8f5c5fee50176</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AvenuesAI-Posts-Record-Q3-Hikes-FY26-Outlook-on-AI-Push/698eecec48d8f5c5fee50176</guid><description>AvenuesAI Limited reported a record Q3 FY26, with gross revenue surging 221% YoY to ₹2,381.2 Crore and adjusted PAT climbing 59% YoY to ₹86.1 Crore. The company, now rebranded from Infibeam Avenues, has upwardly revised its full-year FY26 guidance for both revenue and PAT, driven by its strategic transformation into an AI-native transaction infrastructure platform.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:20:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eecec48d8f5c5fee50175.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Textile Stocks Surge on US Zero-Duty Access Deal Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Textile-Stocks-Surge-on-US-Zero-Duty-Access-Deal-Hopes/698eec3348d8f5c5fee4fd1b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Textile-Stocks-Surge-on-US-Zero-Duty-Access-Deal-Hopes/698eec3348d8f5c5fee4fd1b</guid><description>Textile stocks surged Friday, bucking a weak market trend. Hopes of securing zero-duty textile access to the US, mirroring Bangladesh's advantage, are driving gains. Commerce Minister Piyush Goyal indicated progress on a deal expected by March. Key players like Gokaldas Exports and KPR Mill saw significant jumps.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:17:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eec3348d8f5c5fee4fd1a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India M&amp;A Momentum Surges for 2026 on Strategy, Confidence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-MandA-Momentum-Surges-for-2026-on-Strategy-Confidence/698eeaf048d8f5c5fee4f4b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-MandA-Momentum-Surges-for-2026-on-Strategy-Confidence/698eeaf048d8f5c5fee4f4b2</guid><description>India's mergers and acquisitions are poised for significant growth in 2026, fueled by renewed corporate confidence and a strategic focus on scale and capability. Deal volumes surged in the latter half of 2025, with average transaction sizes increasing. However, observers warn that heightened regulatory scrutiny, particularly in the healthcare and tech sectors, will complicate expansion efforts and raise operating costs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:12:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eeaf048d8f5c5fee4f4b1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aimco Pesticides First Indian Firm Secures Brazil Triclopyr Registration</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aimco-Pesticides-First-Indian-Firm-Secures-Brazil-Triclopyr-Registration/698eea7f48d8f5c5fee4f19e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aimco-Pesticides-First-Indian-Firm-Secures-Brazil-Triclopyr-Registration/698eea7f48d8f5c5fee4f19e</guid><description>Aimco Pesticides Limited has secured a significant milestone by becoming the first Indian company to receive a perpetual registration for Triclopyr Technical in Brazil. This opens access to the world's largest market for the herbicide, expected to bolster Aimco's global footprint and support Brazilian agriculture with its crop protection solutions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:10:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eea7f48d8f5c5fee4f19d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AvenuesAI Skyrockets Revenue 122% on AI Push, Lifts FY26 Forecast</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AvenuesAI-Skyrockets-Revenue-122percent-on-AI-Push-Lifts-FY26-Forecast/698ee9ab48d8f5c5fee4eb31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AvenuesAI-Skyrockets-Revenue-122percent-on-AI-Push-Lifts-FY26-Forecast/698ee9ab48d8f5c5fee4eb31</guid><description>AvenuesAI Limited reported record Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue surging 122% year-on-year to ₹238.12 Cr and adjusted PAT up 59% to ₹8.61 Cr. Following its rebranding and strategic pivot to an AI-native transaction infrastructure platform, the company has aggressively revised its full-year FY26 revenue guidance upwards to ₹750-800 Cr.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:06:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee9ab48d8f5c5fee4eb30.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Marico Secures 60% Cosmix Stake for ₹225 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Marico-Secures-60percent-Cosmix-Stake-for-225-Cr/698ee97548d8f5c5fee4e9fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Marico-Secures-60percent-Cosmix-Stake-for-225-Cr/698ee97548d8f5c5fee4e9fe</guid><description>Marico Limited has acquired a 60% majority stake in Cosmix Wellness Limited for ₹225 crore, bolstering its presence in the plant protein and wellness sector. The deal, advised by Vertices Partners and Bharucha &amp; Partners, includes plans for Marico to acquire the remaining 40% stake within three years, aiming to accelerate growth and expand into adjacent wellness categories.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:05:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee97548d8f5c5fee4e9fd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HUL Subsidiary Kwality Wall's India Approved for Stock Market Debut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Subsidiary-Kwality-Walls-India-Approved-for-Stock-Market-Debut/698ee97448d8f5c5fee4e9f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HUL-Subsidiary-Kwality-Walls-India-Approved-for-Stock-Market-Debut/698ee97448d8f5c5fee4e9f6</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever's subsidiary, Kwality Wall’s India Limited (KWIL), has received approval from BSE and NSE for its equity shares to be listed and traded, commencing February 16, 2026. This follows a Scheme of Arrangement between HUL and KWIL, paving the way for a separate listing of the ice cream and refreshments business.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:05:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee97448d8f5c5fee4e9f5.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sharika Enterprises Secures ₹3.75 Cr UP Power Order for Cable Lines</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sharika-Enterprises-Secures-375-Cr-UP-Power-Order-for-Cable-Lines/698ee95048d8f5c5fee4e8a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sharika-Enterprises-Secures-375-Cr-UP-Power-Order-for-Cable-Lines/698ee95048d8f5c5fee4e8a9</guid><description>Sharika Enterprises Limited has bagged a significant ₹3.75 Crore turn-key order from UP Power Transmission Corporation Limited (UPPTCL), a UP Government Undertaking. The contract involves the supply and installation of 132kV underground cable lines, with execution slated within nine months. This order underscores the company's growing presence in government infrastructure projects and adds a substantial boost to its project pipeline.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:05:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee95048d8f5c5fee4e8a8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vadilal Dairy's Annual Loss Widens Amid Revenue Slump; 'Other Income' Surges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Vadilal-Dairys-Annual-Loss-Widens-Amid-Revenue-Slump-Other-Income-Surges/698ee92e48d8f5c5fee4e76e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Vadilal-Dairys-Annual-Loss-Widens-Amid-Revenue-Slump-Other-Income-Surges/698ee92e48d8f5c5fee4e76e</guid><description>Vadilal Dairy International posted a Q3 FY26 net loss of ₹77.20 Cr, narrowing 30.07% YoY and 67.29% QoQ, aided by a 19.67% QoQ revenue increase. However, Q3 revenue from operations declined 26.15% YoY. For the nine months, net loss widened 35.59% YoY to ₹281.21 Cr, despite a 3.43% YoY total revenue rise. A significant jump in 'Other Income' (up 4720% YoY for 9M) alongside operational revenue decline raises concerns. No forward guidance was issued.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:04:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee92e48d8f5c5fee4e76d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alkem Labs Acquires Swiss Firm, Posts Steady Q3 Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alkem-Labs-Acquires-Swiss-Firm-Posts-Steady-Q3-Growth/698ee8c148d8f5c5fee4e4ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alkem-Labs-Acquires-Swiss-Firm-Posts-Steady-Q3-Growth/698ee8c148d8f5c5fee4e4ff</guid><description>Alkem Laboratories reported a 10.7% year-on-year rise in consolidated revenue to ₹37,368.2 million for Q3 FY26, alongside an interim dividend of ₹43 per share. The company also announced a significant strategic move: executing a binding term sheet to acquire a majority stake in Swiss medical devices firm Occlutech Holding AG, aiming to bolster its global medical device segment. While consolidated net profit saw a modest 1.6% YoY increase, standalone operations reported a profit decline.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:02:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee8c148d8f5c5fee4e4fe.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Time Out Market Enters India Amidst F&amp;B Boom, Faces Financial Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Time-Out-Market-Enters-India-Amidst-FandB-Boom-Faces-Financial-Hurdles/698ee80348d8f5c5fee4e101</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Time-Out-Market-Enters-India-Amidst-FandB-Boom-Faces-Financial-Hurdles/698ee80348d8f5c5fee4e101</guid><description>Time Out Market is launching its inaugural Indian location at Worldmark Aerocity, New Delhi, in the second half of 2026. This expansion into a vibrant US$332 billion Indian food and beverage market, expected to reach nearly US$691 billion by 2030, will feature 11 kitchens and two bars across 24,500 sq ft. However, the move coincides with Time Out Group plc reporting significant net losses and a negative P/E ratio, alongside the inherent execution challenges of curating a premium culinary experience in a fiercely competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:59:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee80348d8f5c5fee4e100.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Rules Tighten Grip, Boost Compliance Costs for Tech Firms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Rules-Tighten-Grip-Boost-Compliance-Costs-for-Tech-Firms/698ee78048d8f5c5fee4dc0d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Rules-Tighten-Grip-Boost-Compliance-Costs-for-Tech-Firms/698ee78048d8f5c5fee4dc0d</guid><description>India's newly amended IT Rules (effective Feb 20, 2026) impose stringent obligations on digital intermediaries concerning AI-generated content. Mandated labeling, expedited takedown timelines of 2-3 hours, and enhanced due diligence create significant compliance challenges and potential liability risks for tech platforms. While aiming to curb deepfakes and misinformation, these rules may increase operational costs and present a complex regulatory environment for companies operating in the Indian market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:57:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee78048d8f5c5fee4dc0c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quintegra Solutions Revenue Collapses 99%, Swings to Loss YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Quintegra-Solutions-Revenue-Collapses-99percent-Swings-to-Loss-YoY/698ee6d648d8f5c5fee4d791</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Quintegra-Solutions-Revenue-Collapses-99percent-Swings-to-Loss-YoY/698ee6d648d8f5c5fee4d791</guid><description>Quintegra Solutions reported a catastrophic Q3 FY26, with revenue plummeting 99.33% year-on-year to ₹0.0005 Crores. The company has swung from a net profit of ₹6.13 Lakhs in Q3 FY25 to a net loss of ₹(3.85) Lakhs. Despite the revenue collapse, basic EPS saw a YoY improvement to ₹(0.001) due to aggressive cost management.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:54:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee6d648d8f5c5fee4d790.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GVK Power Auditors Question Survival Amidst ₹1 Lakh Crore Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GVK-Power-Auditors-Question-Survival-Amidst-1-Lakh-Crore-Loss/698ee64948d8f5c5fee4d481</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GVK-Power-Auditors-Question-Survival-Amidst-1-Lakh-Crore-Loss/698ee64948d8f5c5fee4d481</guid><description>GVK Power &amp; Infrastructure, under CIRP, reported alarming Q3 FY26 un-audited results. Standalone net loss surged to ₹1,03,884 Cr, a stark contrast to the prior year's profit. Consolidated net loss narrowed to ₹1,728 Cr. Auditors issued a "Basis of Disclaimer of Conclusion," casting significant doubt on the company's ability to continue as a going concern due to massive accumulated losses, liabilities exceeding assets, and widespread defaults. The company faces numerous litigations and investigations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:52:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee64948d8f5c5fee4d480.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haldyn Glass Q3 Revenue Soars 367%, PAT Jumps 437% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Haldyn-Glass-Q3-Revenue-Soars-367percent-PAT-Jumps-437percent-YoY/698ee5f748d8f5c5fee4d2a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Haldyn-Glass-Q3-Revenue-Soars-367percent-PAT-Jumps-437percent-YoY/698ee5f748d8f5c5fee4d2a1</guid><description>Haldyn Glass reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue leaping 367.5% year-on-year to ₹247.08 Cr and net profit after tax (PAT) surging 437.8% to ₹5.27 Cr. Despite an exceptional expense of ₹1.63 Cr due to new Labour Codes impacting standalone PBT, the overall PAT performance indicates a strong financial recovery for the company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:51:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee5f748d8f5c5fee4d2a0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDfy Secures $53M Series F, Hints at Consolidation Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IDfy-Secures-53M-Series-F-Hints-at-Consolidation-Play/698ee5df48d8f5c5fee4d206</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IDfy-Secures-53M-Series-F-Hints-at-Consolidation-Play/698ee5df48d8f5c5fee4d206</guid><description>Identity verification and RegTech firm IDfy has closed a ₹476 crore ($53 million) Series F funding round led by Neo Asset Management. The investment, comprising primary and secondary transactions, values the company at an estimated $272 million post-money. Funds will target strategic acquisitions, international market expansion, and product enhancement, as IDfy transitions to profitability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:50:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee5df48d8f5c5fee4d205.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Company Posts 30% Revenue Jump, Eyes 35% CAGR with Egypt Plant</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Company-Posts-30percent-Revenue-Jump-Eyes-35percent-CAGR-with-Egypt-Plant/698ee4fc48d8f5c5fee4cd4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Company-Posts-30percent-Revenue-Jump-Eyes-35percent-CAGR-with-Egypt-Plant/698ee4fc48d8f5c5fee4cd4c</guid><description>The company reported a strong 30.8% YoY increase in standalone revenue to ₹102.6 Cr for Q3 FY26, driven by robust demand. Despite a dip in EBITDA margins, future strategy includes a significant 35% CAGR target by FY29, supported by commissioning new manufacturing facilities in Egypt and Palghar, aiming for global market penetration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:46:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee4fc48d8f5c5fee4cd4b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Om Freight Forwarders Posts Stellar PAT Jump Post-IPO</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Om-Freight-Forwarders-Posts-Stellar-PAT-Jump-Post-IPO/698ee4b448d8f5c5fee4cb1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Om-Freight-Forwarders-Posts-Stellar-PAT-Jump-Post-IPO/698ee4b448d8f5c5fee4cb1c</guid><description>Om Freight Forwarders reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated PAT soaring 181% YoY to ₹4.64 Cr, against a 2.26% revenue increase to ₹119.11 Cr. The company also announced the re-appointment of its CMD for five years and detailed its IPO fund utilization post-listing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:45:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee4b448d8f5c5fee4cb1b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Neerav Bairagi Launches 26% Open Offer for JMG Corporation at ¥5.30</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Neerav-Bairagi-Launches-26percent-Open-Offer-for-JMG-Corporation-at-530/698ee49048d8f5c5fee4cab9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Neerav-Bairagi-Launches-26percent-Open-Offer-for-JMG-Corporation-at-530/698ee49048d8f5c5fee4cab9</guid><description>JMG Corporation Limited announced an open offer from acquirer Mr. Neerav Bairagi, targeting up to 26% equity at ¥5.30 per share. The Committee of Independent Directors has published its recommendations regarding this bid, advising shareholders on the move and its implications.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee49048d8f5c5fee4cab8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ASM Technologies Fund Use Confirmed by CRISIL as Per Plan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ASM-Technologies-Fund-Use-Confirmed-by-CRISIL-as-Per-Plan/698ee47348d8f5c5fee4ca3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ASM-Technologies-Fund-Use-Confirmed-by-CRISIL-as-Per-Plan/698ee47348d8f5c5fee4ca3e</guid><description>ASM Technologies Limited has received confirmation from CRISIL Ratings that its ₹170.13 crore preferential issue proceeds are being utilized strictly as per the objectives outlined in the Offer Document. Approximately ₹109.56 crore has been deployed towards organic/inorganic growth opportunities and strategic acquisitions, along with general corporate purposes. Unutilized funds totaling ₹60.57 crore are prudently invested, earning returns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:44:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee47348d8f5c5fee4ca3d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Flora Corp Posts Massive Loss, Faces Alarming Accounting Discrepancy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Flora-Corp-Posts-Massive-Loss-Faces-Alarming-Accounting-Discrepancy/698ee36648d8f5c5fee4c359</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Flora-Corp-Posts-Massive-Loss-Faces-Alarming-Accounting-Discrepancy/698ee36648d8f5c5fee4c359</guid><description>Flora Corporation reported a steep 38.79% YoY revenue decline in Q3 FY26, with net losses widening QoQ. A significant accounting discrepancy has emerged, where total assets do not reconcile with liabilities and equity. The company also faced a gross loss due to high material costs and surging receivables, raising serious concerns for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:40:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee36648d8f5c5fee4c358.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haldyn Glass Q3 Revenue Plunges 76% As Prior Year Data Sparks Questions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Haldyn-Glass-Q3-Revenue-Plunges-76percent-As-Prior-Year-Data-Sparks-Questions/698ee35148d8f5c5fee4c286</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Haldyn-Glass-Q3-Revenue-Plunges-76percent-As-Prior-Year-Data-Sparks-Questions/698ee35148d8f5c5fee4c286</guid><description>Haldyn Glass's consolidated Q3 FY26 revenue plunged 76.5% YoY to ₹2,470 Cr, flagged as a potential data anomaly versus the prior year's ₹10,528 Cr. This contrasts starkly with a robust 226.3% sequential QoQ increase and 98.0% YoY growth for nine-month FY26. Standalone revenue surged 134.7% YoY. While consolidated PAT fell 23.6% YoY, nine-month PAT grew 87.3% YoY.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:39:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee35148d8f5c5fee4c285.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jamna Auto Surges on Stellar Q3; Unveils ₹5,000 Cr Growth Roadmap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jamna-Auto-Surges-on-Stellar-Q3-Unveils-5000-Cr-Growth-Roadmap/698ee2be48d8f5c5fee4bed1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jamna-Auto-Surges-on-Stellar-Q3-Unveils-5000-Cr-Growth-Roadmap/698ee2be48d8f5c5fee4bed1</guid><description>Jamna Auto Industries reported a strong Q3 FY25-26 with 19% YoY revenue growth to ₹668 Cr and a 33% rise in PAT to ₹58 Cr. The company highlighted capacity expansions, including new plant commissions, and a strategic 'LAKSHYA RISE 5000' roadmap targeting ₹5,000 Cr revenue with a focus on new markets and enhanced ROCE.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:37:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee2be48d8f5c5fee4bed0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Liberty Shoes Profit Plummets 70% Despite Sales Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Liberty-Shoes-Profit-Plummets-70percent-Despite-Sales-Rise/698ee28c48d8f5c5fee4be48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Liberty-Shoes-Profit-Plummets-70percent-Despite-Sales-Rise/698ee28c48d8f5c5fee4be48</guid><description>Liberty Shoes posted a sharp 70.0% year-on-year drop in Q3 FY26 net profit to ₹5.91 Cr, despite a 3.8% revenue increase to ₹180.92 Cr. Quarter-on-quarter, PAT fell 75.1%. Nine-month PAT also declined 26.0%. Employee costs rose due to new labour codes, impacting profitability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:36:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee28c48d8f5c5fee4be47.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Liberty Shoes Sees 75% PAT Plunge Despite 13% Revenue Jump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Liberty-Shoes-Sees-75percent-PAT-Plunge-Despite-13percent-Revenue-Jump/698ee20948d8f5c5fee4bab7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Liberty-Shoes-Sees-75percent-PAT-Plunge-Despite-13percent-Revenue-Jump/698ee20948d8f5c5fee4bab7</guid><description>Liberty Shoes reported mixed Q3 FY26 results, with revenue climbing 13% YoY to ₹180.92 Cr. However, profitability took a major hit, with Profit After Tax (PAT) dropping a sharp 75.10% YoY to ₹0.59 Cr and QoQ by 70.05%. Nine-month PAT also fell 26.04% YoY. An incremental employee cost of ₹1.41 Cr from new labour codes impacted results, while credit ratings were reaffirmed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:34:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee20948d8f5c5fee4bab6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Corporate Action Surge: 50+ Firms Eye Shareholder Payouts Amid Market Wobble</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Corporate-Action-Surge-50-Firms-Eye-Shareholder-Payouts-Amid-Market-Wobble/698ee17b48d8f5c5fee4b6af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Corporate-Action-Surge-50-Firms-Eye-Shareholder-Payouts-Amid-Market-Wobble/698ee17b48d8f5c5fee4b6af</guid><description>A significant wave of corporate actions, including interim dividends from 50+ Indian companies and bonus/stock split announcements, is scheduled from February 16-20, 2026. Escorts Kubota leads with ₹18/share dividend, followed by Torrent Power and Nirlon at ₹15. This concentrated shareholder return strategy unfolds against a backdrop of broader market volatility, particularly a sharp decline in the IT sector driven by AI disruption fears. Companies like Coal India offer robust dividend yields, while others like Apollo Hospitals present lower yields despite substantial payouts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:31:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee17b48d8f5c5fee4b6ae.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW Cement Turns Profitable, Plans 42 MTPA Capacity by 2028</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Cement-Turns-Profitable-Plans-42-MTPA-Capacity-by-2028/698ee15c48d8f5c5fee4b5e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Cement-Turns-Profitable-Plans-42-MTPA-Capacity-by-2028/698ee15c48d8f5c5fee4b5e7</guid><description>JSW Cement reported a strong Q3 FY26 performance, swinging to a Profit After Tax (PAT) of ₹130.6 Cr from a loss last year, with revenue up 13.2% YoY to ₹1,621 Cr. Operating EBITDA grew 31.5% YoY. The company outlined an aggressive capacity expansion plan to reach 41.85 MTPA by CY2028 and secured a credit rating upgrade to AA-/Stable. However, EBITDA per ton saw a sequential decline QoQ.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:31:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee15c48d8f5c5fee4b5e6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Jet Healthcare: Q3 Profit Plummets 59% YoY Amid Rising Expenses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Q3-Profit-Plummets-59percent-YoY-Amid-Rising-Expenses/698ee10f48d8f5c5fee4b3f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Q3-Profit-Plummets-59percent-YoY-Amid-Rising-Expenses/698ee10f48d8f5c5fee4b3f8</guid><description>Blue Jet Healthcare reported a steep 59.4% year-on-year drop in net profit to ₹401.66 Cr for Q3 FY26, down from ₹989.83 Cr in Q3 FY25. While revenue from operations saw a 16.3% sequential increase to ₹1,924.14 Cr, total expenses jumped 25.5% QoQ, leading to a 23.0% sequential decline in net profit. For the nine months, profit fell 6.0% YoY despite a 3.3% revenue rise, as expenses grew 10.4%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:30:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee10f48d8f5c5fee4b3f7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IHCL Stock Dips Despite Record Q3; Flat Margins Fuel Investor Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IHCL-Stock-Dips-Despite-Record-Q3-Flat-Margins-Fuel-Investor-Scrutiny/698ee05848d8f5c5fee4ae6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IHCL-Stock-Dips-Despite-Record-Q3-Flat-Margins-Fuel-Investor-Scrutiny/698ee05848d8f5c5fee4ae6d</guid><description>The Indian Hotels Company (IHCL) reported a 50.2% year-on-year net profit surge to ₹954.2 crore and 12.2% revenue growth to ₹2,842 crore for Q3 FY26. Despite these robust figures, the company's stock fell approximately 4% on the NSE, reflecting market caution. EBITDA margins remained flat at 37.9%, a point of focus for investors, against a backdrop of a subdued broader market. Analysts largely maintain positive outlooks, though some brokerages have recently adjusted price targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:27:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ee05848d8f5c5fee4ae6c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eris Lifesciences Q3 Profit Dips QoQ; Completes Swiss Parenterals Buyout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Eris-Lifesciences-Q3-Profit-Dips-QoQ-Completes-Swiss-Parenterals-Buyout/698ede8ddd367c20e0c664fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Eris-Lifesciences-Q3-Profit-Dips-QoQ-Completes-Swiss-Parenterals-Buyout/698ede8ddd367c20e0c664fa</guid><description>Eris Lifesciences reported consolidated Q3 FY26 revenue growth of 11.00% YoY to ₹807.45 Cr, but net profit fell 19.06% QoQ to ₹108.83 Cr, impacted by ₹17.24 Cr exceptional items. Standalone results showed a sharp QoQ decline, with net profit down 97.93% to ₹3.09 Cr. The company also completed the acquisition of the remaining 30% stake in Swiss Parenterals Limited, making it a wholly-owned subsidiary.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:19:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ede8ddd367c20e0c664f9_1770972428259.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sangal Papers Revenue Plunges 33% YoY, Q3 Profit Jumps 112%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sangal-Papers-Revenue-Plunges-33percent-YoY-Q3-Profit-Jumps-112percent/698ede87dd367c20e0c6649b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sangal-Papers-Revenue-Plunges-33percent-YoY-Q3-Profit-Jumps-112percent/698ede87dd367c20e0c6649b</guid><description>Sangal Papers reported a steep 32.7% year-on-year decline in Q3 FY26 revenue to ₹26.70 Cr. Despite this, the company's net profit for the quarter more than doubled, jumping 111.6% to ₹0.35 Cr. However, over the first nine months of FY26, revenue grew modestly by 6.54% to ₹142.61 Cr, while net profit dropped significantly by 39.45% to ₹1.45 Cr. Installation of a new 4.5 MW turbine is nearing completion. No future guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:19:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ede87dd367c20e0c6649a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GSFC Faces Audit Red Flags: 100% NPA, Going Concern Doubts Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GSFC-Faces-Audit-Red-Flags-100percent-NPA-Going-Concern-Doubts-Emerge/698ede42dd367c20e0c662a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GSFC-Faces-Audit-Red-Flags-100percent-NPA-Going-Concern-Doubts-Emerge/698ede42dd367c20e0c662a8</guid><description>Gujarat State Financial Corporation (GSFC) posted a Q3 FY26 net loss widening by 0.84% YoY to ₹31.93 Cr, despite a 47.65% jump in total income to ₹4.14 Cr. Auditors issued a qualified opinion, citing an eroded net worth and questioning the going concern basis due to 100% NPAs and liquidity issues. Interest expenses continue to pressure financials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:18:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ede42dd367c20e0c662a7_1770972088572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Info Edge Q3 Profit Surges 23%, Declares Dividend Amidst Large Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Info-Edge-Q3-Profit-Surges-23percent-Declares-Dividend-Amidst-Large-Loss/698ede2cdd367c20e0c661ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Info-Edge-Q3-Profit-Surges-23percent-Declares-Dividend-Amidst-Large-Loss/698ede2cdd367c20e0c661ad</guid><description>Info Edge reported a robust Q3 FY26 standalone Net Profit jump of 23.11% YoY to ₹246.46 Cr on 13.85% revenue growth. The company also declared a 2nd interim dividend of ₹2.40/share. However, consolidated results revealed a significant Total Comprehensive Loss of ₹(3,954.63) Cr, primarily due to OCI adjustments, overshadowing operating gains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:17:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ede2cdd367c20e0c661ac.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Jet Healthcare Q3 Revenue Plunges 40% YoY, Profit Halved</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Q3-Revenue-Plunges-40percent-YoY-Profit-Halved/698ede23dd367c20e0c6616b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Blue-Jet-Healthcare-Q3-Revenue-Plunges-40percent-YoY-Profit-Halved/698ede23dd367c20e0c6616b</guid><description>Blue Jet Healthcare reported a steep 39.58% year-on-year decline in revenue for Q3 FY26 to ₹1,924.14 Cr, with net profit slumping 59.42% to ₹401.66 Cr. Sequentially, revenue grew 16.27% driven by higher sales, but net profit contracted 22.96%, indicating margin pressures. No balance sheet or cash flow data was provided.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:17:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ede23dd367c20e0c6616a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eris Lifesciences Q3 Profit Surges 25% YoY; Buys Swiss Parenterals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Eris-Lifesciences-Q3-Profit-Surges-25percent-YoY-Buys-Swiss-Parenterals/698edd24dd367c20e0c65965</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Eris-Lifesciences-Q3-Profit-Surges-25percent-YoY-Buys-Swiss-Parenterals/698edd24dd367c20e0c65965</guid><description>Eris Lifesciences reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated net profit surging 25% YoY to ₹108.83 Cr on 10.99% revenue growth. For the nine months, profit jumped 35.09%. The company also finalized the acquisition of the remaining stake in Swiss Parenterals, making it a wholly-owned subsidiary. Standalone revenue saw a YoY dip, but profitability improved. Financial ratios like Debt-Equity and Interest Coverage Ratio showed positive trends.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 08:13:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698edd24dd367c20e0c65964.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>