<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:21:19 +0000</pubDate><item><title>2026 Market Magic? Mid &amp; Small Caps Poised for a Comeback as Valuations Ease: Expert Reveals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-Market-Magic-Mid-and-Small-Caps-Poised-for-a-Comeback-as-Valuations-Ease-Expert-Reveals/694bace5e10c98d0787af11f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-Market-Magic-Mid-and-Small-Caps-Poised-for-a-Comeback-as-Valuations-Ease-Expert-Reveals/694bace5e10c98d0787af11f</guid><description>Market expert Punita Kumar Sinha of Pacific Paradigm Advisors predicts 2026 will be a stronger year for Indian equities than 2025. She notes easing headwinds, improved valuations closer to 10-year averages, and renewed foreign investor interest. While AI trade dominates global focus, India offers diversification. Sinha highlights financials as core, with selective opportunities in IT, real estate, and capital expenditure themes. She emphasizes 2026 as a 'stock-picker's market', especially for mid and small caps which have seen corrections, urging careful selection due to a large IPO pipeline potentially capping overall returns. Auto and consumption sectors also show promise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:52:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bace5e10c98d0787af11e_1766567582578.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPFO Fixes Pension Mess: New Rules to End Contribution Errors &amp; Secure Your Retirement!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFO-Fixes-Pension-Mess-New-Rules-to-End-Contribution-Errors-and-Secure-Your-Retirement/694bac34e10c98d0787af03e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/EPFO-Fixes-Pension-Mess-New-Rules-to-End-Contribution-Errors-and-Secure-Your-Retirement/694bac34e10c98d0787af03e</guid><description>The Employees' Provident Fund Organisation (EPFO) has introduced new guidelines to rectify mistakes in Employees' Pension Scheme (EPS) contributions. These rules aim to create a uniform process across all regional offices, preventing employees from facing pension settlement issues due to incorrect entries or missed contributions. The circular details how wrongly paid excess amounts will be returned and how employers' failures to deposit contributions will be addressed, ensuring employees secure their rightful pension benefits and reducing future delays and disputes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:49:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bac34e10c98d0787af03d_1766567132454.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Holiday Shockwave: US Christmas Costs Soar as China &amp; India Tariffs Hit Shoppers Hard!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Holiday-Shockwave-US-Christmas-Costs-Soar-as-China-and-India-Tariffs-Hit-Shoppers-Hard/694bab12e10c98d0787aeee0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Holiday-Shockwave-US-Christmas-Costs-Soar-as-China-and-India-Tariffs-Hit-Shoppers-Hard/694bab12e10c98d0787aeee0</guid><description>US Christmas shopping is set to become more expensive this year as tariffs on goods from China and India, the top suppliers, drive up import costs. A Moneycontrol analysis reveals that China and India, along with Cambodia, account for over 90 percent of America's festive merchandise imports. Tariffs imposed on these key Asian exporters mean higher prices for ornaments, decorations, and collectibles for US consumers this holiday season.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:47:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694bab12e10c98d0787aeedf_1766566873498.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anil Ambani Secures Major Relief: Bombay High Court Stays Bank's Coercive Actions Over Faulty Audit Report!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Anil-Ambani-Secures-Major-Relief-Bombay-High-Court-Stays-Banks-Coercive-Actions-Over-Faulty-Audit-Report/694baa86e10c98d0787aee24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Anil-Ambani-Secures-Major-Relief-Bombay-High-Court-Stays-Banks-Coercive-Actions-Over-Faulty-Audit-Report/694baa86e10c98d0787aee24</guid><description>The Bombay High Court has halted coercive actions by Bank of Baroda, IDBI Bank, and Indian Overseas Bank against Anil Ambani. The court ruled that an October 2020 forensic audit report by BDO LLP, used as the basis for these actions, may be invalid because it was not signed by a qualified chartered accountant, contrary to new Reserve Bank of India guidelines. Justice Milind Jadhav also criticized the banks for their delayed proceedings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:46:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694baa86e10c98d0787aee23_1766566768771.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Housing Sales CRASH 16%! Top Cities See Steepest Drop Since 2021 – Which Markets Are Defying the Crisis?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Housing-Sales-CRASH-16percent-Top-Cities-See-Steepest-Drop-Since-2021-Which-Markets-Are-Defying-the-Crisis/694ba942e10c98d0787aebf5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Housing-Sales-CRASH-16percent-Top-Cities-See-Steepest-Drop-Since-2021-Which-Markets-Are-Defying-the-Crisis/694ba942e10c98d0787aebf5</guid><description>Housing sales across India's nine major cities fell 16% year-on-year to 98,019 units in Q4 2025, marking the lowest quarterly volume since Q3 2021, according to PropEquity. Only Navi Mumbai and Delhi-NCR reported sales growth, with Pune seeing the sharpest decline. Developers are increasingly focusing on the premium segment, with fewer launches but higher total value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:42:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ba942e10c98d0787aebf4_1766566636447.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Ports Surges! Brokerage Hikes Target to ₹1,876 After Landmark Acquisition - What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Ports-Surges-Brokerage-Hikes-Target-to-1876-After-Landmark-Acquisition-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694ba54fe10c98d0787ae771</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Ports-Surges-Brokerage-Hikes-Target-to-1876-After-Landmark-Acquisition-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694ba54fe10c98d0787ae771</guid><description>PL Capital has significantly increased its target price for Adani Ports &amp; SEZ to ₹1,876 per share, maintaining a 'Buy' rating. This optimism stems from the recent acquisition of North Queensland Export Terminal (NQXT), described as a high-margin, long-life, dollar-linked asset. The brokerage believes NQXT will bolster Adani Ports' volumes and profitability, with the acquisition structured to be balance-sheet neutral through equity issuance, leading to an estimated 6.7% dilution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:18:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ba54fe10c98d0787ae770_1766566382015.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>City Union Bank Skyrockets to New Highs: Is the Rally Just Getting Started?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/City-Union-Bank-Skyrockets-to-New-Highs-Is-the-Rally-Just-Getting-Started/694ba4a0e10c98d0787ae638</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/City-Union-Bank-Skyrockets-to-New-Highs-Is-the-Rally-Just-Getting-Started/694ba4a0e10c98d0787ae638</guid><description>City Union Bank's stock price surged to a new intraday high of ₹295, marking a remarkable 101% gain from its April low. The private sector bank has significantly outperformed the BSE Sensex over the past three and six months. Analysts remain bullish, citing improved profitability, asset quality, and strong capitalisation, with key brokerages setting price targets as high as ₹330.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:18:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ba4a0e10c98d0787ae637_1766565150318.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Price Target Slashed, Yet Nuvama Sees 25% Surge – What's Driving This Paradox?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Steel-Price-Target-Slashed-Yet-Nuvama-Sees-25percent-Surge-Whats-Driving-This-Paradox/694ba402e10c98d0787ae4ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Steel-Price-Target-Slashed-Yet-Nuvama-Sees-25percent-Surge-Whats-Driving-This-Paradox/694ba402e10c98d0787ae4ce</guid><description>Brokerage firm Nuvama Wealth Management has lowered its price target for Jindal Steel and Power Ltd. (JSPL) by 9.7% to ₹1,264, but maintains a "buy" rating, suggesting a 24.8% upside. The firm cited falling steel prices and higher production costs as headwinds impacting current steel spreads. However, Nuvama forecasts significant future growth for JSPL, projecting a 17% CAGR in capacity utilization and a 28% EBITDA CAGR over FY25-28, driven by volume, better realisations, and cost reductions in later years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:17:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ba402e10c98d0787ae4cd_1766564950078.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Skyrockets 125%! Vedanta Chief Calls 'Just the Beginning' - What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-125percent-Vedanta-Chief-Calls-Just-the-Beginning-Whats-Next/694ba3a3e10c98d0787ae446</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-125percent-Vedanta-Chief-Calls-Just-the-Beginning-Whats-Next/694ba3a3e10c98d0787ae446</guid><description>Vedanta Group Chairman Anil Agarwal believes the current silver price rally is just the start, noting its 125% year-to-date gain, double that of gold. He attributes this surge to silver's growing importance as an industrial commodity in sectors like solar energy, defence, and technology, alongside its traditional role as a store of value. With limited supply growth, Agarwal anticipates further appreciation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:17:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ba3a3e10c98d0787ae445_1766566262321.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manish Sonthalia's 2026 Crystal Ball: Top 3 Investment Themes &amp; Hidden Gems Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Manish-Sonthalias-2026-Crystal-Ball-Top-3-Investment-Themes-and-Hidden-Gems-Revealed/694ba3d2e10c98d0787ae479</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Manish-Sonthalias-2026-Crystal-Ball-Top-3-Investment-Themes-and-Hidden-Gems-Revealed/694ba3d2e10c98d0787ae479</guid><description>Manish Sonthalia, CIO at Emkay Investment Managers, forecasts strong potential in premium discretionary consumption (automobiles, jewellery, real estate), capital markets, and rate-sensitive sectors like banking and insurance for 2026. He anticipates easing sluggishness from 2025, driven by improving macro conditions, earnings visibility, and reasonable valuations, despite a weak rupee. Sonthalia also highlighted specific holdings like VIP Industries, Shriram Finance, Groww, and Pine Labs, while advising caution on EMS companies due to currency risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:17:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ba3d2e10c98d0787ae478_1766565087833.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Skyrockets 7% to 52-Week High as Copper Prices Boom on US Economic Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Copper-Skyrockets-7percent-to-52-Week-High-as-Copper-Prices-Boom-on-US-Economic-Surge/694ba396e10c98d0787ae3e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Copper-Skyrockets-7percent-to-52-Week-High-as-Copper-Prices-Boom-on-US-Economic-Surge/694ba396e10c98d0787ae3e1</guid><description>Hindustan Copper shares surged over 7% to a fresh 52-week high of ₹436.50 on Thursday. This rally is driven by firm global copper prices, which are near record levels. Strong US GDP data boosted demand expectations for copper, while a weaker US dollar, anticipated Fed rate cuts, and supply disruptions also supported the metal's price. Higher copper prices directly benefit Hindustan Copper's revenue and margin prospects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:13:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ba396e10c98d0787ae3e0_1766564854842.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's AI Dilemma: Taming Tech Giants to Save Communist Rule!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Chinas-AI-Dilemma-Taming-Tech-Giants-to-Save-Communist-Rule/694ba2c6e10c98d0787ae2c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Chinas-AI-Dilemma-Taming-Tech-Giants-to-Save-Communist-Rule/694ba2c6e10c98d0787ae2c7</guid><description>China is implementing strict regulations on Artificial Intelligence, fearing it could threaten Communist Party rule. While recognizing AI's importance for economic and military growth, the government is filtering training data, enforcing ideological tests for chatbots, and requiring content labeling to control potentially destabilizing responses and punish misuse. This approach aims to balance innovation with stringent political control, potentially impacting China's global AI competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:12:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ba2c6e10c98d0787ae2c6_1766566149936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BP's $6 Billion Castrol Blockbuster: Selling the Iconic Brand - What It Means for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BPs-6-Billion-Castrol-Blockbuster-Selling-the-Iconic-Brand-What-It-Means-for-Investors/694ba261e10c98d0787ae1eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BPs-6-Billion-Castrol-Blockbuster-Selling-the-Iconic-Brand-What-It-Means-for-Investors/694ba261e10c98d0787ae1eb</guid><description>Energy giant BP is selling a 65% stake in its famous Castrol lubricants business to investment firm Stonepeak for approximately $6 billion. This deal values the entire unit at $10.1 billion. BP will retain a 35% interest in a new joint venture, using the sale proceeds to pay down debt. The move is part of BP's strategy to divest assets and refocus its portfolio.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:10:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ba261e10c98d0787ae1ea_1766565305731.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 2,035 Crore Solar Order Electrifies Vardhman Engineers: Stock Surges!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Rs-2035-Crore-Solar-Order-Electrifies-Vardhman-Engineers-Stock-Surges/694ba222e10c98d0787ae14a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Rs-2035-Crore-Solar-Order-Electrifies-Vardhman-Engineers-Stock-Surges/694ba222e10c98d0787ae14a</guid><description>Vardhman Engineers Ltd. has secured a significant ₹2,035 crore order from Onix Renewables for developing 600 MW (AC) solar projects across Maharashtra. The turnkey EPC contract, to be completed within 12 months, includes all project phases from design to commissioning and component supply. This substantial win boosts the company's order book and strengthens its position in the renewable energy sector, with its stock rising over 11% intraday.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:08:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ba222e10c98d0787ae149_1766565439686.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apollo Hospitals Demerger Sparks Surge: Will This Unlock Massive Value for Investors?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Apollo-Hospitals-Demerger-Sparks-Surge-Will-This-Unlock-Massive-Value-for-Investors/694ba1a5e10c98d0787ae043</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Apollo-Hospitals-Demerger-Sparks-Surge-Will-This-Unlock-Massive-Value-for-Investors/694ba1a5e10c98d0787ae043</guid><description>Apollo Hospitals Enterprise Limited shares climbed after the National Stock Exchange (NSE) gave a 'no objections' letter for restructuring its businesses. The company plans to demerge its omnichannel pharmacy and digital health units into a new entity, aiming for a direct listing on stock exchanges within 18-21 months. This move is expected to unlock significant value for shareholders and create India's largest integrated omnichannel healthcare ecosystem with projected revenues of ₹16,300 crore in FY25.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:08:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ba1a5e10c98d0787ae042_1766564334911.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Debt-Hit PSU Venture Eyes IPO: Can Investors Stomach ₹4,000 Cr Dues?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Debt-Hit-PSU-Venture-Eyes-IPO-Can-Investors-Stomach-4000-Cr-Dues/694b9e8ae10c98d0787adc78</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Debt-Hit-PSU-Venture-Eyes-IPO-Can-Investors-Stomach-4000-Cr-Dues/694b9e8ae10c98d0787adc78</guid><description>State-run power giants NTPC Ltd, Power Finance Corp., REC, and Power Grid Corp. of India are considering an Initial Public Offering (IPO) for their joint venture, Energy Efficiency Services Ltd (EESL). EESL faces significant challenges, with over ₹4,000 crore in outstanding dues from government entities straining its cash flow and forcing reliance on costly short-term loans. Despite financial hurdles, expert views suggest government backing might attract investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:49:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9e8ae10c98d0787adc77_1766565062252.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GK Energy Stock Surges: Massive Government Order Fuels 5% Jump! What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/GK-Energy-Stock-Surges-Massive-Government-Order-Fuels-5percent-Jump-Whats-Next/694b9d96e10c98d0787adb0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/GK-Energy-Stock-Surges-Massive-Government-Order-Fuels-5percent-Jump-Whats-Next/694b9d96e10c98d0787adb0a</guid><description>GK Energy's shares jumped nearly 5% after securing an amendment to its Letter of Empanelment from Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Co. The company will supply an additional 10,000 off-grid solar water pumping systems across Maharashtra, valued at ₹254.30 crore (₹276.93 crore with GST) under the PM-KUSUM B scheme. This follows strong Q2 FY25-26 financial results.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:45:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9d96e10c98d0787adb09_1766564468019.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jindal Steel's Explosive Growth Secret UNLOCKED! Brokerage Reveals ₹1,171 Target &amp; Profit Surge Plan!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Steels-Explosive-Growth-Secret-UNLOCKED-Brokerage-Reveals-1171-Target-and-Profit-Surge-Plan/694b9cbde10c98d0787ad8bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Steels-Explosive-Growth-Secret-UNLOCKED-Brokerage-Reveals-1171-Target-and-Profit-Surge-Plan/694b9cbde10c98d0787ad8bd</guid><description>Antique Stock Broking maintains a 'Buy' rating on Jindal Steel (JSL), setting a target price of ₹1,171. The brokerage anticipates significant profit growth driven by Angul plant expansions, higher volumes, an improved product mix, and cost efficiencies from captive resources. Recent commissioning of major furnaces and strong domestic steel demand further bolster the positive outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9cbde10c98d0787ad8bc_1766563874126.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stocks EXPLODE on Record Volume: Ajanta Pharma, JBMA, Manappuram Finance Surge Higher!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Stocks-EXPLODE-on-Record-Volume-Ajanta-Pharma-JBMA-Manappuram-Finance-Surge-Higher/694b9cf4e10c98d0787ad987</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Stocks-EXPLODE-on-Record-Volume-Ajanta-Pharma-JBMA-Manappuram-Finance-Surge-Higher/694b9cf4e10c98d0787ad987</guid><description>Ajanta Pharma, JBMA Auto, and Manappuram Finance stocks experienced significant price jumps on Wednesday, driven by exceptionally heavy trading volumes. This price-volume breakout, observed on technical charts as a spike not witnessed in months, suggests strong investor interest and potential for continued upward momentum in these specific counters on the National Stock Exchange.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:45:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9cf4e10c98d0787ad986_1766563140837.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BP's $10 Billion Masterstroke: Castrol's Future With Stonepeak Sparks Global Buzz!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BPs-10-Billion-Masterstroke-Castrols-Future-With-Stonepeak-Sparks-Global-Buzz/694b9d13e10c98d0787ad9ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BPs-10-Billion-Masterstroke-Castrols-Future-With-Stonepeak-Sparks-Global-Buzz/694b9d13e10c98d0787ad9ea</guid><description>Energy giant BP is selling a 65% stake in its lubricants unit, Castrol, to investment firm Stonepeak for approximately $6 billion. The deal values Castrol at $10.1 billion. BP will retain a 35% interest in a new joint venture, while Stonepeak will hold the majority. Proceeds will be used by BP to reduce debt as part of its larger $20 billion asset disposal strategy. Canada Pension Plan Investment Board is also investing up to $1.05 billion in the deal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:44:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9d13e10c98d0787ad9e9_1766564344419.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver EXPLODE to Record Highs! 💥 Will This Rally Continue?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-EXPLODE-to-Record-Highs-Will-This-Rally-Continue/694b9ccce10c98d0787ad8f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-EXPLODE-to-Record-Highs-Will-This-Rally-Continue/694b9ccce10c98d0787ad8f8</guid><description>Gold and silver prices have hit unprecedented record highs, driven by safe-haven demand and anticipation of US interest rate cuts. Spot gold surpassed $4,500/ounce, while silver futures on MCX surged over 1.8%. This rally marks gold's biggest annual gain since 1979, with silver outperforming significantly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:44:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9ccce10c98d0787ad8f7_1766563174706.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Castrol India Shares EXPLODE 8% As BP Sells Majority Stake in Parent Company!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Castrol-India-Shares-EXPLODE-8percent-As-BP-Sells-Majority-Stake-in-Parent-Company/694b9bdde10c98d0787ad71f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Castrol-India-Shares-EXPLODE-8percent-As-BP-Sells-Majority-Stake-in-Parent-Company/694b9bdde10c98d0787ad71f</guid><description>Castrol India shares jumped over 8% after its parent company, BP, agreed to sell a 65% stake to Stonepeak for $10.1 billion. BP expects $6 billion in net proceeds, which will be used to reduce debt. This strategic sale by BP aims to simplify its portfolio and focus on core downstream operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:44:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9bdde10c98d0787ad71e_1766562848957.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market's Worst Over? Expert Manish Sonthalia Says 2025 Outlook Brighter, Valuations Unworried!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Worst-Over-Expert-Manish-Sonthalia-Says-2025-Outlook-Brighter-Valuations-Unworried/694b9c72e10c98d0787ad7f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Worst-Over-Expert-Manish-Sonthalia-Says-2025-Outlook-Brighter-Valuations-Unworried/694b9c72e10c98d0787ad7f0</guid><description>Market expert Manish Sonthalia of Emkay Investment Managers believes the worst for Indian markets in 2025 may have passed. He views the recent sharp rupee depreciation as excessive and expects earnings to improve, particularly in FY27 with anticipated government support, projecting 13-14% growth. Sonthalia argues that current market valuations, including for small-caps, are not expensive, with the Nifty 50 trading at reasonable price-to-earnings multiples. He notes market complacency and a wait-and-watch approach pending key triggers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:40:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9c72e10c98d0787ad7ef_1766563746776.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Citi's Bold Call: Indian Banks Set for Modest Q3 Growth – Which Stocks Shine &amp; Which Lag?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Citis-Bold-Call-Indian-Banks-Set-for-Modest-Q3-Growth-Which-Stocks-Shine-and-Which-Lag/694b9afae10c98d0787ad584</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Citis-Bold-Call-Indian-Banks-Set-for-Modest-Q3-Growth-Which-Stocks-Shine-and-Which-Lag/694b9afae10c98d0787ad584</guid><description>Citi forecasts Indian banks to post modest Q3 profit growth, with net interest income up 5% and profits up 4% year-on-year. While credit growth is expected to slow, net interest margins (NIMs) will vary, expanding for HDFC Bank, Kotak Mahindra Bank, and others. Citi maintains a positive outlook on HDFC Bank and Kotak Mahindra Bank but downgrades Federal Bank. The report also includes technical insights for Bank Nifty.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:40:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9afae10c98d0787ad583_1766562629276.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Fuels Bank Growth: M&amp;A Financing Boom Expected by 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Fuels-Bank-Growth-MandA-Financing-Boom-Expected-by-2026/694b9b99e10c98d0787ad683</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Fuels-Bank-Growth-MandA-Financing-Boom-Expected-by-2026/694b9b99e10c98d0787ad683</guid><description>Indian banks are actively building teams and expertise to enter the mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;A) financing sector, following draft guidelines from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI). This move aims to capture a market traditionally dominated by foreign lenders, with acquisition finance set to become a key theme for domestic banks by 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:40:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9b99e10c98d0787ad682_1766563028855.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock Mutual Fund Mysteries: Your Top Questions Answered for Smarter Investing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Mutual-Fund-Mysteries-Your-Top-Questions-Answered-for-Smarter-Investing/694b9aa1e10c98d0787ad4dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Mutual-Fund-Mysteries-Your-Top-Questions-Answered-for-Smarter-Investing/694b9aa1e10c98d0787ad4dd</guid><description>Mutual funds are popular in India. This guide tackles common investor confusion, explaining how many funds to choose (5-7 for diversification), ideal investment amounts based on goals and risk, and tax benefits via ELSS (Equity Linked Savings Schemes) under Section 80C (old tax regime). It also clarifies single/joint holdings and planning for multiple financial goals like buying a car or home.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:39:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9aa1e10c98d0787ad4dc_1766562784657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Startup Dream Realized: $1 Billion ESOP Wealth Unlocked in 2025 IPO Frenzy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Startup-Dream-Realized-1-Billion-ESOP-Wealth-Unlocked-in-2025-IPO-Frenzy/694b9a91e10c98d0787ad49b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Startup-Dream-Realized-1-Billion-ESOP-Wealth-Unlocked-in-2025-IPO-Frenzy/694b9a91e10c98d0787ad49b</guid><description>Indian startup employees cashed out a record $1 billion in 2025 through Employee Stock Options (ESOPs) via public listings. Sixteen startups went public, a significant jump from previous years, turning notional "paper wealth" into tangible financial gains. Consumer and fintech companies were at the forefront of this employee wealth creation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:39:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9a91e10c98d0787ad49a_1766562556011.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Shockwave: Top Stocks Surge, Others Plummet! See Who Gained &amp; Lost Big Today!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Shockwave-Top-Stocks-Surge-Others-Plummet-See-Who-Gained-and-Lost-Big-Today/694b948de10c98d0787ac842</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Shockwave-Top-Stocks-Surge-Others-Plummet-See-Who-Gained-and-Lost-Big-Today/694b948de10c98d0787ac842</guid><description>On December 24, 2025, Indian stock markets saw mixed movements. Shriram Finance Ltd and Hindalco Industries Ltd led the gainers with strong percentage increases. Conversely, Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd and Dr Reddys Laboratories Ltd were among the top losers, experiencing significant declines. The benchmark indices, Sensex and Nifty 50, traded with minor fluctuations, closing slightly down and up respectively, indicating a day of selective stock performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:10:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b948de10c98d0787ac841_1766561823852.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Cement Sector Set for Major Rally? Expert Deven Choksey Reveals Top Picks with 20% Upside Potential!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Cement-Sector-Set-for-Major-Rally-Expert-Deven-Choksey-Reveals-Top-Picks-with-20percent-Upside-Potential/694b93f0e10c98d0787ac76a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Cement-Sector-Set-for-Major-Rally-Expert-Deven-Choksey-Reveals-Top-Picks-with-20percent-Upside-Potential/694b93f0e10c98d0787ac76a</guid><description>Market expert Deven Choksey is optimistic about India's cement sector, predicting strong demand post-monsoon. He favors large, pan-India players like UltraTech Cement and Adani Cements (including Ambuja Cement and ACC), highlighting Ambuja's logistical advantages. Choksey forecasts a 15% to 20% potential upside for these stocks over the next 12 to 15 months due to robust volume growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:06:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b93f0e10c98d0787ac769_1766560884411.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auto Sector Rocketing: Expert Deven Choksey Reveals Which Vehicles Are Set for Massive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Sector-Rocketing-Expert-Deven-Choksey-Reveals-Which-Vehicles-Are-Set-for-Massive-Growth/694b93a6e10c98d0787ac68b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Sector-Rocketing-Expert-Deven-Choksey-Reveals-Which-Vehicles-Are-Set-for-Massive-Growth/694b93a6e10c98d0787ac68b</guid><description>Market expert Deven Choksey is favoring commercial vehicles (CVs) over passenger vehicles (PVs) in the current auto market rally. He points to strong economic drivers like infrastructure development, new freight corridors, and industrial expansion fueling demand for CVs. Choksey views companies like Tata Motors and Ashok Leyland as safer bets, anticipating minimal downside risk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:05:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b93a6e10c98d0787ac68a_1766560775223.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharat Dynamics Shares Skyrocket 5% After DRDO's Akash-NG Missile Trial Success!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Bharat-Dynamics-Shares-Skyrocket-5percent-After-DRDOs-Akash-NG-Missile-Trial-Success/694b9345e10c98d0787ac5bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Bharat-Dynamics-Shares-Skyrocket-5percent-After-DRDOs-Akash-NG-Missile-Trial-Success/694b9345e10c98d0787ac5bf</guid><description>Bharat Dynamics Limited (BDL) shares surged nearly 5 percent to ₹1,496.70 after the Defence Research and Development Organisation (DRDO) successfully completed User Evaluation Trials for the Next Generation Akash (Akash-NG) missile system. The advanced missile successfully intercepted aerial targets, meeting all performance requirements, bolstering India's air defence capabilities and boosting investor confidence in the defence sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:05:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9345e10c98d0787ac5be_1766561588632.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Aviation Dream Shattered? 2025's Deadly Crash, Mass Delays &amp; Financial Crisis EXPOSED!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Aviation-Dream-Shattered-2025s-Deadly-Crash-Mass-Delays-and-Financial-Crisis-EXPOSED/694b92d8e10c98d0787ac4e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Aviation-Dream-Shattered-2025s-Deadly-Crash-Mass-Delays-and-Financial-Crisis-EXPOSED/694b92d8e10c98d0787ac4e4</guid><description>In 2025, India's aviation sector faced severe tests despite strong passenger growth. A fatal Air India crash killed 260, while IndiGo cancelled thousands of flights due to new pilot rules. Concerns over GPS spoofing arose. Despite robust traffic, most airlines reported significant losses, including Air India's ₹10,859 crore loss, highlighting operational strains and financial instability amidst infrastructure development.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:03:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b92d8e10c98d0787ac4e3_1766560703027.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Top Hospitals See Stunning Revenue Jump: Here's Why High-Tech Treatments &amp; Insurance Are Driving Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Top-Hospitals-See-Stunning-Revenue-Jump-Heres-Why-High-Tech-Treatments-and-Insurance-Are-Driving-Growth/694b9291e10c98d0787ac432</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Top-Hospitals-See-Stunning-Revenue-Jump-Heres-Why-High-Tech-Treatments-and-Insurance-Are-Driving-Growth/694b9291e10c98d0787ac432</guid><description>India's top private hospitals report a significant 23% surge in average daily revenue per bed for FY25, reaching ₹49,304. This growth is fueled by a rise in expensive high-tech treatments like cancer care and robotic surgeries, coupled with increased patient affordability via insurance coverage. Experts note this reflects a sector-wide shift towards specialized care and consolidation, attracting global investment. While most major chains saw gains, some like Max Healthcare and Rainbow Children's Hospital reported dips.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:02:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b9291e10c98d0787ac431_1766560988596.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Secrets of India's Richest Unlocked: Nuvama Reveals How UHNIs Build Dynastic Wealth &amp; Legacies!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Secrets-of-Indias-Richest-Unlocked-Nuvama-Reveals-How-UHNIs-Build-Dynastic-Wealth-and-Legacies/694b923ce10c98d0787ac390</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Secrets-of-Indias-Richest-Unlocked-Nuvama-Reveals-How-UHNIs-Build-Dynastic-Wealth-and-Legacies/694b923ce10c98d0787ac390</guid><description>Nuvama Private has launched 'The Exceptionals,' a report detailing the wealth creation journeys of India's Ultra High Net Worth Individuals (UHNIs). The insights cover resilience, long-term vision, philanthropy, and legacy planning. It highlights unique investment strategies, asset allocation, and global luxury preferences of these affluent individuals, offering a glimpse into how they shape India's evolving financial landscape.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 07:00:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b923ce10c98d0787ac38f_1766560447364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIFT City Unleashes Financial Freedom: IFSCA Scraps Key Rules to Boost GHCs &amp; Service Providers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GIFT-City-Unleashes-Financial-Freedom-IFSCA-Scraps-Key-Rules-to-Boost-GHCs-and-Service-Providers/694b923ae10c98d0787ac365</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GIFT-City-Unleashes-Financial-Freedom-IFSCA-Scraps-Key-Rules-to-Boost-GHCs-and-Service-Providers/694b923ae10c98d0787ac365</guid><description>International Financial Services Centres Authority (IFSCA) has eased crucial regulations for GIFT City. The 20% employee transfer cap for Global In-House Centres (GHCs) from India has been removed, boosting operational flexibility. Additionally, the mandatory 60 sq ft per-employee office space rule for Book-keeping, Accounting, Taxation, and Financial Crime (BATF) service providers has been scrapped, reducing entry barriers and promoting growth. These changes aim to attract more high-value financial services and talent to GIFT City.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:59:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b923ae10c98d0787ac364_1766560874408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Chip Breakthrough for Cars: Blue Cloud Softech Partners for Automotive Security, Stock Jumps!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Chip-Breakthrough-for-Cars-Blue-Cloud-Softech-Partners-for-Automotive-Security-Stock-Jumps/694b8f11e10c98d0787abe96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Chip-Breakthrough-for-Cars-Blue-Cloud-Softech-Partners-for-Automotive-Security-Stock-Jumps/694b8f11e10c98d0787abe96</guid><description>Blue Cloud Softech Solutions' stock price climbed 3% to ₹25.20 following the announcement of a strategic Memorandum of Understanding with ConnectM Technology Solutions. The collaboration aims to jointly develop a cutting-edge semiconductor-based EdgeAI System-on-Chip (SoC) designed for advanced automotive cybersecurity applications. This partnership signifies Blue Cloud Softech's entry into automotive semiconductor development, with a projected business volume of $50 million over five years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:36:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b8f11e10c98d0787abe95_1766560629711.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Economy Surges Unexpectedly, Fuelling Global Markets &amp; Record Highs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Economy-Surges-Unexpectedly-Fuelling-Global-Markets-and-Record-Highs/694b8e6fe10c98d0787abd6f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Economy-Surges-Unexpectedly-Fuelling-Global-Markets-and-Record-Highs/694b8e6fe10c98d0787abd6f</guid><description>Asian markets showed mixed movements on Wednesday, largely influenced by the US economy's surprisingly strong third-quarter GDP growth of 4.3%. This robust performance propelled the S&amp;P 500 to a new record high in US trading. However, trading volumes remained thin across Asia as many markets prepared for Christmas holidays, with some closing early. Inflation remains a concern, with the PCE index rising to 2.8%.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:36:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b8e6fe10c98d0787abd6e_1766559430568.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Thirumalai Chemicals Surges! Promoter Family Invests ₹56 Cr, Stock Hits 1-Month High!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Thirumalai-Chemicals-Surges-Promoter-Family-Invests-56-Cr-Stock-Hits-1-Month-High/694b8e90e10c98d0787abddb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Thirumalai-Chemicals-Surges-Promoter-Family-Invests-56-Cr-Stock-Hits-1-Month-High/694b8e90e10c98d0787abddb</guid><description>Thirumalai Chemicals' stock price jumped nearly 6% to a one-month high of ₹250.25 after the company successfully raised ₹56.14 crore through a preferential allotment to its promoter group. Key individuals and trusts within the promoter family acquired shares at ₹296 each. This comes as the company's subsidiary progresses with its new manufacturing facility in West Virginia, USA.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:36:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b8e90e10c98d0787abdda_1766559673769.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TV Today Network Surges After Promoter's Big Stake Buy! Radio Business Sale Heats Up Market Buzz!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/TV-Today-Network-Surges-After-Promoters-Big-Stake-Buy-Radio-Business-Sale-Heats-Up-Market-Buzz/694b8de4e10c98d0787abcaa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/TV-Today-Network-Surges-After-Promoters-Big-Stake-Buy-Radio-Business-Sale-Heats-Up-Market-Buzz/694b8de4e10c98d0787abcaa</guid><description>TV Today Network shares climbed over 2.6% following news that its promoter, Living Media India, acquired an additional 4,50,000 shares. This stake purchase comes as the company also moves forward with selling its FM radio broadcasting business, comprising stations in Mumbai, Delhi, and Kolkata, to Abhijit Realtors and Infraventures for ₹10 crore plus taxes. The radio business, which generated ₹14.16 crore revenue but posted a loss of ₹10.54 crore in FY25, is expected to be sold as a going concern by May 2026, subject to approvals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:36:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b8de4e10c98d0787abca9_1766559271991.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Mania: Top Stocks Soar &amp; Plunge Today! See Who Made Big Moves!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Mania-Top-Stocks-Soar-and-Plunge-Today-See-Who-Made-Big-Moves/694b8d76e10c98d0787abc16</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Mania-Top-Stocks-Soar-and-Plunge-Today-See-Who-Made-Big-Moves/694b8d76e10c98d0787abc16</guid><description>On December 24, 2025, Indian stock markets saw mixed movements. Apollo Hospitals Enterprise Ltd and Shriram Finance Ltd led the gains, while Dr Reddys Laboratories Ltd and Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd were among the top losers. The Sensex, Nifty 50, and Nifty Bank indices closed slightly higher, indicating a generally positive but selective trading session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:35:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b8d76e10c98d0787abc15_1766559786742.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>