<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:20:24 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Vedanta Aluminum Outlook Slashed, Peers Outperform</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedanta-Aluminum-Outlook-Slashed-Peers-Outperform/6998c2b8c364d0dd7857c790</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedanta-Aluminum-Outlook-Slashed-Peers-Outperform/6998c2b8c364d0dd7857c790</guid><description>Vedanta Limited has significantly lowered its earnings expectations for its aluminum business, projecting EBITDA of $2.7 billion for the current fiscal year, down from prior forecasts exceeding $4 billion. This recalibration signals potential operational challenges and a divergence from the robust performance reported by industry peers such as Hindalco and Alcoa, raising questions about Vedanta's competitive positioning and future growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:23:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998c2b8c364d0dd7857c78f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta Refinances Debt Amid Demerger Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Vedanta-Refinances-Debt-Amid-Demerger-Uncertainty/6998c2afc364d0dd7857c777</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Vedanta-Refinances-Debt-Amid-Demerger-Uncertainty/6998c2afc364d0dd7857c777</guid><description>Vedanta Resources has secured $350 million in financing from global banks, including First Abu Dhabi Bank, Mashreq Bank, Standard Chartered, Deutsche Bank, and JPMorgan, to refinance upcoming maturities and interest payments. This move is part of a broader strategy to improve its credit profile, which has seen gross debt decline from $9.1 billion in 2022 to approximately $4.7 billion by June 2025. The company's ongoing demerger into five verticals, currently targeting completion by March 31, 2026, faces pending regulatory approvals, adding a layer of complexity to its financial maneuvering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:23:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998c2afc364d0dd7857c776_1771619321758.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCE India Growth: Design Edge Faces Margin Test in EPC Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TCE-India-Growth-Design-Edge-Faces-Margin-Test-in-EPC-Race/6998c2adc364d0dd7857c760</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TCE-India-Growth-Design-Edge-Faces-Margin-Test-in-EPC-Race/6998c2adc364d0dd7857c760</guid><description>Tata Consulting Engineers (TCE) reported ₹2,092 crore in revenue for FY2024-25, fueled by India's robust investments in power, semiconductors, and data centers. Operating under an Owner's Engineer and Project Consultant (OEPC) model, TCE prioritizes design and engineering, consciously avoiding direct construction execution. While its expertise is evident in landmark projects, this specialized approach may face margin pressures and competitive challenges against integrated EPC firms. The recent acquisition of CDI Engineering Solutions aims to expand its global reach as TCE navigates a dynamic infrastructure market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:23:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998c2adc364d0dd7857c75f_1771619160237.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Tiering: Premium Subscriptions Drive New Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Digital-Tiering-Premium-Subscriptions-Drive-New-Revenue/6998c25fc364d0dd7857c68a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Digital-Tiering-Premium-Subscriptions-Drive-New-Revenue/6998c25fc364d0dd7857c68a</guid><description>Indian digital platforms are increasingly moving beyond basic loyalty programs to offer layered subscription services, a trend dubbed 'premium-within-premium.' This strategy involves adding extra paid privileges on top of existing memberships to monetize enhanced user experiences like speed, certainty, and status. Companies like Zomato, Amazon, Flipkart, and Swiggy are implementing these tiered offerings to drive revenue, cater to aspirational consumers, and build deeper customer segmentation in a competitive market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:21:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998c25fc364d0dd7857c689.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Peak XV Raises $1.3B Fund: Smaller Size, AI Focus Signals VC Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Peak-XV-Raises-13B-Fund-Smaller-Size-AI-Focus-Signals-VC-Shift/6998c235c364d0dd7857c673</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Peak-XV-Raises-13B-Fund-Smaller-Size-AI-Focus-Signals-VC-Shift/6998c235c364d0dd7857c673</guid><description>Following its split from Sequoia Capital, Peak XV Partners has secured $1.3 billion for its inaugural independent fund, a significant reduction from prior vehicles. The capital will target seed and early-stage ventures in India and across the Asia-Pacific region, with a sharpened focus on artificial intelligence and cross-border opportunities amidst increased competition and a more discerning VC market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998c235c364d0dd7857c672_1771619038292.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axis Bank: Ex-Director Faces Fund Diversion Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-Ex-Director-Faces-Fund-Diversion-Probe/6998c235c364d0dd7857c65c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-Ex-Director-Faces-Fund-Diversion-Probe/6998c235c364d0dd7857c65c</guid><description>Mumbai Police are conducting a preliminary inquiry into a complaint by Axis Bank accusing former Reliance Commercial Finance Ltd director Devang Mody of deliberately diverting ₹38.95 crore. The funds represent a principal sacrifice under RCFL's resolution plan. A forensic audit commissioned by lead lender Bank of Baroda highlighted questionable fund utilization and circular transactions, prompting Axis Bank to seek charges under the new Bharatiya Nyaya Sanhita.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998c235c364d0dd7857c65b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TryfactaConnex's $7.7B India AI Data Center Plan Faces Fiery Competition, Energy Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TryfactaConnexs-77B-India-AI-Data-Center-Plan-Faces-Fiery-Competition-Energy-Hurdles/6998b587c364d0dd7857c2d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TryfactaConnexs-77B-India-AI-Data-Center-Plan-Faces-Fiery-Competition-Energy-Hurdles/6998b587c364d0dd7857c2d2</guid><description>TryfactaConnex announced a $7.7 billion investment to build a 1-gigawatt AI data center campus in Uttar Pradesh, India, integrating power generation and compute capacity. This initiative, revealed at the AI Impact Summit 2026, aims to bolster India's AI infrastructure. However, the project faces significant headwinds including securing phased financing, navigating India's strained energy grid, and competing against colossal investments from global tech giants and domestic conglomerates in an increasingly crowded market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:27:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998b587c364d0dd7857c2d1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump Orders 10% Tariff Surcharge, Tests Executive Power</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trump-Orders-10percent-Tariff-Surcharge-Tests-Executive-Power/6998b518c364d0dd7857c28a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trump-Orders-10percent-Tariff-Surcharge-Tests-Executive-Power/6998b518c364d0dd7857c28a</guid><description>President Trump has imposed a 10% import surcharge, bypassing Congress following a Supreme Court ruling. Enacted under Section 122 of the Trade Act, this move reignites global trade friction. With existing tariffs on China at 47.5% and Brazil at 50%, the new levy heightens supply chain risks and inflationary pressures. Trading partners are expected to retaliate, echoing past trade war volatility and challenging economic stability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:25:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998b518c364d0dd7857c289.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Religare to Split Insurance, Lending Businesses; RFL Listing Planned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-to-Split-Insurance-Lending-Businesses-RFL-Listing-Planned/69989da8c364d0dd7857b1ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-to-Split-Insurance-Lending-Businesses-RFL-Listing-Planned/69989da8c364d0dd7857b1ea</guid><description>Religare Enterprises announced a strategic demerger to separate its financial services arm, including broking and lending, into a new entity, Religare Finvest Limited (RFL), which will be independently listed. The parent company, Religare Enterprises Limited (REL), will continue to house the profitable Care Health Insurance business. RFL aims for an independent listing by Q1 FY2028, while Care Health is set to receive further capital infusion. Despite strong retail growth in insurance, the company faces legacy legal uncertainties and new accounting methods impacting reported profits.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:45:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69989da8c364d0dd7857b1e9_1771609649925.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC MF Buys More Aster DM Amid Sector Growth &amp; Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-MF-Buys-More-Aster-DM-Amid-Sector-Growth-and-Valuation-Scrutiny/69989da8c364d0dd7857b1d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-MF-Buys-More-Aster-DM-Amid-Sector-Growth-and-Valuation-Scrutiny/69989da8c364d0dd7857b1d4</guid><description>HDFC Mutual Fund has acquired an additional 2.2% stake in Aster DM Healthcare, bringing its total holding to over 7%. This move occurs as the Indian healthcare sector gears up for growth, yet Aster DM's valuation metrics and earnings trajectory present a complex investment picture. Concurrently, HDFC's Flexi Cap Fund surpassed ₹1 lakh crore in assets under management, underscoring its diversified strategy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:45:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69989da8c364d0dd7857b1d3_1771609631871.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Clean Max IPO: ₹3,100 Cr Debt Paydown Amidst Sector Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Clean-Max-IPO-3100-Cr-Debt-Paydown-Amidst-Sector-Growth/69989cf30ec0b8861786dad2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Clean-Max-IPO-3100-Cr-Debt-Paydown-Amidst-Sector-Growth/69989cf30ec0b8861786dad2</guid><description>Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions is poised to launch a significant ₹3,100 crore Initial Public Offering (IPO), with a primary objective of reducing its considerable debt burden. The Brookfield-backed renewable energy provider has secured ₹921 crore from anchor investors ahead of its public issue. Despite reporting strong revenue growth and a return to profitability in the six months ending September 2025, the company carries over ₹10,000 crore in outstanding borrowings. The IPO's success will be a critical test of investor appetite for deleveraging strategies within the booming, yet capital-intensive, renewable energy landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:42:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69989cf30ec0b8861786dad1_1771609454388.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Velan Hotels Wins 99% Shareholder Nod for Strategic Asset Sale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Velan-Hotels-Wins-99percent-Shareholder-Nod-for-Strategic-Asset-Sale/69989d39c364d0dd7857b152</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Velan-Hotels-Wins-99percent-Shareholder-Nod-for-Strategic-Asset-Sale/69989d39c364d0dd7857b152</guid><description>Velan Hotels Limited has secured overwhelming shareholder approval to liquidate key corporate assets. In a decisive remote e-voting process concluded on February 20, 2026, 99.99% of votes backed the primary resolution under Section 180(1)(a). A critical secondary motion involving related party transactions also passed, despite promoters abstaining to strictly comply with SEBI regulations. This mandate clears the regulatory path for immediate financial restructuring.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:32:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/manual-news-1771609397571.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>J.B. Chemicals Shareholders Vote on New Board Led by Torrent Pharma.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/JB-Chemicals-Shareholders-Vote-on-New-Board-Led-by-Torrent-Pharma/6998978fd1e5d163a08b6112</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/JB-Chemicals-Shareholders-Vote-on-New-Board-Led-by-Torrent-Pharma/6998978fd1e5d163a08b6112</guid><description>J.B. Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals is calling for shareholder votes on appointing new board members, including Aman Mehta as Managing Director, following its acquisition by Torrent Pharmaceuticals. The e-voting period runs from February 22 to March 23, 2026. Shareholders' decision will shape the company's future direction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:19:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998978fd1e5d163a08b6111.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SCOTUS Strikes Down Tariffs, US Trade Policy Faces Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/SCOTUS-Strikes-Down-Tariffs-US-Trade-Policy-Faces-Uncertainty/699896a2057e346edab46e92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/SCOTUS-Strikes-Down-Tariffs-US-Trade-Policy-Faces-Uncertainty/699896a2057e346edab46e92</guid><description>The US Supreme Court invalidated broad reciprocal tariffs, reinstating lower Most Favoured Nation (MFN) rates on approximately 55% of Indian exports. While offering immediate relief, the ruling highlights a shift towards sector-specific measures like Section 232, maintaining policy uncertainty. US consumers and businesses continue to bear the economic burden of tariffs, while the US administration signals reliance on executive discretion for future trade actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:15:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699896a2057e346edab46e91_1771607838781.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cube Highways Trust to Go Public, Boost Assets After Unitholder Nod</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cube-Highways-Trust-to-Go-Public-Boost-Assets-After-Unitholder-Nod/699895cd057e346edab46d9f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cube-Highways-Trust-to-Go-Public-Boost-Assets-After-Unitholder-Nod/699895cd057e346edab46d9f</guid><description>Cube Highways Trust unitholders have overwhelmingly approved key resolutions, paving the way for a significant transformation. The approvals include a change in the Trust's sponsor, its conversion from a privately-held entity to a publicly traded Infrastructure Investment Trust (InvIT), and the acquisition of infrastructure assets from two related companies. All resolutions received unanimous backing (100%) from voting unitholders, signaling strong confidence in the Trust's future direction and expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:11:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699895cd057e346edab46d9e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Birla AI Labs Launched: Conglomerate Bets on Cognitive Amplification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Birla-AI-Labs-Launched-Conglomerate-Bets-on-Cognitive-Amplification/699895b0057e346edab46d89</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Birla-AI-Labs-Launched-Conglomerate-Bets-on-Cognitive-Amplification/699895b0057e346edab46d89</guid><description>Ananya Birla has launched Birla AI Labs, signaling a strategic push by the $120 billion Aditya Birla Group to harness Artificial Intelligence. The initiative aims to amplify cognitive abilities across the conglomerate's diverse global businesses, spanning manufacturing to financial services. A dual mandate includes deploying AI for tangible value generation within existing operations and establishing a global research arm to develop proprietary market products. This move places the group within a burgeoning Indian AI ecosystem, marked by substantial investments from competitors like Reliance and Adani, and strategic partnerships by Tata Group.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699895b0057e346edab46d88_1771607625259.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIC Housing Finance Raises ₹150 Crore via NCDs Amidst Profit Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GIC-Housing-Finance-Raises-150-Crore-via-NCDs-Amidst-Profit-Dip/699891d0057e346edab46bfc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GIC-Housing-Finance-Raises-150-Crore-via-NCDs-Amidst-Profit-Dip/699891d0057e346edab46bfc</guid><description>GIC Housing Finance Ltd. is raising Rs 150 crore by issuing Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) with a 7.59% annual interest rate. The funds will be used to expand housing finance operations and manage existing debt. This comes as the company reported a profit dip in Q1 FY26 due to higher provisions. While the NCDs carry strong ratings of AA+/Stable, investors should note potential risks like market trading post-listing and competitive pressures in the housing finance sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:54:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699891d0057e346edab46bfb.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Singer India Surges 53% on Govt Orders, Appliances Lag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Singer-India-Surges-53percent-on-Govt-Orders-Appliances-Lag/69989171057e346edab46b5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Singer-India-Surges-53percent-on-Govt-Orders-Appliances-Lag/69989171057e346edab46b5f</guid><description>Singer India's Q3 FY26 saw revenue surge 53% to ₹161 crore, led by a 75% jump in sewing machines fueled by government orders and e-commerce. However, the appliance division declined 7% with margin pressure. The company expects double-digit growth, plans a new plant, but investors eye valuation concerns and appliance segment weakness.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:53:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69989171057e346edab46b5e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LIC's Cipla Stake Grows Amid Analyst Downgrades</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/LICs-Cipla-Stake-Grows-Amid-Analyst-Downgrades/69989101057e346edab46a9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/LICs-Cipla-Stake-Grows-Amid-Analyst-Downgrades/69989101057e346edab46a9c</guid><description>Life Insurance Corp. of India (LIC) has significantly increased its shareholding in Cipla Ltd. to 9.09%, acquiring over 2% in three months. This accumulation occurs against a backdrop of recent broker downgrades for Cipla following weaker-than-expected December quarter results, which highlighted soft US sales and margin concerns. Despite analyst skepticism, LIC's continued investment suggests a contrarian institutional perspective on the pharmaceutical major.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:51:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69989101057e346edab46a9b_1771606440834.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Ruling Creates Policy Flux; India Trade Pact Revs Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Ruling-Creates-Policy-Flux-India-Trade-Pact-Revs-Up/699890fb057e346edab46a85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Ruling-Creates-Policy-Flux-India-Trade-Pact-Revs-Up/699890fb057e346edab46a85</guid><description>The US Supreme Court nullified former President Trump's broad tariff orders, injecting significant uncertainty into global trade dynamics. Simultaneously, India and the US are advancing a bilateral trade agreement, set to operationalize by April 2026 with reduced tariffs. India's entry into the 'Pax Silica' initiative further deepens technological cooperation. This contrasts sharply with the persistent sell-off in India's IT sector, which remains down 17% over three weeks, highlighting divergent market forces.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:51:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699890fb057e346edab46a84_1771606471907.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aditya Ispat Sells Core Steel Unit Amid Heavy Losses &amp; Net Worth Erosion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aditya-Ispat-Sells-Core-Steel-Unit-Amid-Heavy-Losses-and-Net-Worth-Erosion/699890f8057e346edab46a6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Aditya-Ispat-Sells-Core-Steel-Unit-Amid-Heavy-Losses-and-Net-Worth-Erosion/699890f8057e346edab46a6b</guid><description>Aditya Ispat Limited's board has approved selling its non-alloy steel manufacturing and trading division, the company's primary revenue generator. This drastic move aims to combat substantial losses and the erosion of the company's net worth. The buyer and sale price are yet to be determined, and the deal requires shareholder and regulatory approvals. The alloy steel trading business will continue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:51:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699890f8057e346edab46a6a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors Tackles India's Entry-Level EV Hurdle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Tackles-Indias-Entry-Level-EV-Hurdle/69989011057e346edab46977</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Tackles-Indias-Entry-Level-EV-Hurdle/69989011057e346edab46977</guid><description>India's electric vehicle market growth hinges on penetrating the sub-₹12 lakh segment, currently at just 1.6% EV adoption. Tata Motors is addressing this critical gap with the refreshed Punch.ev, offering enhanced range, faster charging, and an unprecedented lifetime battery warranty, alongside a Battery-as-a-Service (BaaS) model to lower upfront costs. This strategic pivot aims to build consumer trust and value proposition, essential for transitioning from niche adoption to mass market appeal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:47:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69989011057e346edab46976.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Canada Forge 'Sovereign AI' Alliance Amid Global Tech Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Canada-Forge-Sovereign-AI-Alliance-Amid-Global-Tech-Race/69988ea5057e346edab46885</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Canada-Forge-Sovereign-AI-Alliance-Amid-Global-Tech-Race/69988ea5057e346edab46885</guid><description>Canada's Minister for AI and Digital Innovation, Evan Solomon, and India's IT Minister Ashwini Vaishnaw are advancing Memoranda of Understanding (MoUs) to foster "Sovereign AI." This partnership prioritizes national control over digital destiny, intellectual property, and AI infrastructure, positioning India and Canada as key players in a global AI landscape increasingly dominated by the US and China. The initiative includes investment in AI safety technologies like LawZero and aims to address workforce transitions, but faces substantial challenges in compute capacity, regulatory harmonization, and competition with established tech giants.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:41:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69988ea5057e346edab46884.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Trade Pacts Fuel Market Optimism Amidst Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Pacts-Fuel-Market-Optimism-Amidst-Global-Headwinds/69988dd8057e346edab4675d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Pacts-Fuel-Market-Optimism-Amidst-Global-Headwinds/69988dd8057e346edab4675d</guid><description>India's economic outlook remains robust, buoyed by finalized Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) with the EU and an interim pact with the US, which are set to enhance market access and export competitiveness for key sectors like textiles, pharmaceuticals, and auto ancillaries. Foreign portfolio investments staged a significant comeback in February, signaling renewed investor confidence. The Union Budget's focus on record capital expenditure and fiscal consolidation further supports this trajectory. However, persistent global economic slowdowns, potential commodity price volatility, and lingering competitiveness challenges require careful monitoring.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:37:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69988dd8057e346edab4675c_1771605556193.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>WeWork India Expands Bengaluru Operations Amidst Governance Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/WeWork-India-Expands-Bengaluru-Operations-Amidst-Governance-Concerns/69988db0057e346edab46746</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/WeWork-India-Expands-Bengaluru-Operations-Amidst-Governance-Concerns/69988db0057e346edab46746</guid><description>WeWork India is boosting its Bengaluru capacity by adding about 3,100 desks through a lease of 1,69,485 square feet. This expansion, expected by September 2026 with a ₹42 crore investment, aims to meet growing demand. However, the company faces scrutiny over promoter-related legal issues and governance risks, even as the Indian coworking market sees robust growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:37:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69988db0057e346edab46745.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Inflation: Policy Resilience Over TOP Price Shocks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Inflation-Policy-Resilience-Over-TOP-Price-Shocks/69988a8f057e346edab46529</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Inflation-Policy-Resilience-Over-TOP-Price-Shocks/69988a8f057e346edab46529</guid><description>A Reserve Bank of India study reveals that while recurrent spikes in tomato, onion, and potato (TOP) prices are major sources of India's headline retail inflation volatility, they have been largely contained. Effective supply-side management and a robust flexible inflation targeting framework have moderated overall price swings compared to pre-2016 periods. Despite these supply shocks, the system demonstrates increasing resilience, a trend further supported by recent adjustments to the Consumer Price Index (CPI) basket, which reduces food's weight and enhances the focus on core inflation dynamics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69988a8f057e346edab46528_1771604760677.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FDI Paradox: Repatriation Outpaces Inflows, Pressuring Rupee</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FDI-Paradox-Repatriation-Outpaces-Inflows-Pressuring-Rupee/69988a88057e346edab46512</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FDI-Paradox-Repatriation-Outpaces-Inflows-Pressuring-Rupee/69988a88057e346edab46512</guid><description>India experienced a significant net foreign direct investment (FDI) deficit in December 2025, marking the fourth consecutive month of outflows. This trend was primarily driven by a record $7.45 billion in capital repatriation by foreign investors, coupled with a 30.5% year-on-year surge in Indian companies' outward FDI to $2.74 billion. Despite robust gross inward FDI, the substantial capital exits are exerting downward pressure on the Indian rupee, which has touched new all-time lows. The Reserve Bank of India's data highlights a complex investment picture where strong gross inflows are being overshadowed by aggressive capital withdrawal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:23:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69988a88057e346edab46511.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NaBFID Bond Sale Scrapped as Yields Spike on Geopolitical Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NaBFID-Bond-Sale-Scrapped-as-Yields-Spike-on-Geopolitical-Fears/69988a7c057e346edab464fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NaBFID-Bond-Sale-Scrapped-as-Yields-Spike-on-Geopolitical-Fears/69988a7c057e346edab464fa</guid><description>National Bank for Financing Infrastructure and Development (NaBFID) scrapped its planned three-year bond issuance after receiving bids at a yield of approximately 7.15%, which was unacceptable to the issuer. This withdrawal highlights increasing investor caution driven by hardening government bond yields and elevated geopolitical tensions. The failed auction contrasts with NABARD's earlier successful three-year bond sale at a lower 7.01% yield and underscores a broader trend of subdued corporate fundraising in the current fiscal year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:23:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69988a7c057e346edab464f9_1771604801535.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Investor Shifts Spark Shankara, MIC, Ganesh Benzoplast Activity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Investor-Shifts-Spark-Shankara-MIC-Ganesh-Benzoplast-Activity/699889f5057e346edab46470</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Investor-Shifts-Spark-Shankara-MIC-Ganesh-Benzoplast-Activity/699889f5057e346edab46470</guid><description>Significant institutional and promoter trades reshaped holdings in key Indian equities on February 20. Ballygunge Family Trust acquired a 2.1% stake in Shankara Building Products from Marval Guru Fund. Concurrently, MIC Electronics witnessed further promoter divestment. In Ganesh Benzoplast, Malabar India Fund sold a substantial stake, which was immediately absorbed by Goel Seema as the stock broke out on high volume.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:21:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699889f5057e346edab4646f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Holds Rates: India Navigates Growth Surge with Cautious Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-India-Navigates-Growth-Surge-with-Cautious-Outlook/6998881b057e346edab46328</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-India-Navigates-Growth-Surge-with-Cautious-Outlook/6998881b057e346edab46328</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) unanimously decided to hold the repo rate steady at 5.25% and maintain a neutral policy stance. Governor Sanjay Malhotra highlighted strong macroeconomic fundamentals and revised GDP forecasts upward to 7.4% for FY26 and 6.9%-7.0% for Q1/Q2 FY27. Inflation projections were also nudged up slightly to 2.1% for FY26, with future inflation and growth outcomes heavily dependent on incoming data. Despite optimistic domestic conditions, external risks and a divergence in opinion on the policy stance signal a watchful approach.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:13:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998881b057e346edab46327_1771604219377.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Uravi Defence Buys 10% UK Firm Stake for Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Uravi-Defence-Buys-10percent-UK-Firm-Stake-for-Growth/69988810057e346edab46311</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Uravi-Defence-Buys-10percent-UK-Firm-Stake-for-Growth/69988810057e346edab46311</guid><description>Uravi Defence and Technology Limited, through its subsidiary Bharat Technology Limited, has acquired a 10% stake in UK-based Spafax International Holdings Limited for 340,000 British Pounds. This move is a step in Uravi's phased acquisition plan to bolster its defence technology offerings and expand its global footprint, leveraging Spafax's specialized automotive safety and defence solutions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:13:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69988810057e346edab46310.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supreme Court Strikes Down Trump Tariffs, But Economic Headwinds Persist</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Supreme-Court-Strikes-Down-Trump-Tariffs-But-Economic-Headwinds-Persist/699884e9057e346edab461c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Supreme-Court-Strikes-Down-Trump-Tariffs-But-Economic-Headwinds-Persist/699884e9057e346edab461c2</guid><description>The Supreme Court's 6-3 decision on Friday invalidated President Trump's use of the International Emergency Economic Powers Act for global tariffs, a move that initially boosted U.S. equities. However, this decision lands amidst a landscape of persistent economic challenges. Fourth-quarter GDP growth slowed to a weaker-than-expected 1.4%, while core inflation, measured by the PCE price index, remained elevated at 3% in December. These factors continue to complicate the economic outlook and the Federal Reserve's policy path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699884e9057e346edab461c1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Insurance Surge: Parametric Solutions Crucial Amidst Climate Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Surge-Parametric-Solutions-Crucial-Amidst-Climate-Crisis/69988319057e346edab460bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Surge-Parametric-Solutions-Crucial-Amidst-Climate-Crisis/69988319057e346edab460bd</guid><description>India endured relentless extreme weather in early 2025, resulting in significant loss of life and economic damage. Traditional relief and insurance face limitations against escalating climate volatility. Parametric insurance, offering rapid, data-driven payouts, is emerging as a critical solution as the Indian insurance market anticipates strong growth, signaling a strategic pivot toward climate-resilient financial tools.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:51:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69988319057e346edab460bc_1771602804982.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Curbs Bank Exposure, Derivative Volumes Face Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Curbs-Bank-Exposure-Derivative-Volumes-Face-Scrutiny/69988273057e346edab45ff6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Curbs-Bank-Exposure-Derivative-Volumes-Face-Scrutiny/69988273057e346edab45ff6</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has enacted new regulations restricting scheduled commercial banks from financing share purchases and proprietary trading by stockbrokers, capping exponential growth in equity derivatives volumes. This move, driven by concerns over leveraged trading and bank stability, imposes stricter collateral requirements for guarantees and seeks to rein in market speculation, though broker bodies warn of potential liquidity impacts. The RBI aims to balance financial stability with continued support for essential client-facing broker operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:49:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69988273057e346edab45ff5_1771602709174.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Peak XV Raises $1.3B, Bets Big on AI Amidst Investor Rush</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Peak-XV-Raises-13B-Bets-Big-on-AI-Amidst-Investor-Rush/699880f5057e346edab45eaf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Peak-XV-Raises-13B-Bets-Big-on-AI-Amidst-Investor-Rush/699880f5057e346edab45eaf</guid><description>Peak XV Partners has successfully raised $1.3 billion across new India and Asia-focused funds, bolstering its assets under management to over $10 billion. The firm is strategically concentrating capital on artificial intelligence and cross-border ventures, earmarking the majority for India. This move signals a heightened focus on generating high returns amidst increasing competition and a reshuffling of senior leadership.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:42:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699880f5057e346edab45eae.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BRICS Currency Talk Fades, Dollar Alternative Push Continues</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/BRICS-Currency-Talk-Fades-Dollar-Alternative-Push-Continues/69987dd3057e346edab45d5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/BRICS-Currency-Talk-Fades-Dollar-Alternative-Push-Continues/69987dd3057e346edab45d5f</guid><description>Brazilian President Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva has clarified that BRICS nations are not currently debating a common currency, tempering market speculation. Despite this denial, the bloc's underlying objective to reduce reliance on the U.S. dollar and foster greater intra-bloc trade through alternative payment mechanisms and bilateral currency agreements remains a significant, ongoing strategic priority.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:29:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69987dd3057e346edab45d5e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brazil-India Trade: Local Currencies &amp; Supply Chain Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Brazil-India-Trade-Local-Currencies-and-Supply-Chain-Shifts/69987d4e057e346edab45cc9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Brazil-India-Trade-Local-Currencies-and-Supply-Chain-Shifts/69987d4e057e346edab45cc9</guid><description>Brazil's President Lula champions bilateral trade between India and Brazil using their own currencies, signaling a gradual move away from dollar dominance. While cautioning against overnight changes, he highlighted the potential for increased local-currency settlements. This push coincides with Embraer's announcement of a new manufacturing plant in India, aiming to diversify supply chains and foster deeper economic ties, targeting $30-$40 billion in bilateral trade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:27:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69987d4e057e346edab45cc8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's NRI Tax Rules Tighten: Compliance Burden Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-NRI-Tax-Rules-Tighten-Compliance-Burden-Looms/69987cb1057e346edab45c06</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-NRI-Tax-Rules-Tighten-Compliance-Burden-Looms/69987cb1057e346edab45c06</guid><description>India's tax landscape for returning Non-Resident Indians (NRIs) is undergoing significant shifts, demanding meticulous compliance and potentially altering global income taxation. Stricter residential status rules, the need for comprehensive foreign asset disclosure, and the complexities of Foreign Tax Credit (FTC) claims are now paramount. Failure to adhere can lead to substantial penalties and tax liabilities. Proactive financial planning and expert consultation are essential to navigate these evolving regulations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:24:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69987cb1057e346edab45c05_1771601232066.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Beer Giants Pivot to India Amidst European Contraction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Global-Beer-Giants-Pivot-to-India-Amidst-European-Contraction/69987c5f057e346edab45b93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Global-Beer-Giants-Pivot-to-India-Amidst-European-Contraction/69987c5f057e346edab45b93</guid><description>Soufflet Malt is investing €100 million in a new Indian production facility while closing European plants, mirroring a global shift as Europe's beer market stagnates due to demographic and health trends. India, with its rapidly growing young population, urbanization, and favorable policies including tax reforms and the EU-India FTA, presents a critical growth engine. Carlsberg is exploring an IPO in India, designating it its top growth market, while Heineken doubles down on its UBL subsidiary. This strategic rebalancing highlights India's emergence as the pivotal frontier for international brewers seeking volume and value.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:23:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69987c5f057e346edab45b92.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US GDP Slows Sharply; Sticky Inflation &amp; AI Boom Defy Downturn</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-GDP-Slows-Sharply-Sticky-Inflation-and-AI-Boom-Defy-Downturn/69987ac8057e346edab45a81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-GDP-Slows-Sharply-Sticky-Inflation-and-AI-Boom-Defy-Downturn/69987ac8057e346edab45a81</guid><description>The U.S. economy's expansion decelerated sharply to a 1.4% annualized rate in the fourth quarter of 2025, significantly underperforming expectations. This slowdown was primarily attributed to a record-length government shutdown, reduced government spending, and a cooling in consumer outlays. However, robust business investment in artificial intelligence and persistent core inflation above the Federal Reserve's target indicate underlying economic dynamics that complicate the growth narrative.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:16:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69987ac8057e346edab45a80_1771600760389.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>