<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 12:37:53 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Geopolitical Tensions Disrupt India's Basmati Exports</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Geopolitical-Tensions-Disrupt-Indias-Basmati-Exports/69a42cc03d2913aa7c2125e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Geopolitical-Tensions-Disrupt-Indias-Basmati-Exports/69a42cc03d2913aa7c2125e2</guid><description>Geopolitical instability stemming from US and Israeli military actions in Iran has directly impacted India's basmati rice export sector. Exporters in Haryana face significant payment delays and shipment disruptions, particularly for consignments destined for Iran and Afghanistan transiting through Iran's Bandar Abbas port. This disruption has already precipitated a decline in basmati rice rates, highlighting vulnerabilities in established trade routes and merchant margins.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 12:10:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a42cc03d2913aa7c2125e1_1772367150903.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Retirement Savings: NPS vs. Mutual Funds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Retirement-Savings-NPS-vs-Mutual-Funds/69a42b753d2913aa7c21250b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Retirement-Savings-NPS-vs-Mutual-Funds/69a42b753d2913aa7c21250b</guid><description>The National Pension System (NPS) provides a disciplined, constrained approach to retirement savings, featuring lock-ins and mandatory annuities for assured income. In contrast, mutual funds offer significant flexibility, liquidity, and investor control, enabling active management for higher growth potential and tax optimization. The choice hinges on prioritizing forced savings versus dynamic investment strategies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 12:05:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a42b753d2913aa7c21250a_1772366865112.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPI Monthly Dip Masks Infrastructure Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/UPI-Monthly-Dip-Masks-Infrastructure-Shift/69a425013d2913aa7c212281</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/UPI-Monthly-Dip-Masks-Infrastructure-Shift/69a425013d2913aa7c212281</guid><description>Unified Payments Interface (UPI) transaction volumes saw a 6% dip in February, totaling 20.39 billion, and a 5% value decrease to Rs 26.84 trillion. This month-on-month moderation is attributed to February's shorter duration. However, daily transaction averages increased to 728 million, with values reaching Rs 95,865 crore, underscoring UPI's maturation into essential financial infrastructure. Other digital payment systems like IMPS, FASTag, and AePS also experienced monthly declines, though some showed increased daily activity, reflecting a broader trend of scaling and optimization within India's digital payment ecosystem. Annual growth for UPI remained robust, up 27% in volume and 22% in value compared to the prior year.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 11:37:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a425013d2913aa7c212280_1772365151895.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mercedes V-Class Reimagined: India's Luxury MPV Race Heats Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mercedes-V-Class-Reimagined-Indias-Luxury-MPV-Race-Heats-Up/69a423033d2913aa7c21218c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mercedes-V-Class-Reimagined-Indias-Luxury-MPV-Race-Heats-Up/69a423033d2913aa7c21218c</guid><description>Mercedes-Benz is reintroducing its V-Class in India, repositioning it as an ultra-luxury, chauffeur-focused flagship with a price tag exceeding ₹1.5 crore. This strategic move targets the rapidly expanding 'chauffeur-first' economy and a growing demand for high-margin vehicles, marking a significant departure from its previous, less successful iteration.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 11:29:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a423033d2913aa7c21218b_1772364684153.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Feb Sales Surge 44% on Strong Demand, EV Traction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Feb-Sales-Surge-44percent-on-Strong-Demand-EV-Traction/69a41a953d2913aa7c211e8c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Feb-Sales-Surge-44percent-on-Strong-Demand-EV-Traction/69a41a953d2913aa7c211e8c</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp reported robust February 2026 sales with a 44% year-on-year increase in dispatches to 558,216 units. VAHAN registrations also climbed 18%, while its electric mobility brand VIDA showed significant traction. The company also achieved double-digit growth in its global business operations, indicating broad-based momentum.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 10:53:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a41a953d2913aa7c211e8b_1772362552603.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hormuz Tensions Strain India's Energy Security; LNG, LPG Most Exposed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Hormuz-Tensions-Strain-Indias-Energy-Security-LNG-LPG-Most-Exposed/69a416c93d2913aa7c211ce6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Hormuz-Tensions-Strain-Indias-Energy-Security-LNG-LPG-Most-Exposed/69a416c93d2913aa7c211ce6</guid><description>India possesses sufficient short-term crude oil inventories to mitigate immediate supply disruptions from Strait of Hormuz closure, but the crisis acutely exposes vulnerabilities in liquefied natural gas (LNG) and liquefied petroleum gas (LPG) imports. While price volatility is the foremost concern, prolonged blockades could strain alternatives for gas and LPG, despite diversification efforts and strategic reserves. Analysts highlight that India's increased reliance on Middle Eastern crude amplifies exposure to escalating geopolitical risks in the region.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 10:36:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a416c93d2913aa7c211ce5_1772361493750.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Defence Expands Arsenal with Punj Lloyd Unit Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Defence-Expands-Arsenal-with-Punj-Lloyd-Unit-Acquisition/69a414faedbd0c0ef0197540</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Defence-Expands-Arsenal-with-Punj-Lloyd-Unit-Acquisition/69a414faedbd0c0ef0197540</guid><description>Adani Defence Systems and Technologies Ltd (ADSTL), a subsidiary of Adani Enterprises, is significantly expanding its defense capabilities. It has acquired Punj Lloyd Ltd's defense manufacturing unit in Malanpur, Madhya Pradesh, via a slump sale. Additionally, ADSTL is increasing its controlling stake in Air Works India (Engineering) Private Ltd. to 99.98%. These moves aim to consolidate Adani's presence and production capacity within India's burgeoning defence ecosystem, leveraging acquired assets for accelerated growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 10:29:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a414faedbd0c0ef019753f_1772361100702.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eicher Motors Growth Skewed by Budget Bikes Amidst Premium Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Growth-Skewed-by-Budget-Bikes-Amidst-Premium-Slump/69a414f6edbd0c0ef0197529</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Growth-Skewed-by-Budget-Bikes-Amidst-Premium-Slump/69a414f6edbd0c0ef0197529</guid><description>Eicher Motors posted an 11% year-on-year increase in motorcycle sales for February 2026, reaching 1,00,905 units. However, this growth is heavily concentrated in its lower-engine capacity segment, which surged 16%, while the higher-margin premium (&gt;350cc) category saw a significant 14% decline. International business also contracted by 2%. This divergence highlights a potential shift in consumer demand away from its flagship premium offerings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 10:29:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a414f6edbd0c0ef0197528_1772361126156.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Global Growth Ambitions Clash with External Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Global-Growth-Ambitions-Clash-with-External-Risks/69a41439edbd0c0ef0197488</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Global-Growth-Ambitions-Clash-with-External-Risks/69a41439edbd0c0ef0197488</guid><description>Former Reserve Bank of India Governor Shaktikanta Das posits India will architect global growth this decade, backed by fiscal consolidation towards a 50% debt-to-GDP ratio by 2031, elevated investment, and a trade policy shift. Ambitious targets for green hydrogen and India Stack 2.0 are set. However, persistent geopolitical fragmentation and supply chain realignments pose significant global downside risks, threatening capital flow volatility for emerging markets. India's manufacturing competitiveness is growing but faces infrastructure challenges compared to regional rivals like Vietnam and Mexico.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 10:26:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a41439edbd0c0ef0197487_1772361151296.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Launches 'Insiders' Program for 1M+ Riders, Offering ₹50k Benefits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Launches-Insiders-Program-for-1M-Riders-Offering-50k-Benefits/69a41389edbd0c0ef019738e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Launches-Insiders-Program-for-1M-Riders-Offering-50k-Benefits/69a41389edbd0c0ef019738e</guid><description>Ola Electric has unveiled 'Ola Insiders', a new community program aimed at its over 1 million riders. The initiative offers significant benefits, including vehicle upgrade incentives of up to ₹50,000 and add-on benefits up to ₹20,000. This move seeks to deepen customer loyalty and encourage repeat business in a competitive EV market.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 10:23:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a41389edbd0c0ef019738d_1772360715471.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GST Revenue Jumps 8.1%, But Growth Quality Questioned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/GST-Revenue-Jumps-81percent-But-Growth-Quality-Questioned/69a41342edbd0c0ef0197330</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/GST-Revenue-Jumps-81percent-But-Growth-Quality-Questioned/69a41342edbd0c0ef0197330</guid><description>India's Goods and Services Tax (GST) collections for February 2026 reached ₹1.83 lakh crore, an 8.1% year-on-year increase. This figure, up from ₹1.69 lakh crore in February 2025, signals continued economic activity. Sequential collections also rose from ₹1.71 lakh crore in January 2026. Year-to-date gross collections stand at ₹20.27 lakh crore, an 8.3% rise. However, scrutiny of this nominal growth is warranted given prevailing inflation trends and regional fiscal divergences.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 10:21:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a41342edbd0c0ef019732f_1772360710394.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Loan Moratoriums: Strategic Tool vs. Costly Pause</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Loan-Moratoriums-Strategic-Tool-vs-Costly-Pause/69a40eddedbd0c0ef0197099</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Loan-Moratoriums-Strategic-Tool-vs-Costly-Pause/69a40eddedbd0c0ef0197099</guid><description>Loan moratoriums, while offering immediate cash flow relief, carry significant long-term costs due to accruing interest. Financial institutions utilize them as a strategic risk management tool to prevent defaults and maintain borrower relationships. However, for borrowers, misjudging the temporary nature of income disruptions against structural issues can lead to a magnified repayment burden. Prudent application, clear communication with lenders on credit reporting, and a thorough assessment of revised amortization schedules are paramount.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 10:03:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a40eddedbd0c0ef0197098_1772359813714.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Tensions Drive Travel Insurance Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Geopolitical-Tensions-Drive-Travel-Insurance-Demand/69a40ed9edbd0c0ef0197082</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Geopolitical-Tensions-Drive-Travel-Insurance-Demand/69a40ed9edbd0c0ef0197082</guid><description>Escalating geopolitical tensions in the Middle East have triggered widespread flight cancellations and airspace closures, leading to a significant surge in demand for travel insurance. Indian insurers, including ICICI Lombard and TATA AIG, are experiencing heightened inquiries and policy purchases as travelers seek protection against trip disruptions, delays, and cancellations. This trend highlights the growing importance of comprehensive travel insurance in an increasingly volatile global environment. The situation has prompted airlines to reroute flights and offer rescheduling support, while travel agencies are providing real-time updates to stranded passengers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 10:03:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a40ed9edbd0c0ef0197081_1772359512780.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Chip Ambition: Production Surge Amidst Global Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Chip-Ambition-Production-Surge-Amidst-Global-Challenges/69a40e04edbd0c0ef0196f68</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Chip-Ambition-Production-Surge-Amidst-Global-Challenges/69a40e04edbd0c0ef0196f68</guid><description>India's semiconductor drive accelerates with Micron's Sanand facility commencing production and three more plants slated for 2026. This expansion, part of a ₹1.60 lakh crore initiative, aims to bolster India's tech sovereignty. However, the nation faces steep competition, infrastructure deficits, and a critical shortage of specialized manufacturing talent, challenging its path to global semiconductor leadership.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:59:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a40e04edbd0c0ef0196f67_1772359423615.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Guarantor Ruling Bolsters SBI, Sets Debt Recovery Precedent</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Guarantor-Ruling-Bolsters-SBI-Sets-Debt-Recovery-Precedent/69a40e01edbd0c0ef0196f50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Guarantor-Ruling-Bolsters-SBI-Sets-Debt-Recovery-Precedent/69a40e01edbd0c0ef0196f50</guid><description>The National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) has dismissed appeals by Rajkumar and Pradeep Dhoot, upholding the initiation of personal insolvency proceedings against them by State Bank of India (SBI). This ruling, stemming from Videocon Industries' substantial debt default for which the brothers were personal guarantors, reinforces the legal framework empowering financial creditors under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC). The decision strengthens SBI's recovery posture and sets a precedent for guarantor accountability in large corporate defaults.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:59:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a40e01edbd0c0ef0196f4f_1772359297175.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Middle East Conflict Rattles India: Inflation, FDI, and Auto Sector Risks Escalate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Middle-East-Conflict-Rattles-India-Inflation-FDI-and-Auto-Sector-Risks-Escalate/69a40d92edbd0c0ef0196e91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Middle-East-Conflict-Rattles-India-Inflation-FDI-and-Auto-Sector-Risks-Escalate/69a40d92edbd0c0ef0196e91</guid><description>Indian equity markets face a sharp, negative opening on Monday due to escalating Middle East hostilities and the reported death of Iran's Supreme Leader. This geopolitical shock intensifies economic vulnerabilities for India, primarily through higher crude oil prices, which threaten inflation, fiscal stability, and delay interest rate cut expectations. The situation also casts a shadow over foreign investor sentiment and adds a layer of risk to upcoming domestic macroeconomic data releases.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:57:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a40d92edbd0c0ef0196e90_1772359156920.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCRs Exceed Estimates: Government Boosted by Asset Monetization</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/MCRs-Exceed-Estimates-Government-Boosted-by-Asset-Monetization/69a40cfbedbd0c0ef0196e00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/MCRs-Exceed-Estimates-Government-Boosted-by-Asset-Monetization/69a40cfbedbd0c0ef0196e00</guid><description>Miscellaneous Capital Receipts (MCRs) have surpassed revised budget estimates for FY26, propelled by significant asset monetization. Collections now exceed ₹34,000 crore, largely due to the minority stake sale in Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) and substantial realisations from Infrastructure Investment Trusts (InvITs), which contributed over ₹18,800 crore. The government has set an ambitious ₹80,000 crore target for MCRs in the next fiscal year, signaling a continued emphasis on asset monetization as a key revenue generation strategy.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:55:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a40cfbedbd0c0ef0196dff_1772359063223.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Ports Stock Slips Despite Haifa Port Reassurance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Ports-Stock-Slips-Despite-Haifa-Port-Reassurance/69a406f1edbd0c0ef0196bb0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Ports-Stock-Slips-Despite-Haifa-Port-Reassurance/69a406f1edbd0c0ef0196bb0</guid><description>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd confirmed its Haifa Port remains fully functional despite heightened security tensions in northern Israel, assuring investors and global partners of operational continuity and asset security. However, the company's stock closed 1.98% lower on Friday, February 28, 2026, at ₹1,519.90. This immediate market reaction suggests that ongoing regional instability is prompting investors to reprice geopolitical risk, potentially outweighing assurances of operational status for Adani's strategically vital Mediterranean gateway. Despite this dip, the stock has surged nearly 45% over the past year, significantly outperforming the Nifty 50's 14% gain.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:29:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a406f1edbd0c0ef0196baf_1772357590072.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IIFCL IPO Approved: Navigating PSU Valuation &amp; Infrastructure Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IIFCL-IPO-Approved-Navigating-PSU-Valuation-and-Infrastructure-Growth/69a4069bedbd0c0ef0196b3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IIFCL-IPO-Approved-Navigating-PSU-Valuation-and-Infrastructure-Growth/69a4069bedbd0c0ef0196b3b</guid><description>State-owned India Infrastructure Finance Company (IIFCL) has secured government approval for its Initial Public Offering (IPO), a move aimed at bolstering its capital base and aligning with national disinvestment strategies. The company, which reported a record net profit of ₹2,165 crore in fiscal year 2025, plans to leverage its strong financial performance and the government's infrastructure focus for its market debut. Managing Director Rohit Rishi outlined an ambitious vision for growth, emphasizing technological adoption and diversification into emerging sectors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:27:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a4069bedbd0c0ef0196b3a_1772357539307.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Defence Boosts Air Works India Stake to 99.98% in MRO Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Defence-Boosts-Air-Works-India-Stake-to-9998percent-in-MRO-Consolidation/69a40323edbd0c0ef0196a0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Defence-Boosts-Air-Works-India-Stake-to-9998percent-in-MRO-Consolidation/69a40323edbd0c0ef0196a0a</guid><description>Adani Defence Systems &amp; Technologies Ltd (ADSTL) has acquired an additional 14.2% stake in Air Works India from Punj Lloyd Aviation Ltd (PLAL). This transaction raises ADSTL's total ownership in the aviation MRO firm to 99.98%, significantly consolidating its control. The move is part of Adani Group's strategy to bolster its defence and aerospace capabilities, integrating Air Works' extensive maintenance, repair, and overhaul services into its growing ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a40323edbd0c0ef0196a09_1772356500733.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Loans Surge: Higher LTVs Mask Borrower Volatility Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Loans-Surge-Higher-LTVs-Mask-Borrower-Volatility-Risk/69a3f9d3edbd0c0ef0196696</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Loans-Surge-Higher-LTVs-Mask-Borrower-Volatility-Risk/69a3f9d3edbd0c0ef0196696</guid><description>Gold loans are experiencing explosive growth, surpassing Rs 3.3 lakh crore, driven by geopolitical tensions and tighter unsecured lending norms. While the RBI's new tiered Loan-to-Value (LTV) ratios, effective April 2026, aim to boost credit access for smaller borrowers, this expansion into a volatile commodity market presents substantial risks. Borrowers face increased potential for rapid collateral auctions and financial distress if gold prices correct sharply, a factor often underestimated amid the allure of higher immediate liquidity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 08:33:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3f9d3edbd0c0ef0196695_1772354213081.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kia India Sets Record Sales Amidst Intense Auto Market Rivalry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Kia-India-Sets-Record-Sales-Amidst-Intense-Auto-Market-Rivalry/69a3f94bedbd0c0ef01965cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Kia-India-Sets-Record-Sales-Amidst-Intense-Auto-Market-Rivalry/69a3f94bedbd0c0ef01965cc</guid><description>Kia India achieved its highest-ever February sales, selling 27,610 units for a 10.3% year-over-year increase, driven by strong demand for models like the Seltos and Sonet. This performance underscores sustained customer confidence. However, the competitive Indian automotive landscape is intensifying, with rivals like Hyundai and Tata Motors posting significant growth. Kia Corporation, the parent company, maintains a moderate P/E ratio, suggesting investors are weighing localized success against broader industry dynamics and global challenges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 08:31:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3f94bedbd0c0ef01965cb_1772353980161.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW MG Motor India's Premium SUV Gambit Amidst 24% Sales Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-MG-Motor-Indias-Premium-SUV-Gambit-Amidst-24percent-Sales-Surge/69a3f8faedbd0c0ef019654e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-MG-Motor-Indias-Premium-SUV-Gambit-Amidst-24percent-Sales-Surge/69a3f8faedbd0c0ef019654e</guid><description>JSW MG Motor India posted a 24% year-on-year increase in February wholesales, reaching 4,957 units. This growth spans both internal combustion engine (ICE) and electric vehicle (EV) segments. The company also initiated pre-bookings for its new premium SUV, the MG MAJESTOR, signaling a strategic push into higher-margin segments. This move comes as the broader Indian automotive market experiences robust demand, with analysts forecasting continued growth driven by economic factors and new model introductions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 08:29:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3f8faedbd0c0ef019654d_1772353914600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eicher Motors Feb Sales Jump 11%; Invests ₹958 Cr for Royal Enfield Capacity Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Feb-Sales-Jump-11percent-Invests-958-Cr-for-Royal-Enfield-Capacity-Hike/69a3f2bbedbd0c0ef0196303</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Eicher-Motors-Feb-Sales-Jump-11percent-Invests-958-Cr-for-Royal-Enfield-Capacity-Hike/69a3f2bbedbd0c0ef0196303</guid><description>Eicher Motors' iconic Royal Enfield brand posted an 11% year-on-year sales increase in February 2026, selling 1,00,905 motorcycles. To meet surging demand, the company has approved a significant ₹958 crore investment for brownfield expansion at its Cheyyar facility, aiming to boost annual production capacity from 14.6 lakh to 20 lakh units within 18 months.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 08:03:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3f2bbedbd0c0ef0196302_1772352330430.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Customs Duty Deferral Scheme: A Closer Look</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-New-Customs-Duty-Deferral-Scheme-A-Closer-Look/69a3ed4bedbd0c0ef01960f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-New-Customs-Duty-Deferral-Scheme-A-Closer-Look/69a3ed4bedbd0c0ef01960f1</guid><description>Starting April 1, 2026, India will implement the Eligible Manufacturer Importer (EMI) scheme, permitting approved businesses to defer customs duty payments monthly instead of upfront. This move aims to improve working capital and bolster domestic manufacturing. The scheme, valid until March 31, 2028, encourages businesses to achieve higher Authorized Economic Operator (AEO) status, while introducing potential fiscal risks for the government and favoring compliant, established entities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:39:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3ed4bedbd0c0ef01960f0_1772350877599.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor Feb Sales Surge 31%; International Biz Hits Record High</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Feb-Sales-Surge-31percent-International-Biz-Hits-Record-High/69a3eca9edbd0c0ef0196064</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-Feb-Sales-Surge-31percent-International-Biz-Hits-Record-High/69a3eca9edbd0c0ef0196064</guid><description>TVS Motor Company reported a robust 31% year-on-year sales growth for February 2026, selling 529,308 units. The company achieved its highest-ever monthly sales in its international business segment, shipping 158,268 units. This strong performance was broad-based, with three-wheelers up 77% and electric vehicles seeing a 60% increase, underscoring continued demand across diverse segments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:37:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3eca9edbd0c0ef0196063_1772350742356.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors PV Sales Feb’26: Total Volumes Up 35%, EV Sales Jump 57%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-PV-Sales-Feb26-Total-Volumes-Up-35percent-EV-Sales-Jump-57percent/69a3e9d8edbd0c0ef0195f25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-PV-Sales-Feb26-Total-Volumes-Up-35percent-EV-Sales-Jump-57percent/69a3e9d8edbd0c0ef0195f25</guid><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd. reported total sales of 63,331 units in February 2026, compared to 46,811 units in February 2025, reflecting a solid 35% year-on-year (YoY) growth.
The growth was supported by strong domestic demand, exceptional international business expansion, and continued traction in electric vehicle (EV) sales, which rose 57% YoY during the month.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:25:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e9d8edbd0c0ef0195f24_1772350039308.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vardhman Textiles Commences New Technical Textiles Plant in Baddi</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Vardhman-Textiles-Commences-New-Technical-Textiles-Plant-in-Baddi/69a3e777edbd0c0ef0195e28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Vardhman-Textiles-Commences-New-Technical-Textiles-Plant-in-Baddi/69a3e777edbd0c0ef0195e28</guid><description>Vardhman Textiles Limited has announced the commencement of commercial production at its new Technical Textiles Plant in Baddi, Himachal Pradesh, effective March 1, 2026. This facility is a significant addition, capable of producing 15 lakh meters of fabric monthly, marking a key step in the company's strategic capacity expansion plans first revealed in May 2024.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:15:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e777edbd0c0ef0195e27_1772349411336.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors Feb CV Sales Surge 32% on Strong Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Feb-CV-Sales-Surge-32percent-on-Strong-Demand/69a3e6a2edbd0c0ef0195d57</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Feb-CV-Sales-Surge-32percent-on-Strong-Demand/69a3e6a2edbd0c0ef0195d57</guid><description>Tata Motors Limited posted a robust 32% year-on-year growth in commercial vehicle sales for February 2026, selling 42,940 units. The strong performance was driven by a significant 32.8% increase in domestic sales and a 17.9% rise in international business, highlighting broad market demand.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:11:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e6a2edbd0c0ef0195d56_1772349196474.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FPIs Re-Enter India Equities: Sector Rotation Amid AI Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FPIs-Re-Enter-India-Equities-Sector-Rotation-Amid-AI-Fears/69a3e617edbd0c0ef0195ce4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FPIs-Re-Enter-India-Equities-Sector-Rotation-Amid-AI-Fears/69a3e617edbd0c0ef0195ce4</guid><description>Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) injected ₹22,615 crore into Indian equities in February, the highest monthly inflow in 17 months, signaling a turnaround from substantial 2025 outflows. This shift was propelled by an interim India-US trade agreement, corrected domestic valuations, and robust Q3 FY26 corporate earnings, which grew 14.7%. FPIs favored financials and capital goods while divesting from the IT sector amid AI disruption concerns. Market capitalization for Indian listed companies reached $5.001 trillion in January 2026, with the Nifty 50 P/E ratio around 22.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:09:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e617edbd0c0ef0195ce3_1772349104430.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki Sales: Exports Surge, UVs Shine, Compact Cars Lag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Sales-Exports-Surge-UVs-Shine-Compact-Cars-Lag/69a3e3beedbd0c0ef0195b0e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Sales-Exports-Surge-UVs-Shine-Compact-Cars-Lag/69a3e3beedbd0c0ef0195b0e</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki India's total sales for February 2026 rose 7.32% year-over-year to 213,995 units, propelled by a significant surge in exports (+56.5%) and strong utility vehicle (UV) demand. However, domestic passenger vehicle sales remained flat at 161,000 units, with a notable decline in the compact car segment contrasting sharply with UV performance. Hyundai Motor India posted a robust 12.6% growth, achieving its best-ever February sales, while Mahindra &amp; Mahindra saw 18% expansion driven by SUVs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:59:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e3beedbd0c0ef0195b0d_1772348556782.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India Hits Record February Sales Amid Market Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Hits-Record-February-Sales-Amid-Market-Boom/69a3e3bbedbd0c0ef0195af7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Hits-Record-February-Sales-Amid-Market-Boom/69a3e3bbedbd0c0ef0195af7</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India Limited (HMIL) achieved record-breaking total and domestic sales for February, selling 66,134 units. Domestic sales rose 9.8% to 52,407 units, while exports surged 24.8% to 13,727 units. This performance follows January's record-breaking month, underscoring HMIL's sustained sales momentum and its competitive edge in a booming Indian automotive sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e3bbedbd0c0ef0195af6_1772348474350.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India Hits Record Sales Amidst Sector Slowdown &amp; AI Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Hits-Record-Sales-Amidst-Sector-Slowdown-and-AI-Pivot/69a3e3b7edbd0c0ef0195ae0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Hits-Record-Sales-Amidst-Sector-Slowdown-and-AI-Pivot/69a3e3b7edbd0c0ef0195ae0</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India Ltd. (HMIL) achieved its highest-ever February sales in 2026, selling 66,134 units, a 12.6% year-on-year increase. Domestic sales grew 9.8% to 52,407 units, while exports surged 24.8% to 13,727 units. This performance contrasts with a projected slowdown in the broader Indian automotive sector, which anticipates a moderate 3-6% growth for FY2026-27. Furthermore, HMIL's parent, Hyundai Motor Company, is making substantial investments in AI and robotics, signaling a long-term strategic evolution beyond traditional automotive sales.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:59:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3e3b7edbd0c0ef0195adf_1772348518604.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Feb Sales: 97,177 Units | Auto &amp; Tractor Growth Surges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Feb-Sales-97177-Units-Auto-and-Tractor-Growth-Surges/69a3d716edbd0c0ef0195730</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-Feb-Sales-97177-Units-Auto-and-Tractor-Growth-Surges/69a3d716edbd0c0ef0195730</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra reported strong February 2026 sales, with total auto volumes up 18% YoY to 97,177 units, led by a 19% jump in domestic UV sales. The farm equipment sector also posted significant gains, with domestic tractor sales rising 35% YoY. These figures highlight robust demand across key segments, though management monitors external challenges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:05:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d716edbd0c0ef019572f_1772345208760.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mafatlal's Bold Pivot: "Uniforms to AI" Drive Record Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mafatlals-Bold-Pivot-Uniforms-to-AI-Drive-Record-Growth/69a3d5a6edbd0c0ef0195624</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mafatlals-Bold-Pivot-Uniforms-to-AI-Drive-Record-Growth/69a3d5a6edbd0c0ef0195624</guid><description>Mafatlal Industries, the flagship of the Arvind Mafatlal Group, is aggressively pivoting beyond its textile legacy, aiming for leadership in education, AI, and health/hygiene. The company has achieved record revenues, signaling a strong turnaround driven by both core textile operations and new ventures in future skills and hygiene products. This ambitious "uniforms to AI" strategy faces significant execution challenges, juxtaposing established manufacturing with nascent technology sectors in a bid to redefine the group's future.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:59:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d5a6edbd0c0ef0195623_1772344913565.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE IPO Proceeds as OFS, Regulatory Hurdle Blocks Self-Listing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-IPO-Proceeds-as-OFS-Regulatory-Hurdle-Blocks-Self-Listing/69a3d531edbd0c0ef019559f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/NSE-IPO-Proceeds-as-OFS-Regulatory-Hurdle-Blocks-Self-Listing/69a3d531edbd0c0ef019559f</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange (NSE) is preparing for its Initial Public Offering (IPO) after receiving a no-objection certificate from SEBI. However, Indian regulations will prevent the NSE from listing on its own platform, requiring an alternative exchange. The IPO will be structured solely as an Offer for Sale (OFS), meaning no new capital will be raised for the company; instead, existing shareholders will sell a portion of their holdings. This structure aims to provide liquidity to its approximately 195,000 shareholders and enhance corporate governance through public scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:57:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d531edbd0c0ef019559e_1772344790616.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Escorts Kubota Feb Sales Surge; Tractor Growth Leads</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Feb-Sales-Surge-Tractor-Growth-Leads/69a3d451edbd0c0ef01954e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Feb-Sales-Surge-Tractor-Growth-Leads/69a3d451edbd0c0ef01954e4</guid><description>Escorts Kubota reported robust February 2026 sales, with tractor volumes climbing 20.4% year-on-year to 10,339 units and construction equipment sales rising 4.8% to 588 units. The strong performance reflects positive rural sentiment and infrastructure project execution, signaling continued industry momentum, though past market share concerns persist.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:53:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d451edbd0c0ef01954e3_1772344493977.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GAIL Appoints Deepak Gupta as CMD from March 1, Leveraging 35+ Yrs Experience</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GAIL-Appoints-Deepak-Gupta-as-CMD-from-March-1-Leveraging-35-Yrs-Experience/69a3d3caedbd0c0ef019545e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GAIL-Appoints-Deepak-Gupta-as-CMD-from-March-1-Leveraging-35-Yrs-Experience/69a3d3caedbd0c0ef019545e</guid><description>Shri Deepak Gupta has taken charge as Chairman and Managing Director (CMD) of GAIL (India) Limited, effective March 1, 2026. With over 35 years of experience in the oil and gas sector, including his recent role as Director (Projects) at GAIL, Mr. Gupta is expected to steer the Maharatna PSU through India's energy transition. His appointment signifies a leadership transition at a critical juncture for the company, which operates an extensive natural gas and LPG pipeline network.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:51:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d3caedbd0c0ef019545d_1772344374240.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bijoy Hans Board to Decide on Promoter Reclassification on March 4</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Bijoy-Hans-Board-to-Decide-on-Promoter-Reclassification-on-March-4/69a3d260edbd0c0ef0195389</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Bijoy-Hans-Board-to-Decide-on-Promoter-Reclassification-on-March-4/69a3d260edbd0c0ef0195389</guid><description>Bijoy Hans Limited's Board of Directors will convene on March 4, 2026, to deliberate on a crucial request for reclassifying certain individuals from its promoter and promoter group to the public shareholder category. This move, aligned with SEBI Listing Regulations, could significantly alter the company's shareholding structure and free float.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3d260edbd0c0ef0195388_1772344043347.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VOC Port's ₹15,000 Cr Outer Harbour: A Bid to Outpace Rivals?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/VOC-Ports-15000-Cr-Outer-Harbour-A-Bid-to-Outpace-Rivals/69a3cf1aedbd0c0ef0195245</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/VOC-Ports-15000-Cr-Outer-Harbour-A-Bid-to-Outpace-Rivals/69a3cf1aedbd0c0ef0195245</guid><description>VO Chidambaranar Port Authority is investing ₹15,000 crore in its Outer Harbour project to dramatically increase cargo handling capacity and position Tamil Nadu as a premier South Indian transshipment hub. This strategic move aims to compete directly with established international ports like Singapore and Colombo, driven by recent growth in cargo and container volumes. Funding is secured through a tripartite agreement with IRFC and Sagarmala Finance Corporation Limited, signaling a significant push towards modernizing infrastructure and attracting larger vessels.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 05:31:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3cf1aedbd0c0ef0195244_1772343188525.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>