<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:39:53 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Nexus Select Trust Pivots to Development in JV with Runwal Enterprises</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nexus-Select-Trust-Pivots-to-Development-in-JV-with-Runwal-Enterprises/699cb20904a25a58c84e1535</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nexus-Select-Trust-Pivots-to-Development-in-JV-with-Runwal-Enterprises/699cb20904a25a58c84e1535</guid><description>Nexus Select Trust, India's first listed retail REIT, is partnering with Runwal Enterprises to develop a 730,000 sq ft mall in Dombivli near Mumbai, valued at over ₹900 crore. This marks a strategic deviation from its established focus on completed, income-generating assets, indicating an aggressive expansion into development projects to capture future value. Runwal Enterprises will manage construction, while Nexus Select Trust will lead leasing and asset management.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:01:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699cb20904a25a58c84e1534_1771878894621.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Dominates APAC Office Supply: A 'Flight to Quality' Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Dominates-APAC-Office-Supply-A-Flight-to-Quality-Play/699cb20304a25a58c84e151e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Dominates-APAC-Office-Supply-A-Flight-to-Quality-Play/699cb20304a25a58c84e151e</guid><description>India will account for nearly 40% of new Grade-A office supply across the Asia Pacific in 2026, solidifying its role as a primary growth engine. Bengaluru, Delhi-NCR, and Mumbai are poised for significant completions. This surge is propelled by sustained demand from Global Capability Centers (GCCs), AI firms, and institutional capital, creating a "flight-to-quality" dynamic. Despite peak supply in APAC, India's market fundamentals, driven by talent availability and cost-competitiveness, position it favorably against regional peers facing potential oversupply.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Aster DM's India Push: Merger Hurdles and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aster-DMs-India-Push-Merger-Hurdles-and-Valuation-Concerns/699cb20104a25a58c84e1507</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aster-DMs-India-Push-Merger-Hurdles-and-Valuation-Concerns/699cb20104a25a58c84e1507</guid><description>Aster DM Healthcare plans a significant ₹2,300 crore investment for aggressive expansion in India, aiming to add 2,368 beds post-demerging its GCC operations and merging with Quality Care India (QCIL). This strategic shift creates a formidable entity, poised to be among India's top hospital chains. However, the intricate integration of multiple brands and intense market competition present substantial execution risks for the venture, which currently trades at a premium valuation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:01:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699cb20104a25a58c84e1506_1771877087114.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Credit Surge: NBFCs Lead as Equity Funding Dries Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Credit-Surge-NBFCs-Lead-as-Equity-Funding-Dries-Up/699cb19004a25a58c84e1445</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Credit-Surge-NBFCs-Lead-as-Equity-Funding-Dries-Up/699cb19004a25a58c84e1445</guid><description>Outstanding commercial credit in India surged 14.7% year-on-year to over ₹300 lakh crore by end-January, spurred by the Reserve Bank of India's (RBI) 125-basis-point policy rate reduction. Incremental credit growth in the first ten months of the fiscal year jumped 35% to ₹34.5 lakh crore. Notably, Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs) expanded credit by 20%, outpacing commercial banks' 14% rise, despite banks reclaiming overall market share. This growth occurred alongside a significant 12% contraction in equity issuances, indicating a shift in corporate funding preferences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:59:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699cb19004a25a58c84e1444_1771877069014.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quick Commerce Reshapes India FMCG: Giants Race for Digital Shelf</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Quick-Commerce-Reshapes-India-FMCG-Giants-Race-for-Digital-Shelf/699ca5e104a25a58c84e0ed2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Quick-Commerce-Reshapes-India-FMCG-Giants-Race-for-Digital-Shelf/699ca5e104a25a58c84e0ed2</guid><description>Quick commerce is rapidly transforming India's grocery sector, pushing organized channels to 40-50% of key food sales. Major FMCG players like Hindustan Unilever, Marico, Dabur, Godrej Consumer Products, and Tata Consumer Products are intensifying their focus on these channels to capture evolving consumer demand. While rapid growth presents opportunities, intense competition, high valuations, and evolving consumer behavior pose strategic challenges for established players seeking to maintain market leadership.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:09:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ca5e104a25a58c84e0ed1_1771873887416.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Regulator Expands Staff to Match US FDA Drug Approval Speeds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Regulator-Expands-Staff-to-Match-US-FDA-Drug-Approval-Speeds/699ca5d104a25a58c84e0eb9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Regulator-Expands-Staff-to-Match-US-FDA-Drug-Approval-Speeds/699ca5d104a25a58c84e0eb9</guid><description>India's Central Drugs Standard Control Organisation (CDSCO) is establishing a 1,500-member scientific cadre to expedite drug approvals and align with international standards, addressing historical bottlenecks. With approximately 40% of positions designated for contract roles, including potential global experts, the initiative aims to rival or exceed US FDA efficiency. This strategic move is particularly relevant for facilitating advanced therapies like cell and gene treatments, signaling a critical juncture for India's pharmaceutical sector and its global regulatory standing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ca5d104a25a58c84e0eb8_1771876792015.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Plunges on ₹590 Cr Fraud Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Plunges-on-590-Cr-Fraud-Probe/699ca55d04a25a58c84e0e38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Plunges-on-590-Cr-Fraud-Probe/699ca55d04a25a58c84e0e38</guid><description>IDFC First Bank's stock plummeted nearly 20% following the disclosure of an alleged ₹590 crore fraud involving Haryana government accounts at its Chandigarh branch. Four employees are suspended, KPMG is conducting a forensic audit, and the Haryana government has de-empanelled the bank. The Reserve Bank of India, however, stated there is no systemic risk to the broader Indian banking sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:07:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ca55d04a25a58c84e0e37_1771873757515.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MobiKwik Subsidiary Gets BSE Approval for Stock Broking Launch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MobiKwik-Subsidiary-Gets-BSE-Approval-for-Stock-Broking-Launch/699c95e11f6d54278453a8ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MobiKwik-Subsidiary-Gets-BSE-Approval-for-Stock-Broking-Launch/699c95e11f6d54278453a8ec</guid><description>One MobiKwik Systems Ltd.'s broking arm, MobiKwik Securities Broking Private Limited (MSBPL), has secured approval from the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) to commence stockbroking operations. Effective February 24, 2026, this development marks a key step in MobiKwik's strategic expansion into the competitive Indian financial services landscape, leveraging its existing digital platform and user base to enter the retail investment market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MobiKwik Subsidiary Secures BSE Trading Membership Approval</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MobiKwik-Subsidiary-Secures-BSE-Trading-Membership-Approval/699c93111f6d542784538e52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MobiKwik-Subsidiary-Secures-BSE-Trading-Membership-Approval/699c93111f6d542784538e52</guid><description>MobiKwik's wholly-owned subsidiary, Mobikwik Securities Broking Private Limited, has secured approval from BSE Limited to operate as a Trading Member. This marks a significant expansion for the fintech giant into the stockbroking domain, building upon its existing financial services portfolio. The approval follows earlier registrations, paving the way for the subsidiary to offer trading services on the exchange.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c93111f6d542784538e51_1771869265595.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sancode Technologies Board Meeting Feb 26 to Decide on Fundraising</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sancode-Technologies-Board-Meeting-Feb-26-to-Decide-on-Fundraising/699c930f1f6d542784538e3c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sancode-Technologies-Board-Meeting-Feb-26-to-Decide-on-Fundraising/699c930f1f6d542784538e3c</guid><description>Sancode Technologies Limited has scheduled a board meeting for February 26, 2026. The primary agenda item is to evaluate a proposal for raising capital through a preferential allotment of equity shares or convertible warrants. This move signals potential expansion plans but also raises questions about future share dilution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Steel's New Plant: Growth Amidst Price Woes &amp; Legal Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steels-New-Plant-Growth-Amidst-Price-Woes-and-Legal-Scrutiny/699c8debd83cd4ce4fe95fe5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steels-New-Plant-Growth-Amidst-Price-Woes-and-Legal-Scrutiny/699c8debd83cd4ce4fe95fe5</guid><description>Tata Steel is launching a new 0.75 MTPA Electric Arc Furnace (EAF) steel plant in Ludhiana, Punjab, with an investment of ₹3,200 crore, creating 2,500 jobs. This facility, utilizing 100% scrap, aligns with sustainability goals. However, the company operates amidst fluctuating steel prices, intensifying competition, and a significant antitrust investigation involving major Indian steel producers, including JSW Steel and SAIL. Analysts maintain a positive outlook on Tata Steel's expansion strategy despite these headwinds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:27:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c8debd83cd4ce4fe95fe4_1771868000436.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Retail Frenzy: Info Gap Fuels Volatility, SEBI Tackles Finfluencers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Indias-Retail-Frenzy-Info-Gap-Fuels-Volatility-SEBI-Tackles-Finfluencers/699c8d82d83cd4ce4fe95e37</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Indias-Retail-Frenzy-Info-Gap-Fuels-Volatility-SEBI-Tackles-Finfluencers/699c8d82d83cd4ce4fe95e37</guid><description>SEBI highlights that information asymmetry in Indian markets stems from comprehension gaps, not just availability. A surge in retail investors, particularly in options trading, is fueled by cognitive biases like FOMO and overconfidence. Regulatory actions against financial influencers aim to curb misleading advice. Despite SEBI's efforts, the combination of behavioral economics and amplified retail participation poses systemic risks, contrasting with institutional investment strategies and potentially leading to mispriced assets and heightened market volatility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:25:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c8d82d83cd4ce4fe95e36_1771868147198.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Burry Warns: AI Build-Out Risks Financial Strain, Asset Obsolescence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Burry-Warns-AI-Build-Out-Risks-Financial-Strain-Asset-Obsolescence/699c8d7bd83cd4ce4fe95e13</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Burry-Warns-AI-Build-Out-Risks-Financial-Strain-Asset-Obsolescence/699c8d7bd83cd4ce4fe95e13</guid><description>Veteran investor Michael Burry has issued a stark warning regarding the astronomical capital expenditures funneling into artificial intelligence data center build-outs. His primary concern centers on the financial sustainability of this spending spree, which he believes is consuming corporate cash flows and necessitating increased leverage. Burry points to potential accounting strategies that could mask tightening finances and highlights the risk of AI hardware rapidly becoming obsolete, echoing the unsustainable boom and bust cycles of the dot-com era. Investors are advised to scrutinize capital expenditure plans and free cash flow generation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c8d7bd83cd4ce4fe95e12_1771867730102.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Grid Inflexibility Threatens RE Targets Amidst Coal Bottleneck</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Grid-Inflexibility-Threatens-RE-Targets-Amidst-Coal-Bottleneck/699c8ca1d83cd4ce4fe932d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Grid-Inflexibility-Threatens-RE-Targets-Amidst-Coal-Bottleneck/699c8ca1d83cd4ce4fe932d1</guid><description>India curtailed 2.3 TWh of renewable energy between May and December 2025, primarily due to thermal power plants' inability to operate below 55% Minimum Technical Load (MTL) and grid inflexibility. This highlights systemic commercial and regulatory barriers that threaten the nation's ambitious 500 GW renewable energy target by 2030. While a roadmap exists to lower MTL to 40%, uptake is slow, hindered by operational concerns and a lack of adequate incentives, alongside significant transmission infrastructure gaps and insufficient energy storage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:21:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c8ca1d83cd4ce4fe932d0_1771867756394.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zelio E-Mobility Doubles Production Capacity to 1.8 Lakh Units Annually</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Zelio-E-Mobility-Doubles-Production-Capacity-to-18-Lakh-Units-Annually/699c844fd83cd4ce4fe86b84</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Zelio-E-Mobility-Doubles-Production-Capacity-to-18-Lakh-Units-Annually/699c844fd83cd4ce4fe86b84</guid><description>Zelio E-Mobility has significantly ramped up its manufacturing prowess, doubling its annual production capacity from 72,000 to 1,80,000 units. This expansion, driven by enhanced output at its Hisar facility and a new plant in Odisha operational from February 23, 2026, positions the company to better capture the burgeoning demand for electric vehicles in India. The move aims to bolster supply chain efficiencies and operational leverage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:46:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c844fd83cd4ce4fe86b83_1771865341344.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Annapurna Finance Secures $100M Social Loan for Impact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Annapurna-Finance-Secures-100M-Social-Loan-for-Impact/699c82c1d83cd4ce4fe80398</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Annapurna-Finance-Secures-100M-Social-Loan-for-Impact/699c82c1d83cd4ce4fe80398</guid><description>Microfinance leader Annapurna Finance has secured a $100 million syndicated multi-currency social loan facility, arranged by Standard Chartered Bank. Denominated in USD and JPY, this funding reinforces the company's commitment to social impact, financial inclusion, and women's empowerment. The deal underscores a growing trend of institutional capital targeting ESG-aligned financial services in India, positioning Annapurna for further expansion and deeper community engagement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:39:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c82c1d83cd4ce4fe80397_1771864916320.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Le Travenues Tech Sets Feb 26 Analyst Meet Using Q3 FY26 Results</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Le-Travenues-Tech-Sets-Feb-26-Analyst-Meet-Using-Q3-FY26-Results/699c82aed83cd4ce4fe8037c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Le-Travenues-Tech-Sets-Feb-26-Analyst-Meet-Using-Q3-FY26-Results/699c82aed83cd4ce4fe8037c</guid><description>Le Travenues Technology Limited, operating the ixigo platform, has announced an analyst and investor meeting scheduled for February 26, 2026. The virtual event will utilise the company's investor presentation from January 22, 2026, which details the financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. This meeting follows a strong Q3 FY26 performance marked by record revenue, though profitability concerns remain a point of investor focus.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:39:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c82aed83cd4ce4fe8037b_1771864873187.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lancer Container Lines: 4 Individuals Secure 27.96% Stake Via Preferential Allotment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lancer-Container-Lines-4-Individuals-Secure-2796percent-Stake-Via-Preferential-Allotment/699c82a8d83cd4ce4fe80366</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lancer-Container-Lines-4-Individuals-Secure-2796percent-Stake-Via-Preferential-Allotment/699c82a8d83cd4ce4fe80366</guid><description>Lancer Container Lines Ltd. has announced a significant shift in its shareholding structure following a preferential allotment of 10.29 crore equity shares. Four individuals have collectively acquired a 27.96% stake, boosting the company's equity share capital to Rs. 176.63 crore. This move also facilitates the acquisition of PK M General Trading LLC, a UAE-based entity, which will now become a wholly owned subsidiary.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:39:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c82a8d83cd4ce4fe80365_1771864936717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Strategic Edge: Trade Tensions &amp; Bio-Agri Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Strategic-Edge-Trade-Tensions-and-Bio-Agri-Boom/699c81e2d83cd4ce4fe801e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Strategic-Edge-Trade-Tensions-and-Bio-Agri-Boom/699c81e2d83cd4ce4fe801e1</guid><description>India is skillfully navigating a volatile global trade environment, using a US Supreme Court ruling to its strategic advantage in renegotiating terms. Simultaneously, it's fostering a burgeoning domestic market for marine bio-fertilizers, aiming to revolutionize agriculture through sustainable, cost-effective inputs, despite adoption challenges. This dual focus positions India for enhanced economic resilience and global influence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:35:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c81e2d83cd4ce4fe801e0_1771864641615.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra, Manulife Tap India's Insurtech Growth with New JV</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Mahindra-Manulife-Tap-Indias-Insurtech-Growth-with-New-JV/699c81c0d83cd4ce4fe801bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Mahindra-Manulife-Tap-Indias-Insurtech-Growth-with-New-JV/699c81c0d83cd4ce4fe801bb</guid><description>Mahindra Group and Manulife have appointed Suresh Agarwal as the designate CEO for their proposed 50:50 life insurance joint venture in India. The venture aims to combine Mahindra's extensive rural distribution with Manulife's global expertise to capture demand for long-term savings and protection products. This strategic move targets India's underpenetrated insurance market, projected for strong growth, with operations expected to commence post-regulatory approval. Agarwal brings nearly three decades of experience in scaling insurance businesses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:35:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c81c0d83cd4ce4fe801ba_1771865303192.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's NMP 2.0: Ambitious Asset Monetisation Faces Execution Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-NMP-20-Ambitious-Asset-Monetisation-Faces-Execution-Headwinds/699c8150d83cd4ce4fe80111</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-NMP-20-Ambitious-Asset-Monetisation-Faces-Execution-Headwinds/699c8150d83cd4ce4fe80111</guid><description>India unveiled the National Monetisation Pipeline 2.0 (NMP 2.0), targeting ₹16.72 lakh crore over five years (FY26-FY30) to recycle public assets. This ambitious program aims to leverage ₹5.8 lakh crore in private investment, building on NMP 1.0's reported 90% achievement. Key sectors like highways, power, and railways will spearhead the initiative. However, past underperformance in certain sectors and inherent execution risks raise questions about the feasibility of these scaled-up targets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:33:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c8150d83cd4ce4fe80110_1771864716402.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's NMP 2.0: Rs 16.7L Cr Infrastructure Plan Faces Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-NMP-20-Rs-167L-Cr-Infrastructure-Plan-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/699c8142d83cd4ce4fe800ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-NMP-20-Rs-167L-Cr-Infrastructure-Plan-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/699c8142d83cd4ce4fe800ef</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman unveiled the National Monetisation Pipeline 2.0, aiming to unlock Rs 16.72 lakh crore over five years (FY26-FY30) for infrastructure development. This ambitious plan significantly surpasses NMP 1.0's Rs 6 lakh crore target, of which Rs 5.3 lakh crore was achieved. NMP 2.0 leverages Public-Private Partnerships and aims to attract substantial private investment, aligning with the Viksit Bharat vision. However, its success hinges on overcoming persistent challenges in land acquisition, regulatory clarity, and the effective mobilization of capital amidst global economic uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c8142d83cd4ce4fe800ee_1771865557671.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's IPO Engine: Operational Grit for Global Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Indias-IPO-Engine-Operational-Grit-for-Global-Capital/699c7ce8d83cd4ce4fe74409</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Indias-IPO-Engine-Operational-Grit-for-Global-Capital/699c7ce8d83cd4ce4fe74409</guid><description>India's Association of Investment Bankers (AIBI) convened its 14th Annual Convention, emphasizing operational enhancements and investor literacy as crucial steps to attract global capital. The focus on streamlining offer documents, enhancing SME listings, and fostering international collaboration signals a pragmatic approach to sustainable growth and positioning India as a premier destination for investment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:14:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c7ce8d83cd4ce4fe74408_1771863841547.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FIIs Fuel India Rally Amidst US Tariff Turmoil</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FIIs-Fuel-India-Rally-Amidst-US-Tariff-Turmoil/699c7cb9d83cd4ce4fe743c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FIIs-Fuel-India-Rally-Amidst-US-Tariff-Turmoil/699c7cb9d83cd4ce4fe743c3</guid><description>Foreign Institutional Investors (FIIs) turned aggressive buyers, infusing ₹3,484 crore into Indian equities on Monday, February 23, 2026, propelling benchmark indices for a second consecutive session. This inflow countered Domestic Institutional Investors' (DIIs) profit-taking of ₹1,292 crore. The rally occurred against a backdrop of global uncertainty stemming from the US Supreme Court striking down President Trump's tariffs, though the US market showed resilience. Indian market P/E ratios remain elevated, around 22.4 for Nifty 50 and 22.7 for Sensex, with market cap nearing ₹469 lakh crore.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:13:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c7cb9d83cd4ce4fe743c2_1771865724466.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trade Policy Relief Lifts Indices Amidst Sector Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Policy-Relief-Lifts-Indices-Amidst-Sector-Divergence/699c7b76d83cd4ce4fe7424b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Policy-Relief-Lifts-Indices-Amidst-Sector-Divergence/699c7b76d83cd4ce4fe7424b</guid><description>Benchmark Indian equity indices climbed for a second consecutive session, buoyed by the US Supreme Court's decision to strike down reciprocal tariffs. The Sensex and Nifty registered gains, supported by buying in heavyweight stocks. However, a significant disparity emerged between Foreign Portfolio Investor (FPI) inflows and Domestic Institutional Investor (DII) outflows, alongside negative market breadth, signaling that the rally's benefits were not broadly distributed. While sectors like PSU banks and healthcare advanced, IT and metal stocks lagged, highlighting a bifurcated market sentiment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:08:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c7b76d83cd4ce4fe7424a_1771863516780.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Balrampur Chini Mills' ₹2850 Cr PLA Bet Targets ₹2000 Cr Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balrampur-Chini-Mills-2850-Cr-PLA-Bet-Targets-2000-Cr-Revenue/699c7ab5d83cd4ce4fe74125</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balrampur-Chini-Mills-2850-Cr-PLA-Bet-Targets-2000-Cr-Revenue/699c7ab5d83cd4ce4fe74125</guid><description>Balrampur Chini Mills is launching India's first industrial-scale Polylactic Acid (PLA) plant in Uttar Pradesh with a ₹2,850 crore investment. The facility aims for 80,000 tonnes annual capacity and targets ₹2,000 crore in peak revenue with a 35% EBITDA margin. This strategic move into bio-plastics, validated by an initial order from the Lucknow Cantonment Board, positions the company to benefit from the global shift away from single-use plastics and align with India's sustainability goals. The venture represents a significant diversification beyond its core sugar and distillery operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:05:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c7ab5d83cd4ce4fe74124_1771862888120.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Cloud Softech to acquire Global Impex for clean energy tech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Blue-Cloud-Softech-to-acquire-Global-Impex-for-clean-energy-tech/699c7aafd83cd4ce4fe7410e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Blue-Cloud-Softech-to-acquire-Global-Impex-for-clean-energy-tech/699c7aafd83cd4ce4fe7410e</guid><description>Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd. has agreed to acquire 100% of Global Impex Inc. (GIX) from ConnectM Technology Solutions Inc. The deal, an all-equity share swap, aims to integrate GIX's India-based clean energy and mobility assets into BCSSL's 'Blue Energy' platform. Expected to close in 6-9 months, this strategic move signals BCSSL's push into technology-driven sustainable infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:05:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c7aafd83cd4ce4fe7410d_1771863201793.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Collateral Squeeze Looms Over Booming Indian PMS Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/RBI-Collateral-Squeeze-Looms-Over-Booming-Indian-PMS-Sector/699c7a9fd83cd4ce4fe740c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/RBI-Collateral-Squeeze-Looms-Over-Booming-Indian-PMS-Sector/699c7a9fd83cd4ce4fe740c6</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) is reviewing broker representations challenging the Reserve Bank of India's (RBI) stringent collateral norms for bank funding, set to take effect April 1, 2026. These rules mandate 100% collateral, potentially squeezing broker liquidity and increasing costs, even as India's Portfolio Management Services (PMS) sector experiences significant AUM growth to ₹10.5 trillion. SEBI Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey confirmed the examination of these issues while outlining SEBI's own comprehensive agenda to update PMS regulations and other market rules.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:04:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c7a9fd83cd4ce4fe740c5_1771862965846.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jubilant FoodWorks Q3FY26 Profit Surges 94%; Revenue Up 13.3%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Jubilant-FoodWorks-Q3FY26-Profit-Surges-94percent-Revenue-Up-133percent/699c76f1ee97f501b0ebe4e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Jubilant-FoodWorks-Q3FY26-Profit-Surges-94percent-Revenue-Up-133percent/699c76f1ee97f501b0ebe4e1</guid><description>Jubilant FoodWorks delivered robust Q3FY26 results, with consolidated revenue rising 13.3% to Rs. 24,372 million and PAT surging 93.9% year-on-year to Rs. 981 million. The company is leveraging technology and supply chain investments to drive efficiency, while aggressively expanding its Popeyes brand and innovating its Domino's portfolio.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c76f1ee97f501b0ebe4e0_1771863270466.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks Lag EM Amid AI Boom; Valuations Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Stocks-Lag-EM-Amid-AI-Boom-Valuations-Key/699c7631ee97f501b0ebe3eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Stocks-Lag-EM-Amid-AI-Boom-Valuations-Key/699c7631ee97f501b0ebe3eb</guid><description>India's equity markets endured their worst relative underperformance against emerging market peers in 30 years during 2025. This divergence is attributed not to India's fundamentals, but to a global capital rotation towards markets benefiting from the AI infrastructure boom, particularly in South Korea and Taiwan. While India's foreign outflows reached a record $18.4 billion, its domestic growth drivers and unique market characteristics position it as a potential 'hedge' against AI trade cyclicality, with future capital return hinging on the AI cycle's duration and policy shifts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sigma Advanced Systems Secures ₹100 Cr Defence Orders; Boosts Missile &amp; Naval Segments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sigma-Advanced-Systems-Secures-100-Cr-Defence-Orders-Boosts-Missile-and-Naval-Segments/699c749eee97f501b0ebe221</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sigma-Advanced-Systems-Secures-100-Cr-Defence-Orders-Boosts-Missile-and-Naval-Segments/699c749eee97f501b0ebe221</guid><description>Sigma Advanced Systems has announced securing new orders worth approximately ₹100 crore from the Ministry of Defence and its associated defence public sector undertakings (PSUs). These contracts span strategic programmes in missile systems, naval platforms, and airborne applications, reinforcing the company's engineering capabilities and its position in India's defence manufacturing sector. The win aligns with the nation's push for indigenous defence capabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:39:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c749eee97f501b0ebe220_1771861281084.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Mega-Lenders, Pauses PSB Bank Merger Roadmap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Eyes-Mega-Lenders-Pauses-PSB-Bank-Merger-Roadmap/699c7420ee97f501b0ebe160</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Eyes-Mega-Lenders-Pauses-PSB-Bank-Merger-Roadmap/699c7420ee97f501b0ebe160</guid><description>India's Finance Ministry has announced a strategic shift, shelving immediate public sector bank (PSB) mergers in favor of a 'High-Level Committee on Banking for Viksit Bharat'. This body will devise a long-term blueprint for creating 'mega-lenders' designed to support the nation's ambitious growth trajectory. The move signals a transition from consolidation tactics to strategic architectural planning for the banking sector. Concurrently, Reserve Bank of India Governor Sanjay Malhotra affirmed banks are adequately capitalized to sustain credit growth, although a widening gap between credit and deposit expansion, marked by an elevated loan-to-deposit ratio, presents a funding challenge.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:37:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c7420ee97f501b0ebe15f_1771861703843.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mercedes-Benz India: Premium Push Sparks Sales Dip Amidst Rival Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Luxury-Products/Mercedes-Benz-India-Premium-Push-Sparks-Sales-Dip-Amidst-Rival-Gains/699c73d0ee97f501b0ebe0ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Luxury-Products/Mercedes-Benz-India-Premium-Push-Sparks-Sales-Dip-Amidst-Rival-Gains/699c73d0ee97f501b0ebe0ce</guid><description>Mercedes-Benz India reported a 2.9% decline in retail sales for CY2025, selling 19,007 units as it strategically shifted focus to 'value over volume' and higher-priced premium vehicles. This move, while boosting revenue and average selling prices (ASP) to approximately ₹1 crore, saw its entry-luxury segment shrink by 20%. In contrast, rival BMW Group India posted a robust 14% sales increase, selling 18,001 units and doubling its EV penetration to 21% of sales. Audi India experienced a significant 22.46% volume drop. The overall luxury car market saw only a marginal 1.6% growth, indicating a strategic recalibration rather than broad-based expansion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:35:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c73d0ee97f501b0ebe0cd_1771861296218.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Mass Market Struggles Amidst Premium Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Mass-Market-Struggles-Amidst-Premium-Shift/699c72c4ee97f501b0ebdf81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Mass-Market-Struggles-Amidst-Premium-Shift/699c72c4ee97f501b0ebdf81</guid><description>The Indian December quarter revealed persistent weakness in mass consumption across apparel, jewellery, and food, as consumers grapple with inflation and stagnant real wages. Despite tax cuts and festive periods, demand for entry-level and middle-class products remained muted. Retailers are increasingly focusing on premiumization strategies to offset volume declines. Companies like Shoppers Stop and Page Industries are seeing slower demand at entry price points, while Titan Company faces pressure in its sub-₹1 lakh jewellery segment. Westlife Foodworld reported flat growth in the quick-service restaurant sector. Experts emphasize that sustained recovery hinges on actual income growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:31:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c72c4ee97f501b0ebdf80_1771861957696.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cipla proposes Achin Gupta as MD &amp; GCEO; P.R. Ramesh for Director re-appointment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Cipla-proposes-Achin-Gupta-as-MD-and-GCEO-PR-Ramesh-for-Director-re-appointment/699c7244ee97f501b0ebdee3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Cipla-proposes-Achin-Gupta-as-MD-and-GCEO-PR-Ramesh-for-Director-re-appointment/699c7244ee97f501b0ebdee3</guid><description>Cipla is seeking shareholder approval for significant leadership changes. Achin Gupta is proposed as the new Managing Director &amp; Global Chief Executive Officer for a five-year term starting April 1, 2026. P. R. Ramesh is also proposed for re-appointment as an Independent Director. The company has outlined remuneration details and an e-voting period for shareholders to cast their votes on these crucial appointments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:29:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c7244ee97f501b0ebdee2_1771860677868.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Global Capital for Climate Risk With ILS Framework</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Eyes-Global-Capital-for-Climate-Risk-With-ILS-Framework/699c6fb9ee97f501b0ebdc89</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Eyes-Global-Capital-for-Climate-Risk-With-ILS-Framework/699c6fb9ee97f501b0ebdc89</guid><description>The International Financial Services Centres Authority (IFSCA) is advancing a proposal to the Indian government for a specialized insurance framework enabling investment in insurance-linked securities (ILS) like catastrophe bonds. This strategic move aims to broaden domestic risk-sharing mechanisms and attract global capital to GIFT City. The initiative is projected to be formalized within months, following consultations. It addresses India's increasing vulnerability to climate-related disasters by creating sophisticated tools for risk transfer to capital markets, a sector experiencing robust global growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:18:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6fb9ee97f501b0ebdc88_1771860043989.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Policy Shift: New CPI Data Meets Inflation Target Review Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Policy-Shift-New-CPI-Data-Meets-Inflation-Target-Review-Uncertainty/699c6f76ee97f501b0ebdc1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Policy-Shift-New-CPI-Data-Meets-Inflation-Target-Review-Uncertainty/699c6f76ee97f501b0ebdc1e</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has introduced a new Consumer Price Index (CPI) series, using 2024 prices and tracking 358 items, aimed at better reflecting household consumption and reducing data volatility. This comes as the central bank prepares for a mandated five-year review of its flexible inflation targeting (FIT) regime, with the current 4% target and 2-6% tolerance band under scrutiny. Governor Sanjay Malhotra indicated that upcoming April projections will incorporate the new methodology. Separately, he clarified that observed changes in US securities holdings are due to valuation shifts, not a strategic reduction, highlighting the impact of currency fluctuations on reserves.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:17:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6f76ee97f501b0ebdc1d_1771860867365.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aditya Ispat Sells Core Steel Unit for ₹3.68 Cr to Related Party</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Aditya-Ispat-Sells-Core-Steel-Unit-for-368-Cr-to-Related-Party/699c6f72ee97f501b0ebdc07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Aditya-Ispat-Sells-Core-Steel-Unit-for-368-Cr-to-Related-Party/699c6f72ee97f501b0ebdc07</guid><description>Aditya Ispat Limited's board has greenlit the slump sale of its entire non-alloy steel manufacturing and trading business to Jai Bapji Ispat Private Limited, a related party, for ₹3.68 crore. This strategic divestment, representing 97.75% of FY25 turnover and 88.85% of net worth, is deemed crucial for the company's survival amidst high debt and eroding net worth. Shareholder approval via postal ballot is pending.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:17:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6f72ee97f501b0ebdc06_1771859957277.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Auctions G-Sec 2035 Amid Large Borrowing Program</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Auctions-G-Sec-2035-Amid-Large-Borrowing-Program/699c6d3dee97f501b0ebd9ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Auctions-G-Sec-2035-Amid-Large-Borrowing-Program/699c6d3dee97f501b0ebd9ba</guid><description>The Government of India is set to auction its 6.48% Government Security maturing in 2035, seeking to raise ₹32,000 crore with an option for an additional ₹2,000 crore. This issuance is a component of the Centre's extensive market borrowing program designed to finance fiscal requirements and maintain liquidity in the bond markets. The auction, scheduled for February 27, 2026, involves participation from Primary Dealers through the RBI's e-Kuber system. Analysts are monitoring this issuance in the context of substantial overall debt supply and the Reserve Bank of India's steady monetary policy stance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:07:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6d3dee97f501b0ebd9b9_1771860087950.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shree Salasar Eyes Capital Infusion; Board to Weigh Fund Raising Feb 26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Shree-Salasar-Eyes-Capital-Infusion-Board-to-Weigh-Fund-Raising-Feb-26/699c6b8aee97f501b0ebd840</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Shree-Salasar-Eyes-Capital-Infusion-Board-to-Weigh-Fund-Raising-Feb-26/699c6b8aee97f501b0ebd840</guid><description>Shree Salasar Investments Limited has called a board meeting for February 26, 2026, to explore proposals for raising capital. The company may issue equity shares, convertible or non-convertible securities, or warrants. Any approved plan will require shareholder consent, potentially impacting ownership and future strategic moves.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6b8aee97f501b0ebd83f_1771858938015.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>