<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:15:19 +0000</pubDate><item><title>RBI's New Rules Could Significantly Slow Urban Co-op Bank Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-New-Rules-Could-Significantly-Slow-Urban-Co-op-Bank-Expansion/694ed692cde967caf666d544</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-New-Rules-Could-Significantly-Slow-Urban-Co-op-Bank-Expansion/694ed692cde967caf666d544</guid><description>New Reserve Bank of India guidelines on business authorisation plans are likely to slow the expansion of urban cooperative banks (UCBs). Banks crossing deposit thresholds of ₹100 crore, ₹1,000 crore, and ₹10,000 crore are moved to higher regulatory tiers with stricter norms, including higher capital adequacy ratios. Officials indicate these rules, partly due to a recent UCB failure, will increase compliance costs and act as a disincentive to growth, potentially leading to consolidation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:26:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ed692cde967caf666d543_1766774587030.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Foreign Capital Drains from India's Top Funds – Is Domestic Money the New King?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Foreign-Capital-Drains-from-Indias-Top-Funds-Is-Domestic-Money-the-New-King/694ed610cde967caf666d495</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Foreign-Capital-Drains-from-Indias-Top-Funds-Is-Domestic-Money-the-New-King/694ed610cde967caf666d495</guid><description>Foreign investors' share in India's Alternative Investment Funds (AIFs) has dropped significantly, falling from 40.9% in March 2024 to 34.8% by September 2025. This decline occurs as total funds raised by AIFs increased to ₹7.3 trillion. The trend is attributed to factors like rupee depreciation, global market performance, and India's specific investment landscape. Meanwhile, domestic investors are showing increased comfort and faster growth in AIF fundraising, particularly in areas like private credit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:25:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ed610cde967caf666d494_1766774447471.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sensex Plunges Again! Is Monday December 29th Set for More Pain? Investors Brace for Holiday Correction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Plunges-Again-Is-Monday-December-29th-Set-for-More-Pain-Investors-Brace-for-Holiday-Correction/694ed57acde967caf666d3de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Plunges-Again-Is-Monday-December-29th-Set-for-More-Pain-Investors-Brace-for-Holiday-Correction/694ed57acde967caf666d3de</guid><description>Indian stock markets saw another day of losses as the BSE Sensex fell 367 points and the NSE Nifty declined 99.80 points. This marks the third consecutive session of decline for the Sensex, driven by weak market momentum, ongoing foreign fund outflows, and a lack of significant domestic catalysts. Profit-taking dominated the holiday-shortened trading week, with analysts predicting further correction ahead as key support levels are tested.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:25:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ed57acde967caf666d3dd_1766774212530.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹50 Lakh Credit Card Trap! Friends' Spending Triggers Shocking Income Tax Notice – Are You Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/50-Lakh-Credit-Card-Trap-Friends-Spending-Triggers-Shocking-Income-Tax-Notice-Are-You-Next/694ed333cde967caf666c9e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/50-Lakh-Credit-Card-Trap-Friends-Spending-Triggers-Shocking-Income-Tax-Notice-Are-You-Next/694ed333cde967caf666c9e9</guid><description>A chartered accountant highlighted a case where a taxpayer received an income tax notice for spending over ₹50 lakh on credit cards without filing returns. The taxpayer used credit cards for friends' expenses, accumulating rewards. The Income-Tax department treated this as unexplained expenditure under Section 69C, as financial institutions report high-value transactions. Maintaining a clear audit trail is crucial to avoid tax liabilities on such disproportionate spending.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ed333cde967caf666c9e8_1766773636102.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Luxury Housing Secret Revealed: Top 10 Micro-Markets Poised for Explosive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Luxury-Housing-Secret-Revealed-Top-10-Micro-Markets-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/694ecb8dcde967caf6662358</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Luxury-Housing-Secret-Revealed-Top-10-Micro-Markets-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/694ecb8dcde967caf6662358</guid><description>India's luxury housing demand is shifting from major cities to specific micro-markets, identified by a Magicbricks report. These 10 high-growth pockets, including Dwarka Expressway, Noida Expressway, and Sushant Golf City in Lucknow, are attracting affluent buyers and NRIs with a blend of infrastructure, amenities, and future growth potential. Tier-2 cities are also emerging as hotspots for premium homes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:45:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ecb8dcde967caf6662357_1766771866006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Hidden Strength: Unlocking Billions by Exporting Workers to Fill Global Labor Gaps!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Hidden-Strength-Unlocking-Billions-by-Exporting-Workers-to-Fill-Global-Labor-Gaps/694eca95cde967caf665fb33</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Hidden-Strength-Unlocking-Billions-by-Exporting-Workers-to-Fill-Global-Labor-Gaps/694eca95cde967caf665fb33</guid><description>India is poised to leverage its large, young workforce as a strategic export, addressing labor shortages in aging developed economies. Structured mobility agreements offer a win-win, providing workers with better opportunities and remittances to India, while filling critical job gaps abroad. This trend, crucial for India's growth, requires careful management to maximize benefits and avoid domestic complacency.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:38:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694eca95cde967caf665fb32_1766771465153.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Flexi-cap Funds Skyrocket: Investors' Top Choice in 2025 Amid Market Uncertainty!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Flexi-cap-Funds-Skyrocket-Investors-Top-Choice-in-2025-Amid-Market-Uncertainty/694ec673cde967caf66545be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Flexi-cap-Funds-Skyrocket-Investors-Top-Choice-in-2025-Amid-Market-Uncertainty/694ec673cde967caf66545be</guid><description>Flexicap funds have become the most preferred equity mutual fund category in 2025, attracting the highest net inflows of ₹70,960 crore. This surge has propelled them to become the largest equity segment by assets, with their Assets Under Management growing to ₹5.45 trillion. Investors are favoring these flexible funds due to volatile market conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:22:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ec673cde967caf66545bd_1766770401249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Digital Gold Frenzy: Young Indians Gobble Up 12 Tonnes, But SEBI's Shock Warning Just Changed Everything!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Digital-Gold-Frenzy-Young-Indians-Gobble-Up-12-Tonnes-But-SEBIs-Shock-Warning-Just-Changed-Everything/694ec397cde967caf664cd15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Digital-Gold-Frenzy-Young-Indians-Gobble-Up-12-Tonnes-But-SEBIs-Shock-Warning-Just-Changed-Everything/694ec397cde967caf664cd15</guid><description>Young Indians purchased an estimated 12 tonnes of digital gold from January to November, significantly up from around 8 tonnes in the previous year. This digital format, popular for its low entry barrier and accessibility via apps, allows users to buy, sell, and hold gold online. However, trading has slowed since the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) warned in November that digital gold is not a regulated security, urging caution. Industry players are pushing for a regulatory framework, with the India Bullion &amp; Jewellers Association establishing a self-regulatory body to build buyer confidence and deepen the market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:08:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ec397cde967caf664cd14_1766769707999.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Forex Reserves Surge by $4.4 Billion: RBI's Smart Swap Boosts National Kitty!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Surge-by-44-Billion-RBIs-Smart-Swap-Boosts-National-Kitty/694ec2c6cde967caf664cc2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Surge-by-44-Billion-RBIs-Smart-Swap-Boosts-National-Kitty/694ec2c6cde967caf664cc2a</guid><description>India's foreign exchange reserves saw a significant jump of nearly $4.4 billion, reaching $693.3 billion in the week ending December 19. This surge is primarily attributed to a $5 billion USD/INR buy-sell swap auction conducted by the Reserve Bank of India on December 16, aimed at injecting liquidity into the banking system. The RBI facilitated banks selling dollars for rupees, with an agreement to buy them back later, boosting the central bank's reserves.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:06:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ec2c6cde967caf664cc29_1766769414869.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Career Boom: Professionals Chase Future Skills as Enrollments Skyrocket on Top Platforms!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Career-Boom-Professionals-Chase-Future-Skills-as-Enrollments-Skyrocket-on-Top-Platforms/694ebcaacde967caf663bdce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Career-Boom-Professionals-Chase-Future-Skills-as-Enrollments-Skyrocket-on-Top-Platforms/694ebcaacde967caf663bdce</guid><description>Indian professionals are rushing to enroll in AI and emerging technology courses, driving unprecedented demand on platforms like Simplilearn, upGrad, Udemy, Emeritus, and Coursera. Key areas of interest include agentic AI, generative AI, and cybersecurity. This surge is fueled by the need to upskill, stay competitive in an AI-driven economy, and meet the evolving demands of organizations integrating AI into their operations. Demand for AI talent in India is projected to more than double by 2027.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:43:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ebcaacde967caf663bdcd_1766767895121.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dollar Doom: Peter Schiff Predicts Historic Economic Collapse as Gold Ascends!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dollar-Doom-Peter-Schiff-Predicts-Historic-Economic-Collapse-as-Gold-Ascends/694ebc96cde967caf663bd99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dollar-Doom-Peter-Schiff-Predicts-Historic-Economic-Collapse-as-Gold-Ascends/694ebc96cde967caf663bd99</guid><description>Economist Peter Schiff warns of an impending historic US economic collapse, stating the US dollar's reign as the primary reserve asset is ending. He points to rising gold prices, central banks shifting from US Treasuries to gold, and a weakening dollar as indicators. Schiff believes this marks a significant shift in global finance, potentially leading to a dollar crash against other currencies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:40:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ebc96cde967caf663bd98_1766767837439.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zepto Sales Skyrocket 129% to ₹9,669 Cr, Losses Widen Amid IPO Rush!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zepto-Sales-Skyrocket-129percent-to-9669-Cr-Losses-Widen-Amid-IPO-Rush/694eb444cde967caf6633efb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Zepto-Sales-Skyrocket-129percent-to-9669-Cr-Losses-Widen-Amid-IPO-Rush/694eb444cde967caf6633efb</guid><description>Zepto has reported a significant 129% surge in total sales to ₹9,669 crore for FY25. However, net losses also widened to ₹3,367 crore as the quick commerce firm invested heavily in expansion and customer acquisition amidst fierce competition. The company is preparing to confidentially file its Draft Red Herring Prospectus (DRHP) this week for its upcoming IPO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:06:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694eb444cde967caf6633efa_1766765707013.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCLAT Curbs CoC Powers: Approved Insolvency Plans Now Immutable for Creditors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NCLAT-Curbs-CoC-Powers-Approved-Insolvency-Plans-Now-Immutable-for-Creditors/694eb3bfcde967caf6633dec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NCLAT-Curbs-CoC-Powers-Approved-Insolvency-Plans-Now-Immutable-for-Creditors/694eb3bfcde967caf6633dec</guid><description>The National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) has ruled that the Committee of Creditors (CoC) cannot alter an already approved insolvency resolution plan to reallocate funds from dissenting financial creditors. This significant decision in the Reliance Communications Infrastructure Ltd (RCIL) case clarifies that the CoC's 'commercial wisdom' does not extend to modifying the financial distribution framework after a plan has been sanctioned by the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), thus reinforcing the finality of approved plans.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:03:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694eb3bfcde967caf6633deb_1766765610092.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo Faces Government Probe! Secret Report on Flight Chaos Submitted to DGCA - What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Faces-Government-Probe-Secret-Report-on-Flight-Chaos-Submitted-to-DGCA-Whats-Next/694eb04ce10c98d0788eccbf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Faces-Government-Probe-Secret-Report-on-Flight-Chaos-Submitted-to-DGCA-Whats-Next/694eb04ce10c98d0788eccbf</guid><description>A government-appointed committee has submitted a confidential report to India's Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA) investigating recent widespread flight disruptions at IndiGo. The panel examined potential operational lapses leading to delays and cancellations. The DGCA will now review the findings to determine necessary regulatory actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:44:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694eb04ce10c98d0788eccbe_1766764765814.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Ship Repair Sector Shines: Kolkata-Cochin JV Posts Record ₹5.94 Cr Profit, Boosts 'Make in India'!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Ship-Repair-Sector-Shines-Kolkata-Cochin-JV-Posts-Record-594-Cr-Profit-Boosts-Make-in-India/694eafcae10c98d0788ecb53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Ship-Repair-Sector-Shines-Kolkata-Cochin-JV-Posts-Record-594-Cr-Profit-Boosts-Make-in-India/694eafcae10c98d0788ecb53</guid><description>Syama Prasad Mookerjee Port, Kolkata, and Cochin Shipyard Ltd have reaffirmed their joint venture, the Cochin-Kolkata Ship Repair Unit (CKSRU). This partnership successfully generated a profit of ₹5.94 crore, highlighting the strategic potential of indigenous ship repair facilities. The collaboration aims to strengthen India's maritime ecosystem and actively support the 'Make in India' initiative, with plans for further expansion of repair activities in Kolkata.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:44:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694eafcae10c98d0788ecb52_1766764707385.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Heroes Get Special Home Loans: New Partnership Promises Cheaper Rates!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Defence-Heroes-Get-Special-Home-Loans-New-Partnership-Promises-Cheaper-Rates/694eaf03e10c98d0788ec994</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Defence-Heroes-Get-Special-Home-Loans-New-Partnership-Promises-Cheaper-Rates/694eaf03e10c98d0788ec994</guid><description>Housing finance firms are now offering specialized home loans for defense personnel, recognizing them as a distinct borrower group. A partnership between BASIC Home Loan and udChalo aims to provide tailored financial products, addressing unique challenges like frequent postings and varied income components. These loans focus on affordable and mid-income housing near cantonments, starting at ₹20 lakh, targeting end-users in Tier-2 and Tier-3 cities. The initiative, launching in Chandigarh and Pune, anticipates ₹1,000 crore in disbursals over three years, highlighting lender confidence in this stable borrower segment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:42:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694eaf03e10c98d0788ec993_1766764378555.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coinbase: Top 2026 Fintech Pick! Analyst Reveals Stunning $415 Price Target Amidst Blockchain Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coinbase-Top-2026-Fintech-Pick-Analyst-Reveals-Stunning-415-Price-Target-Amidst-Blockchain-Boom/694eaf5ae10c98d0788eca45</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coinbase-Top-2026-Fintech-Pick-Analyst-Reveals-Stunning-415-Price-Target-Amidst-Blockchain-Boom/694eaf5ae10c98d0788eca45</guid><description>Clear Street analyst Owen Lau has named Coinbase a top three fintech pick for 2026, ranking it alongside Nasdaq and S&amp;P Global. Lau set a $415 price target for Coinbase (COIN), citing its strong position in blockchain adoption and regulatory clarity. The analyst highlighted Coinbase's diversified revenue streams beyond volatile trading, including subscriptions, stablecoin activity, and on-chain services, as key drivers for weathering crypto cycles.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:42:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694eaf5ae10c98d0788eca44_1766764532600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RIL's $247 Million KG Basin Showdown: Global Arbitration Nears Climax, Resolution Expected 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/RILs-247-Million-KG-Basin-Showdown-Global-Arbitration-Nears-Climax-Resolution-Expected-2026/694eafe2e10c98d0788ecb99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/RILs-247-Million-KG-Basin-Showdown-Global-Arbitration-Nears-Climax-Resolution-Expected-2026/694eafe2e10c98d0788ecb99</guid><description>Reliance Industries Ltd (RIL) faces a $247 million dispute with the Indian government over disallowed costs in the KG-D6 block. The arbitration process is in its final stages, with a resolution anticipated in 2026. This case involves complex production-sharing contract interpretations and could affect India's attractiveness as an investment destination for deepwater exploration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:41:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694eafe2e10c98d0788ecb98_1766764884297.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBCC Strikes Landmark Deal: Rs 8,500 Crore South Delhi Mega Project Unlocked After Govt Settlement!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCC-Strikes-Landmark-Deal-Rs-8500-Crore-South-Delhi-Mega-Project-Unlocked-After-Govt-Settlement/694ead97e10c98d0788ec7d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCC-Strikes-Landmark-Deal-Rs-8500-Crore-South-Delhi-Mega-Project-Unlocked-After-Govt-Settlement/694ead97e10c98d0788ec7d4</guid><description>NBCC India has settled a long-standing dispute with the Delhi government over 42.46 acres of land in Sultanpur. This settlement clears the way for NBCC to develop a massive 4.5 million sq ft real estate project in South Delhi, with an estimated revenue potential of ₹8,500 crore. The land will be split, and NBCC will pay approximately ₹220 crore to resolve dues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:38:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ead97e10c98d0788ec7d3_1766764204976.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fiscal Target Under Threat? Government Faces Tax Shortfall, Explores Options to Plug Gap!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Target-Under-Threat-Government-Faces-Tax-Shortfall-Explores-Options-to-Plug-Gap/694ead1fe10c98d0788ec6f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Target-Under-Threat-Government-Faces-Tax-Shortfall-Explores-Options-to-Plug-Gap/694ead1fe10c98d0788ec6f2</guid><description>India's Centre faces challenges meeting its fiscal deficit target of 4.4% of GDP this year. Underwhelming direct tax growth (4.2%) and decelerating indirect tax collections (CGST 5.7%) are key concerns. However, strong non-tax revenues, including a substantial dividend from the Reserve Bank of India (₹2.68 lakh crore) and dividend payouts from CPSEs, alongside potential strategic sales like IDBI and front-loaded capital expenditure, may help bridge the shortfall and maintain fiscal prudence.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:34:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ead1fe10c98d0788ec6f1_1766763902031.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Visa Snag: India Pushes for Resolution Amidst H-1B Interview Disruptions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Visa-Snag-India-Pushes-for-Resolution-Amidst-H-1B-Interview-Disruptions/694ea639e10c98d0788ebf75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Visa-Snag-India-Pushes-for-Resolution-Amidst-H-1B-Interview-Disruptions/694ea639e10c98d0788ebf75</guid><description>India is actively discussing with the United States to resolve disruptions affecting Indian nationals due to the cancellation and rescheduling of H-1B visa interviews. Since December 15, the US has increased scrutiny of social media for H-1B and H-4 visa applicants, leading to postponed interviews, stranded professionals, family separations, and financial hardships. The Ministry of External Affairs has flagged these concerns to the US government.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:02:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ea639e10c98d0788ebf74_1766762152061.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PNB Flags ₹2,434 Crore Borrowal Fraud Linked to SREI Ex-Promoters! RBI Notified</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PNB-Flags-2434-Crore-Borrowal-Fraud-Linked-to-SREI-Ex-Promoters-RBI-Notified/694ea04be10c98d0788eb975</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PNB-Flags-2434-Crore-Borrowal-Fraud-Linked-to-SREI-Ex-Promoters-RBI-Notified/694ea04be10c98d0788eb975</guid><description>Punjab National Bank has reported a significant borrowal fraud of ₹2,434 crore to the Reserve Bank of India. The fraud involves the erstwhile promoters of SREI Equipment Finance and SREI Infrastructure Finance. PNB has confirmed making 100% provisions for the full outstanding amounts, while noting that the SREI entities have been resolved under NCLT.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:41:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ea04be10c98d0788eb974_1766760626610.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways' Bold Plan: Double Train Capacity in 48 Cities by 2030 – Get Ready for a Travel Revolution!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indian-Railways-Bold-Plan-Double-Train-Capacity-in-48-Cities-by-2030-Get-Ready-for-a-Travel-Revolution/694e9e1ee10c98d0788eb6f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indian-Railways-Bold-Plan-Double-Train-Capacity-in-48-Cities-by-2030-Get-Ready-for-a-Travel-Revolution/694e9e1ee10c98d0788eb6f0</guid><description>Indian Railways plans to double its originating train capacity in 48 major cities by 2030 to accommodate rapid travel growth. The Ministry will augment infrastructure, add platforms, create new terminals, and build maintenance facilities. This progressive expansion aims to meet future traffic demands and improve services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:34:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e9e1ee10c98d0788eb6ef_1766760065317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Investors Pour Record ₹3 Trillion into SIPs: Is This the End of Lump-Sum Investing?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Investors-Pour-Record-3-Trillion-into-SIPs-Is-This-the-End-of-Lump-Sum-Investing/694e99f9e10c98d0788eb29f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Investors-Pour-Record-3-Trillion-into-SIPs-Is-This-the-End-of-Lump-Sum-Investing/694e99f9e10c98d0788eb29f</guid><description>In 2025, investor preference dramatically shifted towards Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs), pushing inflows past a record ₹3 trillion, according to AMFI data. This surge in SIPs, especially into equity schemes, occurred as one-time lump-sum investments saw a significant decline amid market volatility. SIPs now represent a larger share of overall equity inflows, underscoring their growing importance for long-term wealth building.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:09:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e99f9e10c98d0788eb29e_1766758981137.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 IPO Boom! Govt Accelerates Green Energy Listings for PSU Giants NLC &amp; SJVN!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/2026-IPO-Boom-Govt-Accelerates-Green-Energy-Listings-for-PSU-Giants-NLC-and-SJVN/694e997be10c98d0788eb1e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/2026-IPO-Boom-Govt-Accelerates-Green-Energy-Listings-for-PSU-Giants-NLC-and-SJVN/694e997be10c98d0788eb1e5</guid><description>The Indian government plans to fast-track IPOs for PSU green energy subsidiaries in 2026. DIPAM is prioritizing NLC Green (H1) and SJVN Green (H2) listings, anticipating favorable market conditions. NLC India and SJVN are preparing for these significant public offerings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:08:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e997be10c98d0788eb1e4_1766758889408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Timex India Stake Sale Alert! Promoter Offloads Millions of Shares at ₹275 - What Investors Must Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Timex-India-Stake-Sale-Alert-Promoter-Offloads-Millions-of-Shares-at-275-What-Investors-Must-Know/694e98a1e10c98d0788eb0b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Timex-India-Stake-Sale-Alert-Promoter-Offloads-Millions-of-Shares-at-275-What-Investors-Must-Know/694e98a1e10c98d0788eb0b5</guid><description>Timex Group Luxury Watches BV, the promoter of Timex Group India Ltd, plans to sell up to 4.47% stake via an Offer for Sale (OFS) on December 29-30. The floor price is set at ₹275 per share, with an option to increase the sale size to nearly 8.93% if oversubscribed. Kotak Securities is managing the transaction on the BSE, following SEBI regulations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:08:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e98a1e10c98d0788eb0b4_1766758642720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blum's Secret India Plan: Global Furniture Giant Bets Big on Rising Consumer Demand!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Blums-Secret-India-Plan-Global-Furniture-Giant-Bets-Big-on-Rising-Consumer-Demand/694ee7534342f77179d5d28d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Blums-Secret-India-Plan-Global-Furniture-Giant-Bets-Big-on-Rising-Consumer-Demand/694ee7534342f77179d5d28d</guid><description>Global furniture fittings leader Blum Group is making India a central focus for its growth. Senior leaders visited to understand the market, signaling significant investment in expanding its network of experience centers and training facilities. Blum aims to support India's growing demand for high-quality, functional, and well-designed furniture, aligning with the nation's rising expectations and export potential.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:08:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ee7534342f77179d5d28c_1766778810200.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal Mines Approval Speed-Up: Govt Scraps Key Red Tape, Boosts Production Hopes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-Mines-Approval-Speed-Up-Govt-Scraps-Key-Red-Tape-Boosts-Production-Hopes/694e97ade10c98d0788eaf37</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-Mines-Approval-Speed-Up-Govt-Scraps-Key-Red-Tape-Boosts-Production-Hopes/694e97ade10c98d0788eaf37</guid><description>India's government has amended rules to streamline approvals for opening coal and lignite mines. The Coal Controller's Organisation's prior permission requirement has been removed, with authority now resting with the concerned coal company's board. This reform is expected to cut mine operationalization time by up to two months, aiming to boost coal production and efficiency.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:01:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e97ade10c98d0788eaf36_1766758415963.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerage Sees Big Growth: Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals Rated BUY with ₹340 Target Price!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Brokerage-Sees-Big-Growth-Crompton-Greaves-Consumer-Electricals-Rated-BUY-with-340-Target-Price/694e96b2e10c98d0788ead5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Brokerage-Sees-Big-Growth-Crompton-Greaves-Consumer-Electricals-Rated-BUY-with-340-Target-Price/694e96b2e10c98d0788ead5b</guid><description>A brokerage firm has initiated coverage on Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals with a 'Buy' rating and a target price of ₹340. The recommendation highlights the company's "Crompton 2.0" strategy, focusing on premiumisation and innovation, alongside significant traction and growth potential in its solar rooftop and solar pumps businesses. Potential risks include commodity price volatility, competition, and policy dependence for solar ventures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:58:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e96b2e10c98d0788ead5a_1766758142004.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banking Squeeze Intensifies: Deposits Lag Loans by 200 BPS as RBI Data Reveals Tightness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banking-Squeeze-Intensifies-Deposits-Lag-Loans-by-200-BPS-as-RBI-Data-Reveals-Tightness/694e919de10c98d0788ea83e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banking-Squeeze-Intensifies-Deposits-Lag-Loans-by-200-BPS-as-RBI-Data-Reveals-Tightness/694e919de10c98d0788ea83e</guid><description>Latest RBI data for December 12 shows deposit growth slowing to 9.7% year-on-year while credit growth accelerated to 11.7%. This 200 basis points gap highlights persistent deposit tightness in India's banking system, pressuring banks to fund rising credit demand and potentially pushing savers towards equity markets for better returns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:36:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e919de10c98d0788ea83d_1766756838592.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock Rs 9000 Monthly Income Guaranteed! Post Office Savings Scheme Details Revealed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Rs-9000-Monthly-Income-Guaranteed-Post-Office-Savings-Scheme-Details-Revealed/694ee6e34342f77179d5d1fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Rs-9000-Monthly-Income-Guaranteed-Post-Office-Savings-Scheme-Details-Revealed/694ee6e34342f77179d5d1fd</guid><description>The Post Office Monthly Income Scheme (POMIS), also known as the National Savings Monthly Income Scheme, offers a low-risk, government-backed savings option providing guaranteed monthly returns. With a current interest rate of 7.4% per annum, Indian residents aged 18 and above are eligible. A maximum investment of ₹15 lakh in a joint account can yield up to ₹9,250 per month. The scheme has a maturity period of five years, after which funds can be withdrawn or reinvested.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:36:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ee6e34342f77179d5d1fc_1766778693775.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Opens 5 New Branches, Boosts Q2 Business!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tamilnad-Mercantile-Bank-Opens-5-New-Branches-Boosts-Q2-Business/694ee5ef4342f77179d5d156</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tamilnad-Mercantile-Bank-Opens-5-New-Branches-Boosts-Q2-Business/694ee5ef4342f77179d5d156</guid><description>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Limited has expanded its network by opening five new branches in Velandipalayam, Kalapatti, Davanagere, Puthukkadai, and Nikol. This strategic expansion aims to increase the bank's presence in these areas. The bank also reported a 11.47% year-on-year growth in its total business for the second quarter, reaching ₹1,02,417 crore. Thiru S Balasubramanian was appointed Data Protection Officer effective December 26, 2025. The bank's share closed down 1.59% at ₹504.15 on Friday, December 26.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:36:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ee5ef4342f77179d5d155_1766778416838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's First Medical Tech University Set to Ignite Global Innovation Hub in Vizag!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-First-Medical-Tech-University-Set-to-Ignite-Global-Innovation-Hub-in-Vizag/694e8fb9e10c98d0788ea52e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-First-Medical-Tech-University-Set-to-Ignite-Global-Innovation-Hub-in-Vizag/694e8fb9e10c98d0788ea52e</guid><description>India's first specialized medical technology university, the Erba Global Institute of Medical Technology (EGIMT), is set to launch in Vizag's Andhra Pradesh Medtech Zone (AMTZ). It will offer postgraduate and PhD programs in medical technology, bio-engineering, and healthcare innovation, leveraging AMTZ's manufacturing and R&amp;D ecosystem to foster a global med-tech hub.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:26:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8fb9e10c98d0788ea52d_1766756675987.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Revolution in India: 2026 Will Be Year of Accountability, Not Just Hype!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Revolution-in-India-2026-Will-Be-Year-of-Accountability-Not-Just-Hype/694e8ed2e10c98d0788ea366</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Revolution-in-India-2026-Will-Be-Year-of-Accountability-Not-Just-Hype/694e8ed2e10c98d0788ea366</guid><description>India's AI journey is accelerating, moving rapidly from pilot projects to full-scale production. By 2026, Artificial Intelligence is predicted to become foundational infrastructure for Indian companies, transforming operations, security, and business models. Expect AI companions, agentic workflows, and a sharp focus on cost, governance, and engineering discipline over mere novelty.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:24:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8ed2e10c98d0788ea365_1766756369341.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Forex Reserves Skyrocket to Record $693 Billion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Skyrocket-to-Record-693-Billion/694e89b6e10c98d0788e9d27</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Forex-Reserves-Skyrocket-to-Record-693-Billion/694e89b6e10c98d0788e9d27</guid><description>India's foreign exchange reserves saw a significant jump of $4.368 billion, reaching a new high of $693.318 billion in the week ending December 19. This surge was primarily driven by substantial increases in foreign currency assets and gold reserves, as reported by the Reserve Bank of India. The overall kitty also benefited from growth in Special Drawing Rights and India's reserve position with the IMF, signaling robust economic standing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:03:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e89b6e10c98d0788e9d26_1766754892724.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Binge-Watching Pays Off! Your Favorite OTT Shows Are Fueling an Unseen Northeast Travel Boom – See How!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Binge-Watching-Pays-Off-Your-Favorite-OTT-Shows-Are-Fueling-an-Unseen-Northeast-Travel-Boom-See-How/694ee5234342f77179d5bfc6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Binge-Watching-Pays-Off-Your-Favorite-OTT-Shows-Are-Fueling-an-Unseen-Northeast-Travel-Boom-See-How/694ee5234342f77179d5bfc6</guid><description>A report by ixigo reveals that popular Indian OTT shows featuring the Northeast have significantly boosted tourism, driving a strong year-on-year growth in flight bookings to cities like Dimapur, Agartala, Guwahati, and Imphal in 2025. The trend highlights how on-screen content influences real-world travel demand, turning lesser-explored regions into sought-after destinations. The report also noted Japan and South Korea as top international picks and highlighted Gen Z's role in spiritual travel surges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:57:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ee5234342f77179d5bfc5_1766778296860.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Housing Market Shock: Sales Volume Down 14%, But Luxury Demand Skyrockets Value Past ₹6 Lakh Crore!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Housing-Market-Shock-Sales-Volume-Down-14percent-But-Luxury-Demand-Skyrockets-Value-Past-6-Lakh-Crore/694e8750e10c98d0788e9a80</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Housing-Market-Shock-Sales-Volume-Down-14percent-But-Luxury-Demand-Skyrockets-Value-Past-6-Lakh-Crore/694e8750e10c98d0788e9a80</guid><description>India's residential real estate saw a 14% drop in housing sales volume in 2025 across the top seven cities, selling 3,95,625 units compared to 4,59,645 in 2024. Despite this, the total sales value increased by 6% to over ₹6 lakh crore, driven by strong demand for luxury properties. Chennai was the only city with sales growth, while MMR and Pune saw significant declines. New launches saw a slight increase. Experts attribute the sales dip to economic uncertainties and IT sector layoffs but are optimistic for 2026 if RBI cuts rates and developers manage prices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:54:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8750e10c98d0788e9a7f_1766754351709.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Demat Account Surge: 2026 Outlook Hinges on Smarter Investors Amidst Market Resilience!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Demat-Account-Surge-2026-Outlook-Hinges-on-Smarter-Investors-Amidst-Market-Resilience/694e8745e10c98d0788e9a3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Demat-Account-Surge-2026-Outlook-Hinges-on-Smarter-Investors-Amidst-Market-Resilience/694e8745e10c98d0788e9a3a</guid><description>Indian demat accounts reached 21.28 crore by November 2025, showing resilience despite market volatility and FII outflows. Experts note a shift towards long-term investing, with younger investors under 30 from smaller towns driving new accounts via digital platforms. Growth in 2026 will depend on deeper, intelligent participation rather than just account numbers, influenced by macro fundamentals and household savings shifting to financial assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:53:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8745e10c98d0788e9a39_1766754189932.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CarDekho Fuels Edtech Future: $10 Million Injection into CollegeDekho Signals Major Expansion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CarDekho-Fuels-Edtech-Future-10-Million-Injection-into-CollegeDekho-Signals-Major-Expansion/694ee3bd4342f77179d59d9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CarDekho-Fuels-Edtech-Future-10-Million-Injection-into-CollegeDekho-Signals-Major-Expansion/694ee3bd4342f77179d59d9c</guid><description>CarDekho Group has invested $10 million (₹89.9 Cr) in its edtech subsidiary, CollegeDekho, to expand its presence in non-metro markets. CollegeDekho, which connects students with colleges and offers online courses, reported a 32% revenue increase to ₹216 Cr in FY24, alongside a net loss of ₹129 Cr. This investment aligns with CarDekho Group's strategic restructuring and profitability focus.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:51:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ee3bd4342f77179d59d9b_1766777968409.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock HUGE Gains Monday? Experts Reveal Top Stocks to Buy for Bumper Returns! Don't Miss These Picks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Unlock-HUGE-Gains-Monday-Experts-Reveal-Top-Stocks-to-Buy-for-Bumper-Returns-Dont-Miss-These-Picks/694e8259e10c98d0788e9502</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Unlock-HUGE-Gains-Monday-Experts-Reveal-Top-Stocks-to-Buy-for-Bumper-Returns-Dont-Miss-These-Picks/694e8259e10c98d0788e9502</guid><description>Indian markets (Sensex, Nifty) closed lower on Friday, December 26, amid foreign fund outflows. However, market experts have identified several 'stocks to buy' for the upcoming week starting Monday, December 29, anticipating bumper gains. Top recommendations include NMDC, BEL, Suzlon Energy, Titan, BHEL, MMTC, IRCON International, IRFC, and IRCTC, with specific price targets and stop-loss levels provided by analysts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:31:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e8259e10c98d0788e9501_1766753211756.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>