<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:30:24 +0000</pubDate><item><title>LMEL Posts Record Q3: Revenue Surges 204%, PAT Up 180% Amid Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LMEL-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-Surges-204percent-PAT-Up-180percent-Amid-Expansion/698257cff5a3f0ebac98073b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LMEL-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-Surges-204percent-PAT-Up-180percent-Amid-Expansion/698257cff5a3f0ebac98073b</guid><description>Lloyds Metals and Energy Limited (LMEL) delivered a stellar Q3 FY26, achieving record consolidated revenue of INR 51,553 million (+204% YoY) and PAT of INR 10,895 million (+180% YoY). Growth was fueled by a 110% YoY jump in iron ore volumes, robust domestic demand, and operational efficiencies. Strategic moves include a Tata Steel MoU for collaborations and a 50% stake in a DRC copper platform, signaling aggressive expansion despite increased borrowings for capital expenditure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:20:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698257cff5a3f0ebac98073a_1770153481676.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rashi Peripherals Posts Robust Q4 Growth: PAT Surges 132% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Rashi-Peripherals-Posts-Robust-Q4-Growth-PAT-Surges-132percent-YoY/69825749f5a3f0ebac980424</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Rashi-Peripherals-Posts-Robust-Q4-Growth-PAT-Surges-132percent-YoY/69825749f5a3f0ebac980424</guid><description>Rashi Peripherals reported a stellar Q4 FY26, with consolidated revenue soaring 43.6% YoY to ₹40,304.12 million and consolidated PAT jumping an impressive 132.6% YoY to ₹745.94 million. Standalone figures mirrored this strong performance. The company also appointed Rajesh Goenka as Whole-Time Director &amp; CEO and announced the formation of a UAE step-down subsidiary. IPO proceeds utilization is on track, with a slight extension for general corporate purposes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825749f5a3f0ebac980423_1770153558677.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KSDL Production Record: Mysore Sandal Soap Maker Eyes ₹5,000 Cr Turnover</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/KSDL-Production-Record-Mysore-Sandal-Soap-Maker-Eyes-5000-Cr-Turnover/69825839f5a3f0ebac980984</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/KSDL-Production-Record-Mysore-Sandal-Soap-Maker-Eyes-5000-Cr-Turnover/69825839f5a3f0ebac980984</guid><description>Karnataka Soaps and Detergents Limited (KSDL), the maker of Mysore Sandal soap, has achieved an unprecedented production milestone, manufacturing 4,894.777 metric tonnes in January 2026. The state-owned enterprise is targeting a significant turnover of ₹5,000 crore by 2030, signaling ambitious growth plans fueled by market expansion and product diversification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:16:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825839f5a3f0ebac980983_1770153370149.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Cut Boosts Indian Seafood Exports Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/US-Tariff-Cut-Boosts-Indian-Seafood-Exports-Outlook/69825f08f5a3f0ebac982e55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/US-Tariff-Cut-Boosts-Indian-Seafood-Exports-Outlook/69825f08f5a3f0ebac982e55</guid><description>Indian seafood exporters anticipate a strong rebound following the US agreement to reduce import tariffs. Shipments, valued at $2.7 billion to the US in 2024-25, faced significant pressure from duties that previously climbed to 50%. The new reduced tariff rate of 18% is expected to restore competitiveness and revive trade flows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825f08f5a3f0ebac982e54_1770153329741.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yamaha EC-06 India Launch: Premium EV Scooter Enters Market at ₹1.67 Lakh</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Yamaha-EC-06-India-Launch-Premium-EV-Scooter-Enters-Market-at-167-Lakh/69825856f5a3f0ebac980a44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Yamaha-EC-06-India-Launch-Premium-EV-Scooter-Enters-Market-at-167-Lakh/69825856f5a3f0ebac980a44</guid><description>India Yamaha Motor has introduced its first electric scooter, the EC-06, priced at ₹1.67 lakh ex-showroom Delhi. Manufactured in collaboration with River, the EC-06 boasts a 169-km certified range and 79 km/h top speed. This move marks Yamaha's strategic entry into India's expanding EV market, leveraging local manufacturing and government initiatives while targeting the premium commuter segment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:15:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825856f5a3f0ebac980a43_1770153352510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>YC Embraces Stablecoins: VCs See Institutional Crypto Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/YC-Embraces-Stablecoins-VCs-See-Institutional-Crypto-Shift/69825e4af5a3f0ebac982c78</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/YC-Embraces-Stablecoins-VCs-See-Institutional-Crypto-Shift/69825e4af5a3f0ebac982c78</guid><description>Y Combinator (YC) is enabling startups to receive its standard $500,000 seed investment via stablecoins on Base, Solana, and Ethereum blockchains. This move, effective with the spring cohort, prioritizes transaction efficiency, cost reduction, and access for founders globally, especially in emerging markets. It represents a significant institutional endorsement of blockchain payment rails, aligning with evolving regulatory clarity and a broader trend of increasing VC interest in the stablecoin ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825e4af5a3f0ebac982c77_1770153204531.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Firms: AI Disrupts Growth Metrics, Creates Valuation Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Firms-AI-Disrupts-Growth-Metrics-Creates-Valuation-Jitters/69825e3ef5a3f0ebac982c03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Firms-AI-Disrupts-Growth-Metrics-Creates-Valuation-Jitters/69825e3ef5a3f0ebac982c03</guid><description>The Indian IT sector, including giants like Wipro, Infosys, and TCS, is undergoing a fundamental shift. Traditional growth indicators such as headcount and Total Contract Value (TCV) are becoming less relevant as Artificial Intelligence automates tasks and boosts operational efficiency. This transition necessitates a recalibration of valuation models, pushing investors to seek new metrics that capture AI's true impact on profitability and future revenue generation. Sector-wide, AI adoption is accelerating, yet readiness gaps persist, creating an uncertain outlook for established growth projections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:13:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825e3ef5a3f0ebac982c02_1770153216475.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Cut to 18% Reshapes India Exports; Banks Face Mixed Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/US-Tariff-Cut-to-18percent-Reshapes-India-Exports-Banks-Face-Mixed-Outlook/69825e1cf5a3f0ebac982b23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/US-Tariff-Cut-to-18percent-Reshapes-India-Exports-Banks-Face-Mixed-Outlook/69825e1cf5a3f0ebac982b23</guid><description>The United States has reduced import tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, a move anticipated to invigorate key export sectors like textiles and gems. This tariff adjustment, particularly significant against competitor nations such as China and Vietnam, is expected to spur demand for export financing from Indian banks. However, the broader implications for bank credit growth are tempered by existing margin pressures and the strategic trade-offs India made, including halting Russian oil purchases. While the immediate outlook is positive for exporters, the long-term sustainability hinges on global economic stability and robust credit management by financial institutions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825e1cf5a3f0ebac982b22_1770153081735.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trade Deal Hype Lifts Rupee, Bonds Face Supply Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Deal-Hype-Lifts-Rupee-Bonds-Face-Supply-Woes/69825de1f5a3f0ebac982993</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Deal-Hype-Lifts-Rupee-Bonds-Face-Supply-Woes/69825de1f5a3f0ebac982993</guid><description>A speculative India-US trade deal announcement propelled the Indian rupee to its strongest single-day gain in seven years, while government bonds saw yields ease but remain pressured by fiscal deficits and record borrowing projections. Market sentiment improved dramatically on hopes of reduced tariffs, but underlying supply-demand issues persist in the debt market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825de1f5a3f0ebac982992_1770152928127.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Pause Likely: Inflation Rises, Growth Slows, Liquidity Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/RBI/RBI-Pause-Likely-Inflation-Rises-Growth-Slows-Liquidity-Focus/69825dc1f5a3f0ebac9828aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/RBI/RBI-Pause-Likely-Inflation-Rises-Growth-Slows-Liquidity-Focus/69825dc1f5a3f0ebac9828aa</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee is poised to maintain the repo rate at 5.25% on February 6. This decision reflects a delicate balance between persistent inflationary pressures, evident in November's 0.71% CPI rise, and a projected economic growth slowdown to 6.7-7% for FY27. With inflation data revisions due, the central bank prioritizes policy space and liquidity management, utilizing open market operations and forex swaps. The static rate environment signals a strategic pause, steering clear of further easing while safeguarding against growth shocks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825dc1f5a3f0ebac9828a9_1770152850794.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Trade Deal Sparks $1.5 Trillion Wealth Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Trade-Deal-Sparks-15-Trillion-Wealth-Surge/69825daaf5a3f0ebac9827db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Trade-Deal-Sparks-15-Trillion-Wealth-Surge/69825daaf5a3f0ebac9827db</guid><description>A U.S.-India trade deal, reducing tariffs to 18%, spurred a substantial rally in Indian equities, adding approximately ₹12.1 lakh crore ($1.5 trillion) to investor wealth. The Sensex and Nifty climbed over 2.5%, reversing prior concerns and signaling a strategic shift. Foreign portfolio investors injected significant capital, with key sectors like electronics manufacturing services, auto ancillaries, and textiles poised for growth as India solidifies its "China Plus One" strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:06:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825daaf5a3f0ebac9827da_1770152805041.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Fuels Content Dominance with Sikhya Entertainment Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Reliance-Fuels-Content-Dominance-with-Sikhya-Entertainment-Acquisition/69825d48f5a3f0ebac982693</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Reliance-Fuels-Content-Dominance-with-Sikhya-Entertainment-Acquisition/69825d48f5a3f0ebac982693</guid><description>Reliance Industries, through Jio Studios, has secured a 50.1% majority stake in Oscar-winning production house Sikhya Entertainment for ₹150 crore. This acquisition is a strategic move to bolster Jio Studios' content pipeline, secure intellectual property, and amplify its global reach in the rapidly consolidating Indian media and entertainment sector. The deal signifies a shift towards acquiring proven creative talent and IP as large corporations increasingly invest in established studios to drive growth and content dominance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825d48f5a3f0ebac982692_1770152637826.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ad Industry's K-Shape: Digital Skyrockets, Traditional Plummets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Ad-Industrys-K-Shape-Digital-Skyrockets-Traditional-Plummets/69825d30f5a3f0ebac9825af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Ad-Industrys-K-Shape-Digital-Skyrockets-Traditional-Plummets/69825d30f5a3f0ebac9825af</guid><description>The advertising and marketing services industry is defined by a K-shaped divergence, where digital-first sectors such as AI and performance marketing are rapidly outperforming the broader economy. Traditional models, however, are contracting, necessitating a sharp focus on agility, data-driven creativity, and client-centric solutions. India is highlighted as a significant innovation hub. This environment pushes marketing to the boardroom, demanding demonstrable ROI for every expenditure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:02:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825d30f5a3f0ebac9825ae_1770152552146.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kansai Nerolac Profit Plummets Amid Regulatory Hit, Valuation Gains Traction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kansai-Nerolac-Profit-Plummets-Amid-Regulatory-Hit-Valuation-Gains-Traction/69825cd1f5a3f0ebac9823f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kansai-Nerolac-Profit-Plummets-Amid-Regulatory-Hit-Valuation-Gains-Traction/69825cd1f5a3f0ebac9823f5</guid><description>Kansai Nerolac reported a stark 75% year-on-year decline in net profit to ₹131.20 crore for the December quarter. This sharp drop was primarily driven by an exceptional charge of ₹44.72 crore linked to new labor code provisions impacting gratuity and leave liabilities. Despite the bottom-line contraction, the company's operational performance, as indicated by Earnings Before Interest, Tax, Depreciation, and Amortisation (EBITDA), remained largely flat at ₹247.3 crore, highlighting underlying business resilience.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:01:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825cd1f5a3f0ebac9823f4_1770152479499.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India REITs Trail Global Peers Amid GCC Office Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-REITs-Trail-Global-Peers-Amid-GCC-Office-Boom/69825d2ff5a3f0ebac98259c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-REITs-Trail-Global-Peers-Amid-GCC-Office-Boom/69825d2ff5a3f0ebac98259c</guid><description>India's REIT market, currently representing about 20% of its institutional real estate, significantly lags global benchmarks. While a boom in Global Capability Centres (GCCs) is driving record office leasing and market resilience, the REIT sector's adoption rate presents a notable disparity. Projections indicate REIT penetration could reach 25-30% by 2030, contingent on diversification into alternative assets like data centers, logistics, and retail, aligning with trends in more developed markets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:00:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825d2ff5a3f0ebac98259b_1770152430584.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Cut Fuels India Electronics Exports, Boosts Competitiveness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/US-Tariff-Cut-Fuels-India-Electronics-Exports-Boosts-Competitiveness/69825cb5f5a3f0ebac98232d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/US-Tariff-Cut-Fuels-India-Electronics-Exports-Boosts-Competitiveness/69825cb5f5a3f0ebac98232d</guid><description>A significant reduction in US tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, down from 50%, is revitalizing export prospects for Indian electronics manufacturers. Companies like Dixon Technologies, Havells India, and Blue Star are poised for growth, gaining a competitive edge against Asian rivals. This trade policy shift supports India's role in global supply chain diversification and is projected to unlock substantial opportunities in the electronics and semiconductor sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:58:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825cb5f5a3f0ebac98232c_1770152308038.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Pact: Diamond Duty Clarity Key to Export Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-US-Trade-Pact-Diamond-Duty-Clarity-Key-to-Export-Recovery/69825cc3f5a3f0ebac9823a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-US-Trade-Pact-Diamond-Duty-Clarity-Key-to-Export-Recovery/69825cc3f5a3f0ebac9823a0</guid><description>Washington's reciprocal tariff reduction offers a lifeline to India's beleaguered gems and jewellery exporters, who saw shipments to the US plunge by 44% in April-December 2025. While the broader sector expects a boost, the crucial segment of polished diamonds awaits clarity on zero-duty access under Annexure III, a condition that could determine the extent of market recovery. The sector experienced a dramatic escalation in duties on polished diamonds and coloured gemstones, surging from 0% to 50% over several months in 2025. Lab-grown diamond trade participants express optimism for increased market share, viewing the tariff reduction as a timely positive development.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:57:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825cc3f5a3f0ebac98239f_1770152257765.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trade Deal Triggers Short Cover Rally, But Fundamentals Remain Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Deal-Triggers-Short-Cover-Rally-But-Fundamentals-Remain-Key/69825bf1f5a3f0ebac9820f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Deal-Triggers-Short-Cover-Rally-But-Fundamentals-Remain-Key/69825bf1f5a3f0ebac9820f5</guid><description>The India-US trade agreement, slashing tariffs to 18%, ignited a significant short covering rally on February 3, 2026, pushing the Nifty 50 up 2.55% to 25,727.55 and the Sensex 2.54% higher to 83,739.13. Foreign portfolio investors, holding record bearish derivative positions, unwound shorts, amplifying buying pressure. However, analysts caution that this technical bounce faces scrutiny, with sustained gains dependent on corporate earnings recovery and genuine FPI flow reversal rather than short-term positioning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:57:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825bf1f5a3f0ebac9820f4_1770152220223.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India prioritizes pragmatic crude imports amid geopolitical shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-prioritizes-pragmatic-crude-imports-amid-geopolitical-shifts/69825be0f5a3f0ebac982062</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-prioritizes-pragmatic-crude-imports-amid-geopolitical-shifts/69825be0f5a3f0ebac982062</guid><description>New Delhi will sustain crude oil imports from non-sanctioned entities, including Russian suppliers, driven by logistical realities and substantial price discounts. Despite geopolitical pressures and an ongoing diversification strategy incorporating US and UAE supplies, these shifts are incremental, underscoring India's pragmatic approach to energy security and economic stability. Near-term imports remain largely locked in, preventing immediate disruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:54:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825be0f5a3f0ebac982061_1770152063521.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unveils Tax Reforms: Focus on Easing Compliance, Boosting Liquidity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Unveils-Tax-Reforms-Focus-on-Easing-Compliance-Boosting-Liquidity/69825bc3f5a3f0ebac981f69</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Unveils-Tax-Reforms-Focus-on-Easing-Compliance-Boosting-Liquidity/69825bc3f5a3f0ebac981f69</guid><description>The Indian government is set to implement significant tax reforms via the Finance Bill 2026 and forthcoming GST Council meetings. Direct tax changes focus on empowering taxpayers with extended return filing options, broader immunity provisions, and streamlined dispute resolution mechanisms under the new Income Tax Act, 2025. Critically, the Goods and Services Tax (GST) agenda prioritizes addressing refund delays to unlock crucial working capital for businesses, a move strongly advocated by industry experts to alleviate liquidity constraints.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:53:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825bc3f5a3f0ebac981f68_1770152006448.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fractal Analytics Slashes IPO Size by 42%, Eyes ₹2,834 Crore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-Slashes-IPO-Size-by-42percent-Eyes-2834-Crore/69825b6ef5a3f0ebac981dd6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-Slashes-IPO-Size-by-42percent-Eyes-2834-Crore/69825b6ef5a3f0ebac981dd6</guid><description>AI solutions unicorn Fractal Analytics has drastically reduced its Initial Public Offering (IPO) size by 42%, targeting ₹2,834 crore. The revised plan includes a fresh issue of ₹1,023.5 crore and an offer for sale worth ₹1,810.4 crore, involving key investors like Quinag Bidco Ltd. The IPO is set to open for subscription on February 9, following anchor bidding on February 6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:52:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825b6ef5a3f0ebac981dd5_1770151909734.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Fuels PepsiCo International Snacks Growth Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Fuels-PepsiCo-International-Snacks-Growth-Surge/69825b5ff5a3f0ebac981cf7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Fuels-PepsiCo-International-Snacks-Growth-Surge/69825b5ff5a3f0ebac981cf7</guid><description>PepsiCo's latest earnings reveal India as a primary driver for its international snacks business growth in Calendar Year 2025. The company highlighted India's strong contribution to revenue and market share gains in the savory snack segment. This performance underpins PepsiCo's ongoing commitment to expanding its global manufacturing and product innovation, eyeing further profitable growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:51:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825b5ff5a3f0ebac981cf6_1770151868204.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks Surge 2.5% On US Trade Deal; Fine Print Risks Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Stocks-Surge-25percent-On-US-Trade-Deal-Fine-Print-Risks-Emerge/69825b53f5a3f0ebac981ca5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Stocks-Surge-25percent-On-US-Trade-Deal-Fine-Print-Risks-Emerge/69825b53f5a3f0ebac981ca5</guid><description>Indian equity markets recorded their largest gain in nearly nine months, surging 2.5% on Tuesday. The rally was ignited by a US-India trade agreement that slashed tariffs on Indian exports to 18% from 50%. This boosted export-oriented sectors and fueled a significant recovery in the Indian rupee. However, market participants await precise deal terms, with concerns surfacing over potential geopolitical commitments and the sustainability of this upward momentum.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825b53f5a3f0ebac981ca4_1770151697149.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lloyds Metals posts 204% revenue jump; plans ₹8,000 Cr pipeline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Metals-posts-204percent-revenue-jump-plans-8000-Cr-pipeline/69825ae8f5a3f0ebac981aa7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Metals-posts-204percent-revenue-jump-plans-8000-Cr-pipeline/69825ae8f5a3f0ebac981aa7</guid><description>Lloyds Metals &amp; Energy Limited posted stellar Q3 FY26 results with consolidated revenue soaring 204.5% YoY to ₹5,155.31 Cr and PAT surging 181.3% YoY to ₹1,089.56 Cr, driven by a new 'MOO Operation' segment. The company also unveiled ambitious expansion plans including an ₹8,000 Cr Slurry Pipeline Project, capacity enhancements for pellet plants, and significant international acquisitions in Singapore and South Africa to bolster its global presence. However, consolidated finance costs ballooned to ₹152.37 Cr due to increased debt for these growth initiatives.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:46:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825ae8f5a3f0ebac981aa6_1770151614357.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pushes HSR Ambition Amidst Doubled Costs and New Corridor Spree</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Pushes-HSR-Ambition-Amidst-Doubled-Costs-and-New-Corridor-Spree/69825afff5a3f0ebac981ba1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Pushes-HSR-Ambition-Amidst-Doubled-Costs-and-New-Corridor-Spree/69825afff5a3f0ebac981ba1</guid><description>The Mumbai-Ahmedabad High Speed Rail project achieved a tunnel breakthrough in Palghar, Maharashtra. This engineering milestone occurs as the project's cost has nearly doubled to ₹1.98 lakh crore, with completion now slated for December 2029. Concurrently, the Union Budget 2026-27 announced seven new high-speed rail corridors, collectively estimated at ₹16 lakh crore, signaling a massive national push for high-speed connectivity despite persistent challenges in project execution and financing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:46:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825afff5a3f0ebac981ba0_1770151599656.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ADF Foods Posts Record Revenue &amp; Profit, Margins Expand Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ADF-Foods-Posts-Record-Revenue-and-Profit-Margins-Expand-Sharply/69825ad5f5a3f0ebac9819bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ADF-Foods-Posts-Record-Revenue-and-Profit-Margins-Expand-Sharply/69825ad5f5a3f0ebac9819bb</guid><description>ADF Foods Limited reported stellar Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue up 29.5% YoY to ₹191 Cr and EBITDA climbing 40.6% to ₹37.1 Cr. EBITDA margins expanded 150 bps to 19.4%, while PAT surged 55.7%. Management cited strong brand traction and US business growth as drivers, with the Surat facility set to boost future capacity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825ad5f5a3f0ebac9819ba_1770151506525.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lloyds Metals Surges on 190% Revenue Growth Amid Expansion Spree</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Lloyds-Metals-Surges-on-190percent-Revenue-Growth-Amid-Expansion-Spree/69825a85f5a3f0ebac981881</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Lloyds-Metals-Surges-on-190percent-Revenue-Growth-Amid-Expansion-Spree/69825a85f5a3f0ebac981881</guid><description>Lloyds Metals and Energy Limited reported stellar Q3 FY2026 results with consolidated revenue soaring 190% YoY to ₹4,909.38 crore and PAT jumping 180% YoY to ₹1,089.56 crore. The company also greenlit major expansion plans including an ₹8,000 crore Slurry Pipeline Project, pellet plant capacity hikes, and international acquisitions in Singapore and South Africa. A note highlighted 'Emphasis of Matter' on ₹481 crore disputed receivables from NTPC.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825a85f5a3f0ebac981880_1770151411183.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rashi Peripherals Surges on 132% Q3 Profit Jump, Appoints New CEO</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Rashi-Peripherals-Surges-on-132percent-Q3-Profit-Jump-Appoints-New-CEO/69825a7af5a3f0ebac9817ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Rashi-Peripherals-Surges-on-132percent-Q3-Profit-Jump-Appoints-New-CEO/69825a7af5a3f0ebac9817ff</guid><description>Rashi Peripherals reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated PAT surging 132.6% YoY to ₹745.94 million, driven by a 42.6% revenue jump. The company also approved key appointments including Rajesh Goenka as Whole-Time Director &amp; CEO and the formation of a UAE subsidiary. Nine-month performance also showed healthy PAT growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:42:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825a7af5a3f0ebac9817fe_1770151333543.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Satin Creditcare Posts 404% PAT Surge, Eyes 15% FY27 AUM Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Satin-Creditcare-Posts-404percent-PAT-Surge-Eyes-15percent-FY27-AUM-Growth/69825a5af5a3f0ebac9816e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Satin-Creditcare-Posts-404percent-PAT-Surge-Eyes-15percent-FY27-AUM-Growth/69825a5af5a3f0ebac9816e1</guid><description>Satin Creditcare Network Limited (SCNL) reported a robust Q3 FY26 with a 404% YoY PAT jump to ₹72 crore and 10% AUM growth to ₹13,341 crore. The company achieved its 18th consecutive profitable quarter, targeting reduced credit costs and 10-15% MFI AUM growth in FY27. Strategic tech acquisition and de-risking initiatives are also underway.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:40:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825a5af5a3f0ebac9816e0_1770151222163.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCMIL Q3 Profit Surges 47% on Margin Gains Amid Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MCMIL-Q3-Profit-Surges-47percent-on-Margin-Gains-Amid-Expansion/69825a08f5a3f0ebac981560</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MCMIL-Q3-Profit-Surges-47percent-on-Margin-Gains-Amid-Expansion/69825a08f5a3f0ebac981560</guid><description>Manaksia Coated Metals (MCMIL) reported a strong Q3 FY26 with Net Profit soaring 46.71% YoY to ₹7.35 Cr, driven by EBITDA growth and margin expansion to 9.90%, despite an 8.62% revenue dip due to a planned shutdown. The 9M FY26 performance was even more robust, with Net Profit jumping 241.25% YoY. The company commissioned a new Alu-Zinc line and targets significant EBITDA growth, while successfully reducing its debt-to-equity ratio to 0.32.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:37:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825a08f5a3f0ebac98155f_1770151074945.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TAC Infosec: CyberScope IPO Fuels High Growth, But Valuation Gaps Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TAC-Infosec-CyberScope-IPO-Fuels-High-Growth-But-Valuation-Gaps-Emerge/698259f4f5a3f0ebac981481</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TAC-Infosec-CyberScope-IPO-Fuels-High-Growth-But-Valuation-Gaps-Emerge/698259f4f5a3f0ebac981481</guid><description>TAC Infosec added over 600 clients in January 2026, extending its base to nearly 8,000 since April 2024. The company is propelling its global expansion via its ESOF, Socify, and CyberScope platforms. A key strategic move is CyberScope's F-1 filing for a U.S. IPO, aiming to pioneer the publicly listed Web3 security sector. Despite this rapid client acquisition and forward-looking strategy, TAC Infosec trades at a premium valuation, with its P/E ratio significantly exceeding that of larger IT sector peers. This suggests investors are pricing in substantial future growth, driven by its AI-focused 2030 vision and the potential standalone value of CyberScope.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:35:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698259f4f5a3f0ebac981480_1770150934942.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lloyds Metals Posts Stellar Q3, Unveils ₹8,000 Cr Pipeline &amp; Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Metals-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Unveils-8000-Cr-Pipeline-and-Global-Expansion/698259e5f5a3f0ebac9813e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Metals-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Unveils-8000-Cr-Pipeline-and-Global-Expansion/698259e5f5a3f0ebac9813e9</guid><description>Lloyds Metals and Energy Ltd. reported exceptional Q3 FY26 results with standalone revenue soaring 124% YoY to ₹3,800.79 Cr and consolidated revenue jumping 204% YoY to ₹5,155.31 Cr. The company's Board also approved strategic initiatives including an ₹8,000 Crore slurry pipeline, capacity expansions, and international acquisitions in Singapore and South Africa.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698259e5f5a3f0ebac9813e8_1770150798655.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Andhra Pradesh Secures Billions in Global Investment Deals at WEF Davos</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Andhra-Pradesh-Secures-Billions-in-Global-Investment-Deals-at-WEF-Davos/6982599af5a3f0ebac9812ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Andhra-Pradesh-Secures-Billions-in-Global-Investment-Deals-at-WEF-Davos/6982599af5a3f0ebac9812ef</guid><description>Andhra Pradesh aggressively pitched its investment potential at the World Economic Forum 2026 in Davos. The delegation, led by Chief Minister N. Chandrababu Naidu, secured significant global commitments, including Google's largest AI data center outside the US, a ₹1 lakh crore steel plant by ArcelorMittal Nippon Steel, and a $10 billion Green Ammonia project by AM Green. The state highlighted 25 new industrial policies to attract ₹22 lakh crore investments and create 20 lakh jobs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:33:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982599af5a3f0ebac9812ee_1770150823227.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kansai Nerolac Profit Plummets 82% on ₹44.7 Cr Labour Code Hit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kansai-Nerolac-Profit-Plummets-82percent-on-447-Cr-Labour-Code-Hit/69825984f5a3f0ebac981224</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kansai-Nerolac-Profit-Plummets-82percent-on-447-Cr-Labour-Code-Hit/69825984f5a3f0ebac981224</guid><description>Kansai Nerolac Paints reported a dramatic 82.2% year-on-year decline in net profit for Q3 FY26, falling to ₹121 crore from ₹680 crore. This sharp profitability drop occurred despite a marginal 3.1% revenue increase to ₹1,928 crore. A significant factor was a ₹44.7 crore impact from new labour codes. EBITDA margins also saw a slight contraction to 11.6%. While industrial coatings showed strength, the overall results highlight significant pressure on the bottom line.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:30:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69825984f5a3f0ebac981223_1770150630353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lloyds Metals Skyrockets 193% Revenue, Approves ₹8,000 Cr Pipeline Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Lloyds-Metals-Skyrockets-193percent-Revenue-Approves-8000-Cr-Pipeline-Project/6982596df5a3f0ebac98118b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Lloyds-Metals-Skyrockets-193percent-Revenue-Approves-8000-Cr-Pipeline-Project/6982596df5a3f0ebac98118b</guid><description>Lloyds Metals and Energy Limited reported a phenomenal Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue jumping 193.84% YoY to ₹4,909.38 Cr and PAT soaring 117.41% YoY to ₹1,089.56 Cr. The company also greenlit significant strategic initiatives including a ₹8,000 Cr slurry pipeline, pellet plant capacity expansion, new Maharashtra subsidiary, and international acquisitions in Singapore and South Africa. The board also addressed a contingent liability from a dispute with NTPC.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:30:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982596df5a3f0ebac98118a_1770150616685.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aye Finance IPO: Rs 1,010 Cr Issue Opens Feb 9 Amid Mixed Financials</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aye-Finance-IPO-Rs-1010-Cr-Issue-Opens-Feb-9-Amid-Mixed-Financials/6982592af5a3f0ebac981017</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aye-Finance-IPO-Rs-1010-Cr-Issue-Opens-Feb-9-Amid-Mixed-Financials/6982592af5a3f0ebac981017</guid><description>Aye Finance, backed by Elevation Capital and Alphabet's CapitalG, is set to launch its ₹1,010 crore IPO on February 9. The public issue comprises a ₹710 crore fresh issue and a ₹300 crore offer-for-sale. While net profit declined 40% for the six months ended September 2025, the NBFC reported a 15.6% rise in net interest income. Proceeds will bolster its capital base for future growth, targeting India's underserved MSME sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:28:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982592af5a3f0ebac981016_1770150507983.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ACE Q3 PAT Up 4.2% Despite Revenue Dip; Eyes Infra Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ACE-Q3-PAT-Up-42percent-Despite-Revenue-Dip-Eyes-Infra-Boom/6982591bf5a3f0ebac980fbc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ACE-Q3-PAT-Up-42percent-Despite-Revenue-Dip-Eyes-Infra-Boom/6982591bf5a3f0ebac980fbc</guid><description>Action Construction Equipment (ACE) reported a Q3 FY26 PAT of INR 1,164 Mn, up 4.2% YoY, despite a 1.6% YoY revenue decline to INR 8,904 Mn. This dip was attributed to a high base effect from FY25 pre-buying. Margins expanded YoY, with EBITDA margin at 18.59% (+35 bps) and PAT margin at 13.07% (+73 bps), driven by favourable product mix and cost efficiencies. For 9M-FY26, PAT rose 4.6% YoY to INR 3,042 Mn on flat revenues. The company is bullish on India's infrastructure growth and has launched AI-assisted products.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982591bf5a3f0ebac980fbb_1770150346626.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC Sends Flipkart Probe Back, Cites Procedural Flaws</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-Sends-Flipkart-Probe-Back-Cites-Procedural-Flaws/698258f5f5a3f0ebac980ef1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-Sends-Flipkart-Probe-Back-Cites-Procedural-Flaws/698258f5f5a3f0ebac980ef1</guid><description>The Supreme Court has vacated a 2020 NCLAT order directing a Competition Commission of India probe into Flipkart's alleged competition law violations. Remanding the case for fresh adjudication, the apex court cited Flipkart's argument that the NCLAT's decision relied on income tax assessment findings later overturned by the ITAT. This ruling re-emphasizes procedural fairness and evidentiary rigor in Indian e-commerce regulatory investigations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:25:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698258f5f5a3f0ebac980ef0_1770150318864.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exide Industries Eyes EU/US Premium Battery Market Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Exide-Industries-Eyes-EUUS-Premium-Battery-Market-Surge/698258cff5a3f0ebac980d85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Exide-Industries-Eyes-EUUS-Premium-Battery-Market-Surge/698258cff5a3f0ebac980d85</guid><description>Exide Industries plans to significantly ramp up exports to the EU and US, targeting Rs 400-500 crore in incremental sales by FY27, a 25% annual growth. The strategy focuses on premium car segment batteries, leveraging the India-EU trade deal and US tariff adjustments. The company aims to recover export market share lost during periods of high tariffs, supplying advanced AGM and forklift batteries. This move positions Exide to capitalize on evolving trade policies and demand for high-performance energy storage solutions in developed economies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:24:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698258cff5a3f0ebac980d84_1770150280124.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exide Eyes Export Revival Amidst Domestic Divergence and Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Exide-Eyes-Export-Revival-Amidst-Domestic-Divergence-and-Margin-Gains/6982587df5a3f0ebac980b67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Exide-Eyes-Export-Revival-Amidst-Domestic-Divergence-and-Margin-Gains/6982587df5a3f0ebac980b67</guid><description>Exide Industries is targeting an increase in its overseas business to 8-9% of turnover by fiscal year-end 2027, driven by favourable trade agreements with the US and EU and an exclusive European partnership. This export push aims to generate an additional ₹400-500 crore in revenue. While the company reported strong growth in its auto OEM and replacement markets, one segment experienced a significant decline, offsetting overall domestic gains. Concurrently, Exide achieved a sequential EBITDA margin improvement of 221 basis points, supporting ambitious financial targets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:24:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6982587df5a3f0ebac980b66_1770150194613.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>