<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:39 +0000</pubDate><item><title>IndiGo Grounds 118 Flights: Major India Travel Chaos As Fog Blinds Airports!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Grounds-118-Flights-Major-India-Travel-Chaos-As-Fog-Blinds-Airports/69529b364342f77179dde0cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Grounds-118-Flights-Major-India-Travel-Chaos-As-Fog-Blinds-Airports/69529b364342f77179dde0cf</guid><description>India's largest airline, IndiGo, cancelled 118 flights on Monday due to severe fog and operational issues, impacting major airports like Delhi, Mumbai, and Bengaluru. Passengers faced significant delays and disruptions. The airline cited ongoing foggy conditions in North India, with visibility yet to fully improve, extending flight impacts into the afternoon.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:02:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69529b364342f77179dde0ce_1767021503921.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Petrochemical Profit Squeeze Looms: India Faces Oversupply Shock!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Petrochemical-Profit-Squeeze-Looms-India-Faces-Oversupply-Shock/69529ad84342f77179dddfae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Petrochemical-Profit-Squeeze-Looms-India-Faces-Oversupply-Shock/69529ad84342f77179dddfae</guid><description>Indian petrochemical firms, particularly in PVC and Polypropylene (PP), are set to significantly expand capacity, with PVC potentially jumping 2.5 times and PP 1.8 times by FY30. However, global oversupply is expected to keep prices and profitability weak in the near term. Profitability will hinge on cost competitiveness, global dynamics, and government support. Recent rescission of Quality Control Orders may boost imports, intensifying competition, though falling crude oil prices offer some respite.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:59:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69529ad84342f77179dddfad_1767021349459.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Barrick Mining's Wild Ride: CEO Exit, Seized Gold Resolution &amp; Strategic IPO Fuel 198% Stock Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Barrick-Minings-Wild-Ride-CEO-Exit-Seized-Gold-Resolution-and-Strategic-IPO-Fuel-198percent-Stock-Surge/69529a044342f77179ddddc6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Barrick-Minings-Wild-Ride-CEO-Exit-Seized-Gold-Resolution-and-Strategic-IPO-Fuel-198percent-Stock-Surge/69529a044342f77179ddddc6</guid><description>Barrick Mining's stock has surged 198% after CEO Mark Bristow's departure and the resolution of a crisis in Mali where $400 million in gold was seized. The company plans to IPO its premium North American assets, including the Fourmile discovery, following strong Q3 financial results with doubled net earnings and significant cash flow. This move aims to unlock shareholder value by valuing prime assets separately.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:59:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69529a044342f77179ddddc5_1767021301112.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Renewable Future Surge! Danish Giant Baettr Invests ₹73 Crore, Quadruples Wind Turbine Capacity in Tamil Nadu</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Indias-Renewable-Future-Surge-Danish-Giant-Baettr-Invests-73-Crore-Quadruples-Wind-Turbine-Capacity-in-Tamil-Nadu/695299364342f77179dddb20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Indias-Renewable-Future-Surge-Danish-Giant-Baettr-Invests-73-Crore-Quadruples-Wind-Turbine-Capacity-in-Tamil-Nadu/695299364342f77179dddb20</guid><description>Danish renewable energy firm Baettr is expanding its wind turbine casting facility in Tamil Nadu, India. The expansion involves a ₹73 crore investment, bringing the total to ₹280 crore. Licensed production capacity will nearly quadruple from 27,500 to 95,040 tonnes per annum. This move supports growing demand from wind turbine manufacturers and strengthens Tamil Nadu's position as a renewable energy hub.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:57:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695299364342f77179dddb1f_1767020952716.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Mutual Fund Sells ₹108 Cr Nazara Shares; Gaming Firm Posts Loss Despite Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SBI-Mutual-Fund-Sells-108-Cr-Nazara-Shares-Gaming-Firm-Posts-Loss-Despite-Revenue-Surge/695298ed4342f77179ddda93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SBI-Mutual-Fund-Sells-108-Cr-Nazara-Shares-Gaming-Firm-Posts-Loss-Despite-Revenue-Surge/695298ed4342f77179ddda93</guid><description>SBI Mutual Fund divested shares worth approximately ₹108.3 crore in Nazara Technologies through a block deal on December 29, selling 45.09 lakh shares. This occurs as Nazara Technologies reported a net loss of ₹33.9 crore for Q2 FY26, largely due to a significant impairment of its investment in real-money gaming startup Pokerbaazi. Despite the loss and the impact of the real money gaming ban, the company's operating revenue surged by 65% year-on-year to ₹526.5 crore, and it continues its acquisition strategy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:56:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695298ed4342f77179ddda92_1767021025761.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blackstone Powerhouse Horizon Industrial Files Massive ₹2,600 Cr IPO: Investors Watch Closely!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Blackstone-Powerhouse-Horizon-Industrial-Files-Massive-2600-Cr-IPO-Investors-Watch-Closely/6952978e4342f77179ddd77f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Blackstone-Powerhouse-Horizon-Industrial-Files-Massive-2600-Cr-IPO-Investors-Watch-Closely/6952978e4342f77179ddd77f</guid><description>Horizon Industrial Parks, backed by global private equity firm Blackstone, has filed preliminary papers with Sebi for a ₹2,600 crore Initial Public Offering (IPO). The issue consists entirely of fresh equity shares, with approximately ₹2,250 crore earmarked for repaying borrowings. The company is a significant industrial and logistics developer, owning and operating a pan-India portfolio of 60 million square feet across 46 assets. Blackstone currently holds an 89% stake in the company.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:52:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952978e4342f77179ddd77e_1767020685533.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Grasim Industries Powers Up Renewable Energy Hub: Board Approves Major Consolidation Move!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Grasim-Industries-Powers-Up-Renewable-Energy-Hub-Board-Approves-Major-Consolidation-Move/695293e34342f77179ddd093</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Grasim-Industries-Powers-Up-Renewable-Energy-Hub-Board-Approves-Major-Consolidation-Move/695293e34342f77179ddd093</guid><description>Grasim Industries Limited has announced its board's approval for a comprehensive scheme of arrangement to consolidate its renewable energy assets. This strategic move involves transferring Essel Mining &amp; Industries Ltd's renewable undertaking and amalgamating subsidiaries like Electrotherm Renewables Private Ltd into Aditya Birla Renewables Ltd. The objective is to create a unified, efficient, and scaled renewable energy platform, pending necessary regulatory and shareholder approvals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:34:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695293e34342f77179ddd092_1767019564498.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PM Modi, FM Sitharaman Meet Economists: Key Budget &amp; Growth Reforms on the Table!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PM-Modi-FM-Sitharaman-Meet-Economists-Key-Budget-and-Growth-Reforms-on-the-Table/695294094342f77179ddd116</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PM-Modi-FM-Sitharaman-Meet-Economists-Key-Budget-and-Growth-Reforms-on-the-Table/695294094342f77179ddd116</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi and Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman convened with leading economists and experts at NITI Aayog on December 30. The crucial meeting focused on consultations for the upcoming Union Budget, discussing economic situations, future priorities, growth support reforms, macroeconomic stability, and the domestic and global economic outlook. This pre-Budget exercise aims to gather diverse inputs for effective policy making and economic planning.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:34:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695294094342f77179ddd115_1767021422938.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lupin Bags China Deal for Breakthrough Diabetes &amp; Weight Loss Drug: Huge Potential for India?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Bags-China-Deal-for-Breakthrough-Diabetes-and-Weight-Loss-Drug-Huge-Potential-for-India/695293e34342f77179ddd0be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Bags-China-Deal-for-Breakthrough-Diabetes-and-Weight-Loss-Drug-Huge-Potential-for-India/695293e34342f77179ddd0be</guid><description>Drug firm Lupin Ltd. has entered an exclusive agreement with China-based Gan &amp; Lee Pharmaceuticals for bofanglutide, a novel fortnightly GLP-1 drug for type 2 diabetes and weight management in India. This partnership aims to bolster Lupin's chronic disease portfolio, addressing the significant prevalence of diabetes and obesity in the country. The drug offers convenient bi-weekly dosing and comparable efficacy to existing treatments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:34:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695293e34342f77179ddd0bd_1767019636679.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Hotel Boom: 20% Room Surge Expected, But Will Demand Keep Pace? Investors on Alert!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indias-Hotel-Boom-20percent-Room-Surge-Expected-But-Will-Demand-Keep-Pace-Investors-on-Alert/6952930d4342f77179ddce2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indias-Hotel-Boom-20percent-Room-Surge-Expected-But-Will-Demand-Keep-Pace-Investors-on-Alert/6952930d4342f77179ddce2a</guid><description>India's branded hotel sector is set for a significant expansion, with nearly 20,000 new rooms expected over the next two fiscal years, a 20% supply increase. Despite this surge, demand is projected to outpace supply, keeping occupancies steady at 74-75% and pushing average room rates up by 5-7%. Much of this expansion will come from hotel developers using an asset-light management contract model. Growth in domestic tourism, particularly in tier 2 and 3 cities, is fueling this development.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:28:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952930d4342f77179ddce29_1767019588121.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's ATMs Shrink as Digital Payments Surge: RBI Report Reveals Major Banking Shift!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-ATMs-Shrink-as-Digital-Payments-Surge-RBI-Report-Reveals-Major-Banking-Shift/6952929f4342f77179ddcd69</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-ATMs-Shrink-as-Digital-Payments-Surge-RBI-Report-Reveals-Major-Banking-Shift/6952929f4342f77179ddcd69</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's FY25 report shows a decline in ATM numbers, dropping to 2,51,057 from 2,53,417. This trend is driven by increased digitalization and customer preference for digital payments, leading both private and public sector banks to reduce their offsite ATM networks. Meanwhile, bank branches grew by over 2% to 1.64 lakh, with public sector banks leading expansion, particularly in rural areas. Independently operated white-label ATMs also saw an increase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:27:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952929f4342f77179ddcd68_1767019457346.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CERC Unleashes Probe: Power Transmission Giants Face Fury Over Missed Reports!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/CERC-Unleashes-Probe-Power-Transmission-Giants-Face-Fury-Over-Missed-Reports/695292444342f77179ddcc8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/CERC-Unleashes-Probe-Power-Transmission-Giants-Face-Fury-Over-Missed-Reports/695292444342f77179ddcc8e</guid><description>The Central Electricity Regulatory Commission (CERC) has expressed strong displeasure towards Inter-State Transmission System (ISTS) licensees for failing to submit crucial performance statistics and compensation data. In a suo motu order, CERC issued show-cause notices to these licensees, highlighting a widespread non-compliance with reporting regulations, with many failing to provide data for multiple financial years. Penalties under the Electricity Act, 2003, are now being considered.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:25:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695292444342f77179ddcc8d_1767021309906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Textile Mills in Crisis: TASMA Urges Government for 2-Year Export Obligation Extension Amidst US Tariff Pressure!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indian-Textile-Mills-in-Crisis-TASMA-Urges-Government-for-2-Year-Export-Obligation-Extension-Amidst-US-Tariff-Pressure/695291804342f77179ddca7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indian-Textile-Mills-in-Crisis-TASMA-Urges-Government-for-2-Year-Export-Obligation-Extension-Amidst-US-Tariff-Pressure/695291804342f77179ddca7c</guid><description>The Spinning Association (TASMA) has requested Commerce Minister Piyush Goyal to grant a two-year extension for export obligations under the Advance Authorisation Scheme (AAS) without imposing composition fees. This plea comes as US tariffs and global geopolitical uncertainty have made exports of cotton yarn and knitted fabrics unremunerative for Indian spinning mills. TASMA also seeks a reduction in the value-addition norm from 15% to 5% to support the labour-intensive textile industry.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:24:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695291804342f77179ddca7b_1767021201529.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>"Dr Doom" Peter Schiff: Gold is a "Steal" at $4,534; Silver Faces Short-Term Risk!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Dr-Doom-Peter-Schiff-Gold-is-a-Steal-at-4534-Silver-Faces-Short-Term-Risk/695290974342f77179ddc86f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Dr-Doom-Peter-Schiff-Gold-is-a-Steal-at-4534-Silver-Faces-Short-Term-Risk/695290974342f77179ddc86f</guid><description>Renowned economist Peter Schiff, known for predicting the 2008 financial crisis, advises investors to buy gold, calling it a "steal" at $4,534 with minimal risk. However, he urges caution on silver due to its recent volatility, suggesting a wait for consolidation. Silver has significantly outperformed gold year-to-date, surging 181% versus gold's 72%.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:20:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695290974342f77179ddc86e_1767021083678.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's ULI Platform Explodes: 64 Lenders Onboarded, Revolutionizing India's Credit Landscape!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-ULI-Platform-Explodes-64-Lenders-Onboarded-Revolutionizing-Indias-Credit-Landscape/69528cec4342f77179dd6b7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-ULI-Platform-Explodes-64-Lenders-Onboarded-Revolutionizing-Indias-Credit-Landscape/69528cec4342f77179dd6b7b</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Unified Lending Interface (ULI) platform has seen a significant surge, onboarding 64 lenders, up from 36 last year. This digital infrastructure now includes 41 banks and 23 non-banking financial companies (NBFCs). These lenders are utilizing over 136 data services across 12 loan journeys to enhance credit assessment and decision-making, marking a major step in digital lending.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:04:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69528cec4342f77179dd6b7a_1767017855982.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Navi Mumbai Water Crisis Solved Sooner? Afcons Achieves Historic Tunnel Milestone, Finishes Project 6 Months Early!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Navi-Mumbai-Water-Crisis-Solved-Sooner-Afcons-Achieves-Historic-Tunnel-Milestone-Finishes-Project-6-Months-Early/69528c164342f77179dd6957</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Navi-Mumbai-Water-Crisis-Solved-Sooner-Afcons-Achieves-Historic-Tunnel-Milestone-Finishes-Project-6-Months-Early/69528c164342f77179dd6957</guid><description>Afcons Infrastructure Ltd has announced a significant achievement for CIDCO's Hetawane Water Supply Scheme in Navi Mumbai, completing the first water tunnel breakthrough. The company expects to finish the entire project six months ahead of schedule. This critical initiative will substantially increase water supply capacity for Navi Mumbai's growing areas and marks a historic first for CIDCO projects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:03:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69528c164342f77179dd6956_1767017567369.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Powers Up: Massive 3.05 GW Solar Inverter Facility Launched in Gujarat!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Waaree-Energies-Powers-Up-Massive-305-GW-Solar-Inverter-Facility-Launched-in-Gujarat/69528c5f4342f77179dd6a13</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Waaree-Energies-Powers-Up-Massive-305-GW-Solar-Inverter-Facility-Launched-in-Gujarat/69528c5f4342f77179dd6a13</guid><description>Waaree Energies Ltd. announced its subsidiary, Waaree Power Private Ltd., has successfully commissioned a 3.05 GW solar inverter manufacturing facility in Gujarat. Commercial operations began December 29, 2025, expanding the company's renewable energy manufacturing capabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:03:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69528c5f4342f77179dd6a12_1767020984911.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>98% Digital! RBI's Grip Tightens on India's Payments Ecosystem - Are You Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/98percent-Digital-RBIs-Grip-Tightens-on-Indias-Payments-Ecosystem-Are-You-Ready/69528c3e4342f77179dd69c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/98percent-Digital-RBIs-Grip-Tightens-on-Indias-Payments-Ecosystem-Are-You-Ready/69528c3e4342f77179dd69c9</guid><description>India's digital payments have surged to 97.6% of total transaction value in 2024-25, with paper instruments like cheques now at just 2.4%. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is intensifying regulatory oversight across the payment ecosystem to ensure security and efficiency. Key measures include new guidelines for Payment Aggregators and stricter norms for the Aadhaar Enabled Payment System (AePS), alongside efforts to expand UPI's global reach. This reflects a strategic move to manage risks amidst rapid digital adoption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:00:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69528c3e4342f77179dd69c8_1767020939075.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Captain Fresh's $400M IPO Dreams Delayed! What's Holding Back This Seafood Giant?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Captain-Freshs-400M-IPO-Dreams-Delayed-Whats-Holding-Back-This-Seafood-Giant/69528a364342f77179dd0442</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Captain-Freshs-400M-IPO-Dreams-Delayed-Whats-Holding-Back-This-Seafood-Giant/69528a364342f77179dd0442</guid><description>Captain Fresh's parent company, Infifresh Foods Ltd, has withdrawn its draft IPO papers filed for a $400 million offering. The withdrawal, occurring on December 24, is attributed by founder Utham Gowda to unexpected delays in obtaining regulatory approvals for a recent European acquisition. The company aims to refile its IPO documents in early 2026 once these approvals are secured.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:52:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69528a364342f77179dd0441_1767020719994.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Exports to Australia Skyrocket 8% – What This Landmark Trade Deal Means for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Exports-to-Australia-Skyrocket-8percent-What-This-Landmark-Trade-Deal-Means-for-Your-Investments/695289704342f77179dd00de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Exports-to-Australia-Skyrocket-8percent-What-This-Landmark-Trade-Deal-Means-for-Your-Investments/695289704342f77179dd00de</guid><description>India's exports to Australia grew 8% in FY 2024-25, marking three successful years of the India-Australia Economic Cooperation and Trade Agreement (ECTA). Union Minister Piyush Goyal highlighted significant gains across manufacturing, gems, jewellery, and agriculture sectors. From January 1, 2026, 100% of Australian tariff lines will be zero-duty for Indian goods, opening substantial new opportunities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:50:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695289704342f77179dd00dd_1767017072896.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jail for Tax Lapses? India Eyes Radical Shift! NITI Aayog's Decriminalization Plan for Budget 2026 Sparks Investor Buzz!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jail-for-Tax-Lapses-India-Eyes-Radical-Shift-NITI-Aayogs-Decriminalization-Plan-for-Budget-2026-Sparks-Investor-Buzz/695288ce4342f77179dcff48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jail-for-Tax-Lapses-India-Eyes-Radical-Shift-NITI-Aayogs-Decriminalization-Plan-for-Budget-2026-Sparks-Investor-Buzz/695288ce4342f77179dcff48</guid><description>NITI Aayog has proposed significant reforms to decriminalize many income tax offenses, shifting India towards a trust-based compliance regime. The working paper suggests moving away from criminalizing technical or procedural lapses, focusing instead on genuine fraud. This aims to reduce fear, boost investment, and align with international practices. These proposals are expected to be considered for Budget 2026, marking a potential major overhaul of India's tax enforcement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:49:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695288ce4342f77179dcff47_1767020597880.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks' Bad Loan Recovery Soars! RBI Data Reveals Stunning 37% Rise Via IBC</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Bad-Loan-Recovery-Soars-RBI-Data-Reveals-Stunning-37percent-Rise-Via-IBC/695287584342f77179dcfc4b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Bad-Loan-Recovery-Soars-RBI-Data-Reveals-Stunning-37percent-Rise-Via-IBC/695287584342f77179dcfc4b</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India data indicates a significant improvement in bank recovery rates for bad assets in fiscal year 2024-25. Recoveries under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC) rose to nearly 37%, up from 28.3% the previous year. The Securitisation and Reconstruction of Financial Assets and Enforcement of Security Interest (Sarfaesi) Act also saw improved recoveries at 31.5%. This happened despite a reduction in the number of cases referred for resolution under both key mechanisms. Asset reconstruction companies also showed stronger performance in redeeming security receipts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:32:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695287584342f77179dcfc4a_1767020356352.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold's Explosive 70% Surge in 2025: Will the Rally Continue in 2026? Expert Reveals Shocking Structural Reasons!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Explosive-70percent-Surge-in-2025-Will-the-Rally-Continue-in-2026-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-Structural-Reasons/695287f64342f77179dcfdce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Explosive-70percent-Surge-in-2025-Will-the-Rally-Continue-in-2026-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-Structural-Reasons/695287f64342f77179dcfdce</guid><description>Gold prices have skyrocketed by nearly 70% in 2025, driven by long-term global economic shifts rather than temporary geopolitical events, according to Kaushalendra Sinha, CEO of the Indian Association of Gold Excellence &amp; Standards (IAGES). He predicts the momentum will continue into 2026. While Indian jewelry demand has softened due to high prices, investment in gold ETFs and portfolio diversification is growing, with gold showing a historical CAGR of over 14% since 2000, outperforming stocks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:32:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695287f64342f77179dcfdcd_1767020477699.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cupid's Saudi Leap: Board Approves FMCG Manufacturing Unit to Fuel Gulf Expansion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cupids-Saudi-Leap-Board-Approves-FMCG-Manufacturing-Unit-to-Fuel-Gulf-Expansion/695286d04342f77179dcfb47</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cupids-Saudi-Leap-Board-Approves-FMCG-Manufacturing-Unit-to-Fuel-Gulf-Expansion/695286d04342f77179dcfb47</guid><description>Cupid Ltd's board has approved setting up a new FMCG manufacturing unit in Saudi Arabia. This strategic move is part of the company's expansion into the Fast-Moving Consumer Goods (FMCG) sector, aiming to boost its presence and supply capabilities across Saudi Arabia and the wider Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) markets. The project will be financed through internal funds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:31:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695286d04342f77179dcfb46_1767020234609.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Aims for 6G World Domination: Minister Scindia's Bold Plan for Global Patent Leadership Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Aims-for-6G-World-Domination-Minister-Scindias-Bold-Plan-for-Global-Patent-Leadership-Revealed/695286654342f77179dcf9e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Aims-for-6G-World-Domination-Minister-Scindias-Bold-Plan-for-Global-Patent-Leadership-Revealed/695286654342f77179dcf9e2</guid><description>Union Telecom Minister Jyotiraditya Scindia revealed India's ambitious plan to lead the global 6G race. The country aims to secure 10% of all worldwide 6G patents when standards are finalized. Through the Bharat 6G Alliance, India is forging collaborations with nations like the US, Korea, Europe, and Africa. This strategic move signifies a shift from adopting previous technologies to pioneering the next generation, aiming for global leadership in 6G standards and innovation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:31:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695286654342f77179dcf9e1_1767016116632.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MicroStrategy Reloads on Bitcoin! Massive $109 Million Acquisition Boosts Holdings to Over 672,000 BTC!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MicroStrategy-Reloads-on-Bitcoin-Massive-109-Million-Acquisition-Boosts-Holdings-to-Over-672000-BTC/695286bd4342f77179dcfb19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MicroStrategy-Reloads-on-Bitcoin-Massive-109-Million-Acquisition-Boosts-Holdings-to-Over-672000-BTC/695286bd4342f77179dcfb19</guid><description>MicroStrategy has resumed its aggressive bitcoin acquisition strategy, purchasing an additional 1,229 bitcoin for approximately $109 million last week at an average price of $88,568 per coin. This latest move, funded by the sale of Class A common stock, brings the company's total bitcoin holdings to an impressive 672,497 BTC, acquired at an average price of $74,997 per bitcoin. The news comes as bitcoin trades around $87,000 and MicroStrategy shares saw a slight dip in pre-market trading, indicating continued institutional commitment to digital assets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:29:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695286bd4342f77179dcfb18_1767016353177.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBFC Credit Growth Surges: Services &amp; Retail Dominate, RBI Report Reveals FY25 Trends</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFC-Credit-Growth-Surges-Services-and-Retail-Dominate-RBI-Report-Reveals-FY25-Trends/695285cf4342f77179dcf7fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFC-Credit-Growth-Surges-Services-and-Retail-Dominate-RBI-Report-Reveals-FY25-Trends/695285cf4342f77179dcf7fb</guid><description>Non-banking financial companies (NBFCs) in India saw strong credit expansion in FY25, according to the Reserve Bank of India. Industry and retail loans together formed over 81% of total lending, with services emerging as the fastest-growing segment, up 29.8%. The power sector remains the largest industry recipient, though its share slightly decreased. Overall NBFC advances reached ₹48.39 lakh crore, while retail loan growth moderated due to increased risk weights on select segments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:28:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695285cf4342f77179dcf7fa_1767020002002.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blinkit CFO Jumps Ship to Flipkart Ahead of Mega IPO – What It Means for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Blinkit-CFO-Jumps-Ship-to-Flipkart-Ahead-of-Mega-IPO-What-It-Means-for-Investors/695285ab4342f77179dcf7a4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Blinkit-CFO-Jumps-Ship-to-Flipkart-Ahead-of-Mega-IPO-What-It-Means-for-Investors/695285ab4342f77179dcf7a4</guid><description>Vipin Kapooria, the Chief Financial Officer of Blinkit, has resigned after just a year in the role. Sources indicate he is returning to his former employer, Flipkart, where he previously held multiple positions. This move comes as Flipkart gears up for a potential Initial Public Offering (IPO) in 2026, and amid fierce competition in the quick commerce sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:28:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695285ab4342f77179dcf7a3_1767019888718.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Greenlights Four IPOs: Varmora Granito, Knack Packaging &amp; More Gear Up for Market Launch!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/SEBI-Greenlights-Four-IPOs-Varmora-Granito-Knack-Packaging-and-More-Gear-Up-for-Market-Launch/695285eb4342f77179dcf84a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/SEBI-Greenlights-Four-IPOs-Varmora-Granito-Knack-Packaging-and-More-Gear-Up-for-Market-Launch/695285eb4342f77179dcf84a</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has given its approval for Initial Public Offerings (IPOs) from Varmora Granito, Knack Packaging, Shivalaya Construction, and Behari Lal Engineering. These companies can now launch their IPOs within the next year. Meanwhile, Infifresh Foods has withdrawn its confidential draft IPO papers. Varmora Granito aims to raise Rs 400 crore, Knack Packaging Rs 475 crore, Shivalaya Construction Rs 450 crore, and Behari Lal Engineering Rs 110 crore through fresh issuances, with promoters/investors also offloading shares.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:28:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695285eb4342f77179dcf849_1767020115715.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cement Giants Merge! Ambuja Cements Strikes Deal with Orient Cement for Massive Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Giants-Merge-Ambuja-Cements-Strikes-Deal-with-Orient-Cement-for-Massive-Consolidation/695284ec4342f77179dcf5bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Giants-Merge-Ambuja-Cements-Strikes-Deal-with-Orient-Cement-for-Massive-Consolidation/695284ec4342f77179dcf5bf</guid><description>Ambuja Cements Limited and Orient Cement Limited are set to merge in a significant industry consolidation. The deal involves Ambuja Cements issuing its own shares to the shareholders of Orient Cement, with Ambuja's existing stake in Orient being cancelled. The law firm Cyril Amarchand Mangaldas advised both companies on this strategic transaction. This merger follows Ambuja's ongoing integration with ACC Cement, signaling a major push for scale in the Indian cement market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:27:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695284ec4342f77179dcf5be_1767019261704.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Aviation Braces for Massive ₹18,000 Crore Loss in FY26 as ICRA Slashes Traffic Forecast!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Aviation-Braces-for-Massive-18000-Crore-Loss-in-FY26-as-ICRA-Slashes-Traffic-Forecast/695285154342f77179dcf66a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Aviation-Braces-for-Massive-18000-Crore-Loss-in-FY26-as-ICRA-Slashes-Traffic-Forecast/695285154342f77179dcf66a</guid><description>ICRA has drastically revised its forecast for the Indian aviation industry, now estimating a net loss of ₹17,000-18,000 crore for FY26, significantly higher than the previous projection. This downgrade is attributed to a projected slowdown in domestic air passenger traffic growth to just 0-3%, down from 4-6%. Factors contributing to this grim outlook include geopolitical tensions, operational disruptions like IndiGo's mass flight cancellations, and the impact of the Air India aircraft incident on traveler sentiment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:25:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695285154342f77179dcf669_1767019749992.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gaurs Group Lands ₹440 Crore Funding Boost: Expansion and Debt Consolidation on the Horizon!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Gaurs-Group-Lands-440-Crore-Funding-Boost-Expansion-and-Debt-Consolidation-on-the-Horizon/695284794342f77179dcf477</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Gaurs-Group-Lands-440-Crore-Funding-Boost-Expansion-and-Debt-Consolidation-on-the-Horizon/695284794342f77179dcf477</guid><description>Gaurs Group's holding company, Gaursons India Private Limited, has successfully raised ₹440 crore through the issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs), which will be listed on the National Stock Exchange (NSE). This capital infusion, arranged by Kotak Mahindra Bank, is earmarked for business expansion, land acquisition, project execution, and repayment of higher-cost borrowings, bolstering the group's financial resilience and flexibility. ICRA projects a 30-32% collection improvement for the group in FY2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:25:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695284794342f77179dcf476_1767019158426.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Cracks Down: New Rules to End Financial Mis-selling &amp; Digital Scams!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Cracks-Down-New-Rules-to-End-Financial-Mis-selling-and-Digital-Scams/6952846b4342f77179dcf436</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Cracks-Down-New-Rules-to-End-Financial-Mis-selling-and-Digital-Scams/6952846b4342f77179dcf436</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is set to release comprehensive guidelines to prevent the mis-selling of financial products and services. This move, detailed in the Report on Trend and Progress of Banking in India 2024-25, aims to bolster customer protection by tightening advertising, marketing, and sales practices. The RBI is also enhancing measures against digital fraud, including initiatives like MuleHunter.ai and a digital payments intelligence platform, and is reviewing customer liability rules for unauthorized transactions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:23:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952846b4342f77179dcf435_1767015647053.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Insurance Boom Incoming? GST Cut &amp; 100% FDI Set Stage for Major Growth Surge in 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Insurance-Boom-Incoming-GST-Cut-and-100percent-FDI-Set-Stage-for-Major-Growth-Surge-in-2026/695283874342f77179dcf1a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Insurance-Boom-Incoming-GST-Cut-and-100percent-FDI-Set-Stage-for-Major-Growth-Surge-in-2026/695283874342f77179dcf1a7</guid><description>Indian life and health insurers anticipate a significant growth rebound in 2026, driven by a Goods and Services Tax (GST) rate reduction that enhances affordability, and the Insurance Amendment Bill enabling 100% foreign direct investment (FDI). These factors are expected to stimulate both consumer demand and the industry's supply-side capacity. November saw a significant 23% rise in new business premiums for life insurers, signalling a positive trend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:22:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695283874342f77179dcf1a6_1767015514466.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Gaming Revolution: Esports Set to Explode as Real-Money Games Face Ban!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Gaming-Revolution-Esports-Set-to-Explode-as-Real-Money-Games-Face-Ban/695283ea4342f77179dcf294</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Gaming-Revolution-Esports-Set-to-Explode-as-Real-Money-Games-Face-Ban/695283ea4342f77179dcf294</guid><description>India's gaming sector is undergoing a massive transformation in 2025 following the nationwide ban on real-money gaming (RMG) and a new 40% GST on online money games. The 'Promotion and Regulation of Online Gaming Act' (PROGA) has shifted focus to esports, social gaming, and original IP development. Industry leaders like Akshat Rathee of NODWIN Gaming and Animesh Agarwal of S8UL Esports see this as a structural shift towards legitimate career paths and sustainable growth, positioning esports as India's next major youth media engine, with projections for significant CAGR growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:22:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695283ea4342f77179dcf293_1767018949447.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jio, BSNL Win Customer Trust: Vi, Airtel Face Grievance Backlash – Your Telecom Stocks Hang in the Balance!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Jio-BSNL-Win-Customer-Trust-Vi-Airtel-Face-Grievance-Backlash-Your-Telecom-Stocks-Hang-in-the-Balance/6952828f4342f77179dcef23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Jio-BSNL-Win-Customer-Trust-Vi-Airtel-Face-Grievance-Backlash-Your-Telecom-Stocks-Hang-in-the-Balance/6952828f4342f77179dcef23</guid><description>Nearly half of Indian mobile subscribers (47%) experience unresolved issues with their service providers over three years, according to a LocalCircles survey. Vodafone Idea (Vi) and Bharti Airtel report the highest rates of unaddressed complaints, while Reliance Jio and BSNL perform better. Cumbersome complaint processes and persistent issues like network coverage, spam calls, data speed, and billing are major concerns for users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:22:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6952828f4342f77179dcef22_1767019042918.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Breaking: WhiteOak Capital Infuses ₹50 Crore into Tempsens Instruments Ahead of Potential IPO!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Breaking-WhiteOak-Capital-Infuses-50-Crore-into-Tempsens-Instruments-Ahead-of-Potential-IPO/695281ec4342f77179dcee01</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Breaking-WhiteOak-Capital-Infuses-50-Crore-into-Tempsens-Instruments-Ahead-of-Potential-IPO/695281ec4342f77179dcee01</guid><description>WhiteOak Capital India Opportunities Fund has invested ₹50 crore in the pre-IPO funding round of Tempsens Instruments (India). The company, based in Vadodara, specializes in thermal engineering and manufacturing customized temperature sensing solutions, electrical heating solutions, and specialized cables for diverse industries. This investment marks a significant step for Tempsens Instruments as it prepares for future growth and potential public market debut.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:20:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695281ec4342f77179dcee00_1767015176799.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's ₹7.67 Trillion Debt Nightmare: Govt Scrambles to Clear Bank Recovery Backlog!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-767-Trillion-Debt-Nightmare-Govt-Scrambles-to-Clear-Bank-Recovery-Backlog/69527edf4342f77179dce819</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-767-Trillion-Debt-Nightmare-Govt-Scrambles-to-Clear-Bank-Recovery-Backlog/69527edf4342f77179dce819</guid><description>India's Department of Financial Services is organizing a colloquium on December 30, 2025, to address the alarming rise in debt recovery cases pending before Debt Recovery Tribunals (DRTs) and Appellate Tribunals (DRATs). With over 0.137 million cases involving ₹7.49 trillion by September 2025, the meeting aims to find strategies for faster recovery of public funds and stressed assets from public sector banks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:59:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69527edf4342f77179dce818_1767018671245.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nykaa's 2025 Report Reveals Indian Beauty's Bold Shift: Performance Trumps Trends!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nykaas-2025-Report-Reveals-Indian-Beautys-Bold-Shift-Performance-Trumps-Trends/69527e164342f77179dce667</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nykaas-2025-Report-Reveals-Indian-Beautys-Bold-Shift-Performance-Trumps-Trends/69527e164342f77179dce667</guid><description>Nykaa's Beauty Rewind 2025 report highlights a major shift in Indian beauty consumption. Consumers are experimenting rapidly but demanding proven performance and ingredient clarity before committing. Key categories like lipsticks (1,750 sold hourly) and skincare (cleansers, moisturisers) show strong repeat purchases. Korean beauty and ingredient-focused serums are mainstream, while quick-commerce delivery accelerates buying decisions, indicating a market driven by efficacy and routine integration over fleeting trends.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:59:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69527e164342f77179dce666_1767014145642.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RVNL Lands ₹201 Crore Rail Project: A Major Boost for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/RVNL-Lands-201-Crore-Rail-Project-A-Major-Boost-for-Investors/69527d4d4342f77179dce4de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/RVNL-Lands-201-Crore-Rail-Project-A-Major-Boost-for-Investors/69527d4d4342f77179dce4de</guid><description>State-owned Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL) has emerged as the lowest bidder for a significant ₹201.23 crore project from East Coast Railway to set up a 200-wagon capacity periodical overhaul workshop at Kantabanji. The project is to be completed within 18 months. This follows a recent ₹145.35 crore traction power project win from Southern Railway, highlighting RVNL's continuous success in securing key infrastructure contracts and reinforcing its position in the railway sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69527d4d4342f77179dce4dd_1767018569542.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>