<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 01:55:22 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Markets Await Budget: Tax Reforms, Growth Signals Crucial</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Await-Budget-Tax-Reforms-Growth-Signals-Crucial/697ead9b46be08bbe62f69aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Await-Budget-Tax-Reforms-Growth-Signals-Crucial/697ead9b46be08bbe62f69aa</guid><description>Indian markets are treading cautiously ahead of the Union Budget, with a strong consensus among investors and market veterans for significant capital gains tax reforms. Expectations center on standardizing holding periods and potentially reversing recent tax rate adjustments to boost market sentiment. Alongside tax relief, investors anticipate fiscal signals reinforcing GDP growth and corporate earnings recovery. This anticipation occurs against a backdrop of subdued global economic cues, including contraction in China's manufacturing sector, and a recent sharp correction in gold and silver prices.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 01:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ead9b46be08bbe62f69a9_1769909724294.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Day Sparks India Market Focus Amidst Sector Bets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Day-Sparks-India-Market-Focus-Amidst-Sector-Bets/697ead2346be08bbe62f68f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Day-Sparks-India-Market-Focus-Amidst-Sector-Bets/697ead2346be08bbe62f68f1</guid><description>Indian equity markets are engaged in a special Sunday trading session on February 1, 2026, for the Union Budget 2026 presentation. Indices closed Friday lower, extending January's decline due to foreign fund outflows and global uncertainty. Investor attention is fixed on expected Budget allocations favouring defence, infrastructure, railways, and financial sectors, alongside a broader emphasis on capital expenditure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 01:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ead2346be08bbe62f68f0_1769909612319.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Rural Focus, Global Fortitude</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Rural-Focus-Global-Fortitude/697eaac246be08bbe62f67c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Rural-Focus-Global-Fortitude/697eaac246be08bbe62f67c1</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman presented India's Union Budget 2026, projecting a robust 7.4% GDP growth for the fiscal year ending March 31. The budget prioritizes rural development and agriculture, proposing a significant increase for the 'Viksit Bharat - G Ram G' employment scheme. This fiscal plan unfolds amidst India's demonstrated economic resilience, having navigated prohibitive US tariffs and stimulated domestic consumption through tax adjustments and infrastructure spending.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 01:23:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eaac246be08bbe62f67c0_1769909008286.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia CEO Confirms Major OpenAI Investment Amidst Funding Buzz</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-CEO-Confirms-Major-OpenAI-Investment-Amidst-Funding-Buzz/697ea95e46be08bbe62f670c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-CEO-Confirms-Major-OpenAI-Investment-Amidst-Funding-Buzz/697ea95e46be08bbe62f670c</guid><description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang confirmed a substantial, though scaled-back, investment in OpenAI, refuting prior reports of internal doubt. The move comes as OpenAI seeks up to $100 billion, amid increased competition and larger potential investments from rivals like Amazon. Nvidia’s stock saw high trading volume as investors processed the news.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 01:18:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ea95e46be08bbe62f670b_1769908706128.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Q3 Results: Mixed Analyst Views Amidst Record Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Q3-Results-Mixed-Analyst-Views-Amidst-Record-Revenue/697ea43a46be08bbe62f65ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Q3-Results-Mixed-Analyst-Views-Amidst-Record-Revenue/697ea43a46be08bbe62f65ae</guid><description>Bajaj Auto posted its highest-ever quarterly revenue and profit in Q3 FY26, driven by strong domestic and export performance. Despite the robust financials, analysts remain divided, with price targets ranging from ₹9,015 to ₹11,500. Key growth drivers include a recovering export market, an expanding EV portfolio contributing 25% to domestic revenue, and plans for new product launches. However, concerns persist around market share erosion in motorcycles and the company's motorcycle-heavy product mix, fueling debate on its current valuation which trades at a premium to its historical average.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:56:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ea43a46be08bbe62f65ad_1769907387179.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's IPO Surge Tempered by Ethics Call</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-IPO-Surge-Tempered-by-Ethics-Call/697ea25646be08bbe62f64af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-IPO-Surge-Tempered-by-Ethics-Call/697ea25646be08bbe62f64af</guid><description>Amidst record-breaking IPO activity and robust capital market growth, Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey has called for a shift from mere technical compliance to professional conscience. Pandey stressed that ethical substance, not just adherence to rules, is crucial for preventing corporate failures. The Insolvency and Bankruptcy Board of India (IBBI) Chairman Ravi Mital also advocated for streamlining compliance requirements. These discussions occurred at the World Forum of Accountants 2.0, organized by the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India (ICAI), where the evolving role of accountants in an increasingly complex financial ecosystem was a key theme. Technology's impact on auditing and the necessity of human judgment were also highlighted.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:49:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ea25646be08bbe62f64ae_1769906940412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Soars Past $5,500; Supply Side Gears Up Amid Discovery Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Soars-Past-5500-Supply-Side-Gears-Up-Amid-Discovery-Woes/697ea1da46be08bbe62f6348</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Soars-Past-5500-Supply-Side-Gears-Up-Amid-Discovery-Woes/697ea1da46be08bbe62f6348</guid><description>Gold prices have breached $5,500 per ounce, reaching new all-time highs fueled by persistent geopolitical uncertainty, US dollar weakness, and robust central bank demand. This price surge is now prompting a significant increase in gold mining exploration budgets after a period of decline, signaling a potential future supply response. However, the industry faces headwinds from smaller, more costly discoveries and declining ore grades, mirroring parallels with past commodity cycles.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:48:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ea1da46be08bbe62f6347_1769906838869.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Foreign Capital Fuels India Mid-Cap Bank Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Foreign-Capital-Fuels-India-Mid-Cap-Bank-Rally/697ea1eb46be08bbe62f639e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Foreign-Capital-Fuels-India-Mid-Cap-Bank-Rally/697ea1eb46be08bbe62f639e</guid><description>Global financial institutions are increasing stakes in Indian mid-cap banks, attracted by growth potential and valuations significantly below large-cap competitors. This trend, highlighted by Sumitomo Mitsui's investment in YES Bank and Blackstone's planned stake in Federal Bank, signals foreign confidence. Despite pressures on Net Interest Margins (NIMs) for some, mid-sized lenders like IDFC First Bank and Federal Bank are demonstrating operational resilience, driven by robust retail loan expansion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ea1eb46be08bbe62f639d_1769906730308.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Price Crash Batters Hindustan Zinc</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Price-Crash-Batters-Hindustan-Zinc/697e9e9246be08bbe62f6225</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Price-Crash-Batters-Hindustan-Zinc/697e9e9246be08bbe62f6225</guid><description>Hindustan Zinc Ltd. shares experienced their steepest single-day fall since 2008, shedding ₹36,000 crore in market capitalization, following a historic global drop in silver prices. The broader Nifty Metal index also suffered, with HZL and Vedanta contributing significantly to the rout. Vedanta's recent stake sale via OFS adds another layer of investor focus.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e9e9246be08bbe62f6224_1769905919226.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Hotels See $2B Investment Surge, Focus on Cash Flow</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Hotels-See-2B-Investment-Surge-Focus-on-Cash-Flow/697e9cb746be08bbe62f613a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Hotels-See-2B-Investment-Surge-Focus-on-Cash-Flow/697e9cb746be08bbe62f613a</guid><description>The Indian hospitality industry is experiencing a significant influx of approximately $2 billion in investments, with a clear preference for operational hotel properties. This strategic shift away from speculative greenfield developments is driven by high construction costs, elevated interest rates, and a desire for early cash flows. Major players like Indian Hotels Company (IHCL), Chalet Hotels, and Lemon Tree Hotels are actively involved in acquisitions and portfolio expansion. The sector is buoyed by strong domestic demand and a positive macroeconomic outlook for India, projected to grow between 7.5% and 7.8% in fiscal 2025-26.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:24:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e9cb746be08bbe62f6139_1769905450737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>