<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:33:08 +0000</pubDate><item><title>V-Mart Retail Q3: Revenue Jumps 10% Amid Flat Sales - What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/V-Mart-Retail-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-10percent-Amid-Flat-Sales-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6957b6794342f77179fbd3be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/V-Mart-Retail-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-10percent-Amid-Flat-Sales-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6957b6794342f77179fbd3be</guid><description>V-Mart Retail reported a 10% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹1,126 crore for the December quarter (Q3 FY26). However, same-store sales growth (SSSG) remained flat at 0% for the main V-Mart format, with the Unlimited format showing 2% SSSG. The company attributed the flat SSSG to shifts in festive timing, noting that combined Q2 and Q3 performance indicates underlying demand. V-Mart also expanded its footprint, opening 23 new stores during the quarter, bringing its total to 554.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:04:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957b6794342f77179fbd3bd_1767356092418.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Knight FinTech Lands $30M+ Boost! Ex-Infosys Finacle Chief Joins as Investor</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Knight-FinTech-Lands-30M-Boost-Ex-Infosys-Finacle-Chief-Joins-as-Investor/6957b64f4342f77179fbd325</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Knight-FinTech-Lands-30M-Boost-Ex-Infosys-Finacle-Chief-Joins-as-Investor/6957b64f4342f77179fbd325</guid><description>Knight FinTech, a provider of AI-first infrastructure for banking and digital lending, has secured over $30 million in its Series A funding round, led by Accel. Existing investors also participated. The company will use the funds to enhance its AI product roadmap, including risk intelligence and automated credit underwriting, and plans to expand into Middle Eastern and APAC markets. Sanat Rao, former Global CEO of Infosys Finacle, has joined as an investor and board advisor.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:04:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957b64f4342f77179fbd324_1767356181134.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock Your Dream Home! Budget 2026 Sparks Hope for Massive Housing Finance Reforms &amp; Cheaper Loans!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Unlock-Your-Dream-Home-Budget-2026-Sparks-Hope-for-Massive-Housing-Finance-Reforms-and-Cheaper-Loans/6957b5d54342f77179fbd0db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Unlock-Your-Dream-Home-Budget-2026-Sparks-Hope-for-Massive-Housing-Finance-Reforms-and-Cheaper-Loans/6957b5d54342f77179fbd0db</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 is expected to bring significant housing finance reforms. Experts propose increasing home loan tax deductions, reviving PMAY-CLSS subsidies for mid-income buyers, and introducing no-cost loan portability to reduce borrowing costs. Additionally, linking loan disbursements to construction milestones and mandating standardized disclosures are suggested to enhance transparency and buyer confidence amid rising property prices and loan amounts exceeding ₹27 lakh crore.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:00:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957b5d54342f77179fbd0da_1767356018633.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UP's Telecom Boom: India's Digital Highway Ignites Massive Subscriber Surge! See Why!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/UPs-Telecom-Boom-Indias-Digital-Highway-Ignites-Massive-Subscriber-Surge-See-Why/6957b4af4342f77179fbcbb3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/UPs-Telecom-Boom-Indias-Digital-Highway-Ignites-Massive-Subscriber-Surge-See-Why/6957b4af4342f77179fbcbb3</guid><description>Uttar Pradesh has emerged as a leading telecommunications market in India, experiencing significant growth in mobile, broadband, and fixed wireless access services across urban and rural areas. This expansion, fueled by supportive government policies and private investment, has led to millions of new subscribers. The state's digital connectivity is creating opportunities in education, healthcare, and employment, with a notable rise in 5G FWA and wireline connections.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:58:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957b4af4342f77179fbcbb2_1767355803513.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Soar to New Peaks! Nifty Hits All-Time High as Banking, Auto, and Metal Stocks Lead Historic Rally!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Soar-to-New-Peaks-Nifty-Hits-All-Time-High-as-Banking-Auto-and-Metal-Stocks-Lead-Historic-Rally/6957b47d4342f77179fbcaae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Soar-to-New-Peaks-Nifty-Hits-All-Time-High-as-Banking-Auto-and-Metal-Stocks-Lead-Historic-Rally/6957b47d4342f77179fbcaae</guid><description>Indian benchmark indices, Nifty 50 and BSE Sensex, surged to record highs on Friday. The Nifty 50 reached an all-time peak of 26,340, closing up 0.70% at 26,328.55, while the Sensex gained 0.67% to end at 85,762.01. A broad-based rally, led by banking, realty, metals, and auto stocks, fueled the market's ascent. Positive sentiment was driven by an improving earnings outlook, upcoming Union Budget, strong auto sales, supportive bank business updates, and hopes for reforms and a US trade deal. Domestic institutional investors provided steady support, offsetting foreign selling.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:54:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957b47d4342f77179fbcaad_1767356233017.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Crashes Past 90/$! Major Economic Pressures Revealed as Currency Hits New Low</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Crashes-Past-90-Major-Economic-Pressures-Revealed-as-Currency-Hits-New-Low/6957b35d4342f77179fbc607</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Crashes-Past-90-Major-Economic-Pressures-Revealed-as-Currency-Hits-New-Low/6957b35d4342f77179fbc607</guid><description>The Indian rupee has fallen below the psychologically important 90 level against the US dollar, settling at 90.20. This depreciation is driven by weak domestic manufacturing data, a strengthening dollar globally, and significant foreign institutional investor (FII) outflows. While Indian equities rallied sharply and the Reserve Bank of India may have intervened, the currency faces ongoing pressure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:49:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957b35d4342f77179fbc606_1767355329801.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Capital Shares Skyrocket to Record High: Should You Buy Now?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tata-Capital-Shares-Skyrocket-to-Record-High-Should-You-Buy-Now/6957afdc4342f77179fbb923</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tata-Capital-Shares-Skyrocket-to-Record-High-Should-You-Buy-Now/6957afdc4342f77179fbb923</guid><description>Tata Capital shares surged nearly 5% on Friday to hit a fresh 52-week high of ₹357.20, extending its upward momentum. The newly listed Tata Group company saw a significant jump in trading volumes, more than doubling compared to the previous session. Technical indicators show a bullish reversal with analysts recommending buying on dips for targets up to ₹400, citing a strong breakout above the ₹350 resistance level. The company had raised ₹15,512 crore during its IPO in October.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:32:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957afdc4342f77179fbb922_1767354664845.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Faces Billion-Dollar Showdown: KG-D6 Gas Disputes with Government Nearing Crucial 2026 Resolution!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Reliance-Industries-Faces-Billion-Dollar-Showdown-KG-D6-Gas-Disputes-with-Government-Nearing-Crucial-2026-Resolution/6957ae474342f77179fbb34e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Reliance-Industries-Faces-Billion-Dollar-Showdown-KG-D6-Gas-Disputes-with-Government-Nearing-Crucial-2026-Resolution/6957ae474342f77179fbb34e</guid><description>Reliance Industries and its partner BP are embroiled in two major disputes over the KG-D6 gas block with the Indian government. One concerns production shortfalls from the D1 and D3 fields, where the government may seek billions in compensation, a claim Reliance denies, stating the government's actual claim is $247 million for disallowed investments. The second is a 'gas migration' dispute with Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd (ONGC), where the government seeks $2.81 billion. Outcomes for both are anticipated by the first half of 2026, making this a critical development for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:27:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957ae474342f77179fbb34d_1767354053618.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking Price Cut! Adani Total Gas Slashes CNG &amp; Piped Gas Rates After Major Reform!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Shocking-Price-Cut-Adani-Total-Gas-Slashes-CNG-and-Piped-Gas-Rates-After-Major-Reform/6957ae074342f77179fbb1db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Shocking-Price-Cut-Adani-Total-Gas-Slashes-CNG-and-Piped-Gas-Rates-After-Major-Reform/6957ae074342f77179fbb1db</guid><description>Adani Total Gas has reduced prices for Compressed Natural Gas (CNG) and domestic Piped Natural Gas (PNG) by up to ₹4 across multiple markets. This move follows the Petroleum and Natural Gas Regulatory Board's (PNGRB) landmark tariff reform, which simplifies gas transportation charges and lowers costs for distributors. GAIL Gas Limited and Indraprastha Gas Limited have also announced similar price reductions. The reform aims to make natural gas more accessible and accelerate the adoption of cleaner fuels for homes and transport, supporting India's energy mix goals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:24:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957ae074342f77179fbb1da_1767353921317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Government Tightens Grip! Your Car's Fitness Test About to Get Tougher - Are You Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Government-Tightens-Grip-Your-Cars-Fitness-Test-About-to-Get-Tougher-Are-You-Ready/6957ad4b4342f77179fbad93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Government-Tightens-Grip-Your-Cars-Fitness-Test-About-to-Get-Tougher-Are-You-Ready/6957ad4b4342f77179fbad93</guid><description>India's road transport ministry is proposing major changes to vehicle fitness and pollution certificate rules. Private vehicles will soon require mandatory fitness tests at automated stations, with a 10-second geo-tagged video as proof. Vehicles failing the test will get 180 days to repair, or they'll be flagged as End of Life Vehicles (ELV). This move aims to increase transparency, reduce pollution, and remove unsafe vehicles from Indian roads.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:23:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957ad4b4342f77179fbad92_1767353957616.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki's Astonishing Leap: CY25 Production Smashes All Records! Investors Must See This!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzukis-Astonishing-Leap-CY25-Production-Smashes-All-Records-Investors-Must-See-This/6957ad4e4342f77179fbadf3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzukis-Astonishing-Leap-CY25-Production-Smashes-All-Records-Investors-Must-See-This/6957ad4e4342f77179fbadf3</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki announced its highest-ever production of over 22.55 lakh units in calendar year 2025, marking the second consecutive year surpassing 20.63 lakh units. Exports also reached a record 3.95 lakh vehicles, a 21% increase from 2024, solidifying its position as India's top passenger vehicle exporter for the fifth year. The company plans to expand its manufacturing capacity to 4 million units annually.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:22:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957ad4e4342f77179fbadf2_1767353751213.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Marico's Blockbuster Q3: Revenue Skyrockets, Global Growth Fuels Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Maricos-Blockbuster-Q3-Revenue-Skyrockets-Global-Growth-Fuels-Surge/6957ad4d4342f77179fbadc8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Maricos-Blockbuster-Q3-Revenue-Skyrockets-Global-Growth-Fuels-Surge/6957ad4d4342f77179fbadc8</guid><description>Marico reported a strong third quarter for fiscal year 2026, with consolidated revenue growing in the high twenties. This growth was powered by steady high single-digit volume increases in its India business, driven by popular products like Parachute oil and premium personal care items. The company also saw robust international performance with early twenties growth in constant currency, especially from Bangladesh, Vietnam, and South Africa, indicating a positive outlook for future consumption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:22:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957ad4d4342f77179fbadc7_1767353871041.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gig Worker Strike Fails to Halt Delivery Surge: Zomato &amp; Blinkit Smash Records Amidst Worker Unrest!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Gig-Worker-Strike-Fails-to-Halt-Delivery-Surge-Zomato-and-Blinkit-Smash-Records-Amidst-Worker-Unrest/6957abd94342f77179fba678</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Gig-Worker-Strike-Fails-to-Halt-Delivery-Surge-Zomato-and-Blinkit-Smash-Records-Amidst-Worker-Unrest/6957abd94342f77179fba678</guid><description>Despite a nationwide strike by over 2 lakh gig workers on December 25 and 31, delivery platforms Zomato and Blinkit reported record order volumes, with Deepinder Goyal stating over 75 lakh orders were delivered. Swiggy Instamart also saw strong traction. Workers, however, allege unfair practices, low pay, lack of insurance, and dangerous delivery targets, demanding formal recognition and an end to 10-15 minute delivery promises.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:20:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957abd94342f77179fba677_1767353561015.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mirae Asset India Lands Ex-Steadview Capital Chief Puneet Kumar: What It Means for India's Tech Scene!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mirae-Asset-India-Lands-Ex-Steadview-Capital-Chief-Puneet-Kumar-What-It-Means-for-Indias-Tech-Scene/6957ac464342f77179fba8a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mirae-Asset-India-Lands-Ex-Steadview-Capital-Chief-Puneet-Kumar-What-It-Means-for-Indias-Tech-Scene/6957ac464342f77179fba8a9</guid><description>Mirae Asset Venture India has appointed Puneet Kumar, formerly Managing Director at Steadview Capital, as its new Chief Executive Officer. Kumar will lead the firm's venture capital and private investing operations in India, focusing on strategy, global collaboration, and founder partnerships. Mirae Asset Venture India invests in technology platforms, AI, and consumer sectors. This move signals Mirae Asset's ongoing expansion in India's technology investment landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:19:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957ac464342f77179fba8a8_1767353777974.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Mandate Sparks BSE Hiring Frenzy: 3 Top Executive Director Roles Open Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Mandate-Sparks-BSE-Hiring-Frenzy-3-Top-Executive-Director-Roles-Open-Now/6957a7834342f77179fb95aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Mandate-Sparks-BSE-Hiring-Frenzy-3-Top-Executive-Director-Roles-Open-Now/6957a7834342f77179fb95aa</guid><description>Stock exchange BSE is seeking applications for three crucial Executive Director positions: Critical Operations, Regulatory/Compliance/Risk Management/Investor Grievances, and Business. These hires are mandated by the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) to enhance governance standards at market infrastructure institutions. The roles are for a maximum of two five-year terms with an age limit of 65.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:58:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957a7834342f77179fb95a9_1767352267083.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Financial Doors Swing Open: Foreign Banks' Expansion Plans Under Government Review!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Financial-Doors-Swing-Open-Foreign-Banks-Expansion-Plans-Under-Government-Review/6957a63a4342f77179fb9037</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Financial-Doors-Swing-Open-Foreign-Banks-Expansion-Plans-Under-Government-Review/6957a63a4342f77179fb9037</guid><description>A government inter-departmental committee, led by Department of Financial Services Secretary M. Nagaraju, convened to review proposals from foreign banks seeking to establish branches, representative offices, or subsidiaries in India. Applications were received via the Reserve Bank of India, and the committee, including officials from the Ministry of Home Affairs, Ministry of External Affairs, and Department of Commerce, deliberated on security, political, and economic factors before making recommendations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957a63a4342f77179fb9036_1767352017152.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Siddhartha Bhaiya's Shocking Death: Fund Manager Who Warned of 'Epic Bubble' in Indian Equities Dies at 47</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Siddhartha-Bhaiyas-Shocking-Death-Fund-Manager-Who-Warned-of-Epic-Bubble-in-Indian-Equities-Dies-at-47/6957a6894342f77179fb917e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Siddhartha-Bhaiyas-Shocking-Death-Fund-Manager-Who-Warned-of-Epic-Bubble-in-Indian-Equities-Dies-at-47/6957a6894342f77179fb917e</guid><description>Aequitas founder and Managing Director Siddhartha Bhaiya has passed away at the age of 47 due to cardiac arrest. Bhaiya, a prominent figure in the Indian asset management industry, had recently issued a stark warning, describing the Indian equity market as an "epic bubble of epic proportions." He questioned the market's valuations, particularly concerning retail investor portfolios and the dynamics of Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs). His firm, Aequitas, has mourned his loss, remembering him for his visionary leadership and commitment to strong values.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:53:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957a6894342f77179fb917d_1767352181478.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metal Stocks Surge to Record Highs: National Aluminium, Hind Copper Lead Gains as Global Factors Ignite Rally!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Stocks-Surge-to-Record-Highs-National-Aluminium-Hind-Copper-Lead-Gains-as-Global-Factors-Ignite-Rally/6957a6054342f77179fb8f03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metal-Stocks-Surge-to-Record-Highs-National-Aluminium-Hind-Copper-Lead-Gains-as-Global-Factors-Ignite-Rally/6957a6054342f77179fb8f03</guid><description>The Nifty Metal index has reached a new all-time high, marking its fourth consecutive day of gains. Stocks like National Aluminium Company and Hindustan Copper have surged up to 5 percent. This rally is fueled by a weakening dollar, positive factory growth data from China, and rising global metal prices, with aluminum hitting $3,000 a tonne.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:53:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957a6054342f77179fb8f02_1767351880613.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Will This Week's Data Spark a Market Surge? RBI, PMI &amp; Earnings Countdown!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Will-This-Weeks-Data-Spark-a-Market-Surge-RBI-PMI-and-Earnings-Countdown/6957a6094342f77179fb8f46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Will-This-Weeks-Data-Spark-a-Market-Surge-RBI-PMI-and-Earnings-Countdown/6957a6094342f77179fb8f46</guid><description>Investors are keenly watching the upcoming week as crucial economic data points are set to be released. Key highlights include Reserve Bank of India's bank loan and deposit growth figures, final Purchasing Managers' Index (PMI) readings for December, and the commencement of quarterly earnings season. Global economic indicators from the US, China, and Europe will also provide insights into the world economy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:53:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957a6094342f77179fb8f45_1767351896777.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Health Tech Booms 42x by 2050: Study Warns of Huge Carbon Footprint!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Global-Health-Tech-Booms-42x-by-2050-Study-Warns-of-Huge-Carbon-Footprint/6957a5224342f77179fb8b41</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Global-Health-Tech-Booms-42x-by-2050-Study-Warns-of-Huge-Carbon-Footprint/6957a5224342f77179fb8b41</guid><description>A new study predicts wearable healthcare devices will increase 42-fold globally by 2050, reaching nearly two billion units annually. This surge is expected to generate 3.4 metric tonnes of carbon dioxide equivalent, alongside ecotoxicity and e-waste concerns. China and India are projected to lead in greenhouse gas emissions from these devices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:49:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957a5224342f77179fb8b40_1767351647736.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Giant Secures Rs 700 Crore Funding Boost &amp; Soars on Credit Upgrade!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Giant-Secures-Rs-700-Crore-Funding-Boost-and-Soars-on-Credit-Upgrade/6957a5e44342f77179fb8e7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Giant-Secures-Rs-700-Crore-Funding-Boost-and-Soars-on-Credit-Upgrade/6957a5e44342f77179fb8e7c</guid><description>Steel Exchange of India's board has approved a significant fundraising of up to ₹700 crore, utilizing various instruments to strengthen its financial base. The company also received a credit rating upgrade from Infomerics Valuation and Rating, enhancing its credibility. Funds will support balance sheet strengthening, expansion into specialty steel under the PLI scheme, and refinancing high-cost debt, aiming to improve cash flows and reduce interest burden.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:48:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957a5e44342f77179fb8e7b_1767351854303.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Slashes Gas Prices! Your Kitchen &amp; Car Bills Just Dropped – Here's Why!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Slashes-Gas-Prices-Your-Kitchen-and-Car-Bills-Just-Dropped-Heres-Why/6957a4354342f77179fb8766</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Slashes-Gas-Prices-Your-Kitchen-and-Car-Bills-Just-Dropped-Heres-Why/6957a4354342f77179fb8766</guid><description>Adani Total Gas Ltd (ATGL) has cut prices for Compressed Natural Gas (CNG) and Piped Natural Gas (PNG) by up to ₹4 across multiple markets. This follows a significant tariff reform by the Petroleum and Natural Gas Regulatory Board (PNGRB), which simplifies gas transportation charges and lowers input costs for city gas distributors. Other major players like GAIL Gas Ltd and Indraprastha Gas Ltd have also announced price reductions, aiming to make natural gas more affordable and accelerate its adoption as a cleaner fuel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:47:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957a4354342f77179fb8765_1767351421703.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSE 500 Index Surges to 52-Week High: 18 Stocks Hit All-Time Peaks in Major Market Rally!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/BSE-500-Index-Surges-to-52-Week-High-18-Stocks-Hit-All-Time-Peaks-in-Major-Market-Rally/6957a0164342f77179fb7737</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/BSE-500-Index-Surges-to-52-Week-High-18-Stocks-Hit-All-Time-Peaks-in-Major-Market-Rally/6957a0164342f77179fb7737</guid><description>The BSE 500 index reached a new 52-week high of 37,771.93 on Friday, marking a significant 1 per cent gain, driven by strong performance in auto, power, and public sector undertaking (PSU) stocks. The broad market indicator, representing top BSE-listed companies, is now just 2.6 per cent shy of its all-time peak set in September 2024, signaling robust investor confidence in India's economic outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:26:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957a0164342f77179fb7736_1767350506742.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sensex Rockets 573 Points to 85,762! Nifty Surges 182 Points – India Market Boom Ignites!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Rockets-573-Points-to-85762-Nifty-Surges-182-Points-India-Market-Boom-Ignites/6957a0564342f77179fb7848</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Rockets-573-Points-to-85762-Nifty-Surges-182-Points-India-Market-Boom-Ignites/6957a0564342f77179fb7848</guid><description>India's key stock market indices, the Sensex and Nifty, experienced a significant rally today. The BSE Sensex surged by 573.41 points, closing at 85,762.01, while the NSE Nifty advanced by 182 points to reach 26,328.55. This strong upward movement indicates positive investor sentiment in the Indian stock market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:26:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957a0564342f77179fb7847_1767350428640.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UCO Bank Q3 Triumph: Loans Surge 16% Outpacing Deposits, Investor Confidence Soars!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UCO-Bank-Q3-Triumph-Loans-Surge-16percent-Outpacing-Deposits-Investor-Confidence-Soars/69579f954342f77179fb7446</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UCO-Bank-Q3-Triumph-Loans-Surge-16percent-Outpacing-Deposits-Investor-Confidence-Soars/69579f954342f77179fb7446</guid><description>State-owned UCO Bank reported strong third-quarter performance with total business growing 13.3% year-on-year to ₹5.54 lakh crore. Loans saw a significant jump of 16.27% to ₹2.43 lakh crore, outpacing deposit growth of 10.71% to ₹3.10 lakh crore. The bank also improved its CASA ratio to 38.41% and credit-deposit ratio to 78.61%. UCO Bank shares closed higher on the news.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:25:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69579f954342f77179fb7445_1767350373258.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CAG Exposes Massive Fiscal Transparency Lapses: Centre's Debt Soars Past Limits!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/CAG-Exposes-Massive-Fiscal-Transparency-Lapses-Centres-Debt-Soars-Past-Limits/69579ff84342f77179fb765c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/CAG-Exposes-Massive-Fiscal-Transparency-Lapses-Centres-Debt-Soars-Past-Limits/69579ff84342f77179fb765c</guid><description>The Comptroller and Auditor General (CAG) has identified significant transparency gaps in the Central Government's fiscal management under the FRBM Act. Central government debt has risen considerably, exceeding FRBM limits and pre-pandemic levels. The audit also points to disclosure inconsistencies and a substantial burden of interest payments, raising concerns about fiscal health.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:25:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69579ff84342f77179fb765b_1767350353105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haldiram's lands major investment from L Catterton, eyes global domination!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Haldirams-lands-major-investment-from-L-Catterton-eyes-global-domination/69579f504342f77179fb72e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Haldirams-lands-major-investment-from-L-Catterton-eyes-global-domination/69579f504342f77179fb72e1</guid><description>L Catterton has formed a strategic partnership and made a minority investment in Haldiram Snacks Food Private Limited. This collaboration aims to strengthen Haldiram's market leadership in India and accelerate its international expansion, leveraging the company's robust fundamentals and brand equity. Khaitan &amp; Co advised Haldiram, while TT&amp;A represented L Catterton.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:20:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69579f504342f77179fb72e0_1767350279764.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Protean eGov Technologies Acquires NSDL Payments Bank Stake: Unlocking Digital Finance for Underserved India!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Protean-eGov-Technologies-Acquires-NSDL-Payments-Bank-Stake-Unlocking-Digital-Finance-for-Underserved-India/69579e664342f77179fb6da7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Protean-eGov-Technologies-Acquires-NSDL-Payments-Bank-Stake-Unlocking-Digital-Finance-for-Underserved-India/69579e664342f77179fb6da7</guid><description>Protean eGov Technologies Limited has acquired a 4.95% stake in NSDL Payments Bank Limited, with advisory from Luthra and Luthra Law Offices India. This strategic move aims to expand digital banking technologies to underserved segments by merging Protean's nationwide network with NPBL's digital-first platform, enhancing financial inclusion across India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:20:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69579e664342f77179fb6da6_1767350081509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zenrock &amp; EAAA India Buy 50.8% Stake in Indo Borax, Triggering Open Offer!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Zenrock-and-EAAA-India-Buy-508percent-Stake-in-Indo-Borax-Triggering-Open-Offer/69579e0b4342f77179fb6ba0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Zenrock-and-EAAA-India-Buy-508percent-Stake-in-Indo-Borax-Triggering-Open-Offer/69579e0b4342f77179fb6ba0</guid><description>Zenrock Chemicals Private Limited and alternate investment funds managed by EAAA India Alternatives Limited have agreed to purchase a 50.8% promoter stake in Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Limited. This significant acquisition, involving 1,63,00,230 equity shares, triggers a mandatory open offer, potentially leading to a change of control at the boric acid manufacturer. Cyril Amarchand Mangaldas advised on the transaction and financing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:20:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69579e0b4342f77179fb6b9f_1767350036112.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Pharma Dream: Sitharaman's Budget Blueprint to Slash Medicine Costs &amp; Boost Global Role!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Pharma-Dream-Sitharamans-Budget-Blueprint-to-Slash-Medicine-Costs-and-Boost-Global-Role/69579da14342f77179fb690d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Pharma-Dream-Sitharamans-Budget-Blueprint-to-Slash-Medicine-Costs-and-Boost-Global-Role/69579da14342f77179fb690d</guid><description>India's pharmaceutical market is projected to reach $120-130 billion by 2030. To maintain growth and affordability, NITI Aayog and EY India suggest key budgetary interventions. These include boosting R&amp;D through incentives and patent-box tax regime relaxation, offering concessional tax for manufacturing, and investing in healthcare infrastructure. The focus is on diseases impacting large Indian populations, aiming to make medicines cheaper and solidify India's 'pharmacy of the world' status.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:18:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69579da14342f77179fb690c_1767349840309.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Record IPO Surge! India Raises ₹1.75 Lakh Crore in 2025 Driven by Finance &amp; Consumer Giants!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Record-IPO-Surge-India-Raises-175-Lakh-Crore-in-2025-Driven-by-Finance-and-Consumer-Giants/69579dce4342f77179fb6a08</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Record-IPO-Surge-India-Raises-175-Lakh-Crore-in-2025-Driven-by-Finance-and-Consumer-Giants/69579dce4342f77179fb6a08</guid><description>India's IPO market hit an all-time high in 2025, with 103 mainboard IPOs raising ₹1,75,901 crore. Financial services and consumer discretionary sectors dominated, accounting for nearly two-thirds of total funds. Key large-cap listings, including Tata Capital, HDB Financial Services, LG Electronics India, Meesho, and Lenskart, underscored significant investor confidence in these growth areas.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:15:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69579dce4342f77179fb6a07_1767349999503.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's IPO Meltdown: Why Record Funds Raised Led to Massive Investor Losses!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Indias-IPO-Meltdown-Why-Record-Funds-Raised-Led-to-Massive-Investor-Losses/69579c2e4342f77179fb6296</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Indias-IPO-Meltdown-Why-Record-Funds-Raised-Led-to-Massive-Investor-Losses/69579c2e4342f77179fb6296</guid><description>In 2025, India's primary market saw record IPO fundraising of ₹1.75 lakh crore, but by year-end, nearly half of new stocks traded below issue prices. This divergence stems from hype-driven pricing versus fundamental valuation, with smaller IPOs struggling more due to lower institutional ownership and liquidity. Investors are now urged to focus on cash flows and profitability over narratives for sustainable returns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:09:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69579c2e4342f77179fb6295_1767349635630.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DSM Fresh Foods Shocks Market! Mega Acquisition to Unleash RTE/RTC Powerhouse!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/DSM-Fresh-Foods-Shocks-Market-Mega-Acquisition-to-Unleash-RTERTC-Powerhouse/695798b24342f77179fb5272</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/DSM-Fresh-Foods-Shocks-Market-Mega-Acquisition-to-Unleash-RTERTC-Powerhouse/695798b24342f77179fb5272</guid><description>DSM Fresh Foods Limited is making a bold move into the lucrative Ready-to-Eat (RTE) and Ready-to-Cook (RTC) segments by acquiring a 51% controlling stake in Avyom Foodtech Private Limited for ₹7.5 crore cash. This strategic acquisition leverages Avyom Foodtech's operational facility, which previously generated up to ₹16 crore in annual revenue, positioning DSM Fresh Foods for rapid diversification and growth in the convenience food market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:57:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695798b24342f77179fb5271_1767348578693.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDBI Bank Shares EXPLODE to 11-Year High – What's Driving This Massive Rally?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDBI-Bank-Shares-EXPLODE-to-11-Year-High-Whats-Driving-This-Massive-Rally/695798cc4342f77179fb5349</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDBI-Bank-Shares-EXPLODE-to-11-Year-High-Whats-Driving-This-Massive-Rally/695798cc4342f77179fb5349</guid><description>IDBI Bank shares surged 11% to an 11-year high of ₹115.1 on Friday, fueled by record trading volumes nearly four times the average. This rally is amplified by ongoing government plans for a strategic stake sale and strong Q2FY25 results showing a 39% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹1,836 crore, bolstered by improved net interest margins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:51:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695798cc4342f77179fb5348_1767348552572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jaro Institute Shocks Investors: First-Ever Dividend Announced! Will This Turnaround Its Stock?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Jaro-Institute-Shocks-Investors-First-Ever-Dividend-Announced-Will-This-Turnaround-Its-Stock/695798154342f77179fb4f3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Jaro-Institute-Shocks-Investors-First-Ever-Dividend-Announced-Will-This-Turnaround-Its-Stock/695798154342f77179fb4f3e</guid><description>Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research, an e-learning platform, has announced its first-ever interim dividend. Shareholders will receive Rs 2 per share (20% payout on face value of Rs 10) for FY 2025-26. The record date for this dividend is January 16, 2026. The company filing also confirmed payment by January 31, 2026. This news comes as the stock has faced significant pressure recently.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:51:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695798154342f77179fb4f3d_1767348548063.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EV Insurance in India Faces Shockwaves: Repair Costs Skyrocket, Climate Risks Reshape Coverage!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/EV-Insurance-in-India-Faces-Shockwaves-Repair-Costs-Skyrocket-Climate-Risks-Reshape-Coverage/695797764342f77179fb4c2e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/EV-Insurance-in-India-Faces-Shockwaves-Repair-Costs-Skyrocket-Climate-Risks-Reshape-Coverage/695797764342f77179fb4c2e</guid><description>India's booming electric vehicle (EV) market is forcing a major overhaul in insurance and roadside assistance. Insurers are grappling with escalating repair costs driven by complex technology, specialized parts, and advanced systems like ADAS. Climate-related disruptions also pose new challenges. Consequently, EV insurance premiums are rising, with new add-ons like battery protection emerging. The industry is shifting towards tech-led diagnostics, predictive models, and specialized roadside assistance to manage these evolving risks and costs for electric mobility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:50:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695797764342f77179fb4c2d_1767348349259.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zaggle's Visa Deal Boosts Margins! Fintech Giant Reaffirms Strong Growth Targets Amidst Banking Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Zaggles-Visa-Deal-Boosts-Margins-Fintech-Giant-Reaffirms-Strong-Growth-Targets-Amidst-Banking-Expansion/6957979f4342f77179fb4cfe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Zaggles-Visa-Deal-Boosts-Margins-Fintech-Giant-Reaffirms-Strong-Growth-Targets-Amidst-Banking-Expansion/6957979f4342f77179fb4cfe</guid><description>Zaggle's CEO Avinash Godkhindi anticipates improved margins through a strategic Visa partnership, leveraging spend-linked incentives without extra costs. The company is set to launch services with AU Small Finance Bank soon and is exploring more banking collaborations. Zaggle remains confident in achieving its ambitious FY26 growth target of 40-45% and maintaining EBITDA margins between 10-11%, while actively pursuing further acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:50:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957979f4342f77179fb4cfd_1767348192456.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Max Estates CFO REVEALS Delhi NCR Real Estate BOOM: Huge Opportunity &amp; Growth Plans Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-CFO-REVEALS-Delhi-NCR-Real-Estate-BOOM-Huge-Opportunity-and-Growth-Plans-Unveiled/695796794342f77179fb4821</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-CFO-REVEALS-Delhi-NCR-Real-Estate-BOOM-Huge-Opportunity-and-Growth-Plans-Unveiled/695796794342f77179fb4821</guid><description>Max Estates Chief Financial Officer Nitin Kansal confirmed the company's exclusive focus on the Delhi National Capital Region (NCR), citing a significant market opportunity. The firm is on track to meet its ₹6,000–6,500 crore sales booking target, supported by a ₹9,500 crore project launch pipeline. Kansal anticipates 5-10% annual property price growth in NCR and forecasts a substantial increase in commercial rental income to ₹750-800 crore by FY28-29.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:50:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695796794342f77179fb4820_1767347901555.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Rupee's 2026 Forecast: Experts Predict Stability Amidst Global Jitters – Will Bears Finally Rest?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Rupees-2026-Forecast-Experts-Predict-Stability-Amidst-Global-Jitters-Will-Bears-Finally-Rest/695796a24342f77179fb48ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Rupees-2026-Forecast-Experts-Predict-Stability-Amidst-Global-Jitters-Will-Bears-Finally-Rest/695796a24342f77179fb48ec</guid><description>Currency experts anticipate the Indian Rupee will stabilize in 2026 after a sharp depreciation in 2025. The stabilization is contingent upon ongoing US-India trade talks and capital flow trends. While volatility may persist due to global uncertainties, the rupee is projected to trade within the 88-91.50 range against the US dollar. Analysts note that India-specific pressures, such as foreign portfolio investor outflows and trade uncertainties, significantly impacted the currency in 2025. Improved valuations and potential for renewed inflows offer a cautiously constructive outlook for 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:46:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695796a24342f77179fb48eb_1767347938542.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Electronics Leap: Billions Invested to Boost Local PCB, Li-ion Cell Manufacturing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Electronics-Leap-Billions-Invested-to-Boost-Local-PCB-Li-ion-Cell-Manufacturing/695795344342f77179fb42b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Electronics-Leap-Billions-Invested-to-Boost-Local-PCB-Li-ion-Cell-Manufacturing/695795344342f77179fb42b0</guid><description>India's Electronics Component Manufacturing Scheme (ECMS) is significantly bolstering domestic production of critical components like PCBs, Li-ion cells, and display modules. With 46 applications approved, totaling ₹54,567 crore in investment intention, the scheme aims to reduce imports, enhance self-reliance, and position India as a global electronics manufacturing hub. The third tranche alone approves ₹41,863 crore in investment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 09:42:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695795344342f77179fb42af_1767347577996.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>