<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 18:28:18 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Bain Capital Gains RBI Nod for Major Stake in Manappuram Finance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bain-Capital-Gains-RBI-Nod-for-Major-Stake-in-Manappuram-Finance/6990b90d2c7cdffb0a9f866d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bain-Capital-Gains-RBI-Nod-for-Major-Stake-in-Manappuram-Finance/6990b90d2c7cdffb0a9f866d</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has given the green light to Bain Capital's affiliates for acquiring a significant stake in Manappuram Finance. The approval allows Bain Capital to potentially hold up to 41.7% of the gold loan financier, involving a ₹4,385 crore investment and a mandatory open offer to public shareholders. This move will see Bain Capital become a joint promoter, reshaping the company's control and strategic direction.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 18:03:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990a59ce2b1df5863091208_1771090842946.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Equity Funds: Three Schemes Dominate 3, 5, 10-Year Returns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SBI-Equity-Funds-Three-Schemes-Dominate-3-5-10-Year-Returns/6990b0f52c7cdffb0a9ee7ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SBI-Equity-Funds-Three-Schemes-Dominate-3-5-10-Year-Returns/6990b0f52c7cdffb0a9ee7ed</guid><description>SBI Mutual Fund's top equity schemes demonstrated robust, consistent performance over three, five, and ten-year periods. The SBI Contra Fund emerged as a leader in long-term returns, outperforming its peers. While other schemes like SBI Focused Fund and SBI Large &amp; Midcap Fund also posted strong CAGRs, short-term performance presented a different picture, with SBI Focused Fund leading the pack over one year.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:29:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990b0f52c7cdffb0a9ee7ec_1771090265234.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Doubles Climate Spending to 5.6% GDP, Minister Confirms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/India-Doubles-Climate-Spending-to-56percent-GDP-Minister-Confirms/6990a45a2c7cdffb0a9e2a5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/India-Doubles-Climate-Spending-to-56percent-GDP-Minister-Confirms/6990a45a2c7cdffb0a9e2a5a</guid><description>Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced India has significantly boosted climate action spending, reaching nearly 5.6% of GDP. This marks a substantial increase from 3.7% six years ago, highlighting India's commitment to domestic environmental action and self-reliance. She stressed that the country is not solely dependent on international support to meet its environmental goals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:35:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6990a45a2c7cdffb0a9e2a59.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways Eyes ₹30,000 Cr Boost From Gati Shakti Cargo Terminals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Eyes-30000-Cr-Boost-From-Gati-Shakti-Cargo-Terminals/69909e722c7cdffb0a9dd440</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Eyes-30000-Cr-Boost-From-Gati-Shakti-Cargo-Terminals/69909e722c7cdffb0a9dd440</guid><description>Indian Railways aims to generate an additional ₹30,000 crore in revenue over three years through its new Gati Shakti Cargo Terminal (GCT) policy. The expansion will see GCTs grow from 124 to over 500 in five years, boosting freight loading for sectors like automotive, cement, and salt. Concurrently, the railway ministry is prioritizing hygienic travel conditions in general class coaches.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:10:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69909e722c7cdffb0a9dd43f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Doubles Climate Action Spend to 5.6% of GDP: FM</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/India-Doubles-Climate-Action-Spend-to-56percent-of-GDP-FM/69909da22c7cdffb0a9dc7e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/India-Doubles-Climate-Action-Spend-to-56percent-of-GDP-FM/69909da22c7cdffb0a9dc7e2</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced India has significantly boosted spending on climate action, reaching 5.6% of GDP from 3.7% six years prior. The nation has achieved two-thirds of its renewable energy commitments four years ahead of schedule. Sitharaman also advocated for a differentiated approach to climate action costs, suggesting less polluting nations should bear less financial burden. Investments are being channeled into renewable energy and carbon capture strategies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:06:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69909da22c7cdffb0a9dc7e1_1771085341334.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supreme Court Demands FSSAI Act on Food Health Warning Labels</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Supreme-Court-Demands-FSSAI-Act-on-Food-Health-Warning-Labels/699095822c7cdffb0a9d2bd9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Supreme-Court-Demands-FSSAI-Act-on-Food-Health-Warning-Labels/699095822c7cdffb0a9d2bd9</guid><description>The Supreme Court of India has directed the Food Safety and Standards Authority of India (FSSAI) to consider implementing front-of-pack warning labels on packaged foods high in sugar, salt, and saturated fat. Justices JB Pardiwala and KV Viswanathan expressed dissatisfaction with FSSAI's compliance affidavit, noting a lack of concrete progress on the labelling system despite previous directions. The court emphasized the public health implications and the citizens' right to health, urging FSSAI to present a concrete action plan within four weeks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:32:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699095822c7cdffb0a9d2bd8_1771083304197.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Namo Bharat, Meerut Metro Inauguration Set Feb 22, Spurs Real Estate Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Namo-Bharat-Meerut-Metro-Inauguration-Set-Feb-22-Spurs-Real-Estate-Boom/699094e02c7cdffb0a9d245a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Namo-Bharat-Meerut-Metro-Inauguration-Set-Feb-22-Spurs-Real-Estate-Boom/699094e02c7cdffb0a9d245a</guid><description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi is poised to inaugurate the final stretches of the 82-km Delhi-Ghaziabad-Meerut Namo Bharat corridor and the 23-km Meerut Metro on February 22. This significant infrastructure upgrade is already reshaping the region's economy, with property values near stations surging by 30-67% over two years and developers actively launching new projects.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:29:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699094e02c7cdffb0a9d2459_1771083086074.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PM Modi to Inaugurate Namo Bharat, Meerut Metro on Feb 22</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/PM-Modi-to-Inaugurate-Namo-Bharat-Meerut-Metro-on-Feb-22/699094402c7cdffb0a9d1b15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/PM-Modi-to-Inaugurate-Namo-Bharat-Meerut-Metro-on-Feb-22/699094402c7cdffb0a9d1b15</guid><description>The final stretches of the 82-km Delhi-Ghaziabad-Meerut Namo Bharat corridor and the 23-km Meerut Metro are slated for inauguration on February 22, likely by Prime Minister Narendra Modi. This extensive rapid transit system is already spurring significant socio-economic shifts, notably a 30-67% jump in property values within two kilometers of stations and increased developer interest.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:26:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699094402c7cdffb0a9d1b14_1771082956020.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airbnb Profits Soar, But Stock Stalls: What's the Market Missing?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Airbnb-Profits-Soar-But-Stock-Stalls-Whats-the-Market-Missing/699092d02c7cdffb0a9d0c39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Airbnb-Profits-Soar-But-Stock-Stalls-Whats-the-Market-Missing/699092d02c7cdffb0a9d0c39</guid><description>Airbnb reported robust 2025 financials, including $12.2 billion in revenue and strong free cash flow. Despite record profits, the company's stock has declined over the past year. Investors are seeking accelerating growth, often AI-linked, which Airbnb's steady, compounding expansion currently fails to provide, leading to market skepticism despite solid operational metrics and global expansion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699092d02c7cdffb0a9d0c38_1771082572737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Primary Market Freeze: IPOs Plunge Amidst Bearish Sentiment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Primary-Market-Freeze-IPOs-Plunge-Amidst-Bearish-Sentiment/699088992c7cdffb0a9c7747</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Primary-Market-Freeze-IPOs-Plunge-Amidst-Bearish-Sentiment/699088992c7cdffb0a9c7747</guid><description>Primary market issuances have plummeted, with January seeing just three companies raise ₹4,765 crore, a sharp drop from December's ₹21,858 crore. This downturn is attributed to bearish secondary market sentiment, disappointing post-listing performances, and eroded retail investor confidence. Experts note that cautious investors are now preferring beaten-down listed stocks over new issues, leading many firms to defer their listings until market conditions stabilize.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699088992c7cdffb0a9c7746_1771079931816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GRSE Lays Keel for GSI Research Vessels, Expands Defence &amp; Civilian Order Book</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GRSE-Lays-Keel-for-GSI-Research-Vessels-Expands-Defence-and-Civilian-Order-Book/6990714f2c7cdffb0a9b3ce6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GRSE-Lays-Keel-for-GSI-Research-Vessels-Expands-Defence-and-Civilian-Order-Book/6990714f2c7cdffb0a9b3ce6</guid><description>Garden Reach Shipbuilders and Engineers Ltd. (GRSE) has commenced construction on two coastal research vessels (CRVs) for the Geological Survey of India (GSI). These 64-meter vessels will feature advanced labs for geological mapping and mineral exploration. GRSE's busy shipyard also manufactures warships, ocean research vessels, and ferries for various clients, showcasing significant diversification.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:57:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990714f2c7cdffb0a9b3ce5_1771073952745.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Economist Warns India Faces Household Debt Shift Trap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Economist-Warns-India-Faces-Household-Debt-Shift-Trap/699070e72c7cdffb0a9b3816</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Economist-Warns-India-Faces-Household-Debt-Shift-Trap/699070e72c7cdffb0a9b3816</guid><description>Indian household debt has surged to 43.1% of GDP, surpassing the five-year average. Dutch economist Dirk Bezemer warns this trend mirrors a dangerous "debt shift" seen in Western economies, where lending moved from businesses to consumers. This reallocation, particularly with rising personal loans outpacing industrial credit, could undermine growth and financial stability. Bezemer highlights vulnerabilities from unsecured loans and mortgages.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:56:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699070e72c7cdffb0a9b3815_1771073988572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asian Energy Services Profit Skyrockets 125% in Q3 to ₹18 Crore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Asian-Energy-Services-Profit-Skyrockets-125percent-in-Q3-to-18-Crore/699070a32c7cdffb0a9b3477</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Asian-Energy-Services-Profit-Skyrockets-125percent-in-Q3-to-18-Crore/699070a32c7cdffb0a9b3477</guid><description>Asian Energy Services posted a stellar Q3, with net profit more than doubling to ₹18 crore from ₹8 crore year-on-year. Revenue surged to ₹235 crore from ₹92 crore, driven by robust project execution, improved operational efficiency, and strong contributions from long-term operations and maintenance (O&amp;M) contracts. The company is also progressing with its merger with Oilmax Energy, targeting completion in Q3 FY27.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:54:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699070a32c7cdffb0a9b3476.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSIL Partners GalaxEye: Boost for India's Private Space Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/NSIL-Partners-GalaxEye-Boost-for-Indias-Private-Space-Sector/699070812c7cdffb0a9b3322</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/NSIL-Partners-GalaxEye-Boost-for-Indias-Private-Space-Sector/699070812c7cdffb0a9b3322</guid><description>NewSpace India Limited (NSIL), the commercial arm of India's Department of Space, has inked a reseller agreement with Bengaluru-based GalaxEye. The deal allows NSIL to market GalaxEye's advanced satellite imagery, including SyncFused OptoSAR data, aiding sectors like agriculture and disaster management. This partnership marks a significant milestone, positioning GalaxEye as the first private Indian satellite operator to collaborate formally with NSIL under such an arrangement, fostering innovation and competitiveness in India's burgeoning space industry.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:54:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699070812c7cdffb0a9b3321.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fiscal Transfers Shift Focus to Performance, GDP</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Transfers-Shift-Focus-to-Performance-GDP/6990701d2c7cdffb0a9b2e6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Transfers-Shift-Focus-to-Performance-GDP/6990701d2c7cdffb0a9b2e6a</guid><description>India's 16th Finance Commission has revised how central taxes are shared with states, maintaining the 41% vertical devolution. However, horizontal distribution now incorporates GDP contribution, a first. Revenue deficit grants are eliminated, while local body and disaster funding incorporate performance benchmarks, signalling a significant shift towards incentivizing growth and fiscal discipline.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:52:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6990701d2c7cdffb0a9b2e69.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ixigo Buys Spanish Train OTA, AI Firm for €12.15M in Europe Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/ixigo-Buys-Spanish-Train-OTA-AI-Firm-for-1215M-in-Europe-Push/69906f652c7cdffb0a9b23fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/ixigo-Buys-Spanish-Train-OTA-AI-Firm-for-1215M-in-Europe-Push/69906f652c7cdffb0a9b23fb</guid><description>Indian travel platform ixigo is embarking on its first major international acquisition, investing €12.15 million to expand into the European market. The company will acquire a 60% stake in Spanish train booking platform Trenes for €11.7 million and a 45% stake in AI solutions provider Sqaas for €0.45 million. This strategic move targets leveraging ixigo's technology and AI leadership within the European travel sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:49:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69906f652c7cdffb0a9b23fa_1771073467269.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FPIs Inject ₹14,160 Cr into India Markets, Signaling Renewed Investor Appetite</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FPIs-Inject-14160-Cr-into-India-Markets-Signaling-Renewed-Investor-Appetite/69906f2b2c7cdffb0a9b211a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FPIs-Inject-14160-Cr-into-India-Markets-Signaling-Renewed-Investor-Appetite/69906f2b2c7cdffb0a9b211a</guid><description>Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) injected ₹14,160 crore into Indian markets during the week ending February 13. This marks sustained buying interest across five consecutive sessions, with equity markets being the primary focus. The inflows indicate a notable shift in sentiment, partly driven by improving clarity on trade deals, although analysts advise caution regarding the sustainability of this trend.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:48:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69906f2b2c7cdffb0a9b2119_1771073465852.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Launches ₹1 Lakh Cr Urban Fund for Market-Led Development</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Launches-1-Lakh-Cr-Urban-Fund-for-Market-Led-Development/699046ba7e6478cdfc279f0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Launches-1-Lakh-Cr-Urban-Fund-for-Market-Led-Development/699046ba7e6478cdfc279f0a</guid><description>India's Union Cabinet approved the ₹1 lakh crore Urban Challenge Fund (UCF) to drive market-linked urban infrastructure development. The fund aims to attract ₹4 lakh crore in investments over five years by shifting from grants to a 25% central assistance and 50% market-funding model. A ₹5,000 crore corpus will enhance creditworthiness for Tier-II/III cities, with a ₹5,000 crore guarantee scheme for smaller urban bodies. Project funding is tied to reform milestones, demanding greater fiscal discipline and governance from ULBs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:56:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699046ba7e6478cdfc279f09.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tiger Logistics: Profit Slips Despite Volume Surge; Valuation Tested</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Tiger-Logistics-Profit-Slips-Despite-Volume-Surge-Valuation-Tested/6990445a7e6478cdfc279ea1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Tiger-Logistics-Profit-Slips-Despite-Volume-Surge-Valuation-Tested/6990445a7e6478cdfc279ea1</guid><description>Tiger Logistics reported a 29.5% year-over-year decline in Q3 FY26 net profit to Rs 593.77 lakhs, with revenue contracting to Rs 13,902 lakhs, even as TEU volumes surged 52%. Despite an expanded EBITDA margin to 6.0%, rising finance costs and normalized global freight rates pressure profitability. This performance follows significant 5-year returns, but a notable recent stock decline and a P/E around 13-14x highlight valuation concerns.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:46:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6990445a7e6478cdfc279ea0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Gold Rush: ETFs Overtake Equities Amidst FOMO</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Gold-Rush-ETFs-Overtake-Equities-Amidst-FOMO/69903bf27e6478cdfc279d43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Gold-Rush-ETFs-Overtake-Equities-Amidst-FOMO/69903bf27e6478cdfc279d43</guid><description>January saw a record ₹33,503 crore flood into Indian gold and silver ETFs, eclipsing equity fund inflows for the first time. This surge, fueled by recent stellar returns and investor anxiety over volatile equity markets, highlights a growing preference for precious metals as safe-haven assets. While experts acknowledge this as a sign of maturing asset allocation, they caution against chasing performance, emphasizing strategic portfolio integration over speculative momentum. The trend signals a significant shift, with silver ETFs notably outperforming gold over recent periods.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:10:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69903bf27e6478cdfc279d42.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Changi Eyes India's Aviation Boom: Partnership Key Amidst Market Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Changi-Eyes-Indias-Aviation-Boom-Partnership-Key-Amidst-Market-Risks/69903afd7e6478cdfc279cf2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Changi-Eyes-Indias-Aviation-Boom-Partnership-Key-Amidst-Market-Risks/69903afd7e6478cdfc279cf2</guid><description>Singapore's Changi Airport Group is actively monitoring India's rapidly expanding aviation market for new project opportunities, emphasizing strategic local partnerships for mutual success. Chairman Lim Ming Yan highlighted Durgapur Airport as a testament to their ability to add value, even as the group weighs further involvement in India's burgeoning infrastructure development. This strategic pursuit balances India's significant growth potential against the inherent operational and regulatory complexities of the market, suggesting a preference for calculated, synergistic ventures.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:06:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69903afd7e6478cdfc279cf1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Infra Surge, Export Ambitions Face Fiscal &amp; Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Infra-Surge-Export-Ambitions-Face-Fiscal-and-Global-Headwinds/69903a117e6478cdfc279caf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Infra-Surge-Export-Ambitions-Face-Fiscal-and-Global-Headwinds/69903a117e6478cdfc279caf</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 allocates ₹12.21 lakh crore to infrastructure, aiming for substantial economic multipliers and export-led growth, with Maharashtra set to be a key beneficiary. However, analysis reveals lingering concerns over fiscal consolidation, the real-world effectiveness of MSME support schemes, and the potential impact of global economic volatility on ambitious trade objectives.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:02:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69903a117e6478cdfc279cae.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Africa's Mineral Wealth: Conversion Deficit Fuels Geopolitical Opportunity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Africas-Mineral-Wealth-Conversion-Deficit-Fuels-Geopolitical-Opportunity/699033b57e6478cdfc279bbe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Africas-Mineral-Wealth-Conversion-Deficit-Fuels-Geopolitical-Opportunity/699033b57e6478cdfc279bbe</guid><description>Africa's estimated $29.5 trillion in mine-site mineral wealth, with $8.6 trillion undeveloped, is gaining strategic importance due to global supply chain realignments. However, the continent captures a fraction of the value, hampered by a "conversion deficit"—a lack of processing capacity and infrastructure. Geopolitical tensions are compelling nations to seek diversified mineral sources, presenting Africa an opportunity to move beyond raw material export. Key developments include Mozambique's graphite expansion, Ghana's gold reserve strategy, and renewed uranium production in Namibia and Niger. Yet, challenges persist, including fragmented geological data and inadequate infrastructure, requiring integrated regional approaches to unlock true economic potential.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:35:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699033b57e6478cdfc279bbd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Giants Forge Global Trust Alliance Amid Geopolitical Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Giants-Forge-Global-Trust-Alliance-Amid-Geopolitical-Strain/699032967e6478cdfc279b69</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Giants-Forge-Global-Trust-Alliance-Amid-Geopolitical-Strain/699032967e6478cdfc279b69</guid><description>Fifteen technology giants, including Amazon Web Services, Microsoft, and Google Cloud, have formed the Trusted Tech Alliance (TTA). This industry group aims to build trust and transparency across connectivity, cloud infrastructure, semiconductors, software, and AI by establishing common, verifiable operating standards. The alliance positions itself as a direct response to rising geopolitical fragmentation, seeking to decouple technology trust from national origin and create a more predictable environment for global investment and digital innovation. Its core principles focus on ethical governance, secure development, robust supply chains, and support for an open digital ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:30:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699032967e6478cdfc279b68.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways: Kavach Rollout Sparks Safety Investment Boom Amidst Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Kavach-Rollout-Sparks-Safety-Investment-Boom-Amidst-Execution-Hurdles/699031297e6478cdfc279ae9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Kavach-Rollout-Sparks-Safety-Investment-Boom-Amidst-Execution-Hurdles/699031297e6478cdfc279ae9</guid><description>Indian Railways has dramatically increased safety expenditure, channeling approximately ₹1.17 lakh crore over the past decade into critical systems like the indigenous Kavach Automatic Train Protection (ATP) and expanded CCTV surveillance. While these investments are credited with a sharp decline in train accidents, the ambitious Kavach rollout faces significant implementation challenges, cost considerations, and a protracted timeline that raises questions about its broader strategic impact on operational efficiency and system modernization.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:24:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699031297e6478cdfc279ae8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Assam's Rs 18,662 Cr Brahmaputra Tunnel: Election Tactic or Infrastructure Leap?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Assams-Rs-18662-Cr-Brahmaputra-Tunnel-Election-Tactic-or-Infrastructure-Leap/69902c007e6478cdfc279a18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Assams-Rs-18662-Cr-Brahmaputra-Tunnel-Election-Tactic-or-Infrastructure-Leap/69902c007e6478cdfc279a18</guid><description>India's Union Cabinet has greenlit the nation's first underwater twin-tube rail and road tunnel project beneath the Brahmaputra River in Assam, slated for completion at an estimated Rs 18,662 crore. The 33.7 km corridor, connecting Gohpur and Numaligarh, faces scrutiny over its strategic election-timed approval and significant cost, prompting a deeper look beyond the immediate infrastructure benefits.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:02:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69902c007e6478cdfc279a17.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Signature Global, RMZ JV: High-Stakes SPR Commercial Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-RMZ-JV-High-Stakes-SPR-Commercial-Push/69902bfd7e6478cdfc279a10</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-RMZ-JV-High-Stakes-SPR-Commercial-Push/69902bfd7e6478cdfc279a10</guid><description>Signature Global and RMZ have formed a 50:50 joint venture to develop a large-scale mixed-use project along Gurugram's Southern Peripheral Road (SPR). RMZ commits Rs 1,283 crore for a 50% stake in the project, which encompasses office buildings, hotels, and retail spaces with a projected total capital value of Rs 14,000–16,000 crore. This move signifies Signature Global's ambitious entry into commercial real estate, a departure from its core affordable housing focus, introducing significant capital and execution considerations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:02:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69902bfd7e6478cdfc279a0f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MF Central: Bridging India's Mutual Fund Tax Complexity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/MF-Central-Bridging-Indias-Mutual-Fund-Tax-Complexity/69902b8a7e6478cdfc2799d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/MF-Central-Bridging-Indias-Mutual-Fund-Tax-Complexity/69902b8a7e6478cdfc2799d8</guid><description>India's mutual fund taxation has become significantly complex due to evolving rules for equity and debt funds, holding periods, and partial redemptions. MF Central, a SEBI-backed utility by CAMS and KFintech, addresses this by providing consolidated investor data, ensuring accuracy in capital gains reporting and ELSS tracking. This platform is vital for investors navigating fragmented portfolios and increased regulatory scrutiny, particularly during the annual tax filing season.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:00:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69902b8a7e6478cdfc2799d7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Softens India Trade Deal Rhetoric Amidst Political Backlash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Softens-India-Trade-Deal-Rhetoric-Amidst-Political-Backlash/69902b127e6478cdfc27999c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Softens-India-Trade-Deal-Rhetoric-Amidst-Political-Backlash/69902b127e6478cdfc27999c</guid><description>Washington has recalibrated its messaging on the interim trade pact with India, revising key factsheets to soften language regarding purchase commitments and removing references to pulses and digital services tax removal. This recalibration follows political controversy in India, suggesting the deal's implementation hinges on navigating domestic sensitivities and underscores the non-binding nature of initial pronouncements. Indian ministers have moved to reassure domestic stakeholders about agricultural protections.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:58:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69902b127e6478cdfc27999b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Delhi P2P Energy Trading Pilot: Hype vs. Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Delhi-P2P-Energy-Trading-Pilot-Hype-vs-Reality/699029aa7e6478cdfc27993e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Delhi-P2P-Energy-Trading-Pilot-Hype-vs-Reality/699029aa7e6478cdfc27993e</guid><description>Delhi Electricity Regulatory Commission (DERC) has approved a pilot for peer-to-peer (P2P) electricity trading, enabling consumers with solar generation to sell surplus power directly to others. While lauded for consumer empowerment and potential cost savings, the initiative faces significant technical hurdles related to grid integration, the economic viability for small-scale prosumers, and the scalability of blockchain-based transactions within the established utility framework. The pilot's success will hinge on navigating these complexities rather than immediate market disruption.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:52:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699029aa7e6478cdfc27993d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fears Spark IT Sell-Off, Valuation Reset Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/AI-Fears-Spark-IT-Sell-Off-Valuation-Reset-Looms/699026d97e6478cdfc2798ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/AI-Fears-Spark-IT-Sell-Off-Valuation-Reset-Looms/699026d97e6478cdfc2798ca</guid><description>The Nifty IT index plunged over 8% this week, marking its worst drop in over a year, driven by escalating fears of Artificial Intelligence (AI) disrupting the sector. Anand Shah of ICICI Prudential AMC characterized the sell-off as a 'valuation reset' rather than an immediate earnings crisis, noting that AI's impact on revenue and margins is still uncertain despite its potential to automate low-end tasks. Shah's firm has maintained an underweight stance on IT for years. Beyond IT, a more favorable economic recovery outlook for 2026 favors stock-picking, with opportunities seen in metals and precious metals supported by global reflationary trends.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:40:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699026d97e6478cdfc2798c9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unveils ₹1.60 Lakh Crore Infra Push Amidst Admin Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Unveils-160-Lakh-Crore-Infra-Push-Amidst-Admin-Shift/6990254c7e6478cdfc2793ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Unveils-160-Lakh-Crore-Infra-Push-Amidst-Admin-Shift/6990254c7e6478cdfc2793ed</guid><description>In a landmark final meeting at South Block, India's Union Cabinet greenlit development projects valued at ₹1.60 lakh crore, encompassing railways, road infrastructure, urban development, and startup funding. This substantial fiscal allocation marks a strategic bid to accelerate economic growth and innovation, coinciding with the government's transition to the new Seva Teerth complex, signifying a new administrative era. The approvals include critical railway line upgrades, an underwater road tunnel, a large urban development fund, and a significant boost for the Startup India Fund of Funds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:33:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6990254c7e6478cdfc2793ec.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Brazil Pact: Securing Minerals, Boosting Pharma &amp; Aviation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Brazil-Pact-Securing-Minerals-Boosting-Pharma-and-Aviation/69901b967e6478cdfc278de7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Brazil-Pact-Securing-Minerals-Boosting-Pharma-and-Aviation/69901b967e6478cdfc278de7</guid><description>India and Brazil are poised to sign key agreements boosting pharmaceutical exports, critical mineral cooperation, and civil aviation development during President Lula da Silva's visit. This initiative is central to India's strategy of enhancing resource security and manufacturing capabilities, leveraging Brazil's significant mineral wealth and market access. The pact also includes visa facilitation, aiming to deepen economic and people-to-people ties.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69901b967e6478cdfc278de6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan: Revenue Leaps, Profitability Dips Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Revenue-Leaps-Profitability-Dips-Sharply/699017d57e6478cdfc278d3c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Revenue-Leaps-Profitability-Dips-Sharply/699017d57e6478cdfc278d3c</guid><description>Anupam Rasayan India Ltd. reported a 31.4% year-over-year revenue increase to ₹512.4 crore for Q3 FY26. Despite this top-line growth, the company's operating profitability faced significant pressure, with EBITDA margins contracting from 31.8% to 24.9%. Net profit rose a modest 11.6% to ₹60.5 crore. This divergence between sales expansion and margin erosion highlights underlying cost challenges and casts a shadow on the company's growth sustainability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:36:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699017d57e6478cdfc278d3b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Reshapes Indian IT: Beyond Market Panic</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Reshapes-Indian-IT-Beyond-Market-Panic/6990176e7e6478cdfc278d19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Reshapes-Indian-IT-Beyond-Market-Panic/6990176e7e6478cdfc278d19</guid><description>The Indian IT sector, including Infosys and TCS, experienced significant value erosion last week as advanced AI capabilities threatened traditional business models. The Nifty IT index saw an 8% dip, erasing billions in market cap. While a pessimistic view sees AI leading to obsolescence, a more nuanced analysis suggests AI could compress development cycles, expand demand, and necessitate a strategic evolution. Simultaneously, AI is transforming the investment process itself, demanding differentiated interpretation from analysts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:34:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6990176e7e6478cdfc278d18.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Judicial Integrity Spotlighted by Recusal Amid Bribery Claims</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Judicial-Integrity-Spotlighted-by-Recusal-Amid-Bribery-Claims/699016e57e6478cdfc278ce9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Judicial-Integrity-Spotlighted-by-Recusal-Amid-Bribery-Claims/699016e57e6478cdfc278ce9</guid><description>A Madras High Court judge has recused himself from hearing a criminal revision case following allegations that a senior advocate accepted ₹50 lakh from a client, purportedly for bribing the judge. The matter has been forwarded to the High Court's Vigilance Cell for investigation. This development intensifies scrutiny on judicial processes, highlighting risks to legal system integrity and potentially impacting investor confidence due to concerns over dispute resolution fairness and efficiency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:32:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699016e57e6478cdfc278ce8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Startup Capital with ₹10,000 Cr Fund</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-Boosts-Startup-Capital-with-10000-Cr-Fund/69900dfe7e6478cdfc278b7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-Boosts-Startup-Capital-with-10000-Cr-Fund/69900dfe7e6478cdfc278b7f</guid><description>The Department for Promotion of Industry and Internal Trade (DPIIT) has allocated another ₹10,000 crore for its Fund of Funds for Startups (FFS 2.0). This significant capital commitment aims to bolster domestic funding pipelines, particularly for ventures in manufacturing and clean technologies, signaling a strategic shift as global venture capital flows become more discerning. The initiative builds upon the success of the original FFS launched in 2016, underscoring a sustained governmental focus on nurturing India's entrepreneurial ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:54:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69900dfe7e6478cdfc278b7e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Productivity Push: Can Execution Bridge Scale vs. Gains?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Productivity-Push-Can-Execution-Bridge-Scale-vs-Gains/69900d757e6478cdfc278b40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Productivity-Push-Can-Execution-Bridge-Scale-vs-Gains/69900d757e6478cdfc278b40</guid><description>India is pivoting from 'growth at scale' to 'productivity growth' for its 'Viksit Bharat @2047' vision, a strategy detailed by KPMG. The plan prioritizes manufacturing depth, MSME competitiveness, and human capital. However, translating capital investment into sustainable productivity gains faces significant challenges, including persistent regulatory complexities, a skills gap, and the need to scale smaller enterprises effectively. While global supply chain diversification offers opportunities, historical reform impacts on manufacturing productivity remain mixed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:51:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69900d757e6478cdfc278b3f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Natco Pharma Gains Generic Semaglutide Nod Amid Patent War</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Natco-Pharma-Gains-Generic-Semaglutide-Nod-Amid-Patent-War/699001577e6478cdfc27807f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Natco-Pharma-Gains-Generic-Semaglutide-Nod-Amid-Patent-War/699001577e6478cdfc27807f</guid><description>Hyderabad-based Natco Pharma has received approval from India's CDSCO to manufacture and market a generic semaglutide injection, with a planned launch in March 2026. This critical diabetes treatment's market entry, however, is shadowed by ongoing patent revocation suits filed by Natco Pharma and Dr. Reddy's Laboratories against originator Novo Nordisk's patent rights. The company's stock closed lower on Friday, reflecting investor caution regarding the legal battles.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:00:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699001577e6478cdfc27807e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerages Pick 10 Stocks for Upside Amidst Market Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerages-Pick-10-Stocks-for-Upside-Amidst-Market-Dip/698fff8e7e6478cdfc27801d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Brokerages-Pick-10-Stocks-for-Upside-Amidst-Market-Dip/698fff8e7e6478cdfc27801d</guid><description>Amidst a market decline, leading brokerages have pinpointed ten Indian companies exhibiting resilience and growth potential. Firms like Motilal Oswal, Citi, Jefferies, Nuvama, and Axis Securities issued 'Buy' ratings, citing strong earnings, capacity expansions, and market share gains. Hindalco Industries, Eicher Motors, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, Apollo Hospitals, Kotak Mahindra Bank, State Bank of India, and others are highlighted for their distinct operational strengths and favorable outlooks, suggesting selective opportunities amidst broader economic headwinds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:52:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698fff8e7e6478cdfc27801c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>