<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Ingersoll Rand India Surges on Expansion Outlook, Masks Profit Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ingersoll-Rand-India-Surges-on-Expansion-Outlook-Masks-Profit-Dip/698ec7ff119a61fe896f4261</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ingersoll-Rand-India-Surges-on-Expansion-Outlook-Masks-Profit-Dip/698ec7ff119a61fe896f4261</guid><description>Ingersoll Rand India shares experienced a notable surge, driven by a positive growth outlook presented by management, which overshadowed a 7.5% year-over-year profit decline in Q3 FY26. Revenue climbed 19.24% to ₹455.5 crore. The company's expansion into its new Sanand, Gujarat manufacturing facility, a key part of its 'Make in India' strategy and localization efforts, underpins management's confidence in doubling growth over the next few years.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Transgene Biotek Plunges into Deeper Loss, Operations Frozen by SEBI Over Fraud History</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Transgene-Biotek-Plunges-into-Deeper-Loss-Operations-Frozen-by-SEBI-Over-Fraud-History/698ec7bb119a61fe896f424a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Transgene-Biotek-Plunges-into-Deeper-Loss-Operations-Frozen-by-SEBI-Over-Fraud-History/698ec7bb119a61fe896f424a</guid><description>Transgene Biotek Limited posted a sharp increase in its net loss for the third quarter of FY26, with revenue declining year-on-year. The company's operations are currently paralyzed due to a SEBI prohibitory order freezing its bank accounts and assets, stemming from an unpaid penalty. This follows a history of fraud allegations related to Global Depository Receipts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:42:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ec7bb119a61fe896f4249.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Defence Sector Surges on ₹3.6T Procurement; Budget Boosts Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Defence-Sector-Surges-on-36T-Procurement-Budget-Boosts-Outlook/698ec74b119a61fe896f41fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Defence-Sector-Surges-on-36T-Procurement-Budget-Boosts-Outlook/698ec74b119a61fe896f41fe</guid><description>The Nifty India Defence index is trading firm following the Defence Acquisition Council's (DAC) approval of ₹3.6 trillion in procurement proposals, including Rafale jets and P-8I aircraft. The Union Budget 2026 further bolsters the sector with a record ₹7.85 lakh crore allocation, emphasizing domestic manufacturing and enhancing order visibility for key players like HAL, Bharat Electronics, and Bharat Dynamics amidst a strengthening geopolitical outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Flexi Cap Fund Hits ₹1 Lakh Cr AUM</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/HDFC-Flexi-Cap-Fund-Hits-1-Lakh-Cr-AUM/698ec718119a61fe896f416b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/HDFC-Flexi-Cap-Fund-Hits-1-Lakh-Cr-AUM/698ec718119a61fe896f416b</guid><description>HDFC Flexi Cap Fund has surpassed ₹1 lakh crore in Assets Under Management (AUM), a significant milestone achieved on February 13, 2026. This achievement, attributed to the fund's flexible investment mandate and a robust, research-driven process, reflects sustained investor trust. The fund's strategy allows dynamic allocation across market capitalizations and sectors, appealing to investors seeking diversified exposure amid evolving market conditions. This growth aligns with a broader trend of increased inflows into equity mutual funds, particularly within the flexi-cap category, underscoring HDFC Asset Management Company's strong position in the Indian financial sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Profit Divergence: Eternal Soars, Swiggy's Losses Widen</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Profit-Divergence-Eternal-Soars-Swiggys-Losses-Widen/698ec6cd119a61fe896f4141</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Profit-Divergence-Eternal-Soars-Swiggys-Losses-Widen/698ec6cd119a61fe896f4141</guid><description>In early February 2026, food delivery giants Eternal and Swiggy have posted notable stock gains, outperforming the broader market. Eternal reported a significant 73% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹102 crore on a 202% revenue surge in Q3FY26. In stark contrast, Swiggy's net loss widened to ₹1,065 crore despite a 54% revenue jump. Analysts maintain positive targets for both, but Eternal's profitability and Swiggy's persistent losses present a critical divergence.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Stalin's ₹5000 Payout: TN Election Fiscal Strategy Unpacked</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Stalins-5000-Payout-TN-Election-Fiscal-Strategy-Unpacked/698ec6b4119a61fe896f4111</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Stalins-5000-Payout-TN-Election-Fiscal-Strategy-Unpacked/698ec6b4119a61fe896f4111</guid><description>Tamil Nadu Chief Minister M.K. Stalin initiated a significant pre-election fiscal maneuver, crediting ₹5,000 to 13.1 million women beneficiaries under the Kalaignar Women's Rights Scheme. This advance disbursement, comprising three months' advance entitlement and a special summer package, aims to preempt electoral code disruptions and consolidate support. The move is framed alongside a promise to elevate monthly assistance to ₹2,000 under a future 'Dravidian Model 2.0' governance framework, intensifying competitive populism in the state's political landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jaipur Hygiene Breach: McDonald's Faces Brand Risk Amidst Franchise Oversight</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Jaipur-Hygiene-Breach-McDonalds-Faces-Brand-Risk-Amidst-Franchise-Oversight/698ec670119a61fe896f4098</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Jaipur-Hygiene-Breach-McDonalds-Faces-Brand-Risk-Amidst-Franchise-Oversight/698ec670119a61fe896f4098</guid><description>Indian food safety authorities have issued a formal warning to a McDonald's outlet in Jaipur, citing the discovery of reused cooking oil unfit for consumption and spoiled tomatoes. The franchise, Connaught Plaza Restaurants (CPRPL), has been given 14 days to implement corrective actions, facing stricter measures if non-compliance persists. This incident underscores ongoing challenges in maintaining global operational and hygiene standards across McDonald's extensive presence in India, a market with significant competitive pressures and stringent regulatory scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Telecom Debt Clarity: SC Spectrum Ruling Hits Insolvency Shield</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Telecom-Debt-Clarity-SC-Spectrum-Ruling-Hits-Insolvency-Shield/698ec5c5119a61fe896f3e49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Telecom-Debt-Clarity-SC-Spectrum-Ruling-Hits-Insolvency-Shield/698ec5c5119a61fe896f3e49</guid><description>The Supreme Court has ruled that telecom spectrum cannot be shielded by insolvency moratoriums for licence and spectrum dues owed to the government. This decision reclassifies spectrum as a community resource, not a corporate asset, significantly altering how distressed telecom operators can manage their liabilities. The ruling prioritizes public interest over corporate restructuring for this vital national resource, impacting future insolvency proceedings and government recovery efforts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JK Tyre Q3 Profit Surges 3.7x on Record Sales &amp; Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JK-Tyre-Q3-Profit-Surges-37x-on-Record-Sales-and-Margin-Gains/698ec566119a61fe896f3e1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JK-Tyre-Q3-Profit-Surges-37x-on-Record-Sales-and-Margin-Gains/698ec566119a61fe896f3e1e</guid><description>JK Tyre &amp; Industries reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 15% to ₹4,235 Cr and Profit After Tax soaring 3.7 times to ₹209 Cr. The company also announced a significant capacity expansion and secured new EV tyre approvals, signaling a positive growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:32:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ec566119a61fe896f3e1d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BF Utilities Faces Fines, Risk of Promoter Holding Freeze Over Delayed Results</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Faces-Fines-Risk-of-Promoter-Holding-Freeze-Over-Delayed-Results/698ec4f4119a61fe896f3db4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Faces-Fines-Risk-of-Promoter-Holding-Freeze-Over-Delayed-Results/698ec4f4119a61fe896f3db4</guid><description>BF Utilities Limited is facing regulatory action for failing to submit its consolidated unaudited financial results for the September 2025 quarter by the deadline. Stock exchanges BSE and NSE have imposed fines, and there's a risk of promoter shareholding being frozen if compliance isn't met. This adds to previous regulatory scrutiny for the company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:30:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ec4f4119a61fe896f3db3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Auto Sales Surge: Volume Up, But Margin Squeeze Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Sales-Surge-Volume-Up-But-Margin-Squeeze-Looms/698ec3b7119a61fe896f3c1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Sales-Surge-Volume-Up-But-Margin-Squeeze-Looms/698ec3b7119a61fe896f3c1c</guid><description>Domestic vehicle dispatches from Indian manufacturers to dealers saw robust year-on-year growth in January 2026. Passenger vehicles increased by 13%, two-wheelers by 26%, and three-wheelers by 30%. This surge, fueled by sustained demand and favorable policies, masks underlying challenges for the industry, including escalating input costs and intensifying competition, which could impact profitability despite volume gains. Major players like Maruti Suzuki, Tata Motors, and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra reported significant unit sales, but profitability will depend on managing these emergent pressures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: GCCs Pivot to Value Creation via Tax Reforms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Budget-2026-GCCs-Pivot-to-Value-Creation-via-Tax-Reforms/698ec235119a61fe896f38c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Budget-2026-GCCs-Pivot-to-Value-Creation-via-Tax-Reforms/698ec235119a61fe896f38c0</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 introduces significant tax certainty measures, including an expanded Safe Harbour regime and reduced Advance Pricing Agreement timelines, designed to bolster India's appeal for financial services Global Capability Centers (GCCs). This shift is expected to transition GCCs from mere cost-optimization hubs to strategic centers for innovation and risk-managed expansion, attracting higher-value work and long-term investments. The move aligns with global trends in IT spending and BPO growth, positioning India as a stable, globally competitive financial ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>UGRO Capital Confirms Fund Use for Growth &amp; Profectus Buy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UGRO-Capital-Confirms-Fund-Use-for-Growth-and-Profectus-Buy/698ec228119a61fe896f3853</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UGRO-Capital-Confirms-Fund-Use-for-Growth-and-Profectus-Buy/698ec228119a61fe896f3853</guid><description>UGRO Capital has received confirmation from India Ratings that funds raised via recent preferential and rights issues are being utilized as planned. Notably, proceeds are part-funding the acquisition of Profectus Capital Private Limited and bolstering the company's lending base, though a significant portion from an earlier preferential issue remains unutilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:18:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ec228119a61fe896f3852.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BF Utilities Slumps: Q3 Revenue Halved, Auditor Flags ₹500 Cr Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Slumps-Q3-Revenue-Halved-Auditor-Flags-500-Cr-Risk/698ec21f119a61fe896f384d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Slumps-Q3-Revenue-Halved-Auditor-Flags-500-Cr-Risk/698ec21f119a61fe896f384d</guid><description>BF Utilities Ltd. reported a steep 78.6% year-on-year revenue drop for Q3 FY26, with total revenue falling to ₹4.53 Cr. The company posted a net loss of ₹233.43 Cr. A major concern is the auditor's qualified conclusion due to a ₹500 Cr arbitration claim against a subsidiary and other unresolved investment issues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:18:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ec21f119a61fe896f384c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Honda India Power Revenue Jumps 32% But Profit Drops on Labour Code Impact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Honda-India-Power-Revenue-Jumps-32percent-But-Profit-Drops-on-Labour-Code-Impact/698ec1a3119a61fe896f371c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Honda-India-Power-Revenue-Jumps-32percent-But-Profit-Drops-on-Labour-Code-Impact/698ec1a3119a61fe896f371c</guid><description>Honda India Power Products Limited reported a strong 32.43% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹270.40 Cr in Q3 FY26. However, Profit After Tax (PAT) declined by 12.68% YoY to ₹16.67 Cr, primarily due to an exceptional charge of ₹11.84 Cr recognized for the statutory impact of new Labour Codes. The company also declared an interim dividend of 35%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:16:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ec1a3119a61fe896f371b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oswal Pumps Surges 33% Revenue, But Receivables Climb</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oswal-Pumps-Surges-33percent-Revenue-But-Receivables-Climb/698ec0b3119a61fe896f3448</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oswal-Pumps-Surges-33percent-Revenue-But-Receivables-Climb/698ec0b3119a61fe896f3448</guid><description>Oswal Pumps Limited reported a solid third quarter for FY'26, with total income jumping 33.4% year-on-year to ₹507.7 crore. Profit after tax grew to ₹91.6 crore. The company maintained its strong growth guidance, supported by government schemes like PM KUSUM. However, a significant increase in receivable days to 157 days, mainly due to delayed payments from Maharashtra government customers, and rising input costs are key concerns investors will be watching closely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:12:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ec0b3119a61fe896f3447.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lincoln Pharma: Growth Surge Meets Regulatory Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lincoln-Pharma-Growth-Surge-Meets-Regulatory-Hurdles/698ec0b3119a61fe896f3441</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lincoln-Pharma-Growth-Surge-Meets-Regulatory-Hurdles/698ec0b3119a61fe896f3441</guid><description>Lincoln Pharmaceuticals Limited posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with net profit jumping 37.70% to ₹28.60 crore and revenue growing 13.49% to ₹166.32 crore. The company's ambitious target of ₹1,000 crore revenue in three years is underpinned by a CRISIL A/Stable rating. However, despite this financial uplift, Lincoln Pharmaceuticals navigates a competitive regulatory environment and faces headwinds from working-capital intensity, requiring strategic responses to maintain growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dilip Buildcon Secures Gujarat ATF Pipeline Project Worth ₹124 Crore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Dilip-Buildcon-Secures-Gujarat-ATF-Pipeline-Project-Worth-124-Crore/698ec03e119a61fe896f33e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Dilip-Buildcon-Secures-Gujarat-ATF-Pipeline-Project-Worth-124-Crore/698ec03e119a61fe896f33e4</guid><description>Dilip Buildcon Limited (DBL) has received a Letter of Award (LOA) from the Petroleum and Natural Gas Regulatory Board (PNGRB) for an Air Turbine Fuel (ATF) pipeline project in Gujarat. The project, valued at approximately ₹124 crore for Engineering, Procurement, and Construction (EPC) works, comes with a 25-year exclusive license. DBL plans to execute the project over 24 months through a Special Purpose Vehicle.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:10:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ec03e119a61fe896f33e3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BF Utilities Posts Loss, Auditors Raise Red Flags Over ₹500 Cr Arbitration</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Posts-Loss-Auditors-Raise-Red-Flags-Over-500-Cr-Arbitration/698ec03a119a61fe896f33d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BF-Utilities-Posts-Loss-Auditors-Raise-Red-Flags-Over-500-Cr-Arbitration/698ec03a119a61fe896f33d5</guid><description>BF Utilities Limited reported a standalone net loss of ₹2.33 crore for Q3 FY26, a significant worsening from the previous quarter and the same period last year. The company's auditor issued a qualified conclusion, citing material uncertainties related to a ₹500 crore arbitration case, impairment of a subsidiary investment, and a long-standing advance to another subsidiary. Despite these concerns, the board approved the re-appointment of G. D. Apte &amp; Co. as statutory auditors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:10:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ec03a119a61fe896f33d4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Muthoot Finance Plunges 12% on Gold Volatility Despite Strong Earnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Plunges-12percent-on-Gold-Volatility-Despite-Strong-Earnings/698ebfcd119a61fe896f3332</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Plunges-12percent-on-Gold-Volatility-Despite-Strong-Earnings/698ebfcd119a61fe896f3332</guid><description>Muthoot Finance experienced a significant 12% share price decline on February 13, 2026, driven by heightened volatility in gold prices. This downturn occurred despite the company reporting strong operational and financial results for the December quarter of FY26, including a 95% year-on-year net profit increase. Investor sentiment appears more sensitive to the unpredictable bullion market, which impacts loan-to-value ratios and disbursement growth, than to the company's recent performance metrics. The broader market's weakness also contributed to the selling pressure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nifty Metal Tumbles 3% on Profit Booking; Analysts Urge 'Buy the Dip'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nifty-Metal-Tumbles-3percent-on-Profit-Booking-Analysts-Urge-Buy-the-Dip/698ebfca119a61fe896f332a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nifty-Metal-Tumbles-3percent-on-Profit-Booking-Analysts-Urge-Buy-the-Dip/698ebfca119a61fe896f332a</guid><description>The Nifty Metal index fell 3% on Friday, hitting 11,863.65, as investors booked profits after a sustained rally. Analysts attribute the decline to broader market risk aversion and global sentiment, but maintain a positive long-term outlook for the sector, recommending selective buying on dips.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>US Growth Surges on AI, But Equity Peaks Near as Currency Fears Mount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Growth-Surges-on-AI-But-Equity-Peaks-Near-as-Currency-Fears-Mount/698ebf9b119a61fe896f32fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Growth-Surges-on-AI-But-Equity-Peaks-Near-as-Currency-Fears-Mount/698ebf9b119a61fe896f32fe</guid><description>The U.S. economy is projected to grow by 2.8% in 2026, propelled by substantial AI investment directly boosting GDP and supporting equity markets. BofA Global Research anticipates supportive fiscal and monetary policies will further bolster activity. However, significant equity market gains appear constrained, with upside largely priced in from the previous year. Simultaneously, a rally in gold prices signals underlying investor concern over fiat currency stability amidst elevated global deficits. The Federal Reserve faces policy shifts under its new nominee, with market expectations for rate cuts becoming more uncertain following strong jobs data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:07:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Repair Costs Fuel Auto Insurance Hikes, Not Accidents</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Tech-Repair-Costs-Fuel-Auto-Insurance-Hikes-Not-Accidents/698ebefb119a61fe896f322d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Tech-Repair-Costs-Fuel-Auto-Insurance-Hikes-Not-Accidents/698ebefb119a61fe896f322d</guid><description>Motor insurance premiums are escalating, driven by advanced vehicle technology inflating repair costs, not increased accident frequency. This trend, pronounced with electric vehicles, strains insurer payouts and highlights policyholder misconceptions about coverage benefits and claim costs. Price-led buying and underinsurance expose consumers to significant out-of-pocket expenses, even as the sector forecasts robust growth. Major players like ICICI Lombard and Bajaj Allianz navigate this complex pricing environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IEX Shares Dip as Regulatory Battle Over Market Coupling Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IEX-Shares-Dip-as-Regulatory-Battle-Over-Market-Coupling-Looms/698ebed4119a61fe896f3220</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IEX-Shares-Dip-as-Regulatory-Battle-Over-Market-Coupling-Looms/698ebed4119a61fe896f3220</guid><description>Indian Energy Exchange (IEX) shares experienced a notable decline on February 13th, following the Appellate Tribunal for Electricity (APTEL) dismissal of its plea challenging the Central Electricity Regulatory Commission's (CERC) market coupling directive. While IEX retains the option to challenge future regulations, the ruling signifies a prolonged period of regulatory scrutiny and potential disruption to its dominant market position. This event compounds existing investor concerns regarding the ultimate impact of market coupling on the company's revenue model and competitive standing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>US Inflation Eases, But Sticky Pressures &amp; Affordability Crisis Remain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Inflation-Eases-But-Sticky-Pressures-and-Affordability-Crisis-Remain/698ebe83119a61fe896f31b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Inflation-Eases-But-Sticky-Pressures-and-Affordability-Crisis-Remain/698ebe83119a61fe896f31b8</guid><description>January US inflation is forecast to slow, with core prices potentially hitting a near five-year low. However, monthly price increases and a persistent affordability crisis suggest underlying pressures. Economists are divided on the Federal Reserve's next moves, with inflation remaining above target and tariff impacts lingering. Wage growth has shown modest gains, but real purchasing power is still recovering from pandemic-era shocks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Silver Resilience: India Prices Surge Amidst Global Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Resilience-India-Prices-Surge-Amidst-Global-Volatility/698ebe21119a61fe896f309f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Resilience-India-Prices-Surge-Amidst-Global-Volatility/698ebe21119a61fe896f309f</guid><description>Silver prices in India climbed 2.22% on February 13, 2026, reaching ₹243 per gram for a single unit and ₹242,950 per kilogram. This appreciation mirrors international stability near $76 per troy ounce, occurring despite a broad market sell-off in equities and cryptocurrencies. The precious metal's underlying support stems from ongoing debasement concerns and a strategic rotation into hard assets, signaling investor preference for tangible wealth as Federal Reserve policy outlook evolves.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MIC Electronics &amp; Refit Global Forge Alliance for Circular Tech Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MIC-Electronics-and-Refit-Global-Forge-Alliance-for-Circular-Tech-Future/698ebd6b119a61fe896f2ea1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MIC-Electronics-and-Refit-Global-Forge-Alliance-for-Circular-Tech-Future/698ebd6b119a61fe896f2ea1</guid><description>MIC Electronics Limited has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) with Refit Global Private Limited to explore a strategic transaction. The goal is to combine MIC's manufacturing expertise with Refit's refurbished electronics platforms to create a next-generation circular electronics platform. This collaboration aims to drive sustainable growth and accelerate digital inclusion, subject to due diligence and approvals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:58:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ebd6b119a61fe896f2ea0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IHCL Stock Dips Despite Profit Surge: Market Weighs Earnings Quality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/IHCL-Stock-Dips-Despite-Profit-Surge-Market-Weighs-Earnings-Quality/698ebcf9119a61fe896f2e67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/IHCL-Stock-Dips-Despite-Profit-Surge-Market-Weighs-Earnings-Quality/698ebcf9119a61fe896f2e67</guid><description>The Indian Hotels Company (IHCL) saw its share price decline 4% despite reporting a 50.86% surge in Q3 net profit to ₹954.24 crore. This robust profit was significantly bolstered by a ₹327 crore gain from the sale of a joint venture stake. Revenue increased by 12.19% to ₹2,841.96 crore. However, a sharp divergence in analyst ratings from Nuvama Institutional Equities ('Reduce') and Motilal Oswal ('Buy') highlights market apprehension regarding IHCL's sustained operational growth and premium valuation, overshadowing the headline profit increase. The stock's recent performance reflects this uncertainty, with a six-month decline of 8.8%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Climbs Amid Fear; Fed Stance &amp; Strong Labor Data Pose Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Climbs-Amid-Fear-Fed-Stance-and-Strong-Labor-Data-Pose-Risk/698ebc85119a61fe896f2db7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Climbs-Amid-Fear-Fed-Stance-and-Strong-Labor-Data-Pose-Risk/698ebc85119a61fe896f2db7</guid><description>Gold prices experienced a notable surge on February 13, 2026, driven by investor anxieties stemming from fears of AI disruption in US equity markets and geopolitical tensions. However, unexpectedly strong US labor data has tempered expectations for Federal Reserve rate cuts, bolstering the US dollar and presenting a counterforce to gold's safe-haven appeal. While central bank buying and currency debasement concerns provide underlying support, the immediate outlook suggests potential for range-bound trading as the market digests conflicting economic signals. Indian gold prices continue to command a premium over international benchmarks, including Dubai.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Navin Fluorine Posts Stellar Q3 Results: Profit Surges 122% on Strong Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Navin-Fluorine-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-Profit-Surges-122percent-on-Strong-Margin-Gains/698ebc7a119a61fe896f2dad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Navin-Fluorine-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-Profit-Surges-122percent-on-Strong-Margin-Gains/698ebc7a119a61fe896f2dad</guid><description>Navin Fluorine International Limited reported a stellar third quarter for FY26, with profit after tax soaring 122% year-on-year to ₹185 Cr. The company achieved a remarkable 47% revenue growth and saw its EBITDA nearly double, driven by strong pricing power and improved operating efficiencies. Management expressed confidence in continued growth, backed by capacity expansions and a robust pipeline in specialty chemicals and advanced materials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:54:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ebc7a119a61fe896f2dac.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Buys Punj Lloyd: NCLT Greenlights 'Clean Slate' Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Buys-Punj-Lloyd-NCLT-Greenlights-Clean-Slate-Acquisition/698ebafa119a61fe896f2964</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Buys-Punj-Lloyd-NCLT-Greenlights-Clean-Slate-Acquisition/698ebafa119a61fe896f2964</guid><description>The National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) has approved Adani Infra (India) Limited's plan to acquire Punj Lloyd Limited for ₹281.10 crore. The acquisition, sanctioned on a 'going concern' basis, will provide Adani Infra with a 'clean slate' under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC), shielding it from Punj Lloyd's past liabilities. This move signals Adani Group's aggressive expansion in the infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:47:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ebafa119a61fe896f2963.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sri Ramakrishna Mills: Sales Surge 16% But Pre-Tax Profit Dips 47%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Sri-Ramakrishna-Mills-Sales-Surge-16percent-But-Pre-Tax-Profit-Dips-47percent/698eba9d119a61fe896f294e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Sri-Ramakrishna-Mills-Sales-Surge-16percent-But-Pre-Tax-Profit-Dips-47percent/698eba9d119a61fe896f294e</guid><description>Sri Ramakrishna Mills announced robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue climbing 16% year-on-year to ₹8,673.66 Cr. Net profit surged by 169.7% to ₹181.70 Cr. However, Profit Before Tax saw a significant 47.0% decrease YoY. The company also reported a reduced loss from the sale of assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:46:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eba9d119a61fe896f294d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shilpa Medicare inks global pact for new drug development, boosts CDMO future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Shilpa-Medicare-inks-global-pact-for-new-drug-development-boosts-CDMO-future/698eba24119a61fe896f26f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Shilpa-Medicare-inks-global-pact-for-new-drug-development-boosts-CDMO-future/698eba24119a61fe896f26f0</guid><description>Shilpa Medicare Limited has signed a binding agreement with Switzerland-based NXI Therapeutics AG for the development, manufacturing, and supply of a New Chemical Entity (NCE) targeting autoimmune and alloimmune disorders. This move reinforces Shilpa's strategy to act as a global innovation partner and expand its Contract Development and Manufacturing Organization (CDMO) services, leveraging its integrated capabilities in high-value therapeutics. The company aims to enhance its participation in innovation-driven pipelines, though it has a history of regulatory scrutiny from the USFDA.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:44:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eba24119a61fe896f26ef.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jindal Stainless and Railways Forge Path for India's First Steel Salt Container</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Stainless-and-Railways-Forge-Path-for-Indias-First-Steel-Salt-Container/698eb935119a61fe896f25a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Stainless-and-Railways-Forge-Path-for-Indias-First-Steel-Salt-Container/698eb935119a61fe896f25a1</guid><description>Jindal Stainless has teamed up with Indian Railways to develop and trial the nation's first corrosion-resistant stainless steel container for bulk salt transport. This innovation aims to slash maintenance costs, boost durability, and promote sustainability in logistics, aligning with the 'Make in India' initiative. With a FY25 turnover of ₹40,182 crore, the company targets 4.2 million tonnes capacity by FY27, signalling robust growth ambitions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:40:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eb935119a61fe896f25a0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sri Ramakrishna Mills Posts Huge Loss as Sales Plunge 79%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Sri-Ramakrishna-Mills-Posts-Huge-Loss-as-Sales-Plunge-79percent/698eb933119a61fe896f259a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Sri-Ramakrishna-Mills-Posts-Huge-Loss-as-Sales-Plunge-79percent/698eb933119a61fe896f259a</guid><description>Sri Ramakrishna Mills (Coimbatore) Ltd. reported a stark financial downturn. For the quarter ending December 31, 2025, net sales plummeted 79% year-on-year to ₹1,578.68 Cr, leading to a net loss of ₹114.31 Cr, a sharp reversal from last year's profit. The nine-month period also saw significant sales decline and a shift to net loss, with total income dropping over 63%. The company noted no real estate income was recognized in the periods.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:40:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eb933119a61fe896f2599.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MKVentures Q3 Results: Standalone Profit Falls, Consolidated PAT Soars Amid Revenue Drop</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/MKVentures-Q3-Results-Standalone-Profit-Falls-Consolidated-PAT-Soars-Amid-Revenue-Drop/698eb8cd119a61fe896f24d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/MKVentures-Q3-Results-Standalone-Profit-Falls-Consolidated-PAT-Soars-Amid-Revenue-Drop/698eb8cd119a61fe896f24d1</guid><description>MKVentures Capital Limited reported mixed Q3 FY26 results. Standalone revenue surged 58% YoY, but PAT declined 33% YoY. Conversely, consolidated revenue dropped 41% YoY, yet PAT jumped a massive 646% YoY. The company declared a final dividend of ₹0.25 per share.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:38:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698eb8cd119a61fe896f24d0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Growth Outpaces Flows: AI Focus, Trade Risks Challenge Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Growth-Outpaces-Flows-AI-Focus-Trade-Risks-Challenge-Investors/698eb868119a61fe896f247f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Growth-Outpaces-Flows-AI-Focus-Trade-Risks-Challenge-Investors/698eb868119a61fe896f247f</guid><description>Amundi Investment Institute observes a significant gap between India's robust economic growth and foreign portfolio investment. Despite structural advantages, investors are prioritizing AI opportunities and remain cautious over trade frictions, leading to FPI outflows in 2025. However, recent trade agreements and liberalized regulations, such as 100% FDI in insurance, are drawing renewed attention, particularly for direct investment and fixed income.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Forge Surges on Dual Catalysts: Defense Orders and Auto Rebound</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Forge-Surges-on-Dual-Catalysts-Defense-Orders-and-Auto-Rebound/698eb84d119a61fe896f246f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Forge-Surges-on-Dual-Catalysts-Defense-Orders-and-Auto-Rebound/698eb84d119a61fe896f246f</guid><description>Bharat Forge's stock price surged to a 52-week high, propelled by a robust defense order book exceeding ₹11,130 crore and positive management outlook for high double-digit growth in FY27. The company secured significant new orders in Q3 FY26, including a substantial defense segment contribution, alongside expectations of a rebound in the automotive sector. This dual-engine growth strategy is positioning the company for a potential valuation re-rating, despite current high multiples.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Disruption Sparks Indian IT Sell-off, Re-evaluating Sector Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Disruption-Sparks-Indian-IT-Sell-off-Re-evaluating-Sector-Valuations/698eb84a119a61fe896f2467</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Disruption-Sparks-Indian-IT-Sell-off-Re-evaluating-Sector-Valuations/698eb84a119a61fe896f2467</guid><description>Indian IT stocks are experiencing a severe sell-off, driven by AI disruption fears, particularly the 'Anthropic shock,' which threatens the sector's labor-intensive model and application service revenues. The Nifty IT index has plunged significantly year-to-date, with major firms hitting multi-month or 52-week lows. While broader Indian economic indicators remain robust, the IT sector faces a critical need for adaptation amid analyst warnings of further pain and potential structural shifts in valuation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineers India Surges on Q3 Beat, Eyes Global Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Engineers-India-Surges-on-Q3-Beat-Eyes-Global-Growth/698eb6df119a61fe896f19b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Engineers-India-Surges-on-Q3-Beat-Eyes-Global-Growth/698eb6df119a61fe896f19b0</guid><description>Engineers India Ltd. shares rose sharply on February 13, 2026, after reporting a more than threefold increase in net profit to ₹347.2 crore for the December quarter. Revenue jumped 58.3% year-on-year to ₹1,210.2 crore, with EBITDA margins expanding significantly to 29.1%. The company also secured its largest overseas contract to date, a $360 million deal with Nigeria's Dangote Group. International operations now account for 65% of fresh order inflows, signaling a key growth driver.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>