<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:48:42 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Oil Surges on Iran Fears; Trump Navigates Election Price Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Surges-on-Iran-Fears-Trump-Navigates-Election-Price-Risk/699667e1d25eafd9cd0002a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Surges-on-Iran-Fears-Trump-Navigates-Election-Price-Risk/699667e1d25eafd9cd0002a2</guid><description>Escalating geopolitical tensions surrounding potential U.S. military action in Iran have propelled oil prices above $70 a barrel. This surge presents a significant challenge for President Trump, who must weigh international security imperatives against the risk of alienating voters with higher gasoline prices ahead of upcoming mid-term elections. Diplomatic talks remain stalled, while the conflict in Ukraine further complicates global energy supply dynamics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:31:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699667e1d25eafd9cd0002a1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infra Stocks: Axis Direct Picks RITES, Kalpataru, Ahluwalia Amidst Sector Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Infra-Stocks-Axis-Direct-Picks-RITES-Kalpataru-Ahluwalia-Amidst-Sector-Boom/699667d7d25eafd9cd00028b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Infra-Stocks-Axis-Direct-Picks-RITES-Kalpataru-Ahluwalia-Amidst-Sector-Boom/699667d7d25eafd9cd00028b</guid><description>Axis Direct has identified RITES Ltd, Kalpataru Projects International, and Ahluwalia Contracts as key investment opportunities within India's non-road infrastructure sector. The brokerage highlights robust order backlogs and strong revenue visibility as primary drivers for these companies. RITES Ltd is targeted at ₹275, Kalpataru Projects International at ₹1,450, and Ahluwalia Contracts at ₹915, suggesting potential upsides of approximately 25%, 29%, and 13%, respectively. This positive outlook is underpinned by government capital expenditure and a growing infrastructure demand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:31:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699667d7d25eafd9cd00028a_1771464837600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asia Gains Amid US Data Strength; Oil Surge Adds Geopolitical Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Asia-Gains-Amid-US-Data-Strength-Oil-Surge-Adds-Geopolitical-Risk/69966768d25eafd9cd00022a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Asia-Gains-Amid-US-Data-Strength-Oil-Surge-Adds-Geopolitical-Risk/69966768d25eafd9cd00022a</guid><description>Asian stock markets extended gains for a second day, mirroring a strong performance in US equities driven by robust industrial production, business equipment orders, and housing data. The technology sector showed resilience, easing some artificial intelligence-related jitters. However, a significant surge in oil prices, attributed to escalating US-Iran geopolitical tensions, introduced a potential headwind for regional economies. The MSCI Asia Pacific Index advanced, with Japan and Australia leading the gains, while South Korea's KOSPI reached a new record high.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:29:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69966768d25eafd9cd000229.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Investor Risk: Life Changes Trump Market Crashes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Investor-Risk-Life-Changes-Trump-Market-Crashes/69966607d25eafd9cd0000b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Investor-Risk-Life-Changes-Trump-Market-Crashes/69966607d25eafd9cd0000b2</guid><description>Indian financial portfolios are built for market conditions, not the chaotic realities of life. Major life events like job changes, buying homes, or starting families disrupt cash flows and shift priorities, often leading to compromised investments. Traditional planning overlooks this "life-event risk," where portfolios weaken not from market volatility, but from personal transitions that demand liquidity and redirect financial focus, ultimately impacting long-term goals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:23:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69966607d25eafd9cd0000b1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Refiners Tap Venezuela Crude Amid Shifting Geopolitics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Refiners-Tap-Venezuela-Crude-Amid-Shifting-Geopolitics/69966600d25eafd9cd000099</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Refiners-Tap-Venezuela-Crude-Amid-Shifting-Geopolitics/69966600d25eafd9cd000099</guid><description>Bharat Petroleum Corporation and HPCL Mittal Energy Ltd. have initiated significant crude oil procurements from Venezuela, marking Bharat Petroleum's first-ever purchase and HPCL Mittal Energy Ltd.'s first in two years. The companies acquired one million barrels each of Merey crude, opting for co-loading on a very large crude carrier to reduce shipping expenses. This strategic move diversifies India's crude import mix as refiners reduce reliance on Russian supplies, a shift enabled by recent U.S. licensing for Venezuelan oil trade. The deals underscore a broader recalibration of global energy flows, seeking cost efficiencies and supply stability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:23:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69966600d25eafd9cd000098.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Banking Reforms: Committee Tackles Sector's Complex Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banking-Reforms-Committee-Tackles-Sectors-Complex-Future/69966580d25eafd9cd00001f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banking-Reforms-Committee-Tackles-Sectors-Complex-Future/69966580d25eafd9cd00001f</guid><description>India establishes a High-Level Committee on Banking Reforms to address critical structural issues. The agenda includes PSB consolidation, enhancing retail deposits, reviving rural banking, and adapting to new lending frontiers, aiming to modernize the financial sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:21:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69966580d25eafd9cd00001e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia Forges India AI Ecosystem via AIGI Partnership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Forges-India-AI-Ecosystem-via-AIGI-Partnership/6996641ed25eafd9cdffff6c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Forges-India-AI-Ecosystem-via-AIGI-Partnership/6996641ed25eafd9cdffff6c</guid><description>Nvidia is deepening its strategic engagement with India's burgeoning artificial intelligence sector by partnering with AI Grants India (AIGI) via its Inception startup program. The initiative targets empowering up to 500 early-stage AI companies over the next 12 months, offering access to Nvidia's extensive developer tools, infrastructure, and ecosystem support. This move is a calculated effort to foster innovation and solidify Nvidia's foundational position within India's rapidly growing AI economy, anticipating future demand and countering competitor inroads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:15:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996641ed25eafd9cdffff6b_1771463871891.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Small Caps Soar: Defense, EVs, AI Drive Outperformance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Small-Caps-Soar-Defense-EVs-AI-Drive-Outperformance/69966061d25eafd9cdfffd53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Small-Caps-Soar-Defense-EVs-AI-Drive-Outperformance/69966061d25eafd9cdfffd53</guid><description>Amidst a volatile Indian equity market, several small-cap stocks have delivered exceptional returns, far exceeding the Nifty Smallcap 250 index. Force Motors, Hindustan Copper, Netweb Technologies, Kirloskar Oil Engines, and RBL Bank demonstrate how targeted catalysts—including defense contracts, electric vehicle demand, AI infrastructure, B2B restructuring, and strategic capital infusions—are powering significant growth and investor confidence, even as broader market indices show modest gains.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:59:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69966061d25eafd9cdfffd52.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Value Retail Boom: Divergent Strategies, Mixed Fortunes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Value-Retail-Boom-Divergent-Strategies-Mixed-Fortunes/69966059d25eafd9cdfffd3c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Value-Retail-Boom-Divergent-Strategies-Mixed-Fortunes/69966059d25eafd9cdfffd3c</guid><description>India's expanding economy and urbanization are fueling a value retail boom, with companies like Vishal Mega Mart, ABFRL, and V2 Retail vying for market share. While Vishal Mega Mart focuses on scale and private labels with strong buy ratings, V2 Retail pursues aggressive expansion in smaller towns, also garnering buy recommendations. Aditya Birla Fashion and Retail (ABFRL) is pivoting to premiumization but faces net losses and a neutral analyst outlook, highlighting a divergence in strategic execution and financial health within the sector's growth narrative.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:59:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69966059d25eafd9cdfffd3b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goldiam's Hidden Luxury: LGD Pivot Fuels Export Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Luxury-Products/Goldiams-Hidden-Luxury-LGD-Pivot-Fuels-Export-Margins/69966059d25eafd9cdfffd25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Luxury-Products/Goldiams-Hidden-Luxury-LGD-Pivot-Fuels-Export-Margins/69966059d25eafd9cdfffd25</guid><description>Goldiam International has decisively shifted 90.5% of its sales to lab-grown diamond (LGD) jewellery, capitalizing on surging US consumer demand and affordability trends. This B2B export focus generated consolidated revenues of ₹340 crore in Q3 FY26, boasting impressive EBITDA margins of 26.7%. With over ₹504 crore in cash reserves, the company is well-positioned to navigate export market volatility and growing global LGD capacity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:59:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69966059d25eafd9cdfffd24_1771462955804.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Pharma Bets on AI for Global Quality Edge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indian-Pharma-Bets-on-AI-for-Global-Quality-Edge/69966053d25eafd9cdfffce5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indian-Pharma-Bets-on-AI-for-Global-Quality-Edge/69966053d25eafd9cdfffce5</guid><description>The Indian pharmaceutical sector is undergoing a profound digital transformation, leveraging Artificial Intelligence (AI) to move beyond traditional quality management. With significant investments and deployments, companies are enhancing manufacturing consistency, streamlining regulatory compliance, and improving patient safety. This strategic shift is crucial for meeting global standards and maintaining competitiveness, as AI-driven quality systems become foundational for future growth and market access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:58:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69966053d25eafd9cdfffce4_1771462810318.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Turmoil Fuels Mega Trade Bloc Formation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Turmoil-Fuels-Mega-Trade-Bloc-Formation/69965fe3d25eafd9cdfffc60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Turmoil-Fuels-Mega-Trade-Bloc-Formation/69965fe3d25eafd9cdfffc60</guid><description>Navigating global economic uncertainty and escalating geopolitical rivalries, middle powers are consolidating into a new economic alliance. An expanded Comprehensive and Progressive Agreement for Trans-Pacific Partnership (CPTPP), with India and the EU as anchors, is proposed to counter the weaponization of trade and supply chains. This bloc, projected to command significant global GDP and trade volume, aims to leverage the growth of emerging economies with the advanced technology of mature nations to protect national interests and foster stability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:57:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69965fe3d25eafd9cdfffc5f_1771462752809.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Sovereign AI Leap: Sarvam AI Challenges Global Giants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Sovereign-AI-Leap-Sarvam-AI-Challenges-Global-Giants/69965ef7d25eafd9cdfffba1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Sovereign-AI-Leap-Sarvam-AI-Challenges-Global-Giants/69965ef7d25eafd9cdfffba1</guid><description>Sarvam AI has unveiled a 105-billion-parameter large language model (LLM), a significant stride in India's "sovereign AI" strategy. Trained from scratch with government backing, the model claims parity with global frontier systems and superiority in Indian language benchmarks over competitors like DeepSeek R1 and Google's Gemini 2.5 Flash. This launch positions India to build state-of-the-art AI domestically, enhancing technological independence and aiming to compete on the global stage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69965ef7d25eafd9cdfffba0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty 50 Nears 26,000: Domestic Flows Mask Valuation &amp; AI Scramble</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-50-Nears-26000-Domestic-Flows-Mask-Valuation-and-AI-Scramble/69965d88d25eafd9cdfffacf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-50-Nears-26000-Domestic-Flows-Mask-Valuation-and-AI-Scramble/69965d88d25eafd9cdfffacf</guid><description>Indian equity markets, led by the Nifty 50 index, have extended gains for four consecutive sessions, approaching the 26,000 mark. This upward momentum is primarily supported by robust domestic institutional investor inflows, countering cautious foreign investor activity. While macroeconomic fundamentals remain stable with benign inflation and strong GDP growth projections, the rally faces headwinds. Valuations, though below their five-year average, maintain a premium over regional emerging markets. Significant earnings growth is needed to justify current levels, particularly as India lags behind AI-centric Asian economies in attracting capital. The market sentiment is bifurcated, with some analysts projecting substantial upside based on earnings growth and domestic flows, while others warn of global headwinds and potential corrections.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:47:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69965d88d25eafd9cdffface.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Next Wave: Science Over AGI Hype Fuels Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Next-Wave-Science-Over-AGI-Hype-Fuels-Growth/699659d1d25eafd9cdfff9bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Next-Wave-Science-Over-AGI-Hype-Fuels-Growth/699659d1d25eafd9cdfff9bf</guid><description>Demis Hassabis of Google DeepMind positions Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) as a 5-10 year prospect, cautioning current systems are flawed. He asserts AI's most profound near-term impact will be accelerating scientific breakthroughs, not causing widespread job losses. This scientific focus, exemplified by AlphaFold's Nobel recognition, shifts the investment narrative towards AI as a research tool, while persistent risks in biological misuse and cybersecurity governance remain critical considerations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:31:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699659d1d25eafd9cdfff9be_1771461196962.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Navigates $100B AI Investment Race: Sovereignty vs. Big Tech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Navigates-100B-AI-Investment-Race-Sovereignty-vs-Big-Tech/69965433d25eafd9cdfff842</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Navigates-100B-AI-Investment-Race-Sovereignty-vs-Big-Tech/69965433d25eafd9cdfff842</guid><description>Global tech titans are pouring over $100 billion into India's artificial intelligence sector, aiming to bridge the AI adoption gap and tap into the nation's vast talent pool. Microsoft leads with a $50 billion pledge for the Global South, including a substantial $17.5 billion for India. Amazon and Google follow with $35 billion and $15 billion respectively, focusing on infrastructure and skilling. While these investments promise significant economic uplift and job creation, they amplify concerns over digital sovereignty and the potential for increased reliance on foreign technology platforms. India faces a critical balancing act: harnessing this capital for genuine, homegrown AI leadership while safeguarding national interests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:07:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69965433d25eafd9cdfff841_1771459752557.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>