<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:32:03 +0000</pubDate><item><title>UBS India Hiring Surge Masks Global Talent Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UBS-India-Hiring-Surge-Masks-Global-Talent-Shift/698cec1eba46a4833be07677</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UBS-India-Hiring-Surge-Masks-Global-Talent-Shift/698cec1eba46a4833be07677</guid><description>UBS is set to hire up to 3,000 individuals in India, a figure comparable to planned job reductions in Switzerland following the Credit Suisse integration. This strategic expansion into Hyderabad, focusing on technology and AI, effectively doubles the bank's local workforce and points towards a significant global operational realignment. While direct links are denied, the move highlights a broader trend of financial institutions optimizing costs and talent acquisition in emerging tech hubs, potentially creating a competitive advantage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Inox Green Bids ₹600 Crore for Wind World O&amp;M Portfolio</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Inox-Green-Bids-600-Crore-for-Wind-World-OandM-Portfolio/698cd909ba46a4833be06f23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Inox-Green-Bids-600-Crore-for-Wind-World-OandM-Portfolio/698cd909ba46a4833be06f23</guid><description>Inox Green Energy Services has submitted a bid of ₹550 crore to ₹600 crore for Wind World India's renewable energy operation and maintenance (O&amp;M) portfolio. The bid is part of a court-driven process for Wind World, which is undergoing corporate insolvency proceedings. This move signals potential consolidation within India's renewable energy services sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Prime City Rents Jump 25%; Employees Flee High Costs to Outskirts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Prime-City-Rents-Jump-25percent-Employees-Flee-High-Costs-to-Outskirts/698cd875ffb05f82f2202aa8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Prime-City-Rents-Jump-25percent-Employees-Flee-High-Costs-to-Outskirts/698cd875ffb05f82f2202aa8</guid><description>Rents in prime Indian cities like Mumbai, Delhi, and Bengaluru surged up to 25% in 2025 due to rising property prices, return-to-office mandates, and strong corporate demand. This surge is forcing employees to seek housing farther from city centers, with experts predicting continued upward trends in 2026, though affordability pressures may shift demand to peripheral areas.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Opens Insurance FDI to 100%, but Controls Signal Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Opens-Insurance-FDI-to-100percent-but-Controls-Signal-Caution/698cd484ffb05f82f2202892</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Opens-Insurance-FDI-to-100percent-but-Controls-Signal-Caution/698cd484ffb05f82f2202892</guid><description>India has formally enabled 100% foreign direct investment (FDI) in its insurance sector via the automatic route, effective February 5, 2026. This liberalization, stemming from the "Sabka Bima Sabki Raksha" Act, aims to inject capital and foster competition. However, stringent conditions, including mandatory resident Indian leadership in foreign-invested firms and a 20% cap on FDI in the Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC), indicate a calibrated approach to market opening.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Xiaomi India's Premium Gamble: High Stakes Pivot Amidst Market Saturation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Xiaomi-Indias-Premium-Gamble-High-Stakes-Pivot-Amidst-Market-Saturation/698cd22be0bf654360011a4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Xiaomi-Indias-Premium-Gamble-High-Stakes-Pivot-Amidst-Market-Saturation/698cd22be0bf654360011a4d</guid><description>Xiaomi India is aggressively shifting its strategy from high-volume smartphones to premium ecosystem products to counter declining sales and rising prices in 2026. The company targets affluent consumers with high-end handsets and a broader range of connected devices, aiming to increase its ecosystem revenue contribution from 15-17% to 30%. This pivot comes as the Indian premium smartphone market sees significant growth, led by Apple and Samsung, while Xiaomi's market share has contracted due to intense competition and difficulties in penetrating higher price segments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's E-comm: Record Orders, Worker Unrest, Valuation Pressure Grows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-E-comm-Record-Orders-Worker-Unrest-Valuation-Pressure-Grows/698cc858e0bf654360010a7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-E-comm-Record-Orders-Worker-Unrest-Valuation-Pressure-Grows/698cc858e0bf654360010a7d</guid><description>India's leading consumer internet platforms are posting record orders and high valuations, largely driven by ultra-fast delivery promises. However, this growth narrative is increasingly strained by widespread gig worker strikes and mounting discontent. Experts warn that prioritizing speed over workforce stability creates a structural imbalance, risking reputational damage and challenging the sustainability of current market valuations. The core tension pits consumer demand for convenience against company margin pressures and worker demands for better earnings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:20:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cc858e0bf654360010a7c_1770834310491.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Thorium Fuel Push: Hype vs. Hurdles for NTPC &amp; CCTE</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Thorium-Fuel-Push-Hype-vs-Hurdles-for-NTPC-and-CCTE/698cc65ce0bf65436000e9ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Thorium-Fuel-Push-Hype-vs-Hurdles-for-NTPC-and-CCTE/698cc65ce0bf65436000e9ae</guid><description>India's state-owned NTPC Ltd. is partnering with US-based Clean Core Thorium Energy (CCTE) to explore thorium-based ANEEL fuel for its Pressurized Heavy Water Reactors (PHWRs). While the recent SHANTI Act aims to open the nuclear sector to private players and boost energy security, significant regulatory, technical, and economic challenges persist for large-scale deployment of this advanced fuel. This collaboration aims to leverage India's vast thorium reserves but faces a complex path to widespread adoption, contrasting with the promising narrative of energy independence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:11:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cc65ce0bf65436000e9ad_1770833734265.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Meridian Secures $17M for AI Financial Modeling IDE</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meridian-Secures-17M-for-AI-Financial-Modeling-IDE/698cc511084da0f0c7c7a640</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meridian-Secures-17M-for-AI-Financial-Modeling-IDE/698cc511084da0f0c7c7a640</guid><description>Meridian has secured $17 million in seed funding, valuing the AI financial modeling startup at $100 million post-money. Led by Andreessen Horowitz and General Partnership, the investment fuels Meridian's mission to enhance predictability and auditability in financial analysis via a standalone, IDE-like platform. The company reports early traction with $5 million in December contracts, indicating strong demand for its innovative approach that aims to condense hours-long modeling tasks into minutes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:06:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cc511084da0f0c7c7a63f_1770833581000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Toll Revenue Soars: Digital Payments Fuel Economic Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Toll-Revenue-Soars-Digital-Payments-Fuel-Economic-Surge/698cc125084da0f0c7c79e0e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Toll-Revenue-Soars-Digital-Payments-Fuel-Economic-Surge/698cc125084da0f0c7c79e0e</guid><description>India's national highways are poised to achieve record toll collection in fiscal year 2026, with ₹50,345 crore collected in the first three quarters alone. This surge, driven by electronic toll collection (FASTag) and multi-lane free flow systems, demonstrates increased economic activity and traffic volume. The sector's growth is supported by significant government infrastructure spending, though key players exhibit varied valuations and execution risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:49:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cc125084da0f0c7c79e0d_1770832388723.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rolls-Royce Eyes India as Strategic Global Hub for High-Value Engineering</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rolls-Royce-Eyes-India-as-Strategic-Global-Hub-for-High-Value-Engineering/698cc0ee084da0f0c7c79d9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rolls-Royce-Eyes-India-as-Strategic-Global-Hub-for-High-Value-Engineering/698cc0ee084da0f0c7c79d9b</guid><description>Rolls-Royce CEO Tufan Erginbilgic's meeting with Prime Minister Narendra Modi underscored a significant strategic pivot: elevating India from a key market to a "home market" and a global hub for advanced engineering and defense co-development. The company aims to leverage India's burgeoning industrial ecosystem and "Viksit Bharat" initiative to scale high-value manufacturing, expand its Global Centre of Excellence, and co-create next-generation aerospace and propulsion systems. This move signals a deeper integration into India's defense modernization efforts and a strategy to bolster global supply chain resilience.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:48:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cc0ee084da0f0c7c79d9a_1770832475885.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vikram Solar Unpledges 26% Shares, Secures ₹3,200 Cr Credit Facility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Vikram-Solar-Unpledges-26percent-Shares-Secures-3200-Cr-Credit-Facility/698cc0d5084da0f0c7c79cfd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Vikram-Solar-Unpledges-26percent-Shares-Secures-3200-Cr-Credit-Facility/698cc0d5084da0f0c7c79cfd</guid><description>Vikram Solar Limited has inked a significant working capital consortium agreement, led by Indian Bank, for facilities up to ₹3,200 crores. A major highlight is the release of 9,49,60,893 equity shares, representing 26.21% of the company's total equity, which were previously pledged by promoters. This move enhances financial flexibility and reduces promoter risk, bolstering the company's operational capacity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:48:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cc0d5084da0f0c7c79cfc_1770832527779.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Black Box Revenue Up 10.5%, But Auditor Flags Forex Rule Breach</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Black-Box-Revenue-Up-105percent-But-Auditor-Flags-Forex-Rule-Breach/698cbfe3084da0f0c7c79a59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Black-Box-Revenue-Up-105percent-But-Auditor-Flags-Forex-Rule-Breach/698cbfe3084da0f0c7c79a59</guid><description>Black Box Limited reported a 10.5% YoY revenue jump to ₹1,659.58 Cr in Q3 FY26, but consolidated net profit declined 11.4% to ₹49.68 Cr due to significant exceptional expenses. The auditor's report highlighted non-compliance with FEMA for foreign exchange remittances and export proceeds, a notable red flag for investors. Standalone results also showed a net loss.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:44:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cbfe3084da0f0c7c79a58_1770832150540.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Infrastructure Dream: Decades of Delays Plague Highways</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Infrastructure-Dream-Decades-of-Delays-Plague-Highways/698cbf6d084da0f0c7c79a2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Infrastructure-Dream-Decades-of-Delays-Plague-Highways/698cbf6d084da0f0c7c79a2a</guid><description>Despite ambitious targets and proven rapid construction capabilities, India's North-South and East-West corridors, along with major expressways, remain mired in delays exceeding two decades. Systemic issues like land acquisition bottlenecks, contractor performance failures, and financial constraints are contributing to massive cost overruns and project stagnation, creating a significant drag on national development and investor confidence. The sheer scale of ongoing project delays, affecting hundreds of central initiatives, underscores a deep-seated challenge in translating infrastructure allocation into tangible completion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:42:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cbf6d084da0f0c7c79a29_1770832023728.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Swiss Watch Sector Faces Transition Amidst Market Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Swiss-Watch-Sector-Faces-Transition-Amidst-Market-Shifts/698cbcc5fa94ce7dec4eca93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Swiss-Watch-Sector-Faces-Transition-Amidst-Market-Shifts/698cbcc5fa94ce7dec4eca93</guid><description>The Swiss watch industry is experiencing significant shifts, marked by executive restructuring at Greubel Forsey and Audemars Piguet's strategic product diversification. Reduced U.S. tariffs in late 2025 provided a vital export boost, yet the sector grapples with persistent currency volatility and global demand fluctuations. The secondary market continues its professionalization, offering transparency and access as collectors increasingly prioritize intrinsic value and brand heritage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:30:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cbcc5fa94ce7dec4eca92_1770831518370.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Prudential AMC Secures RBI Nod for IDFC FIRST Bank Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Prudential-AMC-Secures-RBI-Nod-for-IDFC-FIRST-Bank-Stake/698cbb5ffa94ce7dec4e8a3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Prudential-AMC-Secures-RBI-Nod-for-IDFC-FIRST-Bank-Stake/698cbb5ffa94ce7dec4e8a3e</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has granted approval for ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company Limited and related ICICI Bank group entities to acquire an aggregate stake of up to 9.95% in IDFC FIRST Bank. This regulatory clearance allows ICICI Prudential AMC to build a significant shareholding, subject to specific conditions and a one-year timeline. The move occurs amidst robust M&amp;A activity in India's financial sector, where IDFC FIRST Bank trades at a premium valuation compared to larger peers, supported by generally positive analyst sentiment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:24:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cbb5ffa94ce7dec4e8a3d_1770830988113.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindalco's Novelis Fire: Cash Hit Doubles, Recovery Dragged</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindalcos-Novelis-Fire-Cash-Hit-Doubles-Recovery-Dragged/698cbb3cfa94ce7dec4e898d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindalcos-Novelis-Fire-Cash-Hit-Doubles-Recovery-Dragged/698cbb3cfa94ce7dec4e898d</guid><description>Hindalco Industries revised its 2026 cash flow projection downward by $1.3 billion to $1.6 billion due to a fire at its Novelis plant in New York. This substantially higher estimate, compared to earlier projections, indicates prolonged operational disruptions and a delayed restart of the affected mill, now slated for the second quarter of 2026. The incident continues to affect downstream customers, including Ford Motor, and highlights increasing supply chain vulnerabilities in the global aluminium sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:24:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cbb3cfa94ce7dec4e898c_1770830992811.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Ethics Push: Core Banking Risk or Compliance Cost?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Ethics-Push-Core-Banking-Risk-or-Compliance-Cost/698cbabcfa94ce7dec4e88ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Ethics-Push-Core-Banking-Risk-or-Compliance-Cost/698cbabcfa94ce7dec4e88ff</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India Deputy Governor Swaminathan J has framed ethics as a foundational control for banking stability, not a mere 'soft theme.' This emphasis signals a potential shift towards more stringent regulatory oversight and impacts institutional credibility and customer trust. Banks, particularly those trading at premium valuations, face heightened scrutiny, where ethical adherence directly influences risk assessment and stock repricing. The RBI's ongoing governance reforms further underscore this commitment to integrity across the sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:22:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cbabcfa94ce7dec4e88fe_1770830837138.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta's 'Green Copper' Bid Hits Regulatory Wall Amidst Sterlite Legacy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedantas-Green-Copper-Bid-Hits-Regulatory-Wall-Amidst-Sterlite-Legacy/698cba65fa94ce7dec4e6c2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedantas-Green-Copper-Bid-Hits-Regulatory-Wall-Amidst-Sterlite-Legacy/698cba65fa94ce7dec4e6c2a</guid><description>Vedanta Ltd. is contesting the Tamil Nadu Pollution Control Board's (TNPCB) rejection of its 'green copper' plant application at the Madras High Court. The TNPCB cited environmental concerns, a stance Vedanta argues is arbitrary and ignores its revised, eco-friendlier proposal. This legal battle reignites debates surrounding the Sterlite plant's controversial history and Vedanta's environmental track record, casting a shadow over its future operational prospects in the region. The company's 'green' initiative aims for reduced carbon footprint through recycled inputs and renewable energy, but faces significant regulatory hurdles and historical skepticism.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:20:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cba65fa94ce7dec4e6c29_1770830711020.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hind Rectifiers Posts Record Revenue, Announces 1:1 Bonus Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hind-Rectifiers-Posts-Record-Revenue-Announces-11-Bonus-Share/698cb8defa94ce7dec4e18e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hind-Rectifiers-Posts-Record-Revenue-Announces-11-Bonus-Share/698cb8defa94ce7dec4e18e1</guid><description>Hind Rectifiers Limited (HREL) reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue soaring 64.2% YoY to a record ₹277.4 crore. The company announced a 1:1 bonus share issuance, rewarding shareholders and enhancing liquidity. Strategic acquisition of BeLink Solutions in France establishes a European hub, while backward integration in copper conductors targets cost efficiencies. Despite minor margin compression in Q3 consolidated, PAT grew 30.1% YoY, and key ratios like ROE and ROCE saw significant year-on-year improvements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:14:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb8defa94ce7dec4e18e0_1770830349774.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>POWERGRID Wins Maharashtra Transmission Project via Competitive Bid</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/POWERGRID-Wins-Maharashtra-Transmission-Project-via-Competitive-Bid/698cb60dfa94ce7dec4dd139</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/POWERGRID-Wins-Maharashtra-Transmission-Project-via-Competitive-Bid/698cb60dfa94ce7dec4dd139</guid><description>Power Grid Corporation of India Limited (POWERGRID) has been declared the successful bidder for a significant intra-state transmission project in Maharashtra, awarded through the Tariff Based Competitive Bidding (TBCB) process. The project, focused on the Pune region, will be developed on a Build, Own, Operate and Transfer (BOOT) basis, securing long-term revenue streams and enhancing grid stability. This strategic win reinforces POWERGRID's role in expanding India's power transmission infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:02:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb60dfa94ce7dec4dd138_1770829626055.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cube Highways Trust Retains Top 'AAA' Credit Rating From Crisil</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Cube-Highways-Trust-Retains-Top-AAA-Credit-Rating-From-Crisil/698cb51dfa94ce7dec4dcfcf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Cube-Highways-Trust-Retains-Top-AAA-Credit-Rating-From-Crisil/698cb51dfa94ce7dec4dcfcf</guid><description>Cube Highways Trust, through its Investment Manager, has secured a reaffirmation of its highest credit ratings from Crisil. Total bank loan facilities aggregating ₹13,850 crore retain CRISIL AAA/Stable, alongside CRISIL A1+ for short-term instruments. Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) and Commercial Papers also maintained top ratings, signifying robust financial stability and the lowest credit risk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:58:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb51dfa94ce7dec4dcfce_1770829387237.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GTT Data Solutions Posts 818% Revenue Surge, But Losses Widen</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GTT-Data-Solutions-Posts-818percent-Revenue-Surge-But-Losses-Widen/698cb4dbfa94ce7dec4dcf94</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GTT-Data-Solutions-Posts-818percent-Revenue-Surge-But-Losses-Widen/698cb4dbfa94ce7dec4dcf94</guid><description>GTT Data Solutions Limited has reported a staggering 817.8% year-on-year increase in consolidated revenue for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹4,214.59 Lakhs. Despite this top-line explosion, the company's net loss widened to ₹182.60 Lakhs from ₹100.88 Lakhs in the prior year's quarter. To fuel growth and acquisitions, the board approved a ₹125 Crore rights issue and advanced its strategy with significant stake acquisitions in subsidiaries. Auditors flagged delays in IP acquisitions due to tax compliance issues.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:56:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb4dbfa94ce7dec4dcf93_1770829300435.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vivriti's ₹5000 Cr Fund: Tapping East India's Yield Seekers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Vivritis-5000-Cr-Fund-Tapping-East-Indias-Yield-Seekers/698cb41ffa94ce7dec4dce33</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Vivritis-5000-Cr-Fund-Tapping-East-Indias-Yield-Seekers/698cb41ffa94ce7dec4dce33</guid><description>Vivriti Asset Management is launching a ₹5,000 crore diversified bond fund, with a ₹2,000 crore greenshoe option, targeting Q2 FY27. The firm is strategically focusing on Eastern India's high-net-worth individuals and family offices to fuel a 40% expansion in its private credit assets under management by FY27. This move leverages demand for yield-generating, lower-volatility investments beyond equities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:53:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb41ffa94ce7dec4dce32_1770829068780.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PFC-REC Merger: Govt Stake Dilution Emerges as Key Hurdle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFC-REC-Merger-Govt-Stake-Dilution-Emerges-as-Key-Hurdle/698cb2e9fa94ce7dec4dbcc7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFC-REC-Merger-Govt-Stake-Dilution-Emerges-as-Key-Hurdle/698cb2e9fa94ce7dec4dbcc7</guid><description>The boards of Power Finance Corporation (PFC) and Rural Electrification Corporation (REC) have greenlit a merger, creating a consolidated entity with a ₹11.5 lakh crore loan book. While intended to boost scale and efficiency in the power financing sector, a significant challenge looms: the government's stake in PFC could fall below the 51% threshold required for a 'government company' status due to share dilution from the merger. This necessitates potential capital infusion or alternative strategies from the government.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:48:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb2e9fa94ce7dec4dbcc6_1770828865502.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vivriti AMC eyes East India expansion for yield-seeking capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Vivriti-AMC-eyes-East-India-expansion-for-yield-seeking-capital/698cb2e7fa94ce7dec4dbcbf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Vivriti-AMC-eyes-East-India-expansion-for-yield-seeking-capital/698cb2e7fa94ce7dec4dbcbf</guid><description>Vivriti Asset Management is targeting Eastern India, particularly West Bengal and Odisha, for investment opportunities in quick-service restaurants (QSR), fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG), and steel. The firm aims to tap into a growing demand from family offices and high-net-worth individuals (HNIs) seeking yield with lower volatility than equity markets. This strategic push coincides with the planned launch of Vivriti's fourth fund, aiming for a base size of ₹3,000 crore with a green-shoe option of ₹2,000 crore. Vivriti's existing debt portfolio exceeds ₹10,000 crore, with an average investment tenure of 3-3.5 years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:48:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb2e7fa94ce7dec4dbcbe_1770828782097.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Electrotherm Posts Heavy Losses; Auditor Flags Going Concern Red Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Electrotherm-Posts-Heavy-Losses-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Red-Flags/698cb206fa94ce7dec4db829</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Electrotherm-Posts-Heavy-Losses-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Red-Flags/698cb206fa94ce7dec4db829</guid><description>Electrotherm (India) Limited has reported substantial net losses for both the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, with standalone net loss at ₹35.50 Crores and consolidated at ₹35.42 Crores for the quarter. Revenue declined 16.4% YoY to ₹903.79 Crores. Crucially, the auditor's limited review highlighted a qualified opinion due to non-provision of ₹1026.92 Crores in interest on NPA loan accounts and raised material uncertainties regarding the going concern status of several subsidiaries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:44:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb206fa94ce7dec4db828_1770828584161.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Niyogin Fintech Surges on Strong Q3: iServeU Drives 70% Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Niyogin-Fintech-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-iServeU-Drives-70percent-Revenue-Growth/698cb186fa94ce7dec4c27a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Niyogin-Fintech-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-iServeU-Drives-70percent-Revenue-Growth/698cb186fa94ce7dec4c27a5</guid><description>Niyogin Fintech reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue surging 70% year-over-year to ₹28.9 Cr. The fintech arm, iServeU, was a major growth engine, more than doubling its revenue YoY to ₹21.2 Cr and contributing significantly to a PBT turnaround. The NBFC segment also showed improved profitability and AUM growth. Management reiterated FY26 guidance, signaling continued optimism.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:42:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb186fa94ce7dec4c27a4_1770828545601.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Universus Photo Q3: Standalone Revenue Drops 19%, Consolidated Swings to Deep Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Universus-Photo-Q3-Standalone-Revenue-Drops-19percent-Consolidated-Swings-to-Deep-Loss/698cb166fa94ce7dec4c1aa9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Universus-Photo-Q3-Standalone-Revenue-Drops-19percent-Consolidated-Swings-to-Deep-Loss/698cb166fa94ce7dec4c1aa9</guid><description>Universus Photo Imagings Limited reported a challenging Q3 FY26, with standalone revenue down 19.58% YoY to ₹384 lakh and Profit After Tax (PAT) declining 34.06% to ₹302 lakh. The nine-month standalone performance also saw significant drops. On a consolidated basis, while the net loss for the quarter improved year-on-year, the company swung from a substantial profit of ₹10,806 lakh in 9M FY25 to a net loss of ₹6,687 lakh in 9M FY26, heavily impacted by associate losses, including €23.38 million from JPF Netherlands B.V. Management provided no outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:42:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb166fa94ce7dec4c1aa8_1770828470129.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's New Rules: Bank Sales Face Overhaul, Compliance Costs Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-New-Rules-Bank-Sales-Face-Overhaul-Compliance-Costs-Surge/698cb14dfa94ce7dec4c1239</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-New-Rules-Bank-Sales-Face-Overhaul-Compliance-Costs-Surge/698cb14dfa94ce7dec4c1239</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is ushering in a new era of consumer protection for banking customers, with draft guidelines slated to become effective July 1, 2026. These regulations mandate rigorous 'suitability' assessments for all financial products, ban deceptive 'dark patterns' in digital interfaces, and impose strict penalties for mis-selling, including full refunds and compensation. Banks face significant operational adjustments, increased compliance costs, and potential impacts on sales volumes and profitability as they adapt to these enhanced accountability measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:41:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb14dfa94ce7dec4c1238_1770828431527.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Tax Overhaul: Perqs Rise, Choices Complicate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Tax-Overhaul-Perqs-Rise-Choices-Complicate/698cb140fa94ce7dec4c0dfc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Tax-Overhaul-Perqs-Rise-Choices-Complicate/698cb140fa94ce7dec4c0dfc</guid><description>India's forthcoming Income Tax Rules overhaul, effective April 2026, substantially revise perquisite valuations, including higher limits for meals and car allowances. While aiming for simplification, the expansion of certain exemptions, particularly for House Rent Allowance (HRA) under the old tax regime, creates a strategic dilemma for salaried employees. This necessitates complex personal tax calculations to determine the optimal regime, potentially shifting focus from immediate consumption to long-term savings and forcing significant administrative adjustments for employers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:41:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb140fa94ce7dec4c0dfb_1770828310272.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TMB's Sales Pivot: Tech Drive Meets Risky Lending Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/TMBs-Sales-Pivot-Tech-Drive-Meets-Risky-Lending-Surge/698cb111fa94ce7dec4bf551</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/TMBs-Sales-Pivot-Tech-Drive-Meets-Risky-Lending-Surge/698cb111fa94ce7dec4bf551</guid><description>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank (TMB) is executing a significant strategic shift, reallocating 50-60% of its workforce to sales roles over two years, driven by substantial technology investments. Concurrently, the bank is increasing its focus on unsecured advances, a departure from past caution. While automation aims to boost efficiency and a ₹250 crore tech outlay is planned for FY26-FY27, this aggressive pivot raises questions about execution risk and potential impacts on asset quality amidst evolving regulatory scrutiny of unsecured lending.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:40:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb111fa94ce7dec4bf550_1770828421864.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Resilience Tested: Growth Signals Clash With Market Selloff</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Resilience-Tested-Growth-Signals-Clash-With-Market-Selloff/698cb0aefa94ce7dec4bd7f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Resilience-Tested-Growth-Signals-Clash-With-Market-Selloff/698cb0aefa94ce7dec4bd7f8</guid><description>India's economy is demonstrating significant resilience, balancing strong domestic demand and fiscal discipline with an ambitious target to reduce debt-to-GDP to 50% by 2031. While vehicle registrations and digital payments surged, and the government maintained its FY26 deficit target at 4.4% and aims for 4.3% in FY27, January saw the Nifty 50 shed 3.1%. Foreign investors pulled $3.2 billion, contrasting with $7.6 billion from domestic players. Analysts project robust GDP growth around 6.9-7.8%, yet the market's January underperformance against global peers, coupled with sustained FII outflows, highlights the challenge of translating macro stability into broad-based market gains and corporate earnings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:39:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cb0aefa94ce7dec4bd7f7_1770828179217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LG India Eyes Global Exports Amid Q3 Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Eyes-Global-Exports-Amid-Q3-Profit-Slump/698caff6fa94ce7dec4bbe62</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LG-India-Eyes-Global-Exports-Amid-Q3-Profit-Slump/698caff6fa94ce7dec4bbe62</guid><description>LG Electronics India reported a 61.5% net profit decline to ₹89.6 crore and a 6.4% revenue drop in Q3 FY26, attributed to softer seasonal demand. However, the company is aggressively pursuing a 'Make India Global' strategy, aiming to double exports via the India-EU FTA and reduced US tariffs, supported by a new manufacturing facility. This export focus aims to drive long-term growth beyond domestic cyclicality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:36:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698caff6fa94ce7dec4bbe61_1770828106063.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland's Record Revenue Masked by EV Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ashok-Leylands-Record-Revenue-Masked-by-EV-Competition/698caf9efa94ce7dec4bbd4e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ashok-Leylands-Record-Revenue-Masked-by-EV-Competition/698caf9efa94ce7dec4bbd4e</guid><description>Ashok Leyland achieved record revenue of ₹11,534 crore and a net profit of ₹796 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by strong performance in MHCV and LCV segments. Despite this, the company's stock saw a dip following the results, highlighting investor caution. While its EV subsidiary Switch Mobility shows progress towards profitability, intense competition in electric buses and a focus on long-term, sustainable contracts introduce potential margin pressures. The company's market share gains in key segments remain a positive, yet the aggressive pricing from new entrants in the EV space warrants scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:34:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698caf9efa94ce7dec4bbd4d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airlines Challenge DGCA Crew Rules, Risking Operational Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Airlines-Challenge-DGCA-Crew-Rules-Risking-Operational-Strain/698caeccfa94ce7dec4bbb56</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Airlines-Challenge-DGCA-Crew-Rules-Risking-Operational-Strain/698caeccfa94ce7dec4bbb56</guid><description>Airlines are contesting the Directorate General of Civil Aviation's (DGCA) draft cabin crew rest norms, labeling them overly restrictive and globally misaligned. The Federation of Indian Airlines (FIA) argues the rules limit operational flexibility and inadequately address fatigue, preferring a focus on Flight Duty Period. This mirrors past pilot FDTL issues that caused widespread disruptions, raising concerns for the sector's efficiency and cost management, particularly for financially stretched carriers like SpiceJet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:31:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698caeccfa94ce7dec4bbb55_1770827710228.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>T20 World Cup Viewership Surge Boosts JioStar's Ad Ecosystem</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/T20-World-Cup-Viewership-Surge-Boosts-JioStars-Ad-Ecosystem/698cadc3fa94ce7dec4b76c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/T20-World-Cup-Viewership-Surge-Boosts-JioStars-Ad-Ecosystem/698cadc3fa94ce7dec4b76c3</guid><description>The ICC Men's T20 World Cup 2026 shattered opening day viewership records on JioStar's platforms, with total consumption reaching 14.7 billion minutes. This 59% increase over the previous edition, driven by India's strong performance and JioHotstar's 81% reach surge, demonstrates a robust appetite for live sports. The event's success validates JioStar's multi-language approach and innovative features, creating a premium advertising ecosystem with substantial scale and advertiser appeal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:26:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cadc3fa94ce7dec4b76c2_1770827753541.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LG India Exports Premium to US/EU Amid Domestic Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LG-India-Exports-Premium-to-USEU-Amid-Domestic-Profit-Slump/698cadb1fa94ce7dec4b69f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LG-India-Exports-Premium-to-USEU-Amid-Domestic-Profit-Slump/698cadb1fa94ce7dec4b69f6</guid><description>LG Electronics India is aggressively expanding exports of premium home appliances, including refrigerators made in its Pune plant, to the US and Europe. This strategic pivot, aiming to double export contribution to 14% of sales, aims to capitalize on favorable trade agreements and competitive production costs. However, the company's domestic performance shows a significant downturn, with third-quarter net profit plummeting 61.5% year-on-year to Rs 89.67 crore on a 6.4% revenue decline, attributed to a compressed festive sales period, inventory corrections, and mounting cost pressures from raw materials and currency depreciation. The upcoming Sri City plant is expected to bolster export capacity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:26:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cadb1fa94ce7dec4b69f5_1770827535315.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NPST Q3 Revenue Surges 147%, Profit Soars 124%, Faces Fund Use Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NPST-Q3-Revenue-Surges-147percent-Profit-Soars-124percent-Faces-Fund-Use-Scrutiny/698cad26fa94ce7dec4b673d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NPST-Q3-Revenue-Surges-147percent-Profit-Soars-124percent-Faces-Fund-Use-Scrutiny/698cad26fa94ce7dec4b673d</guid><description>Network People Services Technologies (NPST) posted a stellar Q3, with consolidated revenue soaring 147.7% YoY to ₹5,262.30 Lakhs and Net Profit rocketing 124.8% to ₹1,154.23 Lakhs. Standalone profits also saw over 127% growth. The company addressed a deviation flagged by CARE Ratings regarding ₹3.18 crore in preferential allotment fund utilization, clarifying it as legitimate operational expenditure. Unutilized proceeds stand at ₹291.67 crore.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:24:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cad26fa94ce7dec4b673c_1770827541640.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bombay Dyeing Posts Loss, But SEBI Order Win Lifts Regulatory Cloud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Bombay-Dyeing-Posts-Loss-But-SEBI-Order-Win-Lifts-Regulatory-Cloud/698cacc2fa94ce7dec4b4ace</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Bombay-Dyeing-Posts-Loss-But-SEBI-Order-Win-Lifts-Regulatory-Cloud/698cacc2fa94ce7dec4b4ace</guid><description>Bombay Dyeing &amp; Manufacturing Company Limited posted a standalone net loss of ₹9.92 crore for Q3 FY26, a sharp reversal from a ₹70 crore profit a year ago. Revenue also declined YoY to ₹324.02 crore. However, a significant positive is the Securities Appellate Tribunal (SAT) setting aside a SEBI order that had imposed penalties for alleged financial inflation. The company also noted the resignation of its CFO and CRO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:22:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cacc2fa94ce7dec4b4acd_1770827279921.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pavna Industries Q3 PAT Surges 297% on Revenue Growth, Eyes ₹250 Cr Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pavna-Industries-Q3-PAT-Surges-297percent-on-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-250-Cr-Expansion/698cacacfa94ce7dec4b3ec1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pavna-Industries-Q3-PAT-Surges-297percent-on-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-250-Cr-Expansion/698cacacfa94ce7dec4b3ec1</guid><description>Pavna Industries Limited reported a stellar Q3FY26 with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring by 297.37% year-on-year to Rs 3.02 Crore, driven by a 36% revenue jump to Rs 108.03 Crore. The company also announced a significant Rs 250 Crore investment MoU with the Uttar Pradesh government for manufacturing expansion over 3-5 years and inaugurated a new R&amp;D centre in Noida. These strategic moves underscore a strong operational quarter and a clear focus on future growth and innovation, particularly in EV-led product development.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:22:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698cacacfa94ce7dec4b3ec0_1770827246602.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>