<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:23:59 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Nykaa Q3 Profit Surges 150%+; Margin Expansion Fuels Beauty Segment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nykaa-Q3-Profit-Surges-150percent-Margin-Expansion-Fuels-Beauty-Segment/69850208e769d12df1d45acf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nykaa-Q3-Profit-Surges-150percent-Margin-Expansion-Fuels-Beauty-Segment/69850208e769d12df1d45acf</guid><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) reported a robust third quarter for FY26, with net profit soaring over 150% year-on-year to ₹67.7 crore on revenue growth of 27% to ₹2,873 crore. Consolidated Gross Merchandise Value (GMV) hit a record ₹5,975 crore, up 28%. The company achieved significant EBITDA margin expansion to 8.0%, primarily driven by its core beauty business, while fashion segment losses narrowed. Despite strong operational performance, Nykaa's premium valuation remains a key point of investor focus.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>LIC Taps Real Estate Value, Shelves Health Insurance Plans</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Taps-Real-Estate-Value-Shelves-Health-Insurance-Plans/69850195e769d12df1d45959</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Taps-Real-Estate-Value-Shelves-Health-Insurance-Plans/69850195e769d12df1d45959</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation (LIC) is prioritizing enhanced income generation from its substantial real estate portfolio, valued at over ₹45,000 crore post-revaluation. Concurrently, the insurer has paused plans to acquire a strategic stake in a health insurance firm. This strategic shift occurs as LIC reported a 17.2% rise in net profit to ₹12,958 crore for the quarter ended December 2025, driven by strong premium income growth. The move towards optimizing real estate assets aligns with government initiatives for asset recycling, potentially unlocking significant value from its property holdings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Govt Expands Startup Recognition, Raises Turnover Limits to ₹200 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Govt-Expands-Startup-Recognition-Raises-Turnover-Limits-to-200-Cr/6984fcf8e769d12df1d453c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Govt-Expands-Startup-Recognition-Raises-Turnover-Limits-to-200-Cr/6984fcf8e769d12df1d453c9</guid><description>The government has significantly broadened its startup recognition framework, doubling the general turnover limit to ₹200 crore and introducing a new 'deep tech' sub-category. This expansion aims to provide support for businesses across various growth stages and foster cutting-edge technological advancements, extending eligibility to cooperative societies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Private Credit Surges as AIFs Fill Banking Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Private-Credit-Surges-as-AIFs-Fill-Banking-Gap/6984fce4e769d12df1d45331</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Private-Credit-Surges-as-AIFs-Fill-Banking-Gap/6984fce4e769d12df1d45331</guid><description>India's private credit market is experiencing robust expansion, fueled by High-Net-Worth Individuals (HNIs) and family offices. This growth, estimated to push the market towards $13 billion in 2025 with assets under management reaching $25-30 billion, is largely channeled through SEBI-regulated Alternative Investment Funds (AIFs). These structures provide investors with comfort and scale, offering yields often superior to traditional debt mutual funds. The sector is vital in bridging a significant funding gap for mid-market companies left by cautious banks, providing non-dilutive, tailored capital solutions across diverse industries.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Disruption Fuels Global Market Sell-off Amid Economic Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Disruption-Fuels-Global-Market-Sell-off-Amid-Economic-Woes/6984fc8ae769d12df1d451be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Disruption-Fuels-Global-Market-Sell-off-Amid-Economic-Woes/6984fc8ae769d12df1d451be</guid><description>Global equity markets experienced a sharp downturn on Thursday, February 5, 2026, driven by a combination of disappointing economic indicators and the disruptive potential of Anthropic's new AI tools. Major indices across Asia, Europe, and the US entered the red zone, reflecting heightened investor anxiety over both economic weakness and structural technological shifts. Commodities also faced significant selling pressure. The Bank of England maintained its interest rate, but the narrow voting margin signaled underlying policy caution amid a challenging economic environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Q3 Loss: JLR Cyberattack Hits Hard, Domestic Sales Soar</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Q3-Loss-JLR-Cyberattack-Hits-Hard-Domestic-Sales-Soar/6984fc6de769d12df1d450e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Q3-Loss-JLR-Cyberattack-Hits-Hard-Domestic-Sales-Soar/6984fc6de769d12df1d450e6</guid><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (TMPV) swung to a consolidated loss of ₹3,483 crore in Q3 FY26, heavily impacted by a cyberattack on its Jaguar Land Rover (JLR) subsidiary that disrupted operations and incurred significant charges. This contrasts sharply with a profit of ₹5,485 crore in the prior year. Despite JLR's revenue falling 34%, Tata's domestic passenger vehicle business achieved a 24% revenue increase, showcasing a bifurcated performance amid broader industry headwinds and rising cybersecurity concerns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India-GCC FTA Talks Restart: Navigating Bloc Hurdles Ahead</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-GCC-FTA-Talks-Restart-Navigating-Bloc-Hurdles-Ahead/6984fbf5e769d12df1d44f9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-GCC-FTA-Talks-Restart-Navigating-Bloc-Hurdles-Ahead/6984fbf5e769d12df1d44f9e</guid><description>India and the six-member Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) bloc have initiated formal negotiations for a Free Trade Agreement by signing Terms of Reference. This accord, signed on February 5, 2026, signals a renewed push for deeper economic ties. The agreement aims to leverage existing trade relationships, which exceed $157 billion annually, and unlock opportunities in sectors like food processing, infrastructure, and petrochemicals. However, the path to a finalized FTA is historically complex, with past negotiations stalling due to the diverse interests within the GCC. This move is positioned as a strategic step amid global economic uncertainty, seeking to bolster trade flows and foster investment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:22:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Health Insurance Cost Squeeze Fuels Grievance Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Health-Insurance-Cost-Squeeze-Fuels-Grievance-Surge/6984f21be769d12df1d44670</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Health-Insurance-Cost-Squeeze-Fuels-Grievance-Surge/6984f21be769d12df1d44670</guid><description>Policyholder complaints in India's health and general insurance sectors surged 41% to 137,361 in FY25, driven by rising healthcare costs and hospital billing practices. Despite a record 32.6 million claims settled, the average payout per claim declined, indicating pressure on insurer profitability. Star Health's P/E ratio at 61.94 significantly exceeds its peers' median of 20.35, highlighting investor optimism versus the current cost realities. This cost-push dynamic threatens the sustainability of the current insurance model.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Mandates Drug Change Approvals: Compliance Costs Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Mandates-Drug-Change-Approvals-Compliance-Costs-Loom/6984eb26e769d12df1d43fce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Mandates-Drug-Change-Approvals-Compliance-Costs-Loom/6984eb26e769d12df1d43fce</guid><description>India's regulatory agency now requires prior approval for drug manufacturing changes impacting identity, strength, quality, purity, or potency. This amendment to the New Drugs and Clinical Trial Rules places significant new compliance demands on pharmaceutical firms. While aimed at enhancing patient safety, the move is expected to increase operational costs, strain administrative resources, and potentially drive consolidation within the industry, particularly affecting smaller manufacturers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BlackBerry Banks on Secure Comms &amp; QNX for India Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/BlackBerry-Banks-on-Secure-Comms-and-QNX-for-India-Growth/6984eb14e769d12df1d43f42</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/BlackBerry-Banks-on-Secure-Comms-and-QNX-for-India-Growth/6984eb14e769d12df1d43f42</guid><description>BlackBerry is in early talks with the Indian government to deploy its secure communications technology, driven by global demand for sovereign, military-grade systems. Concurrently, the company is strengthening its QNX automotive software presence in India, partnering with local automakers. This dual-pronged strategy leverages BlackBerry's pivot to cybersecurity and its foundational role in evolving vehicle technology, aiming to capitalize on India's growing demand for advanced software solutions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IDBI Bank Bids Due: Valuation &amp; Regulatory Hurdles Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDBI-Bank-Bids-Due-Valuation-and-Regulatory-Hurdles-Loom/6984ea9ee769d12df1d43dde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDBI-Bank-Bids-Due-Valuation-and-Regulatory-Hurdles-Loom/6984ea9ee769d12df1d43dde</guid><description>The disinvestment of IDBI Bank enters a critical phase as Kotak Mahindra Bank and Fairfax Financial submit financial bids today, February 6, 2026, for the government's and LIC's 60.72% stake. This marks a key step towards meeting the FY27 disinvestment target of ₹80,000 crore. However, the process is fraught with challenges, including the undisclosed reserve price, a demanding regulatory approval pipeline from the RBI and CCI, and a valuation that appears premium compared to public sector peers, potentially impacting the final transaction price and the successful bidder's future profitability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NCLT Recalls Alchemist Insolvency Amidst ED Fraud Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NCLT-Recalls-Alchemist-Insolvency-Amidst-ED-Fraud-Probe/6984ea25e769d12df1d43cc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NCLT-Recalls-Alchemist-Insolvency-Amidst-ED-Fraud-Probe/6984ea25e769d12df1d43cc3</guid><description>The National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) has nullified the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) against Alchemist Limited. This decision, stemming from an Enforcement Directorate (ED) investigation, found the insolvency proceedings to be tainted by fraud, collusion, and malicious intent. The NCLT upheld the ED's position that insolvency laws must not be weaponized to legitimize proceeds of crime or obstruct anti-money laundering efforts, emphasizing a stricter regulatory oversight on corporate financial dealings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:06:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apeejay Surrendra Hotels: Record Revenue, Profit Plunges on Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Apeejay-Surrendra-Hotels-Record-Revenue-Profit-Plunges-on-Costs/6984e483e769d12df1d402b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Apeejay-Surrendra-Hotels-Record-Revenue-Profit-Plunges-on-Costs/6984e483e769d12df1d402b9</guid><description>Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels reported its best-ever Q3 revenue at ₹200.06 crore, a 12.71% YoY jump, driven by strong occupancy and ARR growth. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) declined by 24.78% YoY to ₹24.19 crore due to a sharp 78.6% rise in finance costs, increased depreciation, and a one-time deferred tax charge. The company completed two strategic acquisitions and plans new projects, aiming for sustained double-digit growth and margin recovery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>EPFO Plans ₹31 Trillion Equity Shift: Eyes Sectoral, Factor Indices</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/EPFO-Plans-31-Trillion-Equity-Shift-Eyes-Sectoral-Factor-Indices/6984e13ae769d12df1d3ad69</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/EPFO-Plans-31-Trillion-Equity-Shift-Eyes-Sectoral-Factor-Indices/6984e13ae769d12df1d3ad69</guid><description>India's EPFO, managing ₹31 trillion, is preparing a significant shift in its equity investment strategy. The fund manager aims to move beyond traditional Sensex and Nifty ETFs, exploring investments in sectoral, factor-based, and emerging industries like defence and rare earths. This diversification push follows a similar, unfruitful attempt in 2016 and could reallocate substantial capital.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Power's Mundra Loss Deepens Amidst PPA Negotiation Deadlock</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Tata-Powers-Mundra-Loss-Deepens-Amidst-PPA-Negotiation-Deadlock/6984df74e769d12df1d23497</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Tata-Powers-Mundra-Loss-Deepens-Amidst-PPA-Negotiation-Deadlock/6984df74e769d12df1d23497</guid><description>Tata Power's 4,000 MW Mundra plant incurred a substantial loss of approximately ₹800 crore in the first nine months of the fiscal year due to an extended six-month shutdown. This operational halt, during which no capacity charges were received while fixed costs persisted, significantly impacted consolidated profits. The plant's restart hinges on finalizing a new Power Purchase Agreement (PPA) with the Gujarat government, but negotiations are stalled over contract duration and the company's transition to greener energy sources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MSE's Liquidity Push Faces Uphill Battle Against Duopoly</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/MSEs-Liquidity-Push-Faces-Uphill-Battle-Against-Duopoly/6984df5ee769d12df1d233a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/MSEs-Liquidity-Push-Faces-Uphill-Battle-Against-Duopoly/6984df5ee769d12df1d233a1</guid><description>Metropolitan Stock Exchange (MSE) has relaunched its equity segment, implementing a liquidity enhancement scheme (LES) and upgraded systems to challenge the NSE-BSE duopoly. Bolstered by over ₹1,240 crore in recent funding from prominent brokers, MSE aims to attract participants through market maker incentives. However, early traction shows modest gains against the dominant market share of its rivals, with an evolving competitive landscape including NCDEX's planned entry into equities, all amidst cautious global investor sentiment and a volatile domestic market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Startup Policy Pivot to Deep Tech, Patient Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Policy-Pivot-to-Deep-Tech-Patient-Capital/6984de82e769d12df1d21b9a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Policy-Pivot-to-Deep-Tech-Patient-Capital/6984de82e769d12df1d21b9a</guid><description>India's government has substantially updated startup recognition policies, doubling the turnover threshold to ₹200 crore and establishing a new category for 'Deep Tech Startups' with an extended age limit to 20 years and a ₹300 crore turnover cap. This strategic pivot aims to nurture R&amp;D-intensive enterprises with long gestation periods and attract patient capital. The policy also extends recognition to cooperative societies, fostering grassroots innovation. These reforms target a more predictable, inclusive, and future-ready innovation ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vi's AGR Reckoning: Committee Decision Looms Amidst Network Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vis-AGR-Reckoning-Committee-Decision-Looms-Amidst-Network-Push/6984de6ee769d12df1d20de1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vis-AGR-Reckoning-Committee-Decision-Looms-Amidst-Network-Push/6984de6ee769d12df1d20de1</guid><description>India's telecom sector's total Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) dues exceed ₹1.77 lakh crore by FY25. Vodafone Idea (Vi) accounts for the largest share at ₹89,952 crore, with a government committee now reassessing its frozen dues. This comes as Vi initiates a $4.89 billion network expansion plan, aiming to regain competitiveness against market leaders Bharti Airtel and Reliance Jio, despite persistent financial strain and a negative P/E ratio.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sai Life Sciences Q3 Profit Surges 86%, Revenue Climbs 27% on Strong Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Q3-Profit-Surges-86percent-Revenue-Climbs-27percent-on-Strong-Growth/6984dc12e769d12df1d1e794</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Q3-Profit-Surges-86percent-Revenue-Climbs-27percent-on-Strong-Growth/6984dc12e769d12df1d1e794</guid><description>Sai Life Sciences reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 86% year-on-year to ₹100 Cr. Revenue from operations grew by a strong 27% to ₹556 Cr, driven by excellent performance in CRO and CDMO services, improved operational efficiencies, and strategic investments in AI and digital platforms. EBITDA also saw a significant 54% jump to ₹191 Cr, with margins expanding substantially. The nine-month period also showcased impressive growth, with PAT up 199% and revenue up 43%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Eyes LLP Shift for AIFs, Global Appeal vs. Local Comforts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Eyes-LLP-Shift-for-AIFs-Global-Appeal-vs-Local-Comforts/6984d9c4e769d12df1d19ab7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Eyes-LLP-Shift-for-AIFs-Global-Appeal-vs-Local-Comforts/6984d9c4e769d12df1d19ab7</guid><description>India is poised to amend the LLP Act, encouraging Alternative Investment Funds (AIFs) to transition from prevalent trust structures to Limited Liability Partnerships (LLPs). This move aims to streamline compliance, enhance transparency, and attract greater foreign capital, aligning Indian fund structures with global norms. While LLPs offer tax efficiency and limited liability, the shift may trade the privacy of trust structures for increased public disclosure, a key consideration for investors. The AIF sector in India has shown robust growth, with commitments reaching ₹15.74 trillion in December 2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Auto Components Poised for Global Surge on EU, US FTAs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Components-Poised-for-Global-Surge-on-EU-US-FTAs/6984d8c9e769d12df1d15bae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Components-Poised-for-Global-Surge-on-EU-US-FTAs/6984d8c9e769d12df1d15bae</guid><description>Union Minister Jitin Prasada declared India's auto component industry is at a defining inflection point. New Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) with the European Union and the United States are poised to reshape global sourcing and manufacturing. These pacts create a narrow, critical window for Indian suppliers to integrate deeply into global automotive value chains, positioning India as a preferred manufacturing and sourcing hub.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Budget: Strategic Tariffs Bolster Manufacturing Ahead of FTAs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Strategic-Tariffs-Bolster-Manufacturing-Ahead-of-FTAs/6984d76de769d12df1d14f81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Strategic-Tariffs-Bolster-Manufacturing-Ahead-of-FTAs/6984d76de769d12df1d14f81</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 introduces a strategic recalibration of customs duties, focusing on boosting domestic manufacturing competitiveness and resilience. The measures, explicitly framed as proactive steps ahead of anticipated Free Trade Agreements (FTAs), target critical sectors like renewable energy, electric vehicles, defense, and MSMEs. This policy shift prioritizes long-term industrial strength over immediate revenue implications, preparing Indian industries to vie in global markets while navigating evolving trade headwinds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Greenlights Blackstone Stake; Federal Bank Posts Strong Q3 Amid Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Greenlights-Blackstone-Stake-Federal-Bank-Posts-Strong-Q3-Amid-Valuation-Scrutiny/6984d432e769d12df1d0d606</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Greenlights-Blackstone-Stake-Federal-Bank-Posts-Strong-Q3-Amid-Valuation-Scrutiny/6984d432e769d12df1d0d606</guid><description>Federal Bank has received Reserve Bank of India approval for Asia II Topco XIII Pte. Ltd. (an affiliate of Blackstone) to acquire up to 9.99% of its paid-up share capital. This strategic investment follows robust third-quarter results where the bank's net profit rose 9% to ₹1,041 crore and Net Interest Income grew 9% to ₹2,653 crore, both exceeding analyst expectations. Asset quality improved sequentially, with Gross NPAs decreasing to 1.72%. Despite these positive indicators and recent stock highs, Federal Bank shares closed marginally down 0.12% on February 5, 2026, amidst broader market and sector-specific valuation discussions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Viyash Scientific Q3: Consolidated PAT Surges, Standalone Earnings Dip Amid Amalgamation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Viyash-Scientific-Q3-Consolidated-PAT-Surges-Standalone-Earnings-Dip-Amid-Amalgamation/6984d41de769d12df1d0d56e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Viyash-Scientific-Q3-Consolidated-PAT-Surges-Standalone-Earnings-Dip-Amid-Amalgamation/6984d41de769d12df1d0d56e</guid><description>Viyash Scientific reported mixed Q3 FY26 results. Consolidated PAT jumped 33.6% YoY to ₹273.70 crore, driven by strong revenue growth. However, standalone PAT fell 19.6% to ₹400.60 crore, and consolidated EPS declined YoY due to increased share count post-amalgamation. Significant exceptional costs of ₹412.60 crore were incurred for the Composite Scheme of Amalgamation, which also led to prior period restatements.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ola Electric Challenges Musk on Battery Tech; EV Race Heats Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Challenges-Musk-on-Battery-Tech-EV-Race-Heats-Up/6984d3c0e769d12df1d0d418</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Challenges-Musk-on-Battery-Tech-EV-Race-Heats-Up/6984d3c0e769d12df1d0d418</guid><description>Ola Electric asserts its dry electrode battery manufacturing process is fully operational, powering its electric scooters. This claim directly counters Tesla CEO Elon Musk's recent assessment of the technology's scalability challenges. The development underscores the intensifying race for cost-effective battery production, with dry electrode technology offering significant potential for reduced manufacturing costs and environmental impact.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DEE Development Engineers Posts Stellar Q3 YoY Growth, Flags Rs 4.2 Cr Labor Code Hit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DEE-Development-Engineers-Posts-Stellar-Q3-YoY-Growth-Flags-Rs-42-Cr-Labor-Code-Hit/6984d3a3e769d12df1d0d334</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DEE-Development-Engineers-Posts-Stellar-Q3-YoY-Growth-Flags-Rs-42-Cr-Labor-Code-Hit/6984d3a3e769d12df1d0d334</guid><description>DEE Development Engineers reported a strong Q3 FY26, with revenue soaring 77% YoY to ₹286.7 Cr and PAT jumping 308.2% to ₹18.6 Cr. Growth was propelled by core segments like Process Piping and Heavy Fabrications. The company also highlighted improved leverage ratios and a robust order book of ₹1303 Cr, with a new seamless pipe plant set to commence operations. However, results were adjusted for a ₹4.2 Cr one-time labor code liability, causing a marginal QoQ EBITDA dip.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>VIL Debt Crisis: Dues Reassessment Sparks Sector Realignments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/VIL-Debt-Crisis-Dues-Reassessment-Sparks-Sector-Realignments/6984d32ae769d12df1d0d1d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/VIL-Debt-Crisis-Dues-Reassessment-Sparks-Sector-Realignments/6984d32ae769d12df1d0d1d3</guid><description>A committee is reassessing Vodafone Idea's (VIL) frozen AGR dues, a critical juncture for the debt-laden operator. While VIL grapples with over ₹2 lakh crore in total debt and a negative net worth, its financially robust competitors, Bharti Airtel and Reliance Jio, continue to dominate the Indian telecom market. The outcome of VIL's debt reassessment and its ability to secure essential funding are paramount, potentially reshaping the industry's competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Air India Fleet Woes Spark DGCA Scrutiny, Peer Impact Assessed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Fleet-Woes-Spark-DGCA-Scrutiny-Peer-Impact-Assessed/6984d264e769d12df1d0d027</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Air-India-Fleet-Woes-Spark-DGCA-Scrutiny-Peer-Impact-Assessed/6984d264e769d12df1d0d027</guid><description>Government data reveals a significant portion of the Air India Group's analyzed fleet, nearly 72%, exhibits recurring defects. This revelation has led to intensified surveillance by the Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA), which is also expanding its technical workforce. While IndiGo and SpiceJet also reported instances of fleet issues, the scale of Air India's findings highlights potential systemic operational challenges and increased regulatory pressure across the Indian aviation industry.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp's EV Bet: Strong Q3 Masks Long-Term Valuation Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorps-EV-Bet-Strong-Q3-Masks-Long-Term-Valuation-Debate/6984d240e769d12df1d0cf50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorps-EV-Bet-Strong-Q3-Masks-Long-Term-Valuation-Debate/6984d240e769d12df1d0cf50</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp posted strong Q3 FY26 results with net profit up 14.4% to ₹1,267.55 crore and revenue growing 21.7% to ₹12,486.82 crore. The company approved an additional ₹275 crore investment in electric vehicle maker Euler Motors and a solar power project. Despite these positive developments, the stock closed down 1.51% on February 5, 2026. This suggests investors are weighing the immediate financial gains against the execution and profitability of its ambitious electric mobility and sustainability strategies amidst a competitive market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PhysicsWallah Soars: Q3 Revenue Jumps 33.7%, Eyes K-12 Expansion.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PhysicsWallah-Soars-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-337percent-Eyes-K-12-Expansion/6984d1f4e769d12df1d0cddc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PhysicsWallah-Soars-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-337percent-Eyes-K-12-Expansion/6984d1f4e769d12df1d0cddc</guid><description>PhysicsWallah (PWL) reported a strong Q3 FY26, with revenue climbing 33.7% YoY to ₹10,824 million and Adjusted EBITDA up 33.7% YoY to ₹3,512 million. For 9M FY26, revenue grew 31% to ₹29,807 million, surpassing full FY25. The company is strategically expanding into K-12 and non-Hindi regions, investing heavily in AI, and reported a robust treasury balance of ₹50,544 million. Profit After Tax for 9M FY26 was ₹450 million, impacted by ₹236 million in one-time expenses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sebi Bans 15 in Unison Metals Manipulation Scheme</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Bans-15-in-Unison-Metals-Manipulation-Scheme/6984d1d6e769d12df1d0cd1d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Sebi-Bans-15-in-Unison-Metals-Manipulation-Scheme/6984d1d6e769d12df1d0cd1d</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) has penalized 15 individuals with a three-year market ban and Rs 3.6 crore in fines for orchestrating a 'pump and dump' scheme involving Unison Metals Ltd. (UML) shares. An additional Rs 3.87 crore was ordered to be disgorged by 10 entities. The manipulation reportedly occurred through misleading recommendations circulated on Telegram channels, artificially inflating stock prices and volumes to the detriment of retail investors. This action underscores the ongoing challenge regulators face in combating digital-driven market manipulation, particularly in the small-cap segment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trent Stock Jumps as Margin Gains Outweigh Growth Slowdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Stock-Jumps-as-Margin-Gains-Outweigh-Growth-Slowdown/6984d1a2e769d12df1d0cc37</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Stock-Jumps-as-Margin-Gains-Outweigh-Growth-Slowdown/6984d1a2e769d12df1d0cc37</guid><description>Trent's third-quarter performance showed slower same-store and like-for-like growth, but margins expanded significantly, with Ebitda rising 194 basis points. Aggressive store network expansion, particularly for Zudio, bolstered revenue by 16%. Analysts largely view the growth concerns as priced in, with a majority recommending a 'buy' and setting an average target price above the current trading level.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Expands Startup Definition, Bolstering Deep Tech and Co-ops</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-Expands-Startup-Definition-Bolstering-Deep-Tech-and-Co-ops/6984d059e769d12df1d0bcf7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/India-Expands-Startup-Definition-Bolstering-Deep-Tech-and-Co-ops/6984d059e769d12df1d0bcf7</guid><description>India has significantly revised its startup recognition criteria. The turnover threshold has been doubled to ₹200 crore, and a new 'Deep Tech Startup' category has been introduced with a ₹300 crore turnover limit and a 20-year recognition period. Cooperative enterprises are now also eligible for startup status, aimed at supporting grassroots innovation in sectors like agriculture. These changes address the evolving nature of the Indian startup ecosystem, characterized by longer innovation cycles and higher capital intensity, particularly in R&amp;D-driven sectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sai Life Sciences PAT Surges 86% on Strong Revenue Growth, Flags ₹83M One-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-PAT-Surges-86percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth-Flags-83M-One-Off/6984d00ee769d12df1d0bbe4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-PAT-Surges-86percent-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth-Flags-83M-One-Off/6984d00ee769d12df1d0bbe4</guid><description>Sai Life Sciences reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated PAT soaring 86.39% YoY to ₹1,003.75 million on a 26.53% revenue increase to ₹5,564.64 million. Nine-month PAT jumped 198.33% YoY. The company recognized an ₹82.93 million one-off loss related to new Labour Codes, classified as non-recurring. Diluted EPS grew substantially, and auditors issued an unmodified conclusion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TRAI Spam Crackdown: Operator Compliance Costs Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/TRAI-Spam-Crackdown-Operator-Compliance-Costs-Rise/6984cfe8e769d12df1d0bae4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/TRAI-Spam-Crackdown-Operator-Compliance-Costs-Rise/6984cfe8e769d12df1d0bae4</guid><description>The Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI) has disconnected approximately 21 lakh telecom connections to combat unsolicited commercial communications (UCC). This intensified crackdown, bolstered by February 2025 regulatory amendments, imposes significant operational and financial burdens on telecom service providers (TSPs). While aimed at consumer protection, the move raises concerns about increased compliance costs and potential impacts on TSPs' growth strategies amidst an already consolidated market landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sai Life Sciences Posts Stellar Q3: PAT Soars 86% YoY on 26.5% Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Posts-Stellar-Q3-PAT-Soars-86percent-YoY-on-265percent-Revenue-Surge/6984cf69e769d12df1d0b969</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Posts-Stellar-Q3-PAT-Soars-86percent-YoY-on-265percent-Revenue-Surge/6984cf69e769d12df1d0b969</guid><description>Sai Life Sciences announced strong Q3 FY2025 results, with consolidated PAT jumping 86.39% YoY to ₹1,003.75 million on a 26.53% revenue increase to ₹5,564.64 million. Nine-month consolidated PAT soared 198.33% YoY. The company also recognized an ₹82.93 million one-off loss related to new Labour Codes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Bets Big on EVs and Solar Amidst Steady Earnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Bets-Big-on-EVs-and-Solar-Amidst-Steady-Earnings/6984cf30e769d12df1d0b81a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Bets-Big-on-EVs-and-Solar-Amidst-Steady-Earnings/6984cf30e769d12df1d0b81a</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp posted third-quarter results exceeding revenue and EBITDA expectations, though slightly missing net profit forecasts. Revenue climbed 20.7% year-over-year to ₹12,328.3 crore, with EBITDA rising 22.6% to ₹1,809.9 crore. The company declared a ₹110 per share interim dividend and committed ₹275 crore to Euler Motors, signaling a strategic push into electric mobility. Significant investments in solar power projects for its plants underscore a growing commitment to sustainability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Stove Kraft Q3 PAT Plunges 66% Amid Export Woes, Eyes IKEA Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stove-Kraft-Q3-PAT-Plunges-66percent-Amid-Export-Woes-Eyes-IKEA-Boost/6984cf10e769d12df1d0b74f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stove-Kraft-Q3-PAT-Plunges-66percent-Amid-Export-Woes-Eyes-IKEA-Boost/6984cf10e769d12df1d0b74f</guid><description>Stove Kraft reported a sharp 66.6% year-on-year drop in Q3 FY26 net profit to ₹4.1 crore, impacted by a 6.4% revenue decline due to muted export sales amid global headwinds and US tariffs. Despite this, domestic business remained robust, contributing 96% of sales. The company is strategically expanding its retail network, advancing its IKEA partnership expected to yield revenue from FY27, and making significant progress towards a cash debt-free status by March 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:10:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Michael Burry Warns: Bitcoin's Death Spiral Accelerates, Threatens Gold</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Michael-Burry-Warns-Bitcoins-Death-Spiral-Accelerates-Threatens-Gold/6984cef6e769d12df1d0b6a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Michael-Burry-Warns-Bitcoins-Death-Spiral-Accelerates-Threatens-Gold/6984cef6e769d12df1d0b6a9</guid><description>Michael Burry, known for predicting the 2008 crisis, has issued a dire warning about Bitcoin. He stated the cryptocurrency has been exposed as a purely speculative asset, failing as a hedge against inflation. Burry cautioned that a further 10% drop could trigger massive losses for corporate holders and impact precious metals markets. Bitcoin has already fallen over 40% from its October peak, erasing gains since late 2024.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dalmia Sugar Profits Soar 17% on Margins, Revenue Dips 17% in Q3</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Dalmia-Sugar-Profits-Soar-17percent-on-Margins-Revenue-Dips-17percent-in-Q3/6984ce79e769d12df1d0b57f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Dalmia-Sugar-Profits-Soar-17percent-on-Margins-Revenue-Dips-17percent-in-Q3/6984ce79e769d12df1d0b57f</guid><description>Dalmia Bharat Sugar reported a mixed Q3 FY26. While consolidated revenue declined 17% YoY to Rs. 698 Cr, operating EBITDA rose 8% to Rs. 109 Cr, boosting EBITDA margins to 16% from 12% a year ago. Profit After Tax (PAT) jumped 17% YoY to Rs. 70 Cr, with EPS at Rs. 8.59. The company is expanding distillery capacity and venturing into Compressed Bio Gas (CBG), signalling diversification, while declaring an interim dividend of Rs. 4.50 per share.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>