<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:53:22 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Hormuz Flashpoint: India's Energy Reserves Tested Amid Asian Security Divide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Hormuz-Flashpoint-Indias-Energy-Reserves-Tested-Amid-Asian-Security-Divide/69a3984aedbd0c0ef0192b56</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Hormuz-Flashpoint-Indias-Energy-Reserves-Tested-Amid-Asian-Security-Divide/69a3984aedbd0c0ef0192b56</guid><description>Military actions near the Strait of Hormuz are heightening global energy market anxieties. While India activates contingency plans, bolstering reserves and exploring alternative routes, the event starkly reveals the varied energy security postures of Asian nations. Japan and South Korea remain highly vulnerable, contrasting with China's diversified approach and India's proactive measures, even as oil prices react to the escalating geopolitical premium.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:37:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3984aedbd0c0ef0192b55_1772329152992.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fear Overdrive: Market Dips Ignore Economic Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fear-Overdrive-Market-Dips-Ignore-Economic-Fundamentals/69a3922dedbd0c0ef019292b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fear-Overdrive-Market-Dips-Ignore-Economic-Fundamentals/69a3922dedbd0c0ef019292b</guid><description>A sensationalist report predicting AI-induced economic collapse due to job losses has spooked markets. However, economic analysis, supported by historical precedent, indicates AI's role as a productivity enhancer will ultimately increase aggregate income and consumption, not trigger a crisis. This disconnect between fear-driven narratives and economic reality may present buying opportunities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:11:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3922dedbd0c0ef019292a_1772327667589.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>March Market Volatility: Geopolitics &amp; Inflation Trump Seasonality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/March-Market-Volatility-Geopolitics-and-Inflation-Trump-Seasonality/69a3922aedbd0c0ef0192914</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/March-Market-Volatility-Geopolitics-and-Inflation-Trump-Seasonality/69a3922aedbd0c0ef0192914</guid><description>February's market turbulence extends into March 2026, fueled by escalating Middle East conflict and stubborn US inflation data, which diminishes hopes for immediate interest rate cuts. While historical seasonal patterns offer a statistical edge for Pidilite Industries, Cummins India, and AIA Engineering, the current macro-economic climate introduces significant, unpredictable risks. A stock-specific strategy is essential, but investors must navigate this volatile environment with heightened caution as external shocks may override established trends.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:11:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a3922aedbd0c0ef0192913_1772327698039.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>