<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:43:53 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's FY27 GDP Growth: Trade Lifts Forecast, Tax Compliance Key to Fiscal Goals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-GDP-Growth-Trade-Lifts-Forecast-Tax-Compliance-Key-to-Fiscal-Goals/69a013589e91847a1e789018</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-GDP-Growth-Trade-Lifts-Forecast-Tax-Compliance-Key-to-Fiscal-Goals/69a013589e91847a1e789018</guid><description>EY forecasts India's real GDP to expand between 6.8% and 7.2% in fiscal year 2027, propelled by extensive bilateral trade agreements. This growth outlook hinges on increasing the tax-GDP ratio through improved tax compliance, as major tax reforms have largely been implemented. The government is expected to meet its fiscal deficit targets despite revenue sacrifices from personal income tax and GST reforms, but future fiscal health depends critically on compliance gains to fund long-term development objectives.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:33:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a013589e91847a1e789017_1772098541039.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BMW Ventures Secures ₹36 Cr BHEL Order for Structural Steel Supply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BMW-Ventures-Secures-36-Cr-BHEL-Order-for-Structural-Steel-Supply/69a013549e91847a1e789001</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BMW-Ventures-Secures-36-Cr-BHEL-Order-for-Structural-Steel-Supply/69a013549e91847a1e789001</guid><description>BMW Ventures Limited has secured a significant ₹36 crore order from Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited (BHEL) for the supply of structural steel. This award for its fabricated steel manufacturing division underscores the company's growing capabilities in serving major public sector undertakings and is expected to be executed within 10 months.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:33:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a013549e91847a1e789000_1772098527738.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RVNL Secures ₹797 Cr NMDC Construction Order; Boosts Order Book</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RVNL-Secures-797-Cr-NMDC-Construction-Order-Boosts-Order-Book/69a011eb9e91847a1e788ebf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RVNL-Secures-797-Cr-NMDC-Construction-Order-Boosts-Order-Book/69a011eb9e91847a1e788ebf</guid><description>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL) has secured a significant Letter of Award (LOA) from NMDC worth ₹796.80 crore for constructing residential towers in Chhattisgarh. This project, with a 34-month execution period, is set to substantially bolster RVNL's order book and enhance its future revenue prospects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:27:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a011eb9e91847a1e788ebe_1772098134725.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Akme Fintrade seeks ₹85.75 Cr via warrants; EGM on March 20</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-seeks-8575-Cr-via-warrants-EGM-on-March-20/69a011ea9e91847a1e788ea9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-seeks-8575-Cr-via-warrants-EGM-on-March-20/69a011ea9e91847a1e788ea9</guid><description>Akme Fintrade (India) Limited has approved a preferential issue of 12.25 crore warrants at ₹7 each, aiming to raise approximately ₹85.75 crore. The funds are earmarked for working capital needs and business expansion. Shareholders will vote on this proposal at an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) scheduled for March 20, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:27:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a011ea9e91847a1e788ea8_1772098082981.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Talks Advance Amid Tariff Policy Flux</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-US-Trade-Talks-Advance-Amid-Tariff-Policy-Flux/69a011459e91847a1e788df5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-US-Trade-Talks-Advance-Amid-Tariff-Policy-Flux/69a011459e91847a1e788df5</guid><description>Commerce Minister Piyush Goyal met with US Secretary of Commerce Howard Lutnick and Ambassador Sergio Gor on February 26, 2026, to progress a Phase 1 trade agreement framework. Despite a planned reduction in US tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, a recent US Supreme Court ruling invalidating prior tariffs and the subsequent, temporary imposition of new US global tariffs introduce immediate policy uncertainty and have postponed final negotiation talks. The market is assessing the impact of this conflicting trade policy environment on bilateral commerce and key Indian export sectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:24:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a011459e91847a1e788df4_1772097985013.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sastasundar Ventures Board Approves Restructuring, Eyes SHBL Merger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sastasundar-Ventures-Board-Approves-Restructuring-Eyes-SHBL-Merger/69a010ae9e91847a1e788d1d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sastasundar-Ventures-Board-Approves-Restructuring-Eyes-SHBL-Merger/69a010ae9e91847a1e788d1d</guid><description>Sastasundar Ventures Limited, operating as Health X Platform, has received in-principle approval from its Board for a significant restructuring. The plan includes a potential merger of its material subsidiary, Sastasundar Healthbuddy Limited (SHBL), into the parent entity. This move aims to establish independent structures for its healthcare and financial services businesses, preserving shareholder economic interests pending final valuation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:21:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a010ae9e91847a1e788d1c_1772097765671.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks: CIO's Buy Call Clashes with AI Risks, Sky-High Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-CIOs-Buy-Call-Clashes-with-AI-Risks-Sky-High-Valuations/69a010279e91847a1e788bdb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-CIOs-Buy-Call-Clashes-with-AI-Risks-Sky-High-Valuations/69a010279e91847a1e788bdb</guid><description>Indian IT services stocks face a stark divergence between optimistic outlooks and harsh market realities. While ASK Investment Managers' CIO George Joseph advocates for a "thumping the table buy" at seemingly compelling valuations, recent market data reveals a different story. The Nifty IT index has plunged amidst escalating AI disruption fears, with current sector P/E ratios higher than global peers and significant revenue growth decoupling. Analysts are issuing downgrades, citing structural threats to traditional outsourcing models, despite India's robust macroeconomic backdrop. The sector grapples with re-evaluating its growth trajectory and pricing power in the AI era.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:19:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a010279e91847a1e788bda_1772097732042.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>8th Pay Commission: Economic Impact and Fiscal Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8th-Pay-Commission-Economic-Impact-and-Fiscal-Strain/69a00fb99e91847a1e788a3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8th-Pay-Commission-Economic-Impact-and-Fiscal-Strain/69a00fb99e91847a1e788a3d</guid><description>The 8th Central Pay Commission's official commencement signals potential salary and pension revisions for millions of central government employees and pensioners. While anticipated to boost consumption, the commission's implementation poses significant fiscal challenges, projected to increase the annual burden by ₹3.7-3.9 lakh crore, potentially widening the fiscal deficit. Concerns also linger over inflationary pressures and the real value of wage increases amidst rising costs, contrasting with earlier pay commission impacts. The fiscal environment remains constrained, requiring a delicate balance between employee welfare and national financial stability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:17:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a00fb99e91847a1e788a3c_1772097720769.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rajesh Power L1 for Ajmer substation; RRVPN project win awaits confirmation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rajesh-Power-L1-for-Ajmer-substation-RRVPN-project-win-awaits-confirmation/69a00fa19e91847a1e788a13</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rajesh-Power-L1-for-Ajmer-substation-RRVPN-project-win-awaits-confirmation/69a00fa19e91847a1e788a13</guid><description>Rajesh Power Services Limited has emerged as the Lowest Bidder (L1) for a significant 132/33 KV, 2x50 MVA GIS Substation project in Ajmer, awarded by Rajasthan Rajya Vidyut Prasaran Nigam Limited (RRVPN). The project, encompassing construction and associated transmission lines, is slated for an 18-month execution. While this L1 status signals potential new business, the company awaits final confirmation from RRVPN.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:17:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a00fa19e91847a1e788a12_1772097636354.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Inditrade Capital Auditors Resign Citing Data Gaps, Liquidity Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Inditrade-Capital-Auditors-Resign-Citing-Data-Gaps-Liquidity-Woes/69a00fa19e91847a1e7889fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Inditrade-Capital-Auditors-Resign-Citing-Data-Gaps-Liquidity-Woes/69a00fa19e91847a1e7889fd</guid><description>Inditrade Capital's statutory auditors, Kirtane &amp; Pandit LLP, have resigned citing the management's failure to provide complete, accurate, and timely financial information. Severe liquidity constraints and operational disruptions, including a lessor seizing company assets in September 2025, prevented the auditors from fulfilling their duties. This move raises serious governance concerns and may delay future audits and compliance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:17:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a00fa19e91847a1e7889fc_1772097595941.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Climate Shockwave: Looming Market Disruptions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Climate-Shockwave-Looming-Market-Disruptions/69a00f9d9e91847a1e7889e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Climate-Shockwave-Looming-Market-Disruptions/69a00f9d9e91847a1e7889e7</guid><description>India's economy faces severe headwinds from escalating climate extremes, with GDP projections showing significant losses and agriculture output projected to drop by 16% by 2030. Extreme weather events are intensifying, impacting infrastructure, increasing insurance costs, and stressing fiscal health. The nation's high vulnerability necessitates substantial investment in adaptation and a strategic shift towards renewables, although transition risks and data gaps pose challenges for financial markets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:17:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a00f9d9e91847a1e7889e6_1772097519269.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rajesh Power Services L1 for ₹109 Cr RRVPN Substation Project in Ajmer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rajesh-Power-Services-L1-for-109-Cr-RRVPN-Substation-Project-in-Ajmer/69a00f919e91847a1e7889cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rajesh-Power-Services-L1-for-109-Cr-RRVPN-Substation-Project-in-Ajmer/69a00f919e91847a1e7889cf</guid><description>Rajesh Power Services has been confirmed as the lowest bidder (L1) for a significant ₹109.87 Cr project from Rajasthan Rajya Vidyut Prasaran Nigam Limited (RRVPN). The contract involves constructing a 132/33 KV, 2x50 MVA GIS substation and associated transmission lines in Ajmer, with an 18-month execution timeline. This L1 status offers substantial revenue visibility, though the final award is pending an LOI/LOA.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a00f919e91847a1e7889ce_1772097532480.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India EV Goals: High Rates, Funding Gaps Threaten 2030 Targets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-EV-Goals-High-Rates-Funding-Gaps-Threaten-2030-Targets/69a00f229e91847a1e788911</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-EV-Goals-High-Rates-Funding-Gaps-Threaten-2030-Targets/69a00f229e91847a1e788911</guid><description>India's electric vehicle sector attracted $25.6 billion in investment from 2020-2025, capturing only 18% of the estimated $143.4 billion needed by 2030. A substantial $117.8 billion funding gap persists. High commercial borrowing rates, ranging from 15% to 33%, severely impede adoption by increasing costs and dampening demand. Infrastructure deficits, particularly in charging stations, further complicate the path to meeting ambitious 2030 electrification targets. Analysts suggest systemic financial reforms are imperative.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:15:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a00f229e91847a1e788910_1772097635747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Unveils Life Cycle Funds, Redefining Long-Term Investing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SEBI-Unveils-Life-Cycle-Funds-Redefining-Long-Term-Investing/69a00f1b9e91847a1e7888f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SEBI-Unveils-Life-Cycle-Funds-Redefining-Long-Term-Investing/69a00f1b9e91847a1e7888f7</guid><description>The Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has launched Life Cycle Funds (LCFs), a new mutual fund category effective February 26, 2026. These open-ended schemes feature a predefined maturity and a 'glide path' that automatically adjusts asset allocation as the target date nears. LCFs replace the existing Solution Oriented Funds (Retirement &amp; Children's Funds), aiming to promote disciplined, long-term, goal-based investing. With tenures ranging from 5 to 30 years, they offer investors a standardized mechanism to align risk with life stages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:15:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a00f1b9e91847a1e7888f6_1772097467849.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Oil Imports in Policy Limbo Amid US Ruling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Oil-Imports-in-Policy-Limbo-Amid-US-Ruling/69a00e2c9e91847a1e7887b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Oil-Imports-in-Policy-Limbo-Amid-US-Ruling/69a00e2c9e91847a1e7887b8</guid><description>Indian refiners have suspended new bookings for Russian crude oil, caught in a policy vacuum following a US Supreme Court decision that clouded a bilateral trade deal. This uncertainty compels a pivot towards alternative, potentially riskier, supply sources from the Middle East, heightening energy security concerns. China, conversely, has ramped up Russian oil imports, absorbing the surplus barrels.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:11:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a00e2c9e91847a1e7887b7_1772097204756.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Panvel Property Surge: Infrastructure Boom Meets Valuation Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Panvel-Property-Surge-Infrastructure-Boom-Meets-Valuation-Reality/69a00db49e91847a1e788715</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Panvel-Property-Surge-Infrastructure-Boom-Meets-Valuation-Reality/69a00db49e91847a1e788715</guid><description>Panvel has emerged as a prime real estate destination, with apartment prices soaring over 53% since late 2022, fueled by the Navi Mumbai International Airport and Mumbai Trans Harbour Link. This infrastructure-led growth has attracted major developers and significant investor interest. However, with a 1-year decline in the Nifty Realty Index and varying valuations among key players like Godrej Properties and Embassy Office Parks REIT, questions arise about the sustainability of recent price gains and potential overvaluation. While the sector forecasts robust future earnings, execution risks and market saturation loom for late entrants.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:09:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a00db49e91847a1e788714_1772097075936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Solarworld Energy Solutions Ratings Upgraded to A-/A2+; Facilities Enhanced to ₹420 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Solarworld-Energy-Solutions-Ratings-Upgraded-to-A-A2-Facilities-Enhanced-to-420-Cr/69a00d379e91847a1e78868d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Solarworld-Energy-Solutions-Ratings-Upgraded-to-A-A2-Facilities-Enhanced-to-420-Cr/69a00d379e91847a1e78868d</guid><description>Solarworld Energy Solutions Limited has received a credit rating upgrade from CRISIL Ratings, with its fund-based facilities moving to CRISIL A-/Stable and non-fund based to CRISIL A2+. The total value of these rated banking facilities has been increased to ₹420 crore from ₹250 crore. The upgrade reflects a stronger order book providing revenue visibility and a healthier financial profile bolstered by recent IPO proceeds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:07:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a00d379e91847a1e78868c_1772096973124.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Urban Company Stock Faces Massive Sell-Off Risk from 66% Share Unlock</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Urban-Company-Stock-Faces-Massive-Sell-Off-Risk-from-66percent-Share-Unlock/69a0091a9e91847a1e788387</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Urban-Company-Stock-Faces-Massive-Sell-Off-Risk-from-66percent-Share-Unlock/69a0091a9e91847a1e788387</guid><description>Urban Company Ltd. shares are trading near their ₹103 IPO price, extending a losing streak. Despite a 33% revenue increase in the third quarter, the company's EBITDA loss widened significantly, and net profit turned to a loss. Investors are now bracing for a colossal supply shock on March 17th, when 66% of the company's outstanding equity will become tradable, raising concerns about substantial price depreciation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:49:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0091a9e91847a1e788386_1772095974876.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KFintech's GST Payout Shift: New Compliance Burden for MF Distributors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KFintechs-GST-Payout-Shift-New-Compliance-Burden-for-MF-Distributors/69a009089e91847a1e78836c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KFintechs-GST-Payout-Shift-New-Compliance-Burden-for-MF-Distributors/69a009089e91847a1e78836c</guid><description>Effective April 1, KFin Technologies is restructuring mutual fund distributor brokerage payouts to be GST-exclusive, aligning with regulatory changes. Distributors must now remit GST to the government and provide proof to KFintech to receive the tax component of their commission. This procedural shift imposes an additional compliance and administrative burden on distributors, potentially impacting their cash flow and operational efficiency. The move aims to clarify GST obligations within the mutual fund distribution ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:49:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a009089e91847a1e78836b_1772095914754.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India: Ambit Sees 12% Upside Amidst Sky-High Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Ambit-Sees-12percent-Upside-Amidst-Sky-High-Valuation/69a009049e91847a1e788355</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Ambit-Sees-12percent-Upside-Amidst-Sky-High-Valuation/69a009049e91847a1e788355</guid><description>Ambit Institutional Equities initiated coverage on Hitachi Energy India with a 'Buy' rating and a target price of ₹28,500, citing strong order visibility and export growth. However, the company trades at a TTM P/E of 292, significantly higher than peers like ABB India (approx. 70), KEC International (approx. 35), and Skipper (approx. 25). This premium valuation necessitates flawless execution of its substantial High-Voltage Direct Current (HVDC) project pipeline, a key area of focus for future revenue growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:49:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a009049e91847a1e788354_1772095915765.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bandhan Bank Pivots: Microfinance Recovery Meets Secured Lending Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bandhan-Bank-Pivots-Microfinance-Recovery-Meets-Secured-Lending-Ambition/69a009029e91847a1e78833e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bandhan-Bank-Pivots-Microfinance-Recovery-Meets-Secured-Lending-Ambition/69a009029e91847a1e78833e</guid><description>Bandhan Bank is navigating a recovery phase, with its microfinance segment showing improved asset quality and collection efficiencies, reaching nearly 99.7%. Concurrently, the bank is accelerating its pivot towards secured lending, which now constitutes 57% of its loan book, ahead of its FY27 target. These strategies aim to reduce credit costs to 1.6-1.7% and improve return on assets to similar levels by FY27. Despite these operational gains and a 35% stock increase over the past year, the bank faces ongoing regulatory scrutiny in the microfinance sector and significant competition in secured lending.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:49:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a009029e91847a1e78833d_1772095828317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shree Salasar Investments OKs ₹323.75 Cr preferential issue via warrants</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Shree-Salasar-Investments-OKs-32375-Cr-preferential-issue-via-warrants/69a0088a9e91847a1e788290</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Shree-Salasar-Investments-OKs-32375-Cr-preferential-issue-via-warrants/69a0088a9e91847a1e788290</guid><description>Shree Salasar Investments Limited's board has approved a preferential issue of up to 18,50,000 warrants, convertible into equity shares at ₹175 each, aiming to raise ₹323.75 crore. Shareholder approval via an EGM is required. This move could dilute existing stakes but aims to bolster the company's capital base for expansion or other corporate needs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:47:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0088a9e91847a1e78828f_1772095728577.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Mandates E20 Petrol with RON 95: Navigating Cost &amp; Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Mandates-E20-Petrol-with-RON-95-Navigating-Cost-and-Infrastructure/69a007a49e91847a1e7881bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Mandates-E20-Petrol-with-RON-95-Navigating-Cost-and-Infrastructure/69a007a49e91847a1e7881bd</guid><description>Effective April 1, 2026, India will mandate the sale of 20% ethanol-blended petrol (E20) with a minimum Research Octane Number (RON) of 95 across all states and Union Territories. This policy aims to reduce oil imports and emissions while supporting farmers. While newer vehicles are largely compatible, older models may face reduced mileage and component wear. The requirement for higher RON 95 seeks to prevent engine knocking, but the transition poses significant logistical and cost considerations for fuel distributors and consumers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:43:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a007a49e91847a1e7881bc_1772095545119.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chatha Foods Presentation: 22% Revenue, 108% PAT CAGR Boosted by Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Chatha-Foods-Presentation-22percent-Revenue-108percent-PAT-CAGR-Boosted-by-Expansion/69a003dc9e91847a1e787fc0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Chatha-Foods-Presentation-22percent-Revenue-108percent-PAT-CAGR-Boosted-by-Expansion/69a003dc9e91847a1e787fc0</guid><description>Chatha Foods Limited submitted a comprehensive investor presentation on February 26, 2026, detailing its business, product portfolio, and strategic expansion plans. The company highlighted impressive compound annual growth rates (CAGRs) of 22% for revenue and 108% for profit after tax (PAT) between FY22 and FY25. Key initiatives include constructing a new vegetarian RTE facility and a joint venture with the Allana Group to boost export market presence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:27:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a003dc9e91847a1e787fbf_1772094536262.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Liquidity Tightening: What March Holds for India's Money Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Liquidity-Tightening-What-March-Holds-for-Indias-Money-Markets/69a0028b9e91847a1e787e0c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Liquidity-Tightening-What-March-Holds-for-Indias-Money-Markets/69a0028b9e91847a1e787e0c</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's (RBI) temporary liquidity support measures are poised for a phase-out after March, as bankers anticipate a return to standard liquidity management. This move follows successful easing of short-term borrowing costs, with system liquidity currently showing a surplus of approximately ₹2 lakh crore. While the RBI's intervention aimed to counter funding pressures that emerged in January, analysts predict a gradual absorption of excess cash, possibly via variable rate reverse repos, to align with the central bank's liquidity framework.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:21:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0028b9e91847a1e787e0c_1772095556479.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Auto Sales Boom: Valuations Diverge Amidst Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Sales-Boom-Valuations-Diverge-Amidst-Growth/69a0026e9e91847a1e787de9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Sales-Boom-Valuations-Diverge-Amidst-Growth/69a0026e9e91847a1e787de9</guid><description>India's automobile sector is poised for strong February 2026 sales, fueled by policy support and consumer demand. However, valuation disparities are widening, with companies like TVS Motor and Ashok Leyland trading at premium multiples. Maruti Suzuki faces capacity constraints and a premium valuation, while Tata Motors' passenger vehicle segment shows concerning financial trends. Rising commodity prices and impending regulatory costs add to a mixed outlook, despite broad-based optimism across segments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:21:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0026e9e91847a1e787de8_1772094209290.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PhysicsWallah Faces Valuation Reset Amidst Growth Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PhysicsWallah-Faces-Valuation-Reset-Amidst-Growth-Ambitions/69a0025c9e91847a1e787da8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PhysicsWallah-Faces-Valuation-Reset-Amidst-Growth-Ambitions/69a0025c9e91847a1e787da8</guid><description>PhysicsWallah Ltd. shares are experiencing a significant valuation reset, trading down 3% on Thursday, February 26, and marking declines in three of the last four sessions. The stock's market capitalization has fallen sharply from its listing valuation, now sitting at ₹25,451 crore, well below its initial public offering price. Technical indicators signal oversold conditions, while a recent shareholder lock-up expiry adds to selling pressure, contrasting with management's outlook for future profitability and expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:20:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a0025c9e91847a1e787da7_1772094324629.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bandhan Bank Surges on SBI MF Stake Approval, Defying Profit Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bandhan-Bank-Surges-on-SBI-MF-Stake-Approval-Defying-Profit-Slump/69a001f89e91847a1e787cd2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bandhan-Bank-Surges-on-SBI-MF-Stake-Approval-Defying-Profit-Slump/69a001f89e91847a1e787cd2</guid><description>Bandhan Bank's stock advanced following RBI approval for SBI Mutual Fund to acquire up to 9.99% stake. This institutional backing contrasts sharply with the bank's Q3 FY26 results, which showed a 51.6% net profit drop and a 4.5% NII decline. Despite these headwinds and elevated credit costs, the market sentiment appears forward-looking, buoyed by a 25% monthly stock surge and recent analyst upgrades.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:19:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a001f89e91847a1e787cd1_1772094123743.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Credit Boom: Secured Lending Fuels Growth Amid Risk Management Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Credit-Boom-Secured-Lending-Fuels-Growth-Amid-Risk-Management-Focus/69a001db9e91847a1e787c7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Credit-Boom-Secured-Lending-Fuels-Growth-Amid-Risk-Management-Focus/69a001db9e91847a1e787c7f</guid><description>India's credit industry surged by 17% YoY to ₹1.30 lakh crore in AUM by December 2025, with new loans up 36% in Q3 FY26. Secured lending, particularly gold and home loans, now leads growth, now accounting for 34% of new loan sourcing. Asset quality improved, with net 30+ delinquency falling to 3.3%. While demand remains strong, the focus shifts to balancing rapid expansion with robust risk management, especially in unsecured segments, to ensure sustainable growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:18:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a001db9e91847a1e787c7e_1772094026423.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>WeWork India Expands Hyderabad Capacity by 2,100 Desks; ₹32 Cr Investment Planned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/WeWork-India-Expands-Hyderabad-Capacity-by-2100-Desks-32-Cr-Investment-Planned/69a001bf9e91847a1e787c58</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/WeWork-India-Expands-Hyderabad-Capacity-by-2100-Desks-32-Cr-Investment-Planned/69a001bf9e91847a1e787c58</guid><description>WeWork India has signed a sub-lease deed to expand its Hyderabad operations by 1,45,114 sq ft, adding approximately 2,100 desks. The initiative requires an estimated investment of ₹32 Crore and is projected for completion by July 2026. This strategic move aims to cater to the increasing demand for flexible workspaces in one of India's fastest-growing commercial hubs, reinforcing its market position.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:18:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a001bf9e91847a1e787c57_1772093999249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supreme Court Slams Tribunals: "Liability" Signals Regulatory Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Supreme-Court-Slams-Tribunals-Liability-Signals-Regulatory-Risk/69a000e19e91847a1e787b2f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Supreme-Court-Slams-Tribunals-Liability-Signals-Regulatory-Risk/69a000e19e91847a1e787b2f</guid><description>The Supreme Court has delivered a sharp rebuke to India's administrative tribunals, terming them a "liability" and a "headache" due to profound accountability and functional crises. Chief Justice Surya Kant highlighted these bodies as operating in a "no man's land," unaccountable to anyone. This stark assessment points to systemic failures that could introduce considerable regulatory uncertainty for sectors reliant on tribunal adjudication, including telecommunications, corporate law, and securities markets. The court's call for "fresh measures" suggests a potential overhaul rather than incremental fixes, raising concerns about immediate market impact and future governance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:14:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a000e19e91847a1e787b2e_1772093872497.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Defense Budget Surges, But Capex Share Shrinks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Defense-Budget-Surges-But-Capex-Share-Shrinks/69a000239e91847a1e787999</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Defense-Budget-Surges-But-Capex-Share-Shrinks/69a000239e91847a1e787999</guid><description>India's defense budget is projected to hit ₹7.85 lakh crore by FY27, a substantial 219% increase from FY16. While actual spending frequently surpasses initial allocations, a critical trend emerges: capital expenditure's share within the total defense outlay has fallen to 28% from approximately 34.91% a decade ago. This shift, occurring against a backdrop of dual-front geopolitical challenges and lower spending as a percentage of GDP compared to international benchmarks, signals potential headwinds for strategic modernization efforts despite overall budget growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:11:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a000239e91847a1e787998_1772093612577.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Swiggy's Train Service Expansion: Profitability Under Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Swiggys-Train-Service-Expansion-Profitability-Under-Scrutiny/699fffde9e91847a1e787940</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Swiggys-Train-Service-Expansion-Profitability-Under-Scrutiny/699fffde9e91847a1e787940</guid><description>Swiggy has nearly doubled its 'Food on Train' service network to 152 stations in 12 months, partnering with IRCTC. This aggressive expansion, timed for the Holi travel season, offers festive menus and discounts. However, the move intensifies scrutiny on Swiggy's operational efficiency and profitability, especially against more financially stable rivals like Zomato, while IRCTC navigates its own catering challenges and market valuation concerns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:10:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fffde9e91847a1e787940_1772095540883.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BRND.ME's India Domicile Shift: A Blueprint for Tech IPOs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/BRNDMEs-India-Domicile-Shift-A-Blueprint-for-Tech-IPOs/699fffde9e91847a1e787929</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/BRNDMEs-India-Domicile-Shift-A-Blueprint-for-Tech-IPOs/699fffde9e91847a1e787929</guid><description>Consumer brands platform BRND.ME, formerly Mensa Brands, has successfully executed a complex, cross-border composite merger, moving its corporate domicile from Singapore to India in under 10 months. This strategic move, which includes consolidating its entities, is a critical step towards its planned initial public offering (IPO) within 12 to 18 months. The company achieved adjusted EBITDA profitability and operating cash-flow positivity in FY26, with revenues of approximately ₹1,500 crore in FY25 and targets of ₹1,700–₹1,800 crore for FY26. This rapid restructuring highlights BRND.ME's operational agility and positions India as a strategic headquarters for future growth and capital markets access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:10:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699fffde9e91847a1e787928_1772093533077.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FREED Secures ₹60 Cr Amidst India's Mounting Household Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/FREED-Secures-60-Cr-Amidst-Indias-Mounting-Household-Debt/699ffe7b9e91847a1e787805</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/FREED-Secures-60-Cr-Amidst-Indias-Mounting-Household-Debt/699ffe7b9e91847a1e787805</guid><description>FREED, an Indian debt relief platform, secured ₹60 crore led by Aavishkaar Capital to expand operations amid rising household debt and consumer credit penetration. Founded in 2020, the company utilizes a tech-driven model to assist individuals in settling unsecured loans and rebuilding credit. With over 200,000 customers counselled and ₹3,200 crore in debt managed, FREED aims to enroll $1 billion in stressed debt within 18 months. The funding will enhance its operational scale, product capabilities, and partnerships.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:04:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ffe7b9e91847a1e787804_1772093455369.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KNR Constructions Subsidiary Signs ₹2,163 Cr ECR Elevated Corridor Pact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-Subsidiary-Signs-2163-Cr-ECR-Elevated-Corridor-Pact/699ffdbf1d644e8733125120</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KNR-Constructions-Subsidiary-Signs-2163-Cr-ECR-Elevated-Corridor-Pact/699ffdbf1d644e8733125120</guid><description>KNR Constructions' subsidiary has formalized a significant ₹2,163 crore Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM) project for a four-lane elevated corridor along the East Coast Road in Tamil Nadu. This marks a key expansion in the company's project pipeline. However, the agreement signing is subject to a court case outcome, and the company has a history of execution challenges and past blacklistings, which investors will monitor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 08:01:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ffdbf1d644e873312511f_1772093026641.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maple Infra Trust Gets AAA Rating; Term Loan Facility Enhanced to ₹3,750 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Maple-Infra-Trust-Gets-AAA-Rating-Term-Loan-Facility-Enhanced-to-3750-Cr/699ffd541d644e873312509b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Maple-Infra-Trust-Gets-AAA-Rating-Term-Loan-Facility-Enhanced-to-3750-Cr/699ffd541d644e873312509b</guid><description>ICRA Limited has assigned Maple Infrastructure Trust the highest 'AAA (Stable)' Issuer Credit Rating. The agency also reaffirmed ratings for several debt instruments and significantly enhanced the long-term fund-based term loan facility to ₹3,750 crore. This top-tier rating underscores the trust's robust financial standing and its capacity to secure capital for infrastructure development.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:59:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ffd541d644e873312509a_1772092874830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ByteDance Valued at $550B as General Atlantic Seeks Lucrative Exit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ByteDance-Valued-at-550B-as-General-Atlantic-Seeks-Lucrative-Exit/699ffb4fcd95b9dc08f9d22d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ByteDance-Valued-at-550B-as-General-Atlantic-Seeks-Lucrative-Exit/699ffb4fcd95b9dc08f9d22d</guid><description>Investment firm General Atlantic is selling a stake in ByteDance at a $550 billion valuation, representing a substantial increase from prior secondary market trades and buybacks. This move highlights robust investor appetite for the Chinese tech giant and signals a strategic exit for General Atlantic as its funds mature. Despite the opacity of private market valuations, ByteDance's aggressive growth, particularly from TikTok, has propelled its value, though regulatory scrutiny and competitive pressures persist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:50:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ffb4fcd95b9dc08f9d22c_1772092427886.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Graphite India Surges on Dual Growth Bets, But EV CaPEx Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Graphite-India-Surges-on-Dual-Growth-Bets-But-EV-CaPEx-Looms/699ffafccd95b9dc08f9d1ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Graphite-India-Surges-on-Dual-Growth-Bets-But-EV-CaPEx-Looms/699ffafccd95b9dc08f9d1ca</guid><description>Graphite India shares have surged to a four-year high, propelled by robust demand for graphite electrodes from the steel industry's shift to EAF production and its strategic diversification into synthetic graphite anode materials for EVs. The company announced a substantial ₹4,330 crore investment for this new venture, leveraging manufacturing expertise for the burgeoning electric vehicle market. However, this aggressive expansion introduces significant financial leverage and execution challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:49:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ffafccd95b9dc08f9d1c9_1772092282551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shadowfax Launches ₹50 Cr Mega-Hub, Boosts Capacity to 1M Shipments/Day</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shadowfax-Launches-50-Cr-Mega-Hub-Boosts-Capacity-to-1M-ShipmentsDay/699ffa0acd95b9dc08f9d053</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shadowfax-Launches-50-Cr-Mega-Hub-Boosts-Capacity-to-1M-ShipmentsDay/699ffa0acd95b9dc08f9d053</guid><description>Logistics firm Shadowfax Technologies has made its largest automated sortation facility, 'OneNCR', operational in the NCR region. The ₹50 Crore investment significantly enhances its capacity to handle 1 million shipments daily, aiming to improve delivery speed and efficiency amid intense e-commerce competition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:45:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ffa0acd95b9dc08f9d052_1772092044140.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>