<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news from Whalesbook</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:08:53 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Nifty Tomorrow: Expert Forecast Reveals Key Support &amp; Resistance Levels - Will the Rally Continue?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/nifty-tomorrow-expert-forecast-reveals-key-support-resistance-levels-will-the-rally-continue/694ab0352a8fb21531f2f9dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/nifty-tomorrow-expert-forecast-reveals-key-support-resistance-levels-will-the-rally-continue/694ab0352a8fb21531f2f9dc</guid><description>Indian stock market indices, Nifty and Sensex, closed flat on December 23rd with profit-taking in IT and pharma sectors. Nifty gained 4.75 points to 26,177.15, while Sensex dipped slightly. The India VIX fell over 3%. Experts predict consolidation after a recent rally, with Nifty finding support around 25,950-26,050 and resistance near 26,300, suggesting a potential continuation of the uptrend with a buy-on-dips strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Steel Secures Full Control of Tata BlueScope: CCI Approves Landmark Acquisition!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial Goods/Services/tata-steel-secures-full-control-of-tata-bluescope-cci-approves-landmark-acquisition/694aafc22a8fb21531f2f947</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial Goods/Services/tata-steel-secures-full-control-of-tata-bluescope-cci-approves-landmark-acquisition/694aafc22a8fb21531f2f947</guid><description>The Competition Commission of India (CCI) has approved Tata Steel Limited's proposal to acquire full ownership of Tata BlueScope Steel Private Ltd. This acquisition ends the 50:50 joint venture with BlueScope Steel Asia Holdings and grants Tata Steel sole control, significantly strengthening its position in the value-added and downstream steel products market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:52:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aafc22a8fb21531f2f946_1766502456054.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emcure Pharma's Gujarat Plant Gets US FDA 'Clean Chit': Major Boost for Exports?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare/Biotech/emcure-pharmas-gujarat-plant-gets-us-fda-clean-chit-major-boost-for-exports/694aae542a8fb21531f2f667</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare/Biotech/emcure-pharmas-gujarat-plant-gets-us-fda-clean-chit-major-boost-for-exports/694aae542a8fb21531f2f667</guid><description>Emcure Pharmaceuticals announced its Gujarat manufacturing facility received a 'No Action Indicated' report from the US FDA after a recent inspection. This signifies the plant meets stringent regulatory standards, bolstering confidence in its export capabilities and compliance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:52:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aae542a8fb21531f2f666_1766502046652.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wall Street Banks Storm Crypto: Are Your Favorite Exchanges Doomed?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking/Finance/wall-street-banks-storm-crypto-are-your-favorite-exchanges-doomed/694aaf122a8fb21531f2f7d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking/Finance/wall-street-banks-storm-crypto-are-your-favorite-exchanges-doomed/694aaf122a8fb21531f2f7d2</guid><description>JPMorgan Chase is reportedly exploring crypto trading services for institutional investors, a move signaled by recent U.S. regulatory guidance from the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC). This guidance allows national banks to broker 'riskless principal' crypto-asset transactions, potentially shifting significant retail order flow from crypto-native exchanges to regulated banking channels. Major banks like Goldman Sachs and BNY Mellon are also expanding their crypto offerings, intensifying competition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:50:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aaf122a8fb21531f2f7d1_1766502291722.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Mutual Fund &amp; BlackRock Snap Up Belrise: Rs 897 Cr Deal Shakes Auto Components Market!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/sbi-mutual-fund-blackrock-snap-up-belrise-rs-897-cr-deal-shakes-auto-components-market/694aaf3a2a8fb21531f2f80a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/sbi-mutual-fund-blackrock-snap-up-belrise-rs-897-cr-deal-shakes-auto-components-market/694aaf3a2a8fb21531f2f80a</guid><description>SBI Mutual Fund and BlackRock have jointly acquired over 6.5 percent equity in automotive parts maker Belrise Industries for approximately ₹897 crore through open market transactions. SBI Mutual Fund purchased 5.8 percent for ₹788.3 crore, while BlackRock bought 0.79 percent for ₹108.37 crore. The stake was sold by promoter entity Sumedh Tools. Belrise Industries shares rallied significantly following the news.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:49:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aaf3a2a8fb21531f2f809_1766502399659.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Economy Surges: GDP Skyrockets 4.3% - Is This the Start of a New Boom?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/us-economy-surges-gdp-skyrockets-43-is-this-the-start-of-a-new-boom/694aae972a8fb21531f2f6f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/us-economy-surges-gdp-skyrockets-43-is-this-the-start-of-a-new-boom/694aae972a8fb21531f2f6f9</guid><description>The United States economy experienced its fastest growth in two years, with Gross Domestic Product (GDP) surging by an annualized 4.3% in the third quarter. This robust expansion was driven by strong consumer and business spending, alongside calmer trade policies. The Bureau of Economic Analysis reported the increase, surpassing expectations, as the economy maintained momentum despite previous disruptions like the government shutdown.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:49:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aae972a8fb21531f2f6f8_1766502116174.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India &amp; New Zealand Forge Landmark Fintech Pact: Your Digital Payments Future Set to Transform!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International News/india-new-zealand-forge-landmark-fintech-pact-your-digital-payments-future-set-to-transform/694aad422a8fb21531f2f4cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International News/india-new-zealand-forge-landmark-fintech-pact-your-digital-payments-future-set-to-transform/694aad422a8fb21531f2f4cc</guid><description>India and New Zealand have concluded a free trade agreement (FTA) with a key annex focused on strengthening fintech collaboration. The pact allows Indian financial service providers to establish cross-border digital operations in New Zealand, subject to local regulations. It also aims to build an interoperable payments system for real-time remittances and merchant payments, paving the way for Indian digital payment platforms like UPI to expand. The agreement facilitates knowledge exchange through regulatory sandboxes, benefiting Indian fintech startups and providing protection against discriminatory treatment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:41:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aad422a8fb21531f2f4cb_1766501948881.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Economy Shocks Wall Street: GDP Surges to Fastest Pace in 2 Years! What It Means for Your Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/us-economy-shocks-wall-street-gdp-surges-to-fastest-pace-in-2-years-what-it-means-for-your-investments/694aab242a8fb21531f2f1c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/us-economy-shocks-wall-street-gdp-surges-to-fastest-pace-in-2-years-what-it-means-for-your-investments/694aab242a8fb21531f2f1c5</guid><description>The United States economy experienced its strongest growth in two years during the third quarter, expanding at a 4.3% annualized rate. This robust performance was fueled by strong consumer and business spending, along with more stable trade policies. However, the positive GDP report led to a drop in Treasury yields and equity futures, indicating market uncertainty despite the economic strength. Inflation remains a concern, with the Fed's preferred measure rising 2.9%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:35:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aab242a8fb21531f2f1c4_1766501261610.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹8,461 Crore Exodus! Indian Investors Turn Sellers in 2025, Ending 6-Year Buying Frenzy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8461-crore-exodus-indian-investors-turn-sellers-in-2025-ending-6-year-buying-frenzy/694aa9462a8fb21531f28bd4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8461-crore-exodus-indian-investors-turn-sellers-in-2025-ending-6-year-buying-frenzy/694aa9462a8fb21531f28bd4</guid><description>After a six-year buying spree, individual investors have become net sellers in the Indian equity market in 2025, withdrawing approximately ₹8,461 crore. This sharp reversal follows record purchases in 2024 and reflects a change in market dynamics amid a tumultuous year characterized by correction and volatility, according to the National Stock Exchange of India.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:21:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aa9462a8fb21531f28bd3_1766500793824.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blackstone's Big Win: Federal Bank Stake Gets Green Light from CCI!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking/Finance/blackstones-big-win-federal-bank-stake-gets-green-light-from-cci/694aa8b82a8fb21531f24748</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking/Finance/blackstones-big-win-federal-bank-stake-gets-green-light-from-cci/694aa8b82a8fb21531f24748</guid><description>The Competition Commission of India (CCI) has approved private equity firm Blackstone's proposal to acquire a 9.99% stake in Federal Bank. The investment will be made through warrants by Blackstone's arm, Asia II Topco XIII Pte Ltd. This approval allows Blackstone to become a significant shareholder and potentially nominate a director to the bank's board.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:21:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aa8b82a8fb21531f24747_1766500626456.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Taxman's 'Nudge' Alert: Correct Bogus Claims by Dec 31 or Face Hefty Penalties!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/taxmans-nudge-alert-correct-bogus-claims-by-dec-31-or-face-hefty-penalties/694aa7ef2a8fb21531f1fb4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/taxmans-nudge-alert-correct-bogus-claims-by-dec-31-or-face-hefty-penalties/694aa7ef2a8fb21531f1fb4c</guid><description>The Central Board of Direct Taxes (CBDT) has launched a 'NUDGE' campaign for the 2025-26 assessment year. This initiative encourages taxpayers to voluntarily review and correct any potentially ineligible deduction or exemption claims, especially those involving bogus donations to political parties. Identified taxpayers must file revised income-tax returns by December 31, 2025, to avoid additional tax liabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:17:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aa7ef2a8fb21531f1fb4b_1766500617203.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blackstone's Mega Stake Boost in Federal Bank Cleared: What it Means for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking/Finance/blackstones-mega-stake-boost-in-federal-bank-cleared-what-it-means-for-your-investments/694aa7862a8fb21531f1bbf2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking/Finance/blackstones-mega-stake-boost-in-federal-bank-cleared-what-it-means-for-your-investments/694aa7862a8fb21531f1bbf2</guid><description>India's competition regulator, the Competition Commission of India (CCI), has approved Blackstone's plan to acquire a 9.99% stake in Federal Bank. The investment will be made through Asia II Topco XIII Pte Ltd, a Blackstone entity, via warrants. This stake acquisition could grant Blackstone the right to nominate a director to Federal Bank's board, signaling strong confidence from the private equity giant in the Indian banking sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Alarm Bells Ring: India's FDI Turns Negative for 3rd Month – What’s Draining Capital?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/alarm-bells-ring-indias-fdi-turns-negative-for-3rd-month-whats-draining-capital/694aa5f72a8fb21531f1715a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/alarm-bells-ring-indias-fdi-turns-negative-for-3rd-month-whats-draining-capital/694aa5f72a8fb21531f1715a</guid><description>Net Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) in India has turned negative for the third consecutive month, with outflows of $1.5 billion in October 2025. This trend, also seen in September ($2.4 billion) and August ($0.6 billion), is driven by significant repatriation and outward investments. Despite these recent outflows, the cumulative FDI from April to October 2025 remains higher year-on-year. Financial services and manufacturing were the primary sectors receiving FDI, while outward investments primarily targeted Singapore, the US, and the UAE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Northeast Power Surge: NHPC Ignites First Unit of Massive Subansiri Hydro Project!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/northeast-power-surge-nhpc-ignites-first-unit-of-massive-subansiri-hydro-project/694aa3b92a8fb21531f0f6ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/northeast-power-surge-nhpc-ignites-first-unit-of-massive-subansiri-hydro-project/694aa3b92a8fb21531f0f6ad</guid><description>NHPC has successfully commissioned the first 250 MW unit of its 2,000 MW Subansiri Lower Hydroelectric Project, located on the Arunachal-Assam border. This milestone is set to significantly enhance energy supply in Northeast India and contribute to the nation's renewable energy capacity and grid stability. The remaining seven units are expected to be commissioned in phases by 2026-27, eventually powering 16 states.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:05:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aa3b92a8fb21531f0f6ac_1766499361255.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PFC's ₹6,000 Crore Bond Sale CRISIS: Yields Spike Forces Major Retreat! Investor Demands Unmet!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking/Finance/pfcs-6000-crore-bond-sale-crisis-yields-spike-forces-major-retreat-investor-demands-unmet/694aa2bd2a8fb21531f0f4b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking/Finance/pfcs-6000-crore-bond-sale-crisis-yields-spike-forces-major-retreat-investor-demands-unmet/694aa2bd2a8fb21531f0f4b8</guid><description>State-owned Power Finance Corp (PFC) has scrapped a ₹6,000 crore bond issuance due to elevated investor yield demands. This marks the third withdrawal in two months, highlighting muted transmission of the Reserve Bank of India's rate cuts and pressure on corporate bond yields. While PFC sought yields below 6.90% for its shorter-duration papers, Bank of India successfully raised ₹10,000 crore via 10-year infrastructure bonds at 7.23%, attracting investors preferring longer tenures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:49:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aa2bd2a8fb21531f0f4b7_1766499343554.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive MF Shake-up Incoming! Prepare for Record Highs as Large/Midcap Cut-offs Skyrocket in January!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual Funds/massive-mf-shake-up-incoming-prepare-for-record-highs-as-largemidcap-cut-offs-skyrocket-in-january/694aa2392a8fb21531f0f395</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual Funds/massive-mf-shake-up-incoming-prepare-for-record-highs-as-largemidcap-cut-offs-skyrocket-in-january/694aa2392a8fb21531f0f395</guid><description>The Association of Mutual Funds in India (AMFI) is set to reclassify its stock universe in early January. Experts predict the market capitalization cut-off for large-cap stocks will surge by 15% to ₹1.05 trillion. The mid-cap threshold is also expected to rise significantly to ₹34,800 crore. This rejig, driven by recent IPOs and increased stock valuations, will redefine which companies fall into the large-cap and mid-cap categories for mutual fund investments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:49:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aa2392a8fb21531f0f394_1766498986375.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vikran Engineering Secures Massive ₹2,035 Crore Solar Power Order: India's Green Energy Boom Continues?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/vikran-engineering-secures-massive-2035-crore-solar-power-order-indias-green-energy-boom-continues/694aa10b2a8fb21531f0eff8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/vikran-engineering-secures-massive-2035-crore-solar-power-order-indias-green-energy-boom-continues/694aa10b2a8fb21531f0eff8</guid><description>Vikran Engineering Limited announced a significant ₹2,035.26 crore EPC contract win from Onix Renewables Limited for a 600 MW solar power project. The project, located across multiple sites in Maharashtra, includes design, procurement, supply, erection, testing, and commissioning, with a 12-month execution timeline. This substantial order strengthens Vikran Engineering's position in India's rapidly expanding renewable energy sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:48:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aa10b2a8fb21531f0eff7_1766498760141.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCLTech Teams Up With Microsoft! Unlocking AI's Power for Scientific Breakthroughs – You Won't Believe What's Next!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/hcltech-teams-up-with-microsoft-unlocking-ais-power-for-scientific-breakthroughs-you-wont-believe-whats-next/694a9fe62a8fb21531f0ed5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/hcltech-teams-up-with-microsoft-unlocking-ais-power-for-scientific-breakthroughs-you-wont-believe-whats-next/694a9fe62a8fb21531f0ed5d</guid><description>HCL Technologies has partnered with Microsoft, joining its advanced AI platform, Discovery. This collaboration aims to accelerate scientific innovation in fields like chemistry, materials science, drug discovery, and semiconductor design. HCL Technologies will work closely with Microsoft's team for deep technical integration and research projects, focusing on enterprise-scale implementations to speed up innovation cycles and bring scientific advancements to market faster. HCLTech shares saw a slight uptick following the announcement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:48:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a9fe62a8fb21531f0ed5c_1766498423616.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Post Office Savings Schemes: Your Quiet Money Haven or Growth Cage? Find Out!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal Finance/post-office-savings-schemes-your-quiet-money-haven-or-growth-cage-find-out/694aa03b2a8fb21531f0ee5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal Finance/post-office-savings-schemes-your-quiet-money-haven-or-growth-cage-find-out/694aa03b2a8fb21531f0ee5c</guid><description>Post office savings schemes offer government-backed safety and predictability, making them ideal for retirees and conservative savers seeking stable income. Schemes like Senior Citizen Savings Scheme, Monthly Income Scheme, and Time Deposits provide planned returns but lack the growth potential of market-linked products. While useful for capital preservation and budgeting, they are not suited for long-term, inflation-beating growth or emergency funds due to potential liquidity constraints and fixed returns.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:45:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aa03b2a8fb21531f0ee5b_1766498477956.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors Chief Challenges Rivals: Will India Hit 2030 EV Target?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/tata-motors-chief-challenges-rivals-will-india-hit-2030-ev-target/694a9fe72a8fb21531f0ed88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/tata-motors-chief-challenges-rivals-will-india-hit-2030-ev-target/694a9fe72a8fb21531f0ed88</guid><description>Tata Motors MD Shailesh Chandra urged Indian automakers to seriously evaluate their electric vehicle (EV) commitments to meet the government's goal of 30% EV penetration by 2030. He noted that India is projected to end 2025 with less than 5% EV penetration, a market Tata Motors leads with 44%. Chandra called for self-reflection among top players, especially as some, like Maruti Suzuki, are significantly behind schedule with new EV launches. Tata Motors, meanwhile, plans substantial investments of ₹16,000-18,000 crore in its EV business through FY30, aiming to launch new models and improve existing ones.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:45:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a9fe72a8fb21531f0ed87_1766498478403.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: India's Massive Infra Push REVEALED! Roads, Rural Growth to Drive Economy?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/budget-2026-indias-massive-infra-push-revealed-roads-rural-growth-to-drive-economy/694aa0092a8fb21531f0ee0d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/budget-2026-indias-massive-infra-push-revealed-roads-rural-growth-to-drive-economy/694aa0092a8fb21531f0ee0d</guid><description>Budget 2026 is set to heavily emphasize infrastructure spending, particularly on roads, highways, and rural development, as a key strategy for India's steady growth and its goal of becoming a developed nation by 2047. The Confederation of Indian Industry expects increased capital expenditure and new initiatives. Despite US tariffs and domestic unemployment concerns, India's robust GDP growth and the Reserve Bank of India's accommodative policy signal a focus on investment-led resilience.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:42:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694aa0092a8fb21531f0ee0c_1766498595106.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Health Boom: Nutraceuticals Explodes as Fastest-Growing Consumer Segment – What's Driving the Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer Products/indias-health-boom-nutraceuticals-explodes-as-fastest-growing-consumer-segment-whats-driving-the-surge/694a9ed22a8fb21531f0eb75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer Products/indias-health-boom-nutraceuticals-explodes-as-fastest-growing-consumer-segment-whats-driving-the-surge/694a9ed22a8fb21531f0eb75</guid><description>India's nutraceuticals market is booming, becoming the fastest-growing consumer segment driven by increased health consciousness and demand for plant-based products. Consumer brand Earthful highlights this trend, launching an initiative for menopause awareness. The Indian market is valued at $30.37 billion in 2024, projected to grow at 13.6% annually until 2030. Earthful aims to quadruple its revenue, focusing on women's health products.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:41:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a9ed22a8fb21531f0eb74_1766498208177.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HMEL Unleashes Rs 2,600 Cr Mega Expansion: Fine Chemicals &amp; Fuel Growth Set to Transform Punjab!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/hmel-unleashes-rs-2600-cr-mega-expansion-fine-chemicals-fuel-growth-set-to-transform-punjab/694a9f6b2a8fb21531f0ec89</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/hmel-unleashes-rs-2600-cr-mega-expansion-fine-chemicals-fuel-growth-set-to-transform-punjab/694a9f6b2a8fb21531f0ec89</guid><description>HPCL Mittal Energy Limited (HMEL) is investing ₹2,600 crore to expand its Guru Gobind Singh Refinery in Bathinda. The expansion includes setting up polypropylene downstream units and fine chemical projects. This move aims to significantly boost industrial activities and employment in Punjab, diversifying HMEL's operations beyond fuel production and positioning the state as a key manufacturing hub for polypropylene and fine chemicals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Maritime Surge: Building a $30 Trillion Economy by 2047 from the Seas!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/indias-maritime-surge-building-a-30-trillion-economy-by-2047-from-the-seas/694a9dd52a8fb21531f0e9c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/indias-maritime-surge-building-a-30-trillion-economy-by-2047-from-the-seas/694a9dd52a8fb21531f0e9c1</guid><description>India is transforming its maritime sector to achieve its goal of a $30 trillion economy by 2047. Recent years have seen significant improvements in port capacity and efficiency, with new developments like the Wadhwan port and strong backing for green shipping and coastal cargo. The Maritime Amrit Kaal Vision 2047 outlines a 25-year roadmap with a $1 trillion investment to boost ports, shipping, and waterways, aiming for substantial export growth and deeper integration into global value chains.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:38:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a9dd52a8fb21531f0e9c0_1766497976088.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Coal Market Set for Major Shake-Up: New Auction Rules to Boost Prices and Transparency!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/indias-coal-market-set-for-major-shake-up-new-auction-rules-to-boost-prices-and-transparency/694a9d842a8fb21531f0e916</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/indias-coal-market-set-for-major-shake-up-new-auction-rules-to-boost-prices-and-transparency/694a9d842a8fb21531f0e916</guid><description>The Indian government has proposed new rules for the national coal exchange, favouring a double-sided closed auction mechanism for price discovery. This aims to maximize economic surplus by considering all bid types and enhancing transparency. Stakeholders are invited to provide feedback on the revised draft Coal Exchange Rules, 2025, by January 13, 2026. The Coal Controller Organisation will regulate exchanges, focusing on market integrity and preventing manipulation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:37:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a9d842a8fb21531f0e915_1766497887929.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SJS Enterprises Seals Game-Changing Tech Deal to Revolutionize India's Automotive Displays!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/sjs-enterprises-seals-game-changing-tech-deal-to-revolutionize-indias-automotive-displays/694a9a3a2a8fb21531f0e518</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/sjs-enterprises-seals-game-changing-tech-deal-to-revolutionize-indias-automotive-displays/694a9a3a2a8fb21531f0e518</guid><description>SJS Enterprises Ltd. has partnered with Hong Kong-based BOE Varitronix Ltd. (BOEVX) to manufacture advanced automotive display systems in India. The agreement involves technology licensing and supply for optical bonding and assembly of displays for four-wheelers. This strategic move aims to boost local manufacturing capabilities and strengthen SJS Enterprises' position in the growing automotive segment. The company's shares saw a positive reaction, closing 3.39% higher on December 23rd.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a9a3a2a8fb21531f0e517_1766496978848.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai's Game-Changing Cricket Move: Global ICC Partnership Revealed - What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/hyundais-game-changing-cricket-move-global-icc-partnership-revealed-what-investors-need-to-know/694a995c2a8fb21531f0e3de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/hyundais-game-changing-cricket-move-global-icc-partnership-revealed-what-investors-need-to-know/694a995c2a8fb21531f0e3de</guid><description>Hyundai Motor Company has inked a significant global partnership with the International Cricket Council (ICC) for its 2026-2027 tournaments. As a premier partner, Hyundai gains exclusive rights, including prominent branding and fan experiences, notably for the 2027 Men's Cricket World Cup. This deal aims to connect with over two billion cricket fans worldwide, strengthening the brand's presence, especially in the vital Indian market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:09:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a995c2a8fb21531f0e3dd_1766496755674.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Generali Central Insurance Eyes Doubling Premium to ₹10,000 Cr by 2030! SME Boom &amp; Bank Power Fuel Growth?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/generali-central-insurance-eyes-doubling-premium-to-10000-cr-by-2030-sme-boom-bank-power-fuel-growth/694a98242a8fb21531f0e12d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/generali-central-insurance-eyes-doubling-premium-to-10000-cr-by-2030-sme-boom-bank-power-fuel-growth/694a98242a8fb21531f0e12d</guid><description>Generali Central Insurance aims to double its gross written premium to ₹10,000 crore by 2030, driven by a 14% annual growth rate and leveraging its partnership with Central Bank of India. The insurer is prioritizing the underserved Small and Medium Enterprise (SME) segment, utilizing the bank's extensive customer base for cross-selling insurance products. This strategy targets significant expansion in a key growth area.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:07:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vardhman Special Steel Invests ₹475 Crore in Ludhiana to Forge Auto Component Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial Goods/Services/vardhman-special-steel-invests-475-crore-in-ludhiana-to-forge-auto-component-future/694a99ec2a8fb21531f0e4c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial Goods/Services/vardhman-special-steel-invests-475-crore-in-ludhiana-to-forge-auto-component-future/694a99ec2a8fb21531f0e4c2</guid><description>Vardhman Special Steel announced a significant investment of ₹475 crore to establish a new steel forging and machining manufacturing facility in Ludhiana, Punjab. This strategic expansion aims to strengthen its position in the automotive supply chain by producing specialized components with technical expertise from Aichi Steel Corporation, promising Japanese quality standards and enhanced customer alignment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:07:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a99ec2a8fb21531f0e4c1_1766496995625.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Billion-Dollar Companies Shrink: Rupee Woes Hit Valuations Despite Market Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/indias-billion-dollar-companies-shrink-rupee-woes-hit-valuations-despite-market-gains/694a980f2a8fb21531f0e0f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/indias-billion-dollar-companies-shrink-rupee-woes-hit-valuations-despite-market-gains/694a980f2a8fb21531f0e0f8</guid><description>The number of Indian companies valued at over $1 billion has decreased to 591 in 2025, down from 610 last year. This decline is primarily attributed to the Indian rupee's significant depreciation against the US dollar. Despite the benchmark Nifty and Sensex indices posting gains year-to-date, the weakening currency increased the Rupee threshold required for a company to reach billion-dollar valuation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:06:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a980f2a8fb21531f0e0f7_1766496376374.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Agritech Revolution: $28 Billion Opportunity Unlocked by AI!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/indias-agritech-revolution-28-billion-opportunity-unlocked-by-ai/694a98e82a8fb21531f0e2af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/indias-agritech-revolution-28-billion-opportunity-unlocked-by-ai/694a98e82a8fb21531f0e2af</guid><description>India's agritech market is set for massive growth, projected to reach $28 billion by 2030, expanding at a 25% CAGR. The sector is transforming from isolated tools to system-level infrastructure, driven by formal credit, data-driven decisions, and increasing AI integration. While adoption faces challenges due to small landholdings and digital literacy, AI is becoming a key catalyst, enhancing yield prediction, crop monitoring, and advisory services, promising a more integrated and resilient agricultural economy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:04:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a98e82a8fb21531f0e2ae_1766496640299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India &amp; New Zealand Forge Landmark FTA: UPI to Unleash Digital Payments Power Down Under!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking/Finance/india-new-zealand-forge-landmark-fta-upi-to-unleash-digital-payments-power-down-under/694a97b52a8fb21531f0e01d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking/Finance/india-new-zealand-forge-landmark-fta-upi-to-unleash-digital-payments-power-down-under/694a97b52a8fb21531f0e01d</guid><description>India and New Zealand have signed a comprehensive Free Trade Agreement (FTA) focusing on expanding financial services cooperation. The pact will allow Indian digital payment platforms like UPI to enter the New Zealand market, boosting cross-border transactions. It also includes measures to improve market access for Indian financial institutions and facilitates increased foreign direct investment. This agreement is projected to significantly boost New Zealand's annual exports to India by $1.1 billion to $1.3 billion, with services forming a central component. Additionally, nearly 5,000 temporary work visas will be available for Indian professionals in various sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:59:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a97b52a8fb21531f0e01c_1766496504033.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VA Tech Wabag's Rs 16,000 Crore Order Surge: Is This India's Next Water Tech Giant?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial Goods/Services/va-tech-wabags-rs-16000-crore-order-surge-is-this-indias-next-water-tech-giant/694a977e2a8fb21531f0dfbd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial Goods/Services/va-tech-wabags-rs-16000-crore-order-surge-is-this-indias-next-water-tech-giant/694a977e2a8fb21531f0dfbd</guid><description>VA Tech Wabag is set for a strong second half with a massive ₹16,000 crore order book, boosted by a new water treatment plant project in Nepal funded by the Asian Development Bank. The company, led by Chairman Rajiv Mittal, is strategically focusing on multilateral-funded projects for payment security and plans to expand into high-technology sectors like future energy solutions and data centres, emphasizing margin-accretive growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Group Powers India's Energy Future: Record Wins in Solar, Wind, and Green Hydrogen!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/adani-group-powers-indias-energy-future-record-wins-in-solar-wind-and-green-hydrogen/694a968a2a8fb21531f0dcf9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/adani-group-powers-indias-energy-future-record-wins-in-solar-wind-and-green-hydrogen/694a968a2a8fb21531f0dcf9</guid><description>Adani Group's clean energy businesses achieved record scale and technological advancements in 2025. Adani Solar hit 15,000 MW module shipments, Adani Wind installed 1 GW of its largest turbines, and ANIL launched India's first solar-powered 5 MW green hydrogen pilot plant. These milestones highlight Adani's expanding role in India's rapidly growing renewable energy sector amidst global supply chain realignments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Global Price Shock: 'Magic' Weight Loss Injections Cost a Fortune Worldwide!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare/Biotech/global-price-shock-magic-weight-loss-injections-cost-a-fortune-worldwide/694a97292a8fb21531f0de67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare/Biotech/global-price-shock-magic-weight-loss-injections-cost-a-fortune-worldwide/694a97292a8fb21531f0de67</guid><description>Popular weight-loss drugs like Ozempic, Mounjaro, and Wegovy are trending globally, but their high costs are a major barrier. Prices vary dramatically across countries, with the US often seeing the highest figures, while India offers more affordable options for some. Experts caution against viewing them as miracle cures, emphasizing lifestyle changes alongside medical supervision.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBL Bank Stock Soars: Is Dubai Giant's $3 Billion Bet the Ultimate Turning Point?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/rbl-bank-stock-soars-is-dubai-giants-3-billion-bet-the-ultimate-turning-point/694a96ba2a8fb21531f0dd45</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/rbl-bank-stock-soars-is-dubai-giants-3-billion-bet-the-ultimate-turning-point/694a96ba2a8fb21531f0dd45</guid><description>RBL Bank is showing signs of recovery, with its stock more than doubling in 12 months following a challenging period. A key driver is the $3 billion investment from Dubai-based Emirates NBD Bank, providing capital and global reach. While stability is emerging, challenges like high operating costs and mixed profitability metrics persist, with limited upside seen by analysts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BIG REVEAL: Coal India's Subsidiary SECL Set for Stock Market Debut!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/big-reveal-coal-indias-subsidiary-secl-set-for-stock-market-debut/694a944e2a8fb21531f0d80e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/big-reveal-coal-indias-subsidiary-secl-set-for-stock-market-debut/694a944e2a8fb21531f0d80e</guid><description>Coal India Limited's board has given the green light for the listing of its key subsidiary, South Eastern Coalfields Limited (SECL), aligning with government divestment plans. While SECL's operational importance is high, details on the listing's timeline and scale remain undisclosed. Coal India shares rose 3.73% ahead of the announcement, following a 7.54% gain last month.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:39:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a944e2a8fb21531f0d80d_1766495748912.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bliss GVS Pharma's Top Leader Set for MD Role: Shareholder Vote Next!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare/Biotech/bliss-gvs-pharmas-top-leader-set-for-md-role-shareholder-vote-next/694a939c2a8fb21531f0d66c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare/Biotech/bliss-gvs-pharmas-top-leader-set-for-md-role-shareholder-vote-next/694a939c2a8fb21531f0d66c</guid><description>Bliss GVS Pharma Limited's Board of Directors has approved the appointment of S.N. Kamath as the company's Managing Director for a three-year term. This key leadership change is subject to shareholder approval. Kamath, who is a promoter and currently serves as the Chief Executive Officer, will take on the dual role of Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer upon receiving shareholder consent through a postal ballot. The company recently reported a quarter-on-quarter rise in revenue for Q2 FY2025-26, though net profit saw a decline.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:39:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a939c2a8fb21531f0d66b_1766495513999.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariffs Shatter India's Diamond Dreams: Surat Workers Face Job Crisis!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/us-tariffs-shatter-indias-diamond-dreams-surat-workers-face-job-crisis/694a93462a8fb21531f0d5cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/us-tariffs-shatter-indias-diamond-dreams-surat-workers-face-job-crisis/694a93462a8fb21531f0d5cf</guid><description>US tariffs on Indian diamonds have triggered a severe downturn in Surat, India's diamond capital. Exports to the US have plummeted, leading to widespread factory shutdowns, job losses for over 1.5 lakh workers, and drastically reduced incomes, pushing many to the brink.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:39:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a93462a8fb21531f0d5ce_1766502086342.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Ports Completes NQXT Acquisition: FY26 Cargo &amp; Earnings Skyrocket – What This Means for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/adani-ports-completes-nqxt-acquisition-fy26-cargo-earnings-skyrocket-what-this-means-for-investors/694a92212a8fb21531f0d29b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/adani-ports-completes-nqxt-acquisition-fy26-cargo-earnings-skyrocket-what-this-means-for-investors/694a92212a8fb21531f0d29b</guid><description>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) has successfully acquired Australia's North Queensland Export Terminal (NQXT). This strategic move prompts APSEZ to significantly raise its financial guidance for Fiscal Year 2026, projecting higher EBITDA earnings between ₹22,350-₹23,350 crore and increased cargo volumes from 545-555 million metric tonnes. The acquisition bolsters APSEZ's international footprint and aligns with its ambitious target of handling one billion tonnes of cargo annually by 2030.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:39:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694a92212a8fb21531f0d29a_1766501638869.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>