<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:17:27 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Yes Bank's Crucial Q3 Results Date Revealed! Board Meeting Set for January 17, 2026 - What Investors Must Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Banks-Crucial-Q3-Results-Date-Revealed-Board-Meeting-Set-for-January-17-2026-What-Investors-Must-Know/69568e554342f77179f69c04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Banks-Crucial-Q3-Results-Date-Revealed-Board-Meeting-Set-for-January-17-2026-What-Investors-Must-Know/69568e554342f77179f69c04</guid><description>Yes Bank has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on Saturday, January 17, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ending December 31, 2025. This announcement details the schedule for the bank's upcoming earnings report, which is crucial for investors monitoring its financial performance for the fiscal year 2025-26. The trading window for company insiders will also be closed until two days after the results are published.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:56:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568e554342f77179f69c03_1767280437683.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Hints at Major Breakout! Can 26,200 Conquer Amidst ITC's Tax Shock?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Hints-at-Major-Breakout-Can-26200-Conquer-Amidst-ITCs-Tax-Shock/69568d274342f77179f696b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Hints-at-Major-Breakout-Can-26200-Conquer-Amidst-ITCs-Tax-Shock/69568d274342f77179f696b7</guid><description>The Nifty 50 index ended near flat, closing up just 16 points at 26,146, extending its winning streak. However, charts suggest a potential breakout above 26,200. Gains were capped by a sharp 9% fall in ITC due to increased excise duty on tobacco and health cess on pan masala. Auto, Realty, and Metal stocks led sectoral gains, while FMCG, Pharma, and Healthcare saw pressure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:55:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568d274342f77179f696b6_1767279980628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyderabad EV Hub Ignites! Olectra Greentech Unveils Massive Production Capacity – A Game Changer for Electric Mobility?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyderabad-EV-Hub-Ignites-Olectra-Greentech-Unveils-Massive-Production-Capacity-A-Game-Changer-for-Electric-Mobility/69568d3c4342f77179f69738</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyderabad-EV-Hub-Ignites-Olectra-Greentech-Unveils-Massive-Production-Capacity-A-Game-Changer-for-Electric-Mobility/69568d3c4342f77179f69738</guid><description>Olectra Greentech Limited has officially commenced commercial operations for Phase I of its new electric vehicle manufacturing facility in Hyderabad. The plant's initial phase brings an annual production capacity of 2,500 electric buses, representing half of the facility's total planned capacity. This significant expansion is expected to bolster the company's manufacturing capabilities and support its growing order book in the booming electric bus segment, reinforcing its commitment to sustainable public transport solutions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:55:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568d3c4342f77179f69737_1767280274383.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KPI Green Energy Bags Crucial Grid Nod for 32.40 MW Projects! What This Means for Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Bags-Crucial-Grid-Nod-for-3240-MW-Projects-What-This-Means-for-Investors/69568b564342f77179f68ebc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/KPI-Green-Energy-Bags-Crucial-Grid-Nod-for-3240-MW-Projects-What-This-Means-for-Investors/69568b564342f77179f68ebc</guid><description>KPI Green Energy announced it has received grid connection approval for 32.40 megawatts of solar and hybrid power projects. These projects are developed for clients under its Captive Power Plant (CPP) business segment. This energization approval is a regulatory green light from grid operators, signifying the final step before connection to the main electricity grid, paving the way for power generation and revenue realization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:49:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568b564342f77179f68ebb_1767279505531.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India's Production Climbs But Offtake Dips in December: What Investors Need to Know</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-Indias-Production-Climbs-But-Offtake-Dips-in-December-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/69568ac94342f77179f68bc2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-Indias-Production-Climbs-But-Offtake-Dips-in-December-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/69568ac94342f77179f68bc2</guid><description>Coal India reported a 4.6% year-on-year increase in production to 75.7 million tonnes (MT) in December. However, offtake fell by 5.2% to 64.9 MT during the same period. For the April-December period of FY26, cumulative production decreased by 2.6% to 529.2 MT, while offtake slipped by 2.2% to 544.7 MT compared to the previous fiscal year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:47:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568ac94342f77179f68bc1_1767279390818.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 2000 Notes Mystery Solved: RBI Reveals Jaw-Dropping 98.41% Returned!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rs-2000-Notes-Mystery-Solved-RBI-Reveals-Jaw-Dropping-9841percent-Returned/69568a774342f77179f689ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rs-2000-Notes-Mystery-Solved-RBI-Reveals-Jaw-Dropping-9841percent-Returned/69568a774342f77179f689ed</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India announced that a significant 98.41% of the withdrawn Rs 2000 banknotes have been returned. As of December 31, 2025, only ₹5,669 crore worth of these high-value notes remain outside circulation, down from ₹3.56 lakh crore when withdrawal began on May 19, 2023. The Rs 2000 banknotes continue to be legal tender.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:46:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568a774342f77179f689ec_1767279299967.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Honda Cars India Roars Back: December Sales Surge 3.6% Amidst Strong Demand!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Honda-Cars-India-Roars-Back-December-Sales-Surge-36percent-Amidst-Strong-Demand/69568a4d4342f77179f688f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Honda-Cars-India-Roars-Back-December-Sales-Surge-36percent-Amidst-Strong-Demand/69568a4d4342f77179f688f7</guid><description>Honda Cars India reported a 3.6% rise in domestic sales for December 2025, reaching 5,807 units compared to 5,603 in December 2024. While exports saw a decline to 2,352 units, the company experienced robust demand across its popular models like the Honda Amaze, City, and Elevate. Honda Cars India attributes this positive momentum to factors including the GST 2.0 implementation and anticipates unlocking new opportunities with multiple product launches planned for 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:46:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568a4d4342f77179f688f6_1767279250419.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking! India's Steel Prices Hit 5-Year Low in 2025 Amidst Global Trade Chaos: Tata Steel CEO Reveals Alarming Trends!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Shocking-Indias-Steel-Prices-Hit-5-Year-Low-in-2025-Amidst-Global-Trade-Chaos-Tata-Steel-CEO-Reveals-Alarming-Trends/69568a084342f77179f68774</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Shocking-Indias-Steel-Prices-Hit-5-Year-Low-in-2025-Amidst-Global-Trade-Chaos-Tata-Steel-CEO-Reveals-Alarming-Trends/69568a084342f77179f68774</guid><description>Tata Steel CEO T V Narendran revealed that Indian steel prices hit a five-year low in 2025, despite robust domestic demand. He cited global trade disruptions, protectionist policies, and a surge in Chinese steel exports as key challenges impacting international markets. While Tata Steel's European business faced pressure, its domestic operations remained stable. Narendran also touched upon the company's expansion plans and expressed optimism about India's strong economic growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:44:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69568a084342f77179f68773_1767279190520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Big Relief for NBFCs: Infrastructure Loan Rules Eased Significantly!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Big-Relief-for-NBFCs-Infrastructure-Loan-Rules-Eased-Significantly/6956878f4342f77179f67af5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Big-Relief-for-NBFCs-Infrastructure-Loan-Rules-Eased-Significantly/6956878f4342f77179f67af5</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has eased proposed risk-weight rules for Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs) lending to infrastructure projects, following industry feedback. The definition of eligible 'high-quality' projects is broadened. Crucially, repayment thresholds for lower risk weights have been significantly reduced, easing lending conditions. However, critical lender protection clauses remain. The new norms will be effective from April 1, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:23:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956878f4342f77179f67af4_1767278595664.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Boom! Record Passenger Vehicle Sales Hit 45.5 Lakh Units in 2025 Driven by GST 2.0!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Boom-Record-Passenger-Vehicle-Sales-Hit-455-Lakh-Units-in-2025-Driven-by-GST-20/695686c44342f77179f676c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Boom-Record-Passenger-Vehicle-Sales-Hit-455-Lakh-Units-in-2025-Driven-by-GST-20/695686c44342f77179f676c2</guid><description>India's passenger vehicle market achieved a record 45.5 lakh units sold in 2025, growing by nearly 6%. Despite a slow start, GST 2.0 reforms in the latter half significantly boosted sales. Market leaders Maruti Suzuki India, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, and Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles posted their highest annual sales, surpassing previous records. SUVs maintained strong traction, comprising 55.8% of total sales, while small cars also showed recovery. Government incentives like tax relief and repo rate cuts further supported the industry's robust performance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:23:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695686c44342f77179f676c1_1767278366305.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Government's Bharat Taxi Set to Launch: Is This India's Answer to Ola &amp; Uber?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Governments-Bharat-Taxi-Set-to-Launch-Is-This-Indias-Answer-to-Ola-and-Uber/695686a74342f77179f6761d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Governments-Bharat-Taxi-Set-to-Launch-Is-This-Indias-Answer-to-Ola-and-Uber/695686a74342f77179f6761d</guid><description>Bharat Taxi, a new ride-hailing service backed by cooperatives, is officially launching in Delhi and other cities by the end of January. Following a successful pilot that averaged 5,500 rides daily, the platform operated by Sahakar Taxi Cooperative Ltd aims to reduce driver dependence on private companies. Drivers benefit from a zero-commission model, keeping full earnings, with cooperative profits shared among them.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:23:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695686a74342f77179f6761c_1767278316123.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Agri-Revolution Ignites! 185 New Seeds Unleashed to Boost Cotton &amp; Feed Millions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Agri-Revolution-Ignites-185-New-Seeds-Unleashed-to-Boost-Cotton-and-Feed-Millions/695686a24342f77179f675da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Agri-Revolution-Ignites-185-New-Seeds-Unleashed-to-Boost-Cotton-and-Feed-Millions/695686a24342f77179f675da</guid><description>India has launched 185 new high-yielding seed varieties across key crops, including 24 for cotton, rice, maize, and pulses. This initiative aims to significantly boost agricultural productivity, reduce import dependence, and strengthen initiatives like Kasturi Cotton. The focus is on improved yields and resilience, marking a significant step for India's agricultural sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:18:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695686a24342f77179f675d9_1767278458962.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Takes Helm! Tarun Garg Appointed Hyundai India MD &amp; CEO - ₹45,000 Cr EV &amp; Export Plans Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Takes-Helm-Tarun-Garg-Appointed-Hyundai-India-MD-and-CEO-45000-Cr-EV-and-Export-Plans-Unveiled/6956864a4342f77179f673bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-Takes-Helm-Tarun-Garg-Appointed-Hyundai-India-MD-and-CEO-45000-Cr-EV-and-Export-Plans-Unveiled/6956864a4342f77179f673bb</guid><description>Tarun Garg has officially taken charge as the Managing Director &amp; Chief Executive Officer (MD &amp; CEO) of Hyundai Motor India (HMIL) from January 1, 2026. This historic appointment marks the first time an Indian national will lead the company in its 29-year history. HMIL plans a significant investment of ₹45,000 crore by FY 2030, focusing on accelerating Electric Vehicles (EVs), hybrids, connected mobility, and establishing India as a key export hub.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:13:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956864a4342f77179f673ba_1767278230130.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nippo Battery Maker Indo National Eyes ₹1,000 Cr Revenue Surge with Bold Diversification!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nippo-Battery-Maker-Indo-National-Eyes-1000-Cr-Revenue-Surge-with-Bold-Diversification/695685e84342f77179f67170</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nippo-Battery-Maker-Indo-National-Eyes-1000-Cr-Revenue-Surge-with-Bold-Diversification/695685e84342f77179f67170</guid><description>Indo National, the maker of Nippo batteries, aims to double its revenue to ₹1,000 crore within five years. The company plans to achieve this by expanding into new business areas like LED lighting, electrical accessories, BLDC fans, and home care products, while also strengthening its position in premium alkaline batteries and exploring sustainability improvements.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:12:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695685e84342f77179f6716f_1767278234235.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Commercial Vehicle Giants Roar: December Sales Skyrocket Amidst GST 2.0 &amp; Festive Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Commercial-Vehicle-Giants-Roar-December-Sales-Skyrocket-Amidst-GST-20-and-Festive-Boom/695685914342f77179f66f33</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Commercial-Vehicle-Giants-Roar-December-Sales-Skyrocket-Amidst-GST-20-and-Festive-Boom/695685914342f77179f66f33</guid><description>Major Indian commercial vehicle manufacturers, including Tata Motors, Ashok Leyland, and Eicher Motor, reported strong sales growth in December 2025 and the third quarter (Q3) of FY26. Tata Motors led with a 24% increase in December, driven by a 40% surge in its Intermediate, Light, and Medium Commercial Vehicles segment. This robust performance is attributed to the positive impact of GST 2.0, sustained festive demand, and a rebound in construction and mining sectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:12:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695685914342f77179f66f32_1767278114929.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GST Revenue Dips 5% Amidst Soaring Refunds: Experts Say Calm Amidst Change!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/GST-Revenue-Dips-5percent-Amidst-Soaring-Refunds-Experts-Say-Calm-Amidst-Change/695685bf4342f77179f67023</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/GST-Revenue-Dips-5percent-Amidst-Soaring-Refunds-Experts-Say-Calm-Amidst-Change/695685bf4342f77179f67023</guid><description>Net Goods and Services Tax (GST) collections in India for December declined by over 5% compared to the previous year, primarily due to a significant 62% surge in refunds. This dip is attributed to the impact of GST 2.0 rate rationalization, which has led to inverted duty structures in several sectors and a subsequent increase in refund applications. Despite the decline in net domestic collections, experts from EY India and Deloitte India remain unconcerned, viewing this as a phase of calibration and expecting revenue to revive strongly. Gross GST collections saw a healthy growth of 6.1%, driven by robust IGST mop-up and contributions from key states.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:11:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695685bf4342f77179f67022_1767278127657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI May Hit Pause on Harsher Options Trading Penalties: What This Means for Traders!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-May-Hit-Pause-on-Harsher-Options-Trading-Penalties-What-This-Means-for-Traders/695684414342f77179f668ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-May-Hit-Pause-on-Harsher-Options-Trading-Penalties-What-This-Means-for-Traders/695684414342f77179f668ce</guid><description>India's Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) is reportedly considering delaying the implementation of significantly increased penalties for order-to-trade ratio (OTR) violations in options trading. This potential deferral follows substantial feedback from market participants concerned about rising trading costs and potential liquidity reduction. SEBI is also exploring a shift to a premium-based OTR calculation method for options.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:11:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695684414342f77179f668cd_1767277700457.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki EXPLODES! December Sales Surge 22% - Investors REJOICE!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-EXPLODES-December-Sales-Surge-22percent-Investors-REJOICE/695681274342f77179f65a32</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-EXPLODES-December-Sales-Surge-22percent-Investors-REJOICE/695681274342f77179f65a32</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki India reported a significant 22.21% jump in total sales for December 2025, reaching 2,17,854 units compared to 1,78,248 units in December 2024. Domestic sales, including passenger vehicles, showed strong growth, with passenger vehicle sales alone rising to 1,78,646 units from 1,30,117 units year-on-year. However, exports saw a decline during the period.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:03:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695681274342f77179f65a31_1767276912761.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>South Indian Bank Surges: Q3 Sees Double-Digit Growth in Loans and Deposits!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/South-Indian-Bank-Surges-Q3-Sees-Double-Digit-Growth-in-Loans-and-Deposits/69567dce4342f77179f64934</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/South-Indian-Bank-Surges-Q3-Sees-Double-Digit-Growth-in-Loans-and-Deposits/69567dce4342f77179f64934</guid><description>South Indian Bank reported a strong December quarter with gross advances up 11.27% to ₹96,765 crore and total deposits rising 12.17% to ₹1.18 lakh crore as of December 31, 2025. CASA deposits grew significantly by 14.65%, improving the CASA ratio to 31.84%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:47:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69567dce4342f77179f64933_1767276072509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GST Breakthrough: India's Tax Revenue Stabilizes Post-Rate Cuts, Imports Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/GST-Breakthrough-Indias-Tax-Revenue-Stabilizes-Post-Rate-Cuts-Imports-Surge/69567dd84342f77179f64979</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/GST-Breakthrough-Indias-Tax-Revenue-Stabilizes-Post-Rate-Cuts-Imports-Surge/69567dd84342f77179f64979</guid><description>India's Goods and Services Tax (GST) collections in December 2025 show signs of stabilization after recent rate cuts, with gross collections rising 2.51% over November. Import-related IGST saw a significant 19.7% year-on-year jump, boosting overall revenue. However, a 31% surge in GST refunds impacted net collections, signaling a policy shift to ease business working capital. Cumulative revenue for April-December grew 8.6%, indicating underlying demand resilience despite lower effective rates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:47:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69567dd84342f77179f64978_1767276081850.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma's Big Move: Subsidiary Acquires Key Business from Khandelwal Labs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharmas-Big-Move-Subsidiary-Acquires-Key-Business-from-Khandelwal-Labs/69567dda4342f77179f649ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharmas-Big-Move-Subsidiary-Acquires-Key-Business-from-Khandelwal-Labs/69567dda4342f77179f649ac</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma's subsidiary, Auro Pharma Ltd, has acquired Khandelwal Laboratories' branded non-oncology prescription formulations business for ₹3,250 million. This strategic deal, effective January 1, 2026, adds 23 brands and significant infrastructure in anti-infective and pain management segments, aiming to bolster Auro Pharma's presence in the Indian market. The acquired business recorded ₹1,135.3 million turnover in FY24-25. Aurobindo Pharma shares closed higher on the news.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:47:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69567dda4342f77179f649ab_1767276126838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Surges: Expansion Fuels Massive Capacity Hike &amp; Analyst 'Buy' Call!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Steel-Surges-Expansion-Fuels-Massive-Capacity-Hike-and-Analyst-Buy-Call/69567b214342f77179f63c1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Steel-Surges-Expansion-Fuels-Massive-Capacity-Hike-and-Analyst-Buy-Call/69567b214342f77179f63c1a</guid><description>Jindal Steel is significantly expanding its Angul facility, nearly doubling hot metal capacity and increasing crude steelmaking capacity. The company is also focusing on backward integration, acquiring new mines, and developing captive resources. Analysts recommend a 'Buy' with an attractive valuation of 7x FY28 EBITDA and a target price of ₹1,123.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:36:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69567b214342f77179f63c19_1767275741277.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bata India's Bold Retail Makeover: 800 Stores by 2026 &amp; Massive Franchise Push!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bata-Indias-Bold-Retail-Makeover-800-Stores-by-2026-and-Massive-Franchise-Push/69567b1e4342f77179f63bdf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bata-Indias-Bold-Retail-Makeover-800-Stores-by-2026-and-Massive-Franchise-Push/69567b1e4342f77179f63bdf</guid><description>Bata India is aggressively expanding its Zero-Based Merchandising (ZBM) strategy, aiming for 800 stores by December 2026. The footwear giant also plans to double its franchise outlets to 1,400 in the next 2-3 years, focusing on urban centers for company-owned stores and smaller towns for franchise expansion. This comes despite a significant 73.72% year-on-year dip in net profit to ₹13.76 crore for Q2 fiscal, with revenue falling to ₹801.33 crore due to deferred purchases post-GST rationalization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:35:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69567b1e4342f77179f63bde_1767275489220.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Elon Musk's Self-Driving Dream vs. Reality: Tesla Sales Plummet Amidst Hype, Sparking Investor Fears!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Elon-Musks-Self-Driving-Dream-vs-Reality-Tesla-Sales-Plummet-Amidst-Hype-Sparking-Investor-Fears/695678e54342f77179f63235</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Elon-Musks-Self-Driving-Dream-vs-Reality-Tesla-Sales-Plummet-Amidst-Hype-Sparking-Investor-Fears/695678e54342f77179f63235</guid><description>Tesla's sales outlook is dimming, despite Elon Musk's strong promotion of autonomous vehicle technology. Analysts expect fourth-quarter deliveries to fall significantly year-over-year, with even more pessimistic internal estimates published by Tesla. Future delivery forecasts for 2026 have been drastically cut. Investors remain focused on long-term AI and robotics prospects, while actual car buyers and the competitive EV market present significant near-term challenges. The company faces regulatory scrutiny over its self-driving features and increased competition, particularly from BYD in China.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:29:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695678e54342f77179f63234_1767275218905.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks Stuck: Govt Freezes Small Savings Rates, Deposit Cuts Blocked!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Stuck-Govt-Freezes-Small-Savings-Rates-Deposit-Cuts-Blocked/695676b54342f77179f62784</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Stuck-Govt-Freezes-Small-Savings-Rates-Deposit-Cuts-Blocked/695676b54342f77179f62784</guid><description>Banks face significant challenges in lowering deposit interest rates as the government has decided to keep rates for a dozen small savings schemes, including PPF and Sukanya Samriddhi Yojana, unchanged for the January-March 2026 quarter. This decision, following eight consecutive quarters of static rates, limits banks' room to maneuver, especially amidst slowing deposit growth and increasing pressure on their net interest margins.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:15:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695676b54342f77179f62783_1767274253163.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MOIL Shocks Market! Manganese Ore Prices Jump 3% - Is Your Portfolio Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MOIL-Shocks-Market-Manganese-Ore-Prices-Jump-3percent-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/695675314342f77179f620bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MOIL-Shocks-Market-Manganese-Ore-Prices-Jump-3percent-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/695675314342f77179f620bf</guid><description>MOIL Limited has announced revised prices for manganese ore effective January 1, 2026. Key Ferro grades (Mn-44% and above) will see a 3% increase. Other grades like SMGR and Fines also experience hikes or reductions, while Chemical grades remain unchanged. The price of EMD has been reduced by ₹5,000 per metric tonne. These adjustments are routine business practices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:15:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695675314342f77179f620be_1767273840247.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MicroStrategy's Six-Month Losing Streak: Bitcoin Strategy Falters as Stock Plummets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MicroStrategys-Six-Month-Losing-Streak-Bitcoin-Strategy-Falters-as-Stock-Plummets/6956748c4342f77179f61d4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MicroStrategys-Six-Month-Losing-Streak-Bitcoin-Strategy-Falters-as-Stock-Plummets/6956748c4342f77179f61d4d</guid><description>MicroStrategy shares are in their first six-month losing streak since adopting Bitcoin as a treasury asset in August 2020. The stock has significantly underperformed both Bitcoin and the Nasdaq 100 index, breaking historical patterns of sharp rebounds following declines. This persistent sell-off suggests a deeper repricing rather than a temporary dip.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:11:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956748c4342f77179f61d4c_1767273753695.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Power vs Tata Power: Who Reigns Supreme in India's Energy Race? Key Factors Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-vs-Tata-Power-Who-Reigns-Supreme-in-Indias-Energy-Race-Key-Factors-Revealed/6956741e4342f77179f61adc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-vs-Tata-Power-Who-Reigns-Supreme-in-Indias-Energy-Race-Key-Factors-Revealed/6956741e4342f77179f61adc</guid><description>Adani Power and Tata Power, India's leading energy giants, are charting distinct growth paths. Adani Power, the largest private thermal producer, is expanding its capacity to 42 GW by 2032 via brownfield projects and long-term Power Purchase Agreements (PPAs), ensuring high revenue visibility. Tata Power, an integrated utility, is heavily investing in a decentralized, green future, aiming for Net Zero by 2045, with significant expansion in rooftop solar and clean energy projects. While Adani Power shows strong recent share gains and higher margins, Tata Power focuses on consecutive profit growth and consumer-facing services. Investors face a choice between Adani's stable, large-scale thermal generation and Tata's diversified, green-focused integrated model.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:05:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956741e4342f77179f61adb_1767273677406.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>January IPO Frenzy! 8 Big Issues Ready to Launch, Eyeing ₹25,000 Crore!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/January-IPO-Frenzy-8-Big-Issues-Ready-to-Launch-Eyeing-25000-Crore/695673884342f77179f6179a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/January-IPO-Frenzy-8-Big-Issues-Ready-to-Launch-Eyeing-25000-Crore/695673884342f77179f6179a</guid><description>India's IPO market is set for a bustling January with up to eight mainboard issues poised to launch, potentially raising over ₹25,000 crore. Companies across AI, renewables, defence, finance, and hospitality sectors are preparing their offerings, pending final regulatory approvals and market conditions. This influx signals strong investor interest in diverse growth sectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:05:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695673884342f77179f61799_1767273682506.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apollo Micro Systems Defence Arm Secures ₹150 Crore Contract, Shares Jump!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apollo-Micro-Systems-Defence-Arm-Secures-150-Crore-Contract-Shares-Jump/69566f3c4342f77179f603fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apollo-Micro-Systems-Defence-Arm-Secures-150-Crore-Contract-Shares-Jump/69566f3c4342f77179f603fc</guid><description>Apollo Micro Systems' defence subsidiary, Apollo Defence Industries Private Limited, has won a ₹150 crore contract for defence electronics from a private sector company. This news follows strong Q2 FY25-26 financial results, which showed a significant surge in revenue and net profit, bolstering the company's order book and driving its share price higher amidst increasing private participation in India's defence manufacturing sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:42:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69566f3c4342f77179f603fb_1767272317450.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Oil Chairman: Crude Prices Comfortably Low, Refining Power Offsets Marketing Woes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indian-Oil-Chairman-Crude-Prices-Comfortably-Low-Refining-Power-Offsets-Marketing-Woes/69566f244342f77179f6033f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indian-Oil-Chairman-Crude-Prices-Comfortably-Low-Refining-Power-Offsets-Marketing-Woes/69566f244342f77179f6033f</guid><description>Indian Oil Corporation Chairman Arvinder Singh Sahney stated that crude oil prices are comfortable, around $60 per barrel and expected to fall further, with no supply deficit. He highlighted that strong refining margins, particularly for diesel, are balancing weaker marketing margins. Sahney confirmed the FY26 capital expenditure of over ₹33,000 crore is on track, focusing on specialty chemicals and value-added products. LPG under-recoveries are also largely compensated through a buffer account mechanism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:42:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69566f244342f77179f6033e_1767272309936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's First! Time Technoplast Cracks HUGE PESO Approval for Revolutionary Composite Cylinders!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-First-Time-Technoplast-Cracks-HUGE-PESO-Approval-for-Revolutionary-Composite-Cylinders/69566e814342f77179f5ffde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-First-Time-Technoplast-Cracks-HUGE-PESO-Approval-for-Revolutionary-Composite-Cylinders/69566e814342f77179f5ffde</guid><description>Time Technoplast Limited has achieved a significant milestone by securing approval from the Petroleum and Explosives Safety Organisation (PESO) and TÜV Rheinland (India) to manufacture and supply high-pressure Type-3 composite cylinders. This makes the company the first in India to receive clearance for these 2-litre capacity cylinders across diverse gas applications, including hydrogen, oxygen, medical uses, and industrial gases. This development is set to enhance its advanced composite solutions portfolio and support the 'Make in India' initiative.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:42:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69566e814342f77179f5ffdd_1767272277115.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive Tax Relief: Akzo Nobel India's ₹177 Crore GST Demand Vanishes to ₹42 Lakh!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-Tax-Relief-Akzo-Nobel-Indias-177-Crore-GST-Demand-Vanishes-to-42-Lakh/69566e6b4342f77179f5ff6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-Tax-Relief-Akzo-Nobel-Indias-177-Crore-GST-Demand-Vanishes-to-42-Lakh/69566e6b4342f77179f5ff6b</guid><description>Akzo Nobel India has received a significant revision from the Karnataka GST Department regarding its financial year 2018-19 tax demand. Initially pegged at ₹176.65 crore, the demand, which included tax, interest, and penalty, has been drastically reduced to ₹41.56 lakh. This substantial reduction follows the company's response to a show-cause notice related to input tax credit disallowance. The company is currently responding to the revised order.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:42:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69566e6b4342f77179f5ff6a_1767272252300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Bank's Q3 FY26 Surge: Business Rockets 13.4%, Investor Confidence Soars!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Q3-FY26-Surge-Business-Rockets-134percent-Investor-Confidence-Soars/69566e394342f77179f5fe45</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indian-Banks-Q3-FY26-Surge-Business-Rockets-134percent-Investor-Confidence-Soars/69566e394342f77179f5fe45</guid><description>Indian Bank has reported a robust 13.4% year-on-year growth in its total business for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹14.30 lakh crore. Gross advances increased by 14.5% to ₹6.40 lakh crore, while total deposits grew by 12.5% to ₹7.90 lakh crore. Current account deposits saw a significant 19.4% jump. Despite these strong figures, the bank's shares closed marginally lower by 0.45% at ₹833.50 on the NSE on Thursday. The bank noted that these are provisional figures, subject to audit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:42:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69566e394342f77179f5fe44_1767272065079.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 638 Crore GST Hit! Vodafone Idea Vows Legal Fight Amidst Huge Govt Relief Package</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Rs-638-Crore-GST-Hit-Vodafone-Idea-Vows-Legal-Fight-Amidst-Huge-Govt-Relief-Package/69566ca74342f77179f5f6bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Rs-638-Crore-GST-Hit-Vodafone-Idea-Vows-Legal-Fight-Amidst-Huge-Govt-Relief-Package/69566ca74342f77179f5f6bf</guid><description>Vodafone Idea has received a significant Goods and Services Tax (GST) penalty order amounting to Rs 637.91 crore from the CGST, Ahmedabad South office. The company stated it disagrees with the order, which pertains to allegations of short payment of tax and excess input tax credit, and plans to take legal action. This comes as reports suggest the Union Cabinet has approved a substantial relief package including a five-year moratorium on adjusted gross revenue (AGR) dues, potentially freezing Rs 87,695 crore.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:35:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69566ca74342f77179f5f6be_1767271696124.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gas Giants Slash Prices! CNG &amp; Piped Cooking Gas Get Cheaper by ₹1 - Is Your Wallet Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Gas-Giants-Slash-Prices-CNG-and-Piped-Cooking-Gas-Get-Cheaper-by-1-Is-Your-Wallet-Ready/69566c6f4342f77179f5f5b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Gas-Giants-Slash-Prices-CNG-and-Piped-Cooking-Gas-Get-Cheaper-by-1-Is-Your-Wallet-Ready/69566c6f4342f77179f5f5b6</guid><description>GAIL Gas Limited has announced a ₹1 price reduction for Compressed Natural Gas (CNG) and Piped Natural Gas (PNG) across its operational areas. This move, effective today, follows the Petroleum and Natural Gas Regulatory Board's (PNGRB) recent rationalization of pipeline tariffs. The announcement comes as other major players like Indraprastha Gas Ltd and Think Gas have also implemented price cuts for household cooking gas and CNG, signaling a competitive trend in the city gas distribution sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69566c6f4342f77179f5f5b5_1767271600693.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unlocks Banks for NPS Pension Funds! Regulator Boosts Competition &amp; Investor Choices.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Unlocks-Banks-for-NPS-Pension-Funds-Regulator-Boosts-Competition-and-Investor-Choices/69566c074342f77179f5f37e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Unlocks-Banks-for-NPS-Pension-Funds-Regulator-Boosts-Competition-and-Investor-Choices/69566c074342f77179f5f37e</guid><description>India's pension regulator, PFRDA, has permitted banks to sponsor National Pension System (NPS) funds, aiming to significantly increase competition. Banks must meet specific financial and prudential criteria set by the Reserve Bank of India. This move is part of broader PFRDA reforms, which previously allowed NPS subscribers to invest in gold ETFs, Nifty 50, and AIFs, and will revise investment fees from April 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:32:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69566c074342f77179f5f37d_1767271503454.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways' Shocking 2025 Leap: Mega Freight Goals &amp; Futuristic Trains Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Shocking-2025-Leap-Mega-Freight-Goals-and-Futuristic-Trains-Revealed/69566c144342f77179f5f428</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Shocking-2025-Leap-Mega-Freight-Goals-and-Futuristic-Trains-Revealed/69566c144342f77179f5f428</guid><description>Indian Railways achieved a landmark year in 2025, significantly expanding its Vande Bharat and Amrit Bharat train networks, laying over 900 km of new track, and achieving 99% broad-gauge electrification. Major engineering projects connected new regions, but challenges persist with the Mumbai-Ahmedabad bullet train and safety concerns. The outlook for 2026 includes Vande Bharat Sleeper trains and ambitious freight targets by FY30, aiming for faster, safer, and smarter rail travel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:31:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69566c144342f77179f5f427_1767271683007.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Pru AMC Shuffles Top Fund Management: Sankaran Naren Out, New Teams Named!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/ICICI-Pru-AMC-Shuffles-Top-Fund-Management-Sankaran-Naren-Out-New-Teams-Named/69566bd14342f77179f5f234</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/ICICI-Pru-AMC-Shuffles-Top-Fund-Management-Sankaran-Naren-Out-New-Teams-Named/69566bd14342f77179f5f234</guid><description>ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company has removed its Chief Investment Officer, Sankaran Naren, from managing the Dynamic Asset Allocation Active Fund of Funds. Effective Thursday, the fund management team for this scheme has been revised, with Naren no longer involved. Additionally, the ICICI Prudential Business Cycle Fund's management team has been updated to include Divya Jain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:31:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69566bd14342f77179f5f233_1767271474840.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Surges! Market Share Skyrockets to 9.3% – Is This the EV Comeback You Waited For?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Surges-Market-Share-Skyrockets-to-93percent-Is-This-the-EV-Comeback-You-Waited-For/695666154342f77179f5d974</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Surges-Market-Share-Skyrockets-to-93percent-Is-This-the-EV-Comeback-You-Waited-For/695666154342f77179f5d974</guid><description>Ola Electric shares rose nearly 4% after reporting a significant month-on-month market share increase to 9.3% in December, up from 7.2% in November. Strong demand for its new S1 Pro+ scooter and government certification for its Roadster X+ motorcycle are key drivers. The company also anticipates scaling its battery energy storage systems business.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:05:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695666154342f77179f5d973_1767270022815.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>