<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:15:58 +0000</pubDate><item><title>TCS Dividend Alert! Record Date Jan 17 for Q3 Payout - Board Meeting on Jan 12</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Dividend-Alert-Record-Date-Jan-17-for-Q3-Payout-Board-Meeting-on-Jan-12/695146d34342f77179daf145</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Dividend-Alert-Record-Date-Jan-17-for-Q3-Payout-Board-Meeting-on-Jan-12/695146d34342f77179daf145</guid><description>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) announced a third interim dividend for the quarter ending December 31, 2025. The company's board will meet on January 12, 2026, to approve financial results. The record date to determine eligible shareholders for this dividend is set for January 17, 2026, though the exact dividend amount has not yet been disclosed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:56:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695146d34342f77179daf144_1766934564350.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGo's Grip Loosens: Market Share Drops Amidst Major Operational Chaos!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-Grip-Loosens-Market-Share-Drops-Amidst-Major-Operational-Chaos/695145764342f77179daef8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGos-Grip-Loosens-Market-Share-Drops-Amidst-Major-Operational-Chaos/695145764342f77179daef8f</guid><description>IndiGo, India's largest airline, saw its domestic market share decline to 63.6% in November from 65.6% in October due to operational disruptions and a 10% winter schedule cut ordered by the DGCA. Meanwhile, the Air India Group expanded its share to 26.7%, and SpiceJet increased its stake to 3.7%. Despite these shifts, overall passenger traffic continued to grow by 4.26% year-on-year, though flight-related customer complaints remained significant.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:49:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695145764342f77179daef8e_1766933965703.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Poised for Strength! Fed Minutes to Guide Next Big Move - Analysts Reveal Price Targets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Poised-for-Strength-Fed-Minutes-to-Guide-Next-Big-Move-Analysts-Reveal-Price-Targets/69513f554342f77179daea44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Poised-for-Strength-Fed-Minutes-to-Guide-Next-Big-Move-Analysts-Reveal-Price-Targets/69513f554342f77179daea44</guid><description>Gold and silver prices are expected to maintain their strength next week, with traders closely watching the US Federal Reserve's FOMC meeting minutes for monetary policy cues. Analysts foresee continued upward momentum in 2026, driven by anticipated global rate cuts, safe-haven demand, and robust industrial requirements, though the pace of gains may slow after an exceptional 2025. Specific price targets have been set for both gold and silver on MCX and international markets.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:23:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69513f554342f77179daea43_1766932391864.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mobile Retailer SS Retail Eyes Rs 500 Crore IPO: Are You Ready for the Next Big Tech Stock?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mobile-Retailer-SS-Retail-Eyes-Rs-500-Crore-IPO-Are-You-Ready-for-the-Next-Big-Tech-Stock/69513e984342f77179dae91d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Mobile-Retailer-SS-Retail-Eyes-Rs-500-Crore-IPO-Are-You-Ready-for-the-Next-Big-Tech-Stock/69513e984342f77179dae91d</guid><description>Mobile phone retailer SS Retail has filed draft papers with SEBI to raise ₹500 crore via an IPO. The issue includes ₹300 crore from fresh shares and ₹200 crore from existing shareholders via offer-for-sale. The company plans to use funds for new store setups and working capital. SS Retail reported a profit of nearly ₹40 crore for FY25.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:19:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69513e984342f77179dae91c_1766932325812.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Shatters Records: A Decade of Unstoppable Growth Ignites India's Market!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Shatters-Records-A-Decade-of-Unstoppable-Growth-Ignites-Indias-Market/69513d654342f77179dae75d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Shatters-Records-A-Decade-of-Unstoppable-Growth-Ignites-Indias-Market/69513d654342f77179dae75d</guid><description>India's Nifty 50 index is poised for its longest-ever winning streak, marking ten consecutive years of positive returns. Despite global headwinds, the Nifty has shown remarkable resilience, outperforming major international indices like the Dow Jones and Shanghai Composite. This sustained growth underscores strong investor confidence in India's robust economic outlook, vast skilled workforce, and supportive government policies, positioning the nation as a premier global investment destination.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:14:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69513d654342f77179dae75c_1766932024505.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Aviation Ministry Launches 24x7 Control Room to Tackle Passenger Grievances Promptly</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Aviation-Ministry-Launches-24x7-Control-Room-to-Tackle-Passenger-Grievances-Promptly/695136cf4342f77179dae048</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Aviation-Ministry-Launches-24x7-Control-Room-to-Tackle-Passenger-Grievances-Promptly/695136cf4342f77179dae048</guid><description>The Indian Civil Aviation Ministry has established a 24x7 Passenger Assistance Control Room (PACR) to swiftly resolve air traveller issues. Staffed by officials from the ministry, DGCA, airlines, and AAI, the center addresses concerns like flight cancellations, delays, and lost baggage. This initiative aims to improve grievance redressal, following recent disruptions, with over 13,000 cases already resolved.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:43:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695136cf4342f77179dae047_1766930327670.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI's 2025 Rulebook: From Creation to Execution! Kotak COO Reveals Major Shift Impacting Your Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-2025-Rulebook-From-Creation-to-Execution-Kotak-COO-Reveals-Major-Shift-Impacting-Your-Investments/69512df94342f77179dad834</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-2025-Rulebook-From-Creation-to-Execution-Kotak-COO-Reveals-Major-Shift-Impacting-Your-Investments/69512df94342f77179dad834</guid><description>In 2025, India's market regulator SEBI shifted its focus from creating new rules to enforcing existing ones, a change highlighted by Sandeep Chordia, COO of Kotak Securities. This transition means more execution and less new rule-making compared to 2024. Key implementations like T+0 settlement are anticipated in 2026, pending system readiness across exchanges, brokers, and custodians. Additionally, measures to curb excessive speculation in equity derivatives, such as adjusting lot sizes and limiting weekly expiries, have successfully reduced retail participation in these high-risk products.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:07:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69512df94342f77179dad833_1766927945095.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Satellite Internet Launch Stuck! Security &amp; Price Hurdles Block Starlink in India; VIL Relief Debate Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Satellite-Internet-Launch-Stuck-Security-and-Price-Hurdles-Block-Starlink-in-India-VIL-Relief-Debate-Intensifies/695127934342f77179dad22a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Satellite-Internet-Launch-Stuck-Security-and-Price-Hurdles-Block-Starlink-in-India-VIL-Relief-Debate-Intensifies/695127934342f77179dad22a</guid><description>India's ambitious satellite internet rollout faces delays as major players like Starlink must first comply with security agency demands regarding international gateways and data localization. Union Telecom Minister Jyotiraditya Scindia stated that spectrum allocation hinges on these clearances and the finalization of spectrum pricing by the Department of Telecom and Telecom Regulatory Authority of India. Meanwhile, discussions continue on potential relief measures for Vodafone Idea, which has substantial dues to the government.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:39:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695127934342f77179dad229_1766926440215.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Ignites EV Race: Deliveries Surge With In-House 'Bharat Cell' Battery!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Ignites-EV-Race-Deliveries-Surge-With-In-House-Bharat-Cell-Battery/6951276c4342f77179dad1da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ola-Electric-Ignites-EV-Race-Deliveries-Surge-With-In-House-Bharat-Cell-Battery/6951276c4342f77179dad1da</guid><description>Ola Electric is significantly increasing deliveries of its S1 Pro+ electric scooter, now powered by its in-house manufactured '4680 Bharat Cell' battery. Deliveries have begun in Tamil Nadu, Kerala, Telangana, and Karnataka, with plans for a nationwide rollout. This marks a major milestone for Ola Electric, establishing it as India's first company to fully own its cell and battery pack manufacturing process, bolstering its integrated EV ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:38:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951276c4342f77179dad1d9_1766926394129.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Poised for Satellite Internet: Security &amp; Spectrum Hurdles Near Resolution; Vodafone Idea Relief Update Underway!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Poised-for-Satellite-Internet-Security-and-Spectrum-Hurdles-Near-Resolution-Vodafone-Idea-Relief-Update-Underway/695126d14342f77179dad13e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Poised-for-Satellite-Internet-Security-and-Spectrum-Hurdles-Near-Resolution-Vodafone-Idea-Relief-Update-Underway/695126d14342f77179dad13e</guid><description>India is set to launch satellite communication services after players like Starlink meet security clearance demands and spectrum pricing is finalized by the Department of Telecom. Meanwhile, the government is actively reviewing relief measures for Vodafone Idea, which faces significant liabilities totaling around ₹2 lakh crore. The DoT is working on a solution to maintain four telecom operators in the robust Indian market.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:37:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695126d14342f77179dad13d_1766926137066.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's NCD Crisis: Experts Propose 'Micro-Hospitals' to Save Lives!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-NCD-Crisis-Experts-Propose-Micro-Hospitals-to-Save-Lives/6951260e4342f77179dad0ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-NCD-Crisis-Experts-Propose-Micro-Hospitals-to-Save-Lives/6951260e4342f77179dad0ac</guid><description>India faces a growing epidemic of non-communicable diseases (NCDs), which cause 63% of deaths. Healthcare experts are recommending the establishment of 'micro-hospitals'. These specialist-led facilities aim to provide coordinated, community-based care, reducing long wait times and fragmentation common in large hospitals. This model seeks to bridge the gap between primary care and tertiary hospitals, offering better diagnostics and treatments closer to home.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:36:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951260e4342f77179dad0ab_1766925905853.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 44,700 Cr Govt Mega-Plan Ignites India's Shipbuilding Future! Massive Boost for Capacity &amp; Jobs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rs-44700-Cr-Govt-Mega-Plan-Ignites-Indias-Shipbuilding-Future-Massive-Boost-for-Capacity-and-Jobs/6951245c4342f77179dace8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rs-44700-Cr-Govt-Mega-Plan-Ignites-Indias-Shipbuilding-Future-Massive-Boost-for-Capacity-and-Jobs/6951245c4342f77179dace8d</guid><description>India's government has launched two major shipbuilding schemes, the Shipbuilding Financial Assistance Scheme (SBFAS) and the Shipbuilding Development Scheme (SbDS), with a combined outlay of over ₹44,700 crore. These initiatives aim to revive the domestic shipbuilding industry, enhance global competitiveness, create long-term capacity, and foster job growth. SBFAS offers financial aid from 15-25%, while SbDS focuses on developing infrastructure, modernizing existing shipyards, and establishing an India Ship Technology Centre. The schemes are expected to support ₹96,000 crore in projects and significantly increase India's shipbuilding capacity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:28:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951245c4342f77179dace8c_1766925724133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Data Guardians Are Coming: New Board Setup Underway, Online Office Ready!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Data-Guardians-Are-Coming-New-Board-Setup-Underway-Online-Office-Ready/695118024342f77179dac5d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Data-Guardians-Are-Coming-New-Board-Setup-Underway-Online-Office-Ready/695118024342f77179dac5d2</guid><description>India's IT Secretary S Krishnan announced that groundwork has begun for appointing members to the new Data Protection Board. The software for its fully online office is developed. Consultations with industry stakeholders are ongoing to assess preparedness for the Digital Personal Data Protection Act (DPDP Act), with a priority on avoiding ecosystem disruption. The board will monitor compliance, inquire into breaches, and impose penalties.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:36:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695118024342f77179dac5d1_1766922545520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Unicorn Fractal's Massive ₹4,900 Cr IPO Nears: Book-Building Starts Next Week!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Unicorn-Fractals-Massive-4900-Cr-IPO-Nears-Book-Building-Starts-Next-Week/6951171f4342f77179dac4db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Unicorn-Fractals-Massive-4900-Cr-IPO-Nears-Book-Building-Starts-Next-Week/6951171f4342f77179dac4db</guid><description>Artificial intelligence leader Fractal Analytics is set to begin its ₹4,900 crore IPO book-building process next week. Having received regulatory approval, the company is nearing its market debut. Fractal is also considering a pre-IPO placement of up to ₹256 crore for institutional investors, which could adjust the final issue size. The company provides advanced analytics and AI solutions to global clients across finance, health, and retail.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:32:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951171f4342f77179dac4da_1766922202684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Financial Revolution: Embedded Finance Set to Explode!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Financial-Revolution-Embedded-Finance-Set-to-Explode/6951160d4342f77179dac359</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Financial-Revolution-Embedded-Finance-Set-to-Explode/6951160d4342f77179dac359</guid><description>India's financial sector is rapidly embracing Embedded Finance (EmFi), integrating financial services seamlessly into non-financial platforms. Fueled by massive mobile penetration and the UPI ecosystem, EmFi is projected to surge from around $6 billion to over $29 billion by 2030. While offering immense convenience and expanding market reach, EmFi faces challenges in data privacy, consumer protection, and regulatory compliance, requiring coordinated efforts for responsible growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:27:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951160d4342f77179dac358_1766921804475.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBFCs Bet Big on Trucks &amp; Tractors: India's 2026 Lending Revolution Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFCs-Bet-Big-on-Trucks-and-Tractors-Indias-2026-Lending-Revolution-Unveiled/695116284342f77179dac39a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NBFCs-Bet-Big-on-Trucks-and-Tractors-Indias-2026-Lending-Revolution-Unveiled/695116284342f77179dac39a</guid><description>Indian Non-Banking Financial Companies (NBFCs) are pivoting strategy for 2026, moving from fast unsecured digital loans to secured lending in the 'real economy.' The focus is shifting to asset-backed financing for trucks, tractors, and small businesses, especially in rural and semi-urban India, driven by an infrastructure boom and resilient consumption. While commercial vehicles show strength, construction equipment faces challenges. NBFCs emphasize collateral and ground-level cash flow understanding, aiming for responsible, sustainable growth rather than rapid unsecured expansion. The RBI's rate cut is expected to improve margins and repayment capacity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:27:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695116284342f77179dac399_1766921837317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sigachi Industries CEO Remanded: Factory Fire Probe Rocks Pharma Giant – Is Your Investment Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sigachi-Industries-CEO-Remanded-Factory-Fire-Probe-Rocks-Pharma-Giant-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/695111334342f77179dabf55</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sigachi-Industries-CEO-Remanded-Factory-Fire-Probe-Rocks-Pharma-Giant-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/695111334342f77179dabf55</guid><description>Sigachi Industries Limited announced its Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer, Amit Raj Sinha, has been remanded in connection with an ongoing investigation into a fire incident at its Hyderabad manufacturing unit on June 30, 2025. Deputy Group CEO Lijo Stephen Chacko will oversee operations on an interim basis to ensure business continuity. The company disclosed the development to stock exchanges as per SEBI regulations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:04:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695111334342f77179dabf54_1766920642201.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>East India Real Estate Surprise: Affordable Demand &amp; Mega Infra Projects Fuel Unstoppable Growth Into 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/East-India-Real-Estate-Surprise-Affordable-Demand-and-Mega-Infra-Projects-Fuel-Unstoppable-Growth-Into-2026/69510ed44342f77179dabc09</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/East-India-Real-Estate-Surprise-Affordable-Demand-and-Mega-Infra-Projects-Fuel-Unstoppable-Growth-Into-2026/69510ed44342f77179dabc09</guid><description>East India's real estate market defied expectations in 2025, prioritizing affordable housing and infrastructure development over premium price hikes. Kolkata led with significant launches and sales, while cities like Bhubaneswar, Guwahati, Patna, and Ranchi benefited from road, rail, and PMAY initiatives. This focus on connectivity and accessible pricing created steady demand, maintaining manageable inventory levels and setting a strong foundation for continued growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:54:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69510ed44342f77179dabc08_1766920392306.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Quality Control Orders: Fueling 'Make in India' Growth and Investment Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Quality-Control-Orders-Fueling-Make-in-India-Growth-and-Investment-Surge/69510f884342f77179dabd1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Quality-Control-Orders-Fueling-Make-in-India-Growth-and-Investment-Surge/69510f884342f77179dabd1a</guid><description>India is rapidly implementing Quality Control Orders (QCOs) to boost domestic manufacturing under the 'Make in India' initiative and enhance product quality. These orders, now exceeding 150, have attracted significant foreign investment and driven growth in sectors like air conditioners, footwear, steel, and toys, reshaping India's trade and manufacturing landscape by promoting local production and reducing reliance on imports.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:54:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69510f884342f77179dabd19_1766920202243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Takeover 2026: Indian IT Giants Set for Massive Revenue Boom &amp; Budget Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Takeover-2026-Indian-IT-Giants-Set-for-Massive-Revenue-Boom-and-Budget-Surge/69510e384342f77179dabb3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Takeover-2026-Indian-IT-Giants-Set-for-Massive-Revenue-Boom-and-Budget-Surge/69510e384342f77179dabb3b</guid><description>Artificial Intelligence is set to dominate the IT sector in 2026, with technology firms anticipating increased IT budgets and widespread AI project adoption. Indian IT leaders like TCS and HCL Technologies project nearly $2 billion in annual recurring revenue from advanced AI offerings. The focus is shifting towards practical, scaled AI solutions driving measurable business outcomes, significantly boosting demand for specialized AI talent.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:54:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69510e384342f77179dabb3a_1766919921860.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jefferies Boosts India, Taiwan Bets! Dumps China, Indonesia in Major Asia Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jefferies-Boosts-India-Taiwan-Bets-Dumps-China-Indonesia-in-Major-Asia-Shift/69510d244342f77179daba29</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jefferies-Boosts-India-Taiwan-Bets-Dumps-China-Indonesia-in-Major-Asia-Shift/69510d244342f77179daba29</guid><description>Global investment bank Jefferies has significantly reallocated its Asia Pacific ex-Japan portfolio, raising India and Taiwan's weightings by one percentage point each. This strategic move, funded by reductions in China and Indonesia exposure, reflects Jefferies' confidence in India's robust domestic demand, infrastructure growth, and improving corporate health, while concerns over China's economic recovery influence the trimming of its allocation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:47:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69510d244342f77179daba28_1766919538687.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Crystal Ball: Will 2026 Deliver Equity Riches or AI Bubble Burst? Investors Watch Closely!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AIs-Crystal-Ball-Will-2026-Deliver-Equity-Riches-or-AI-Bubble-Burst-Investors-Watch-Closely/695107884342f77179dab56c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AIs-Crystal-Ball-Will-2026-Deliver-Equity-Riches-or-AI-Bubble-Burst-Investors-Watch-Closely/695107884342f77179dab56c</guid><description>Global fund managers are shifting back to equities in 2026, moving away from gold and silver, with Artificial Intelligence (AI) expected to be a major driver. Despite past underperformance due to high valuations and weak earnings, India is anticipated to see an earnings recovery driven by interest rate cuts and tax reforms. However, investors must watch for AI bubble risks and compare India's 'growth play' valuation against China's 'value play'.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:25:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695107884342f77179dab56b_1766918100344.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Insurance FDI to 100%! But Who's Protecting You?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Boosts-Insurance-FDI-to-100percent-But-Whos-Protecting-You/695107934342f77179dab5a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Boosts-Insurance-FDI-to-100percent-But-Whos-Protecting-You/695107934342f77179dab5a3</guid><description>India's Parliament has passed the Sabka Bima Sabki Raksha (Amendment of Insurance Laws) Bill, 2025, significantly allowing 100% Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) in insurance companies and reducing capital requirements for reinsurers. While this aims to attract foreign capital and expertise, critics highlight the bill's lack of robust consumer protection measures. A proposed policyholder fund may offer limited relief, as core issues of mis-selling and opaque products persist, potentially prioritizing institutional gains over genuine customer welfare.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:25:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695107934342f77179dab5a2_1766918119370.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shocking Drop! Private Equity Flees Indian Real Estate, Investments Plummet 29%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Shocking-Drop-Private-Equity-Flees-Indian-Real-Estate-Investments-Plummet-29percent/695107124342f77179dab4ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Shocking-Drop-Private-Equity-Flees-Indian-Real-Estate-Investments-Plummet-29percent/695107124342f77179dab4ac</guid><description>Private equity investments in Indian real estate have plunged 29% this year to $3.46 billion, down from $4.9 billion last year. Knight Frank India reports a cautious investor sentiment, with significant drops in housing and warehousing funds, though office and retail sectors saw modest increases. The slowdown occurred despite improved macro-economic conditions, with experts citing cost of capital, exit visibility, and valuation alignment as key issues. An expected recovery to $4.4 billion in 2026 is projected to be selective.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:23:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695107124342f77179dab4ab_1766917983306.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Appliance Market Set for Global Domination! Rs 3 Lakh Crore Boom by 2029!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Appliance-Market-Set-for-Global-Domination-Rs-3-Lakh-Crore-Boom-by-2029/695107404342f77179dab4f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Appliance-Market-Set-for-Global-Domination-Rs-3-Lakh-Crore-Boom-by-2029/695107404342f77179dab4f9</guid><description>India's appliances and consumer electronics sector is projected to become the world's fourth-largest market by FY27, with revenues expected to reach ₹3 lakh crore by FY29, growing at an 11% CAGR. Key drivers include rising incomes, rural demand, easier consumer finance, and smart product innovation. Stricter energy efficiency norms from January 1, 2026, are prompting companies to invest in localization and AI, positioning India as a dynamic global player in consumer durables.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:22:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695107404342f77179dab4f8_1766918219655.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Exports Defy US Tariffs: Record Growth Set to Soar into 2026?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Exports-Defy-US-Tariffs-Record-Growth-Set-to-Soar-into-2026/695105bb4342f77179dab2dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Exports-Defy-US-Tariffs-Record-Growth-Set-to-Soar-into-2026/695105bb4342f77179dab2dd</guid><description>Indian exporters have shown remarkable resilience, navigating a significant 50% US tariff in 2025 by diversifying markets. Despite global headwinds like the pandemic and geopolitical conflicts, India's merchandise exports are projected to maintain strong momentum into 2026. Key drivers include new free trade agreements with the UK, Oman, and New Zealand, alongside government support measures like enhanced credit facilities. Electronics, engineering goods, and pharmaceuticals are leading the charge in this export surge.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:18:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695105bb4342f77179dab2dc_1766917750215.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBCC Unlocks Rs 8,500 Cr South Delhi Mega Project After Delhi Govt Land Dispute Resolved!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCC-Unlocks-Rs-8500-Cr-South-Delhi-Mega-Project-After-Delhi-Govt-Land-Dispute-Resolved/695100c64342f77179daaede</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCC-Unlocks-Rs-8500-Cr-South-Delhi-Mega-Project-After-Delhi-Govt-Land-Dispute-Resolved/695100c64342f77179daaede</guid><description>State-owned NBCC has settled a long-standing land dispute with the Delhi government, securing 21.23 acres in Ghitorni, South Delhi. The agreement resolves litigation over a 42.46-acre plot and allows for equal division of land. NBCC will pay Rs 220 crore for its share, which includes a premium, interest, and ground rent arrears. The company has development rights for a mixed-use project expected to generate approximately Rs 8,500 crore in revenue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695100c64342f77179daaedd_1766916368231.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Viceroy Hotels Leaps Forward! Shareholders Greenlight ₹206 Crore Hyderabad Hotel Buyout – What This Means for Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Viceroy-Hotels-Leaps-Forward-Shareholders-Greenlight-206-Crore-Hyderabad-Hotel-Buyout-What-This-Means-for-Growth/6951006b4342f77179daadf4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Viceroy-Hotels-Leaps-Forward-Shareholders-Greenlight-206-Crore-Hyderabad-Hotel-Buyout-What-This-Means-for-Growth/6951006b4342f77179daadf4</guid><description>Viceroy Hotels Limited shareholders have approved the acquisition of SLN Terminus Hotels and Resorts Private Limited for ₹206 crore in cash. The deal involves SLN Terminus, which operates a Marriott-associated long-stay hotel in Hyderabad's Gachibowli area. This acquisition is set to expand Viceroy's hospitality portfolio and strengthen its market presence.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951006b4342f77179daadf3_1766916281608.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Park Medi World Eyes Doubled Revenue: Agra Hospital Acquisition Poised for Explosive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Park-Medi-World-Eyes-Doubled-Revenue-Agra-Hospital-Acquisition-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/695100b24342f77179daae92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Park-Medi-World-Eyes-Doubled-Revenue-Agra-Hospital-Acquisition-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth/695100b24342f77179daae92</guid><description>Park Medi World expects its newly acquired 360-bed KP Institute of Medical Sciences hospital in Agra to nearly double its monthly revenue to ₹8-10 crore after taking over operations in mid-February. The company plans to launch multi-super-specialties to achieve this, targeting annual revenue of about ₹100 crore with 18-20% EBITDA margins. The ₹245-crore acquisition will be funded primarily through internal accruals.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:56:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695100b24342f77179daae91_1766916412588.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI &amp; Economy Freeze: Big Companies Slash 2026 Hiring Plans! Are Jobs Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-and-Economy-Freeze-Big-Companies-Slash-2026-Hiring-Plans-Are-Jobs-Next/6951001c4342f77179daad7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-and-Economy-Freeze-Big-Companies-Slash-2026-Hiring-Plans-Are-Jobs-Next/6951001c4342f77179daad7a</guid><description>Major companies are bracing for a lean 2026, prioritizing technology over new hires. Forecasters predict minimal job growth, with platforms like Shopify and Chime Financial aiming to keep employee numbers stable. A survey revealed 66% of CEOs plan to cut or maintain staff, reflecting economic unease and AI's growing role in automating tasks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:51:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951001c4342f77179daad79_1766916200058.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Food Delivery Boom: Swiggy &amp; Magicpin Reveal 2026 Growth Secrets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Food-Delivery-Boom-Swiggy-and-Magicpin-Reveal-2026-Growth-Secrets/6950ff034342f77179daabfd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Food-Delivery-Boom-Swiggy-and-Magicpin-Reveal-2026-Growth-Secrets/6950ff034342f77179daabfd</guid><description>India's food delivery market growth in 2026 will hinge on customer experience, speed, and value, according to Swiggy and magicpin. magicpin CEO Anshoo Sharma emphasized deeper merchant inclusion and catering to value-conscious users by lowering entry barriers. Swiggy CEO Rohit Kapoor highlighted adapting to evolving consumer needs for speed, balance, and reliability. The sector generated ₹1.2 lakh crore in 2023-24 and directly employs 1.37 million people.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:49:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950ff034342f77179daabfc_1766915946644.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Gear Up: Key Data, Foreign Flows &amp; Fed Cues to Dictate Week Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Gear-Up-Key-Data-Foreign-Flows-and-Fed-Cues-to-Dictate-Week-Ahead/6950fe3f4342f77179daaaf5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Gear-Up-Key-Data-Foreign-Flows-and-Fed-Cues-to-Dictate-Week-Ahead/6950fe3f4342f77179daaaf5</guid><description>Indian stock markets are poised for a pivotal week, with analysts expecting range-bound trading influenced by crucial domestic and global data releases. Key indicators include November's industrial production, PMI figures, and auto sales data. Global sentiment will hinge on US Federal Reserve meeting minutes and economic cues. Investors are also watching foreign fund activity and the implications of the December F&amp;O expiry amidst a transition into the new year.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:46:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950fe3f4342f77179daaaf4_1766915946585.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coinbase Predicts Crypto's 2026 Future: Three Pillars Will Dominate!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coinbase-Predicts-Cryptos-2026-Future-Three-Pillars-Will-Dominate/6950f0444342f77179da9eaa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coinbase-Predicts-Cryptos-2026-Future-Three-Pillars-Will-Dominate/6950f0444342f77179da9eaa</guid><description>Coinbase Institutional's 2026 outlook suggests crypto markets will shift from narrative momentum to activity concentration. Key areas expected to dominate include perpetual futures, evolving prediction markets, and stablecoins for real-world usage. The report emphasizes institutional participation, refined risk controls, and market plumbing over retail speculation for price formation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:46:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950f0444342f77179da9ea9_1766912225872.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Finance Ministry Mandates Urgent Vigilance Reporting for Bank Directors – Is Your Investment Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Finance-Ministry-Mandates-Urgent-Vigilance-Reporting-for-Bank-Directors-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/6950ef184342f77179da9d05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Finance-Ministry-Mandates-Urgent-Vigilance-Reporting-for-Bank-Directors-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/6950ef184342f77179da9d05</guid><description>India's Finance Ministry, via the Department of Financial Services, has ordered public sector banks and financial institutions to immediately report vigilance matters concerning their whole-time directors. This directive arises from past instances where crucial adverse information was delayed or omitted, potentially affecting appointment and promotion decisions. The move aims to enhance transparency and strengthen governance within these entities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950ef184342f77179da9d04_1766911839445.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's January 2026 Auto Blitz: 7 New Cars &amp; SUVs from Kia, Maruti, Renault, Tata &amp; More! Don't Miss the Upcoming Launch Spree!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-January-2026-Auto-Blitz-7-New-Cars-and-SUVs-from-Kia-Maruti-Renault-Tata-and-More-Dont-Miss-the-Upcoming-Launch-Spree/6950e7ff4342f77179da9573</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-January-2026-Auto-Blitz-7-New-Cars-and-SUVs-from-Kia-Maruti-Renault-Tata-and-More-Dont-Miss-the-Upcoming-Launch-Spree/6950e7ff4342f77179da9573</guid><description>India's auto market gears up for a busy January 2026 with seven new or updated vehicle launches from manufacturers including Kia, Mahindra, Maruti Suzuki, Renault, Tata, and MG. These upcoming models promise bolder designs, advanced technology, enhanced safety features, and diverse powertrain options across various segments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:08:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950e7ff4342f77179da9572_1766910109729.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Brace for Volatility: Key Data &amp; Global Cues to Dictate Week's Trading!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Brace-for-Volatility-Key-Data-and-Global-Cues-to-Dictate-Weeks-Trading/6950e1334342f77179da8df4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Brace-for-Volatility-Key-Data-and-Global-Cues-to-Dictate-Weeks-Trading/6950e1334342f77179da8df4</guid><description>Indian equity markets are expected to be range-bound with a constructive bias this week, influenced by upcoming macroeconomic data and global trends. Key domestic data points include November's industrial production (IIP) and final HSBC manufacturing PMI, alongside closely watched auto sales figures. Globally, investors will focus on US Federal Reserve's FOMC minutes and balance sheet updates, which could impact growth and liquidity expectations. The market anticipates volatility due to the December F&amp;O expiry and year-end trading sessions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 07:42:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950e1334342f77179da8df3_1766908392821.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supreme Court Intervenes: Aravalli Hills Definition Sparks Mining Fears!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Supreme-Court-Intervenes-Aravalli-Hills-Definition-Sparks-Mining-Fears/6950e06f4342f77179da8cd2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Supreme-Court-Intervenes-Aravalli-Hills-Definition-Sparks-Mining-Fears/6950e06f4342f77179da8cd2</guid><description>The Supreme Court of India has taken suo motu cognizance of a new definition for Aravalli hills across Gujarat, Rajasthan, Haryana, and Delhi. This definition, based on an elevation of 100 meters, could expose 50% of the hills, particularly in Rajasthan, and potentially allow mining of strategic and atomic minerals. The court will hear arguments on December 29 amid ecological concerns and protests against unregulated mining.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 07:37:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950e06f4342f77179da8cd1_1766908282966.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Rare Earth Export Twist: Auto Industry Relief Amidst Global Power Play!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Chinas-Rare-Earth-Export-Twist-Auto-Industry-Relief-Amidst-Global-Power-Play/6950df634342f77179da8bac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Chinas-Rare-Earth-Export-Twist-Auto-Industry-Relief-Amidst-Global-Power-Play/6950df634342f77179da8bac</guid><description>China has eased rare earth export curbs by issuing licenses to Indian auto component players, offering crucial relief for companies like Jay Ushin, and vendors for Maruti Suzuki and Mahindra. However, a strict 'civilian-use only' clause remains, blocking military applications. This move comes as India relies heavily on China (80-85%) for rare-earth permanent magnets, vital for the growing electric vehicle and renewable energy sectors. India's government is pushing indigenous manufacturing with a ₹7,280 crore scheme to meet 70-75% of domestic needs by 2030.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 07:32:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950df634342f77179da8bab_1766907841213.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani's Rs 1.8 Lakh Crore Defence Gamble: Is India's Future Warfare Now in Their Hands?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adanis-Rs-18-Lakh-Crore-Defence-Gamble-Is-Indias-Future-Warfare-Now-in-Their-Hands/6950d97d4342f77179da837c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adanis-Rs-18-Lakh-Crore-Defence-Gamble-Is-Indias-Future-Warfare-Now-in-Their-Hands/6950d97d4342f77179da837c</guid><description>Adani Group plans a massive ₹1.8 lakh crore investment in defence manufacturing next year, focusing on unmanned and autonomous systems, advanced guided weapons, and AI-enabled operations. This initiative aims to significantly boost India's indigenous military capabilities and strengthen the nation's self-reliance in defence technology.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 07:09:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950d97d4342f77179da837b_1766906471480.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's RRTS Revolution: Commuters Cheer, Investors Rush as Real Estate Booms Along Transit Corridors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-RRTS-Revolution-Commuters-Cheer-Investors-Rush-as-Real-Estate-Booms-Along-Transit-Corridors/6950d7bf4342f77179da8157</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-RRTS-Revolution-Commuters-Cheer-Investors-Rush-as-Real-Estate-Booms-Along-Transit-Corridors/6950d7bf4342f77179da8157</guid><description>A new Knight Frank India report reveals India's Regional Rapid Transit System (RRTS) is transforming urban mobility and driving significant real estate growth. Commuters express high satisfaction, with 80% seeing enhanced economic opportunities. Investor confidence is surging, with 66% of respondents keen to buy property along RRTS corridors. The Delhi-Ghaziabad-Meerut corridor exemplifies this trend, showcasing how integrated transport and development catalyze decentralized urban expansion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 07:01:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950d7bf4342f77179da8156_1766906152343.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>