<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:31:33 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Yes Bank Faces RBI Scrutiny Over Forex Card Breach, Past Lapses Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Bank-Faces-RBI-Scrutiny-Over-Forex-Card-Breach-Past-Lapses-Loom/699f5b1ccd95b9dc08f9399a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Bank-Faces-RBI-Scrutiny-Over-Forex-Card-Breach-Past-Lapses-Loom/699f5b1ccd95b9dc08f9399a</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has summoned senior Yes Bank officials following a substantial data breach concerning its multi-currency forex cards, where customer card details and CVV numbers were allegedly compromised. This incident intensifies regulatory oversight for Yes Bank, which has a history of cybersecurity lapses and associated penalties, raising concerns about operational integrity and investor confidence. The bank reported fraudulent transactions totaling ₹2.54 crore and blocked attempts worth ₹90 lakh, while BookMyForex denied system compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:27:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f5b1ccd95b9dc08f93999_1772051463393.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Consumer Firms Pivot: Agility Over Forecasting Amidst Global Chaos</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Consumer-Firms-Pivot-Agility-Over-Forecasting-Amidst-Global-Chaos/699f5416cd95b9dc08f936d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Consumer-Firms-Pivot-Agility-Over-Forecasting-Amidst-Global-Chaos/699f5416cd95b9dc08f936d3</guid><description>Consumer sector leaders are abandoning long-term forecasting due to a volatile mix of fluctuating currencies, supply chain disruptions, geopolitical tensions, and commodity price surges. Companies like Voltas are implementing price hikes, while others, such as Tata Consumer Products, are prioritizing operational agility and short-cycle planning to navigate an unpredictable economic environment. This strategic shift reflects a broader industry response to persistent uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:57:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f5416cd95b9dc08f936d2_1772049602208.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Escorts Kubota Loses Ground in India, Exports Surge Amid Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Loses-Ground-in-India-Exports-Surge-Amid-Fierce-Competition/699f5411cd95b9dc08f936bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Loses-Ground-in-India-Exports-Surge-Amid-Fierce-Competition/699f5411cd95b9dc08f936bc</guid><description>Escorts Kubota's domestic tractor market share has slipped to 10.8% in FY26, trailing the industry's overall growth and losing ground to competitors like Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, TAFE, and Sonalika. While exports show robust 54% growth, this has not offset domestic erosion. Management acknowledges challenges with the Kubota brand's limited portfolio and cost structure, and is focused on localization and product development to regain competitiveness, despite a generally positive outlook for the Indian agricultural sector and a 'Neutral' analyst consensus.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:57:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f5411cd95b9dc08f936bb_1772049715866.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Inc Revenue Jumps, Profit Growth Decelerates Amid Cost Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Inc-Revenue-Jumps-Profit-Growth-Decelerates-Amid-Cost-Pressures/699f51d1cd95b9dc08f9354b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Inc-Revenue-Jumps-Profit-Growth-Decelerates-Amid-Cost-Pressures/699f51d1cd95b9dc08f9354b</guid><description>Private listed non-financial companies in India posted 10.1% revenue growth in Q3 FY26, the fastest in 12 quarters, primarily propelled by the manufacturing sector's 11.4% surge. However, aggregate net profit growth slowed significantly to 5.2%, a sharp deceleration from 11.8% in the prior year, indicating that rising operational costs are eroding top-line gains. The IT sector, in particular, faces margin compression and stock market sell-offs due to AI disruption fears, contrasting with manufacturing's resilient output.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:47:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f51d1cd95b9dc08f9354a_1772049114489.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samsung's AI Gamble: S26 Series Targets Premium India Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Samsungs-AI-Gamble-S26-Series-Targets-Premium-India-Market/699f4dbccd95b9dc08f932c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Samsungs-AI-Gamble-S26-Series-Targets-Premium-India-Market/699f4dbccd95b9dc08f932c6</guid><description>Samsung has unveiled its Galaxy S26 smartphone series, heavily emphasizing proprietary AI features for intuitive user experiences. Manufactured in India, the S26 series aims to capture a larger share of the lucrative super-premium smartphone market, where it faces intense competition, particularly from Apple. The company is investing heavily in AI integration, planning to roll out these features across a vast number of devices globally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:30:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f4dbccd95b9dc08f932c5_1772048113590.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>E2E Networks Launches QIP, Fuels AI Infrastructure Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/E2E-Networks-Launches-QIP-Fuels-AI-Infrastructure-Drive/699f4ccfcd95b9dc08f931a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/E2E-Networks-Launches-QIP-Fuels-AI-Infrastructure-Drive/699f4ccfcd95b9dc08f931a9</guid><description>E2E Networks Ltd. has launched a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) with a floor price of ₹2,630.60 per share, signaling a strategic move to bolster its capital base for aggressive expansion in the AI cloud infrastructure domain. The company also clarified its collaboration with Nvidia, emphasizing an existing relationship rather than a new agreement. This capital raise occurs within a booming Indian data center and AI market, providing a robust tailwind for the company's growth ambitions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:26:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f4ccecd95b9dc08f931a8_1772047882441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Lifesciences Unveils Generic Semaglutide with Innovative Pen</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Unveils-Generic-Semaglutide-with-Innovative-Pen/699f48844579bb1d300c8c91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zydus-Lifesciences-Unveils-Generic-Semaglutide-with-Innovative-Pen/699f48844579bb1d300c8c91</guid><description>Zydus Lifesciences is set to launch its generic semaglutide injection, branded as Semaglyn, Mashema, and Altreme, following the upcoming patent expiry of the drug in India. A key differentiator is the company's exclusive right to an indigenously developed, reusable single-pen device, designed to simplify dosage titration and reduce overall patient cost. This move signals an aggressive entry into India's rapidly expanding diabetes and obesity treatment market, where global giants Eli Lilly and Novo Nordisk have already established significant sales. Analysts anticipate a price range of ₹4,000 to ₹5,000 per month, substantially lower than current offerings, poised to disrupt the competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:07:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/manual-news-1772047387682.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRDAI Mandate: Cost Cuts Crucial for India's Insurance Affordability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/IRDAI-Mandate-Cost-Cuts-Crucial-for-Indias-Insurance-Affordability/699f485b4579bb1d300c8c40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/IRDAI-Mandate-Cost-Cuts-Crucial-for-Indias-Insurance-Affordability/699f485b4579bb1d300c8c40</guid><description>The Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority of India (IRDAI) and the FY'26 Economic Survey have intensified scrutiny on the Indian insurance sector's escalating customer acquisition and management expenses. These costs are identified as structural impediments that suppress profitability and hinder product affordability, particularly for the crucial 'missing middle' demographic. The regulator's directive emphasizes an urgent pivot towards cost rationalization and operational efficiency to achieve ambitious goals for universal coverage by 2047 and bridge the significant protection gap.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:07:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/manual-news-1772047611705.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Banks Eye Digital Bank Guarantees Amidst Slow Adoption</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Eye-Digital-Bank-Guarantees-Amidst-Slow-Adoption/699f483c4579bb1d300c8c0f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Eye-Digital-Bank-Guarantees-Amidst-Slow-Adoption/699f483c4579bb1d300c8c0f</guid><description>Indian public sector banks are investigating a centralized portal for paper-based bank guarantees, seeking to curb fraud amid a persistent low adoption rate of digital issuance, which stands at only 20%. This move comes as regulators and the judiciary strongly advocate for a complete shift to electronic bank guarantees (e-BGs), leveraging existing platforms like National E-Governance Services Ltd. (NeSL) to enhance security and efficiency.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:06:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/manual-news-1772048068668.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's PSUs Launch Shipping JV: Capital Strain or Strategic Gain?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-PSUs-Launch-Shipping-JV-Capital-Strain-or-Strategic-Gain/699f47aa4579bb1d300c8b3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-PSUs-Launch-Shipping-JV-Capital-Strain-or-Strategic-Gain/699f47aa4579bb1d300c8b3f</guid><description>Indian Oil, BPCL, and HPCL are partnering with the Shipping Corporation of India (SCI) to establish a dedicated maritime freighting joint venture, allocating ₹15,000-17,000 crore for 59 vessels. This strategic move aims to curb India's substantial annual ₹6 lakh crore expenditure on foreign vessel charters and bolster energy security. While intended to 'onshore' critical logistics, the venture raises questions about execution risks and capital allocation for state-owned enterprises already engaged in massive investment cycles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/manual-news-1772048376569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IIFL Finance Raises $750M Amid Easing RBI Lending Rules</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Finance-Raises-750M-Amid-Easing-RBI-Lending-Rules/699f47a64579bb1d300c8b25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Finance-Raises-750M-Amid-Easing-RBI-Lending-Rules/699f47a64579bb1d300c8b25</guid><description>IIFL Finance is launching a $500-750 million funding drive via ECBs and dollar bonds in March to diversify its resource base and fuel growth. This strategic move aligns with the Reserve Bank of India's recent relaxation of external borrowing limits, which have been raised to $1 billion. The company aims to reduce reliance on banks and bolster its capital structure. This initiative follows recent domestic bond issuances and signals a multi-pronged approach to securing long-term funding.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:04:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/manual-news-1772048699413.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Loans Surge Past Personal Loans in India's Retail Credit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Loans-Surge-Past-Personal-Loans-in-Indias-Retail-Credit/699f3f12bf318914c0a51c93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Loans-Surge-Past-Personal-Loans-in-Indias-Retail-Credit/699f3f12bf318914c0a51c93</guid><description>Gold loans have ascended to become India's second-largest retail credit segment, surpassing personal loans with a ₹16.2 trillion portfolio in Q3FY26, trailing only housing loans. This dramatic shift is fueled by rising gold prices, increased demand for secured credit amid economic uncertainty, and the formalization of lending channels. While gold loans offer quicker disbursal and often lower interest rates than unsecured personal loans, evolving RBI regulations are reshaping the market dynamics for both borrowers and lenders.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BlockFills CEO Exits as Lender Halts Withdrawals Amid $75M Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/BlockFills-CEO-Exits-as-Lender-Halts-Withdrawals-Amid-75M-Loss/699f3d3abf318914c0a5135d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/BlockFills-CEO-Exits-as-Lender-Halts-Withdrawals-Amid-75M-Loss/699f3d3abf318914c0a5135d</guid><description>Crypto lender BlockFills is experiencing significant disruption as CEO Nicholas Hammer departs. The firm reported approximately $75 million in losses and has suspended all client deposits and withdrawals, a move implemented on February 11, 2026. This liquidity crunch echoes past crises in the crypto lending sector, prompting questions about BlockFills' operational stability and future prospects amidst a challenging market environment. The firm stated management is working with investors to restore liquidity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:19:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NCR Mega-Corridor Approved: ₹15K Cr RRTS Set to Reshape Region</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NCR-Mega-Corridor-Approved-15K-Cr-RRTS-Set-to-Reshape-Region/699f3cb4bf318914c0a51051</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NCR-Mega-Corridor-Approved-15K-Cr-RRTS-Set-to-Reshape-Region/699f3cb4bf318914c0a51051</guid><description>Haryana's government has greenlit the final alignment for the ₹15,000 crore Gurugram-Faridabad-Noida-Greater Noida Namo Bharat RRTS-cum-Metro Corridor. Spanning approximately 61 kilometers, this ambitious project, driven by the National Capital Region Transport Corporation (NCRTC), aims to drastically enhance connectivity between key economic hubs. The corridor is poised to unlock significant real estate potential and foster polycentric regional development, reflecting a broader push in India's infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:17:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Spectrum Auction: TRAI Slashes Prices, Lowers Entry Barriers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Spectrum-Auction-TRAI-Slashes-Prices-Lowers-Entry-Barriers/699f3cacbf318914c0a5100e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Spectrum-Auction-TRAI-Slashes-Prices-Lowers-Entry-Barriers/699f3cacbf318914c0a5100e</guid><description>The Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI) has recommended auctioning the entire available 11,790 MHz of spectrum, valued at Rs 2.1 lakh crore, at prices 19% lower than 2022. Entry barriers for new players are halved, aiming to boost competition and expedite 5G deployment. This move comes amidst high sector debt and evolving market dynamics, with major players Jio and Airtel consolidating market share against a financially strained Vodafone Idea.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ED Seizes Rs 598 Cr Land Amid APIL's Financial Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/ED-Seizes-Rs-598-Cr-Land-Amid-APILs-Financial-Crisis/699f3ca6bf318914c0a50ff7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/ED-Seizes-Rs-598-Cr-Land-Amid-APILs-Financial-Crisis/699f3ca6bf318914c0a50ff7</guid><description>The Enforcement Directorate has provisionally attached land valued at Rs 598 crore in Agra as part of a money laundering investigation into Ansal Properties and Infrastructure Ltd (APIL). This action stems from alleged "large-scale" irregularities in Gurugram land acquisition and subsequent fraudulent release to private colonizers. The attachment occurs as APIL grapples with severe financial distress, including unprofitability, a negative P/E ratio, and ongoing corporate insolvency proceedings. The move highlights persistent regulatory scrutiny and historical allegations of impropriety within the company's operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Themis Medicare Seeks Shareholder Nod for ₹430 Cr RPTs, ₹46 Cr Warrant Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Themis-Medicare-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-430-Cr-RPTs-46-Cr-Warrant-Issue/699f3c9ebf318914c0a50f9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Themis-Medicare-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-430-Cr-RPTs-46-Cr-Warrant-Issue/699f3c9ebf318914c0a50f9c</guid><description>Themis Medicare Limited is seeking shareholder approval via postal ballot for material related party transactions (RPTs) amounting to ₹430 crore and the issuance of convertible warrants worth ₹45.96 crore. The transactions aim to streamline operations and ensure supply chain continuity for pharmaceutical intermediates, while the warrants will fund working capital and general corporate needs. E-voting is scheduled from February 26 to March 27, 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's EV Export Push Faces Global Price Wars &amp; Tech Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Export-Push-Faces-Global-Price-Wars-and-Tech-Gap/699f3bbcbf318914c0a50aa5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-EV-Export-Push-Faces-Global-Price-Wars-and-Tech-Gap/699f3bbcbf318914c0a50aa5</guid><description>India's automotive sector shows robust domestic growth and market momentum, with the Nifty Auto index nearing all-time highs. A new FICCI-Yes Bank report emphasizes a critical need for a national electric vehicle (EV) export strategy to leverage global sales tripling by 2030. However, significant challenges loom, including intense competition from China, achieving cost parity, and aligning with stringent international standards. While component exports are rising, a growing trade deficit and high valuations for some domestic players present considerable risks to India's ambition of becoming a global EV manufacturing hub.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Insurers Face Regulatory Squeeze on Costs and Affordability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurers-Face-Regulatory-Squeeze-on-Costs-and-Affordability/699f3a4ebf318914c0a501ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurers-Face-Regulatory-Squeeze-on-Costs-and-Affordability/699f3a4ebf318914c0a501ea</guid><description>The Indian insurance sector faces a stern regulatory push from the IRDAI to curtail escalating customer acquisition and management expenses. This initiative, echoed by the Economic Survey for FY'26, aims to bolster profitability and crucially, enhance product affordability. The directives target a persistent structural constraint that has limited insurance penetration and widened the gap between policy coverage depth and breadth, especially for the 'missing middle' demographic. Insurers are urged to embrace digital transformation and rationalize costs to achieve a sustainable growth path and improve customer value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HSBC India Surges 11% to $1.9B PBT, Bolstering Asian Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HSBC-India-Surges-11percent-to-19B-PBT-Bolstering-Asian-Dominance/699f3a4bbf318914c0a5018f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HSBC-India-Surges-11percent-to-19B-PBT-Bolstering-Asian-Dominance/699f3a4bbf318914c0a5018f</guid><description>HSBC India posted an 11% surge in profit before tax to USD 1.9 billion for the 2025 fiscal year, driven significantly by its corporate and institutional banking segment. This performance solidifies India's role as the second-highest profit contributor in Asia for the group, following Hong Kong. The bank also launched new digital initiatives and expanded its physical presence in key wealth-focused cities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:07:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DFS Eyes NBFC Banking Path: Governance, Digital Security Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/DFS-Eyes-NBFC-Banking-Path-Governance-Digital-Security-Key/699f3789bf318914c0a4ed9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/DFS-Eyes-NBFC-Banking-Path-Governance-Digital-Security-Key/699f3789bf318914c0a4ed9e</guid><description>India's Department of Financial Services (DFS) is meeting with non-banking financial companies (NBFCs) to discuss their potential transition into full-fledged banks. The agenda prioritizes significant governance reforms, including leadership rotation, and enhancing digital payment security through AI and cybersecurity measures. This initiative revives discussions from a 2020 RBI working group, aiming to harmonize NBFC operations with banking standards and strengthen systemic oversight, particularly for large, upper-layer NBFCs, as new banking licenses remain deferred.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tether Bets $200M on Creator Economy, Eyes Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tether-Bets-200M-on-Creator-Economy-Eyes-Global-Expansion/699f3704bf318914c0a4e8e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tether-Bets-200M-on-Creator-Economy-Eyes-Global-Expansion/699f3704bf318914c0a4e8e8</guid><description>Tether has invested $200 million in online marketplace Whop, valuing the startup at $1.6 billion. This strategic infusion aims to bolster stablecoin payments and integrate Tether's crypto wallet into Whop's platform, empowering its 18.4 million users. The deal supports Whop's global expansion and the integration of decentralized finance tools, marking Tether's deeper push into consumer-facing commerce.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Growth Engine: Fiscal Strength, Reforms, and Maritime Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Growth-Engine-Fiscal-Strength-Reforms-and-Maritime-Ambition/699f363104a25a58c858ae00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Growth-Engine-Fiscal-Strength-Reforms-and-Maritime-Ambition/699f363104a25a58c858ae00</guid><description>Economic Advisor Sanjeev Sanyal attributes India's sustained 7-7.5% growth and macroeconomic stability to fiscal conservatism and key structural reforms, notably the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code (IBC). Addressing significant East-West economic disparities, he advocates for West Bengal to capitalize on its maritime potential through port development. This strategic focus aims to bolster India's resilience against global economic turbulence and advance its 'Vikshit Bharat' vision.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Markets: DIIs Shield Against FPI Swings; IPOs Face Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-DIIs-Shield-Against-FPI-Swings-IPOs-Face-Scrutiny/699f35a804a25a58c858a8dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-DIIs-Shield-Against-FPI-Swings-IPOs-Face-Scrutiny/699f35a804a25a58c858a8dd</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey highlighted the evolving market structure. Foreign portfolio investors' equity assets under custody surged to ₹71 lakh crore, yet they were net sellers of ₹1.65 lakh crore in 2025. This outflow was significantly absorbed by Domestic Institutional Investors, who invested ₹7.88 lakh crore, bolstering market resilience. India's IPO market remains robust, raising ₹1.8 lakh crore in FY26, signaling issuer confidence, but this growth is juxtaposed against tighter global liquidity and increasing regulatory focus on market efficiency and technological adoption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity SIP Dip Signals Strategic Investor Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Equity-SIP-Dip-Signals-Strategic-Investor-Shift/699f318e04a25a58c85873f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Equity-SIP-Dip-Signals-Strategic-Investor-Shift/699f318e04a25a58c85873f3</guid><description>Active equity SIP inflows saw a rare dip in January, registering ₹25,091 crore, a ₹240 crore decrease from December. This decline, occurring amidst market volatility rather than a crash, signals a strategic reallocation by investors. Hybrid funds and ETFs/FoFs, particularly those focused on gold and silver, are witnessing a surge in inflows, driven by demand for diversification and safe-haven assets. While equity SIPs moderated, overall SIP contributions remained robust, indicating continued investor discipline.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bitcoin ETF Options Reshape Volatility, Mirroring Equity Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Bitcoin-ETF-Options-Reshape-Volatility-Mirroring-Equity-Market-Dynamics/699f310204a25a58c8586b7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Bitcoin-ETF-Options-Reshape-Volatility-Mirroring-Equity-Market-Dynamics/699f310204a25a58c8586b7f</guid><description>The proliferation of options trading for spot Bitcoin ETFs like IBIT marks a structural shift, transferring volatility drivers from offshore crypto venues to regulated U.S. equity options markets. This integration is strengthening Bitcoin's correlation with major indices and subjecting it to traditional derivative hedging mechanics, complicating its 'digital gold' narrative and increasing its susceptibility to broader market movements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW's Jindal: Short-Term Pressures Hamper R&amp;D, Eyes China Model</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/JSWs-Jindal-Short-Term-Pressures-Hamper-RandD-Eyes-China-Model/699f30ed04a25a58c8586a8a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/JSWs-Jindal-Short-Term-Pressures-Hamper-RandD-Eyes-China-Model/699f30ed04a25a58c8586a8a</guid><description>JSW Group Chairman Sajjan Jindal expressed concerns about insufficient funds for R&amp;D due to quarterly financial demands, contrasting with benchmarks like Uday Kotak's 10% revenue investment goal. He advocated learning from China's cost-effective expansion, viewing AI as a productivity tool, not a disruptor. Jindal also called for protectionist measures for Indian industries and confirmed JSW's entry into the auto market with a car launch before Diwali. This underscores the challenges capital-intensive industries face balancing immediate financial targets with long-term strategic investments and competitive global positioning.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PM Kisan e-KYC Drive: Digital ID Push Targets Fiscal Control</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/PM-Kisan-e-KYC-Drive-Digital-ID-Push-Targets-Fiscal-Control/699f2fa304a25a58c85855ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/PM-Kisan-e-KYC-Drive-Digital-ID-Push-Targets-Fiscal-Control/699f2fa304a25a58c85855ec</guid><description>The Pradhan Mantri Kisan Samman Nidhi (PM-KISAN) scheme is undergoing a rigorous e-KYC and Farmer ID verification push, signaling a strategic government effort to enhance data integrity and fiscal control in agricultural subsidies. This initiative, part of the broader AgriStack digital infrastructure, aims to eliminate ineligible beneficiaries and streamline direct benefit transfers, moving beyond simple welfare distribution towards a data-driven governance model.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RVNL Secures ₹371 Cr NMDC Township Project in Chhattisgarh</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RVNL-Secures-371-Cr-NMDC-Township-Project-in-Chhattisgarh/699f2f9204a25a58c85854b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RVNL-Secures-371-Cr-NMDC-Township-Project-in-Chhattisgarh/699f2f9204a25a58c85854b4</guid><description>Rail Vikas Nigam Limited (RVNL) has received a Letter of Acceptance (LOA) from National Mineral Development Corporation (NMDC) for the development of a township in Kirandul, Chhattisgarh. The project is valued at ₹371.69 crore and is slated for completion within 21 months. This win signifies RVNL's capability in broader infrastructure development beyond its core railway focus.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cytiva's India Hub Fuels Bioeconomy Ambition, Reshapes APAC Pharma</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Cytivas-India-Hub-Fuels-Bioeconomy-Ambition-Reshapes-APAC-Pharma/699f2f0c04a25a58c8584ca9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Cytivas-India-Hub-Fuels-Bioeconomy-Ambition-Reshapes-APAC-Pharma/699f2f0c04a25a58c8584ca9</guid><description>Cytiva has inaugurated a significant 30,000 sq ft facility in Bengaluru, India, designed to accelerate biopharmaceutical development and manufacturing. This expansion directly supports India's national objective to expand its bioeconomy to $300 billion by 2030. The center's advanced single-use bioreactor capabilities aim to shorten development timelines, mitigate manufacturing risks, and enhance scalability for companies across the Asia-Pacific region. This move positions Cytiva as a key enabler of India's growing stature as a global biomanufacturing hub.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sansera Engineering Incorporates JV Subsidiary with Japan's Nichidai Corp</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sansera-Engineering-Incorporates-JV-Subsidiary-with-Japans-Nichidai-Corp/699f2f0b04a25a58c8584c60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sansera-Engineering-Incorporates-JV-Subsidiary-with-Japans-Nichidai-Corp/699f2f0b04a25a58c8584c60</guid><description>Sansera Engineering Limited has officially incorporated Nichidai Sansera Private Limited, a wholly-owned subsidiary, marking the formalization of its joint venture with Japan's Nichidai Corporation. This strategic move, completed on February 25, 2026, establishes a 60:40 shareholding structure and is poised to expand Sansera's product portfolio into advanced automotive components.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Health X Platform Subsidiary Sells 4.68% Stake for ₹500 Cr; Mitsubishi Exits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Health-X-Platform-Subsidiary-Sells-468percent-Stake-for-500-Cr-Mitsubishi-Exits/699f2cb404a25a58c85825e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Health-X-Platform-Subsidiary-Sells-468percent-Stake-for-500-Cr-Mitsubishi-Exits/699f2cb404a25a58c85825e9</guid><description>Health X Platform Limited's material subsidiary, Sastasundar Healthbuddy Limited (SHBL), has executed a Share Purchase Agreement to sell 4.68% of its capital to Envision India Fund for approximately ₹500 crore. Mitsubishi Corporation, the seller, will exit its shareholding in SHBL upon completion of this transaction, signalling a shift in the company's investor base within the digital healthcare sector. Envision India Fund's entry marks a new phase for the subsidiary.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IDfy Secures $53M for Global RegTech Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IDfy-Secures-53M-for-Global-RegTech-Consolidation/699f255804a25a58c8572016</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IDfy-Secures-53M-for-Global-RegTech-Consolidation/699f255804a25a58c8572016</guid><description>Mumbai-based IDfy has secured ₹476 crore ($53 million) in Series F funding, led by Neo Asset Management. The capital injection, which values the company at $272 million post-money, will spearhead aggressive international expansion, strategic acquisitions, and technology enhancements. This move positions IDfy to capitalize on growing global fraud and evolving data privacy regulations, aiming for a "conservative global consolidator" role in the fragmented RegTech sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Charts Unique Growth: Tech, Trade, &amp; Self-Reliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Charts-Unique-Growth-Tech-Trade-and-Self-Reliance/699f24c304a25a58c857150b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Charts-Unique-Growth-Tech-Trade-and-Self-Reliance/699f24c304a25a58c857150b</guid><description>Union Minister Piyush Goyal has charted India's unique growth trajectory, emphasizing democratic values and human engagement over emulating China's development model. The strategy pivots on technology, particularly AI, poised for a revolution, and trade openness via nine new Free Trade Agreements. This aims to bolster Indian firms globally and ensure resilient supply chains for self-reliance. However, challenges loom, including escalating cybersecurity threats from AI adoption, a widening trade deficit, and the complex balance between open trade and domestic industry support. India's market, represented by the Nifty 50 (P/E 22.2), shows steady performance, reflecting optimism, but pragmatic hurdles remain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanofi India's Q4 Surge Masks Stock Underperformance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sanofi-Indias-Q4-Surge-Masks-Stock-Underperformance/699f228604a25a58c856900e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sanofi-Indias-Q4-Surge-Masks-Stock-Underperformance/699f228604a25a58c856900e</guid><description>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India delivered a robust Q4, with net sales jumping 47% to ₹251 crore and net profit soaring 50.1% to ₹67 crore. Despite this operational strength, evidenced by a 44.6% rise in EBITDA, the company's stock (SANOFICONR) has underperformed significantly, trading near its 52-week low and commanding a premium P/E ratio above the industry average. This disconnect highlights market skepticism regarding growth sustainability and future margin pressures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Profit Squeeze: Costs Bite Despite Sales Boom in Indian Firms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Profit-Squeeze-Costs-Bite-Despite-Sales-Boom-in-Indian-Firms/699f228104a25a58c8568fae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Profit-Squeeze-Costs-Bite-Despite-Sales-Boom-in-Indian-Firms/699f228104a25a58c8568fae</guid><description>Private non-financial firms in India saw net profit growth decelerate to 5.2% in the December 2025 quarter, a sharp drop from 11.8% a year earlier. This occurred despite a significant acceleration in sales growth to 10.1%, the first double-digit performance in eleven quarters. The manufacturing sector spearheaded this sales improvement, driven by automobiles and metals. However, escalating raw material and staff costs are compressing margins across sectors, impacting overall profitability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Crypto Rebounds as Shorts Unwind Amidst AI Equity Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Crypto-Rebounds-as-Shorts-Unwind-Amidst-AI-Equity-Surge/699f1dd404a25a58c855da80</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Crypto-Rebounds-as-Shorts-Unwind-Amidst-AI-Equity-Surge/699f1dd404a25a58c855da80</guid><description>The cryptocurrency market experienced a significant rebound as heavily bearish sentiment began to unwind, leading to liquidations of leveraged short positions and a broader relief rally. Bitcoin surpassed $65,000, with major altcoins like Ethereum and Solana posting double-digit gains. Crypto equities also surged, propelled by AI-related themes and the positive turn in the Coinbase Premium Index, signaling renewed U.S. institutional participation. Despite the uptick, extreme market fear persists, and underlying risks remain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:05:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699f1dd404a25a58c855da7f_1772036197801.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSB Surge: Profit Boom Masks Future Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSB-Surge-Profit-Boom-Masks-Future-Challenges/699f1c7104a25a58c855798c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSB-Surge-Profit-Boom-Masks-Future-Challenges/699f1c7104a25a58c855798c</guid><description>Public Sector Banks (PSBs) have achieved a landmark aggregate profit, projected to exceed ₹2 lakh crore, driven by robust loan growth of 14-15% and a significant reduction in NPAs. Despite outperforming private peers, PSBs face pressure to adopt technology, secure future capital, and address competitive threats to sustain their resurgence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bosch, Sarvam Forge 'Sovereign AI' Pact for India &amp; Global Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bosch-Sarvam-Forge-Sovereign-AI-Pact-for-India-and-Global-Markets/699f1c0204a25a58c8556271</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bosch-Sarvam-Forge-Sovereign-AI-Pact-for-India-and-Global-Markets/699f1c0204a25a58c8556271</guid><description>Bosch Global Software Technologies (BGSW) has partnered with Sarvam AI, a startup focused on Indian language models, to co-develop and deploy enterprise-grade AI solutions. This strategic alliance leverages Sarvam's 'sovereign AI' capabilities for India's diverse linguistic needs and BGSW's robust engineering, security platforms like AIShield, and deployment expertise. The collaboration aims to transition AI from experimentation to production-ready systems for automotive, medical devices, and wearables, serving both domestic and international markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CAIL: India Lagging Industry Growth, Europe Faces Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CAIL-India-Lagging-Industry-Growth-Europe-Faces-Headwinds/699f1bdc04a25a58c8556252</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CAIL-India-Lagging-Industry-Growth-Europe-Faces-Headwinds/699f1bdc04a25a58c8556252</guid><description>CIE Automotive (CAIL) reported Q4CY25 revenue of ₹2,390 crore, meeting expectations, with adjusted EBITDA margins at 15.4%. While Europe saw a 21% revenue jump to ₹780 crore, this benefited from a low base and favorable exchange rates. Crucially, India's revenue grew 12% to ₹1,540 crore, significantly trailing the industry's ~20% growth. Management anticipates strong India business expansion but expects European demand weakness to persist, prompting a strategic relocation of production facilities from Europe to India. The company maintains an 'Add' rating with a revised target price of ₹520.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>