<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:08:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>VA Tech Wabag Surges as Saudi Arabia Awards Massive Repeat Water Treatment Contract!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VA-Tech-Wabag-Surges-as-Saudi-Arabia-Awards-Massive-Repeat-Water-Treatment-Contract/6951fdd64342f77179dbea1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VA-Tech-Wabag-Surges-as-Saudi-Arabia-Awards-Massive-Repeat-Water-Treatment-Contract/6951fdd64342f77179dbea1e</guid><description>VA Tech Wabag Ltd. shares climbed after announcing a significant repeat order from the Saudi Water Authority. The EPC contract is for an advanced brackish water reverse osmosis (BWRO) plant with a capacity of 50 million liters per day in Aljouf, Saudi Arabia. Orders in the $30 million to $75 million range are classified as 'large' by the company. The project involves design, supply, and commissioning over 14 months, showcasing VA Tech Wabag's expertise in specialized water treatment technologies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:57:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951fdd64342f77179dbea1d_1766981148565.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Investing Revolution: SIPs &amp; Tech Make Markets Accessible to All!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Indian-Investing-Revolution-SIPs-and-Tech-Make-Markets-Accessible-to-All/6951fdd64342f77179dbe9f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Indian-Investing-Revolution-SIPs-and-Tech-Make-Markets-Accessible-to-All/6951fdd64342f77179dbe9f0</guid><description>Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) are transforming Indian retail investing, moving it beyond traditional deposits and gold. Technology, mobile platforms, and UPI payments have made investing as simple as online shopping, bringing markets closer to the masses. HSBC Mutual Fund CEO Kailash Kulkarni notes future innovations will expand SIP offerings to include thematic, ESG, and customized goal-based products, further deepening market participation and stability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:57:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951fdd64342f77179dbe9ef_1766981158209.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock Tax Savings: Adjust Share/Derivative Losses Against Mutual Fund Gains in FY26!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Tax-Savings-Adjust-ShareDerivative-Losses-Against-Mutual-Fund-Gains-in-FY26/6951fd2d4342f77179dbe8a4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Tax-Savings-Adjust-ShareDerivative-Losses-Against-Mutual-Fund-Gains-in-FY26/6951fd2d4342f77179dbe8a4</guid><description>Indian investors can adjust losses from selling shares or derivatives against capital gains from mutual funds in the financial year 2025-26. According to income tax rules, while speculative losses are restricted, losses from derivative transactions, treated as non-speculative business income, can be set off against capital gains (short-term or long-term). Similarly, share transaction losses can be adjusted against capital gains, depending on their classification. This advice helps optimize tax liabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:52:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951fd2d4342f77179dbe8a3_1766980990573.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Bond Market Shift: Goldilocks Era Ends, Investors Brace for New 'Accrual &amp; Carry' Strategy in 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Bond-Market-Shift-Goldilocks-Era-Ends-Investors-Brace-for-New-Accrual-and-Carry-Strategy-in-2026/6951fc634342f77179dbe730</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Bond-Market-Shift-Goldilocks-Era-Ends-Investors-Brace-for-New-Accrual-and-Carry-Strategy-in-2026/6951fc634342f77179dbe730</guid><description>India enjoyed a 'Goldilocks' economic year in 2025 with low inflation and high growth, prompting the RBI to cut rates. However, 2026 may see monetary policy tightening, signaling the end of the rate-cut cycle. Fixed income investors should transition from a rate-cut strategy to an 'accrual &amp; carry' approach, focusing on generating income rather than capital gains from falling rates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:52:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951fc634342f77179dbe72f_1766980814817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Market Supremacy Fading? Tech's Reign and Debt Woes Spark Investor Alarm – The Shocking Truth Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Market-Supremacy-Fading-Techs-Reign-and-Debt-Woes-Spark-Investor-Alarm-The-Shocking-Truth-Revealed/6951fcda4342f77179dbe821</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Market-Supremacy-Fading-Techs-Reign-and-Debt-Woes-Spark-Investor-Alarm-The-Shocking-Truth-Revealed/6951fcda4342f77179dbe821</guid><description>The United States has dominated global markets since 2008, driven by its strong technology sector and stable institutions. However, recent events like a 'triple red' market signal potential instability. Rising US debt levels, with interest payments exceeding defense spending, and concerns over institutional resilience pose risks. Despite these challenges, investors continue to pour capital into the U.S., largely due to the exceptional returns offered by its technology giants, seeking growth amidst a world of limited alternatives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:52:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951fcda4342f77179dbe820_1766981022545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Analysts Reveal Top 2 Stocks to Buy This Week: Midwest &amp; Ambuja Cement Surge Potential!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Analysts-Reveal-Top-2-Stocks-to-Buy-This-Week-Midwest-and-Ambuja-Cement-Surge-Potential/6951f9b14342f77179dbe47f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Analysts-Reveal-Top-2-Stocks-to-Buy-This-Week-Midwest-and-Ambuja-Cement-Surge-Potential/6951f9b14342f77179dbe47f</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services Ltd has identified Midwest and Ambuja Cement as top stock picks for the week commencing December 29, 2025. Midwest, a leading Black Galaxy granite exporter, is poised for growth through diversification into high-purity quartz and heavy mineral sands. Ambuja Cement is set to expand its footprint and improve profitability through the acquisition of Jaiprakash Associates' cement assets and significant cost reduction initiatives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:40:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f9b14342f77179dbe47e_1766980077932.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Rupee Teeters Near 90! Bonds Brace for Quarter-End Storm - Are You Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Rupee-Teeters-Near-90-Bonds-Brace-for-Quarter-End-Storm-Are-You-Ready/6951f7994342f77179dbe1a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Rupee-Teeters-Near-90-Bonds-Brace-for-Quarter-End-Storm-Are-You-Ready/6951f7994342f77179dbe1a7</guid><description>The Indian rupee is under pressure, facing potential headwinds from maturing non-deliverable forward (NDF) positions, with traders expecting it could slip past 90 per dollar again. Persistent corporate hedging and significant foreign portfolio outflows, tracking record redemptions from local stocks, are weighing on the currency despite Reserve Bank of India (RBI) interventions. Meanwhile, bond traders are closely watching demand-supply dynamics and foreign investor activity, with the 10-year benchmark yield influenced by RBI's bond purchase program and ongoing selling by foreign investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:24:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f7994342f77179dbe1a6_1766979550389.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Investment Bets: Are PSU Banks &amp; IT Your Next Goldmine? Defence Stocks Sky-High!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-Investment-Bets-Are-PSU-Banks-and-IT-Your-Next-Goldmine-Defence-Stocks-Sky-High/6951f7044342f77179dbe016</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-Investment-Bets-Are-PSU-Banks-and-IT-Your-Next-Goldmine-Defence-Stocks-Sky-High/6951f7044342f77179dbe016</guid><description>As 2025 concludes with strong market gains, analysts are strategizing for 2026. They identify PSU banks, IT, and financials as 'undervalued' sectors ripe for entry, citing valuations below historical averages. Conversely, defence, healthcare, and consumer discretionary stocks are flagged as 'overvalued' and potentially overheated after significant rallies this year. Energy and engineering sectors also present future opportunities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:24:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f7044342f77179dbe015_1766979408861.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹1,100 Crore Highway Win: Ceigall India's Shares Set to Soar!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-1100-Crore-Highway-Win-Ceigall-Indias-Shares-Set-to-Soar/6951f6184342f77179dbdf05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-1100-Crore-Highway-Win-Ceigall-Indias-Shares-Set-to-Soar/6951f6184342f77179dbdf05</guid><description>Ceigall India has secured a significant Letter of Award (LoA) from the Madhya Pradesh government for a highway project valued at ₹1,089 crore. Awarded to its subsidiary Ceigall Infra Projects Pvt. Ltd., the project involves constructing the 'Indore Ujjain Greenfield' highway, spanning 48.10 kilometers on a Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM). This win boosts Ceigall India's robust order book, which now stands at ₹14,237 crore, having already surpassed its fiscal year 2026 order inflow target.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:22:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f6184342f77179dbdf04_1766979218817.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Auto Sector Roars in December: Four-Wheelers Lead Surge, Two-Wheelers Still Finding Footing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Sector-Roars-in-December-Four-Wheelers-Lead-Surge-Two-Wheelers-Still-Finding-Footing/6951f6094342f77179dbdeda</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Auto-Sector-Roars-in-December-Four-Wheelers-Lead-Surge-Two-Wheelers-Still-Finding-Footing/6951f6094342f77179dbdeda</guid><description>Domestic auto demand showed resilience in December 2025, with overall registrations rising 9% year-on-year. Passenger vehicles and commercial vehicles spearheaded this growth with robust double-digit increases, alongside a remarkable surge in three-wheelers. However, the two-wheeler segment experienced only modest growth, indicating a gradual recovery in rural and mass-market demand. The divergence between four-wheeler strength and two-wheeler lag was a key feature of the month's performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:22:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f6094342f77179dbded9_1766979191558.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Brace: Bank of Japan Signals Aggressive Rate Hikes as Real Rate Plummets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Brace-Bank-of-Japan-Signals-Aggressive-Rate-Hikes-as-Real-Rate-Plummets/6951f5ca4342f77179dbdd3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Brace-Bank-of-Japan-Signals-Aggressive-Rate-Hikes-as-Real-Rate-Plummets/6951f5ca4342f77179dbdd3e</guid><description>Bank of Japan officials indicated potential further interest rate hikes due to Japan's real interest rate being the lowest globally. The benchmark rate was recently raised to 0.75%, a 30-year high. Discussions also covered adjusting monetary accommodation and managing currency fluctuations, with markets anticipating the next policy move.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:22:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f5ca4342f77179dbdd3d_1766979142257.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian-Origin CEO Jayshree Ullal Now Richer Than Satya Nadella &amp; Sundar Pichai!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-Origin-CEO-Jayshree-Ullal-Now-Richer-Than-Satya-Nadella-and-Sundar-Pichai/6951f56e4342f77179dbdc29</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-Origin-CEO-Jayshree-Ullal-Now-Richer-Than-Satya-Nadella-and-Sundar-Pichai/6951f56e4342f77179dbdc29</guid><description>Jayshree Ullal, the British-born Indian-origin CEO of Arista Networks, has been named the wealthiest Indian-origin executive globally by the Hurun India Rich List 2025. Surpassing Google's Sundar Pichai and Microsoft's Satya Nadella, Ullal's net worth stands at $5.7 billion, primarily driven by her stake in Arista Networks, a key player in cloud networking and AI infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:19:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f56e4342f77179dbdc28_1766979067485.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Payment Future: Monetization, Control, and the Fate of Crypto by 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Digital-Payment-Future-Monetization-Control-and-the-Fate-of-Crypto-by-2026/6951f4ed4342f77179dbdac6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Digital-Payment-Future-Monetization-Control-and-the-Fate-of-Crypto-by-2026/6951f4ed4342f77179dbdac6</guid><description>India's digital payments landscape is set for major shifts by 2026. While UPI remains the backbone, expect 'calibrated charges' for monetization as banks' patience wears thin. The Reserve Bank of India's Digital Rupee (CBDC) will quietly solve infrastructure issues and offer government control, not compete with UPI. Cryptocurrencies will remain regulated as assets, not currency. This evolution moves digital payments from convenience to state-controlled infrastructure, determining who truly manages India's money flow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f4ed4342f77179dbdac5_1766978970526.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock 2026: Your Essential Year-End Portfolio Rebalance Guide for Maximum Wealth Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-2026-Your-Essential-Year-End-Portfolio-Rebalance-Guide-for-Maximum-Wealth-Growth/6951f5114342f77179dbdb26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-2026-Your-Essential-Year-End-Portfolio-Rebalance-Guide-for-Maximum-Wealth-Growth/6951f5114342f77179dbdb26</guid><description>As 2025 concludes, investors should strategically rebalance their portfolios for a robust 2026. Key actions include reviewing asset allocations, reassessing risk appetite, rotating from momentum to quality investments, utilizing debt funds for potential interest rate cuts, strengthening global diversification, and prioritizing tax efficiency through measures like tax-loss harvesting. A disciplined approach ensures alignment with long-term goals and preparation for market stability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951f5114342f77179dbdb25_1766979064399.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Stocks EXPLODE! ₹80,000 Cr Deal Frenzy Looms as Defence Acquisition Council Gears Up for Mega Meet!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stocks-EXPLODE-80000-Cr-Deal-Frenzy-Looms-as-Defence-Acquisition-Council-Gears-Up-for-Mega-Meet/6951ee2e4342f77179dbd4a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stocks-EXPLODE-80000-Cr-Deal-Frenzy-Looms-as-Defence-Acquisition-Council-Gears-Up-for-Mega-Meet/6951ee2e4342f77179dbd4a6</guid><description>Defence stocks including Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd, Bharat Dynamics Ltd, and Bharat Electronics Ltd are in focus ahead of a crucial Defence Acquisition Council meeting. The council is expected to consider proposals worth ₹80,000 crore for acquiring weapon systems. This comes after the approval of Defence Procurement Manual 2025, aimed at boosting domestic manufacturing and private industry participation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:48:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ee2e4342f77179dbd4a5_1766977143079.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹80,000 Crore Defence Deal on the Brink! India's Military Set for Unprecedented Upgrade?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Massive-80000-Crore-Defence-Deal-on-the-Brink-Indias-Military-Set-for-Unprecedented-Upgrade/6951ed854342f77179dbd35e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Massive-80000-Crore-Defence-Deal-on-the-Brink-Indias-Military-Set-for-Unprecedented-Upgrade/6951ed854342f77179dbd35e</guid><description>The Defence Acquisition Council (DAC), chaired by Defence Minister Rajnath Singh, is likely to convene today, December 29, to consider approving defense procurement proposals valued at approximately ₹80,000 crore. Key items on the agenda include advanced Airborne Early Warning and Control (AEW&amp;C) systems, potentially boosting India's military modernization and significantly strengthening indigenous defense manufacturing capabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ed854342f77179dbd35d_1766977004586.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CAG Exposes Massive RLDA Failures: Billions Lost in Railway Land Development!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/CAG-Exposes-Massive-RLDA-Failures-Billions-Lost-in-Railway-Land-Development/6951ee034342f77179dbd44b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/CAG-Exposes-Massive-RLDA-Failures-Billions-Lost-in-Railway-Land-Development/6951ee034342f77179dbd44b</guid><description>A Comptroller and Auditor General (CAG) report has severely criticized the Rail Land Development Authority (RLDA) for significant delays, poor execution, and massive revenue losses in developing railway land. Between 2018-19 and 2022-23, despite managing nearly 998 hectares, not a single commercial site was fully developed. Financial performance was dismal, with RLDA earning only 10.14% of projected earnings from 2017-2022. The audit also found undervaluation of sites by ₹287.76 crore and poor consultant management, raising serious questions about governance and accountability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:47:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ee034342f77179dbd44a_1766977168601.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Avantel Rockets! Defence Ministry Awards ₹4.16 Crore Satcom Contract, Igniting Investor Excitement!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Avantel-Rockets-Defence-Ministry-Awards-416-Crore-Satcom-Contract-Igniting-Investor-Excitement/6951ed674342f77179dbd32c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Avantel-Rockets-Defence-Ministry-Awards-416-Crore-Satcom-Contract-Igniting-Investor-Excitement/6951ed674342f77179dbd32c</guid><description>Avantel Limited shares are in focus after securing a ₹4.16 crore contract from the Ministry of Defence for the Comprehensive Annual Maintenance Contract (CAMC) of satcom equipment. This follows recent significant orders from CRIS worth ₹13.82 crore and Bharat Electronics totaling over ₹25 crore, underscoring the company's growing order book and strategic importance in the defence and communication sectors. The company's market capitalization stands at ₹4,243.49 crore.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:42:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ed674342f77179dbd32b_1766976986681.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Power Demand Plummets in 2025: Will 2026 Bring Revival?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Demand-Plummets-in-2025-Will-2026-Bring-Revival/6951ecb54342f77179dbd227</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Demand-Plummets-in-2025-Will-2026-Bring-Revival/6951ecb54342f77179dbd227</guid><description>Electricity demand in India saw a sharp slowdown in 2025, declining in April-November despite economic growth. This impacted power producers' earnings and thermal plant utilization. Factors include prolonged monsoons, reduced air conditioner usage, and subdued industrial production. Analysts anticipate a recovery in demand from 2026, contingent on normal weather conditions. Investors should monitor key data for early signs of rebound.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:42:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ecb54342f77179dbd226_1766976801643.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget Bombshell: Massive Duty Hikes Planned to Slash China Imports? HUGE Boost for Local Makers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Bombshell-Massive-Duty-Hikes-Planned-to-Slash-China-Imports-HUGE-Boost-for-Local-Makers/6951ec6a4342f77179dbd195</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Bombshell-Massive-Duty-Hikes-Planned-to-Slash-China-Imports-HUGE-Boost-for-Local-Makers/6951ec6a4342f77179dbd195</guid><description>India's government is planning significant policy changes, potentially announced in the upcoming Union Budget, to curb its merchandise trade deficit and reduce reliance on China. Measures being considered include higher customs duties on around 100 products and targeted incentives for domestic manufacturing. This aims to de-risk supply chains, especially for goods like engineering products, steel, and machinery, where import dependence is high. Challenges like lower quality and higher prices of local goods persist, but the government is pushing to strengthen domestic sourcing amid a widening trade gap.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:42:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ec6a4342f77179dbd194_1766976775780.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive EPC Wins Ignite 5 Stocks! Are These Your Next Big Multibaggers?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-EPC-Wins-Ignite-5-Stocks-Are-These-Your-Next-Big-Multibaggers/6951ebfd4342f77179dbd03b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-EPC-Wins-Ignite-5-Stocks-Are-These-Your-Next-Big-Multibaggers/6951ebfd4342f77179dbd03b</guid><description>Several Indian companies are making headlines due to significant Engineering, Procurement, and Construction (EPC) order wins. Dilip Buildcon secured a Rs 3,400 crore road project in Bihar from Adani Road Transport Limited. Solarworld Energy Solutions received a Rs 725.33 crore order for a solar power project. JD Cables won a Rs 8.81 crore order for cables in Bihar &amp; Jharkhand. Diamond Power Infrastructure gained a Rs 66.18 crore order for power cables. Ceigall India's subsidiary received a provisional certificate for a Rs 27.40 km highway project, marking its operational readiness. These wins place these companies in focus for investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:36:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ebfd4342f77179dbd03a_1766976715332.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IOB Eyes Massive ₹4,000 Crore Funding: Government Stake Set for Significant Dilution!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IOB-Eyes-Massive-4000-Crore-Funding-Government-Stake-Set-for-Significant-Dilution/6951eb094342f77179dbcecb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IOB-Eyes-Massive-4000-Crore-Funding-Government-Stake-Set-for-Significant-Dilution/6951eb094342f77179dbcecb</guid><description>Indian Overseas Bank (IOB) is planning to raise ₹4,000 crore through a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) in the fourth quarter of fiscal year 2026. This substantial fundraising move is expected to further reduce the Indian government's shareholding in the state-owned lender by an estimated 3% to 3.5%, potentially marking its largest QIP in a decade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951eb094342f77179dbceca_1766976394095.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver SMASH Equities: 25-Year Returns Reveal Shocking Winner!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-SMASH-Equities-25-Year-Returns-Reveal-Shocking-Winner/6951ea5d4342f77179dbcd6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-SMASH-Equities-25-Year-Returns-Reveal-Shocking-Winner/6951ea5d4342f77179dbcd6a</guid><description>Gold and silver have significantly outperformed Indian equities like the NSE Nifty and BSE Sensex over the past 25 years. Gold delivered a compounded annual growth rate (CAGR) of 14.3%, while silver achieved 14.1%. In comparison, Nifty and Sensex offered returns of 11.7% and 11.5%, respectively. This trend, driven by jewelry demand, store of value, ETFs, and supportive global factors, suggests precious metals could continue their strong performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:32:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ea5d4342f77179dbcd69_1766976186424.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Inc. Scrambles for Clarity: New Labour Codes Trigger Confusion and Cost Worries!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Inc-Scrambles-for-Clarity-New-Labour-Codes-Trigger-Confusion-and-Cost-Worries/6951ea164342f77179dbcccb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Inc-Scrambles-for-Clarity-New-Labour-Codes-Trigger-Confusion-and-Cost-Worries/6951ea164342f77179dbcccb</guid><description>Indian businesses are seeking urgent clarifications from the government on the new labour codes. Key concerns include the effective date for wage definitions, where wages must constitute 50% of remuneration, and the retrospective implementation of rules impacting gratuity and leave encashment. The Institute of Chartered Accountants of India has advised companies to account for increased liabilities from the current quarter, adding to the pressure for clear guidance on operational aspects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:32:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951ea164342f77179dbccca_1766976178681.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Digit Insurance's Bold Move: First-Ever Holding Co Merger Unlocks Simpler Business, What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Digit-Insurances-Bold-Move-First-Ever-Holding-Co-Merger-Unlocks-Simpler-Business-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6951e9ff4342f77179dbcc6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Digit-Insurances-Bold-Move-First-Ever-Holding-Co-Merger-Unlocks-Simpler-Business-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/6951e9ff4342f77179dbcc6d</guid><description>Go Digit General Insurance's board has approved a landmark scheme to merge its unlisted holding company, Go Digit Infoworks Services, with the listed insurer. This marks the first such transaction in India following amendments to insurance laws. The move aims to eliminate the holding company layer, directly aligning shareholders with the insurance business, reducing compliance and administrative costs, and aligning with regulatory intent for leaner structures. Shareholders of the holding company will receive equity shares of the insurer without cash consideration, based on a valuation report.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:32:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e9ff4342f77179dbcc6c_1766976078069.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Warburg Pincus Poised for Massive Exit: IndiaFirst Life Insurance Stake Sale Could Fetch Over ₹10,000 Crore Amidst Regulatory Boost!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Warburg-Pincus-Poised-for-Massive-Exit-IndiaFirst-Life-Insurance-Stake-Sale-Could-Fetch-Over-10000-Crore-Amidst-Regulatory-Boost/6951e9594342f77179dbcb3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Warburg-Pincus-Poised-for-Massive-Exit-IndiaFirst-Life-Insurance-Stake-Sale-Could-Fetch-Over-10000-Crore-Amidst-Regulatory-Boost/6951e9594342f77179dbcb3a</guid><description>Private equity giant Warburg Pincus is reportedly in talks to sell its 26% stake in IndiaFirst Life Insurance, a transaction that could value the insurer at over ₹10,000 crore. This potential sale is significantly influenced by recent changes in Indian insurance laws, which now permit 100% foreign direct investment. Several global strategic investors and private equity funds are showing interest and conducting due diligence. Bank of Baroda remains the anchor shareholder in IndiaFirst Life.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:30:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e9594342f77179dbcb39_1766975936510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Rockets Past $80 Then Crashes! Global Stocks Near Record Highs - What You Must Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Silver-Rockets-Past-80-Then-Crashes-Global-Stocks-Near-Record-Highs-What-You-Must-Know/6951e9184342f77179dbcade</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Silver-Rockets-Past-80-Then-Crashes-Global-Stocks-Near-Record-Highs-What-You-Must-Know/6951e9184342f77179dbcade</guid><description>Global stocks are near record highs as silver surged dramatically to over $80 an ounce before falling sharply, fueled by industrial demand and tight inventories. Analysts warn of a potential "generational bubble." Gold and platinum also hit records. AI trends and Federal Reserve policy remain key factors for 2026 market outlook, with attention turning to the upcoming FOMC minutes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:28:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e9184342f77179dbcadd_1766975946473.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Small-Cap Meltdown: India's Worst Year in 7! Is it Time to Buy the Dip?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Small-Cap-Meltdown-Indias-Worst-Year-in-7-Is-it-Time-to-Buy-the-Dip/6951e6da4342f77179dbb099</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Small-Cap-Meltdown-Indias-Worst-Year-in-7-Is-it-Time-to-Buy-the-Dip/6951e6da4342f77179dbb099</guid><description>India's small-cap index is set for its worst performance in seven years in CY25, slipping 7% while larger indices like Nifty 50 and Sensex posted gains. This comes after significant rallies in 2023-24, leading to rich valuations and concerns over earnings. Analysts suggest the current dip may present an attractive buying opportunity for select quality small-cap stocks in early 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:14:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e6da4342f77179dbb098_1766975461776.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Analyst's Top Stock Picks: Buy TARC, Karur Vysya Bank, APL Apollo for Huge Gains? Discover Targets &amp; Strategy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Analysts-Top-Stock-Picks-Buy-TARC-Karur-Vysya-Bank-APL-Apollo-for-Huge-Gains-Discover-Targets-and-Strategy/6951e6bf4342f77179dbb051</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Analysts-Top-Stock-Picks-Buy-TARC-Karur-Vysya-Bank-APL-Apollo-for-Huge-Gains-Discover-Targets-and-Strategy/6951e6bf4342f77179dbb051</guid><description>Choice Equity Broking analyst Aakash Shah recommends TARC, Karur Vysya Bank, and APL Apollo Tubes. For TARC, buy at ₹160 with a stop-loss of ₹153 and target of ₹173, citing an inverse head and shoulders pattern. Karur Vysya Bank is a buy at ₹262, stop-loss ₹250, target ₹281, showing a strong uptrend. APL Apollo is a buy at ₹1,886, stop-loss ₹1,818, target ₹2,425, signaling renewed bullish momentum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:14:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e6bf4342f77179dbb050_1766975462023.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Netflix &amp; YouTube's Streaming Domination: Is This the End for BBC and Traditional TV? Shocking Report!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Netflix-and-YouTubes-Streaming-Domination-Is-This-the-End-for-BBC-and-Traditional-TV-Shocking-Report/6951e5ba4342f77179dbae78</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Netflix-and-YouTubes-Streaming-Domination-Is-This-the-End-for-BBC-and-Traditional-TV-Shocking-Report/6951e5ba4342f77179dbae78</guid><description>Technology is radically transforming broadcasting, with streaming giants Netflix and YouTube triumphing over traditional broadcasters like the BBC. The BBC faces an 'existential threat,' with its income down by a third, prompting consideration of advertising and premium subscriptions. Commercial broadcasters like Channel 4 have seen ad revenue drop by nearly 40%. YouTube's viewership is surging globally, even surpassing Netflix in daytime US streaming, and generating significant revenue in India. This disruption is pushing traditional players towards mergers to survive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:13:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e5ba4342f77179dbae77_1766974981400.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Spending Pledge Fuels Crude Oil Surge, Global Demand Hopes Soar!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Chinas-Spending-Pledge-Fuels-Crude-Oil-Surge-Global-Demand-Hopes-Soar/6951e6064342f77179dbaf3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Chinas-Spending-Pledge-Fuels-Crude-Oil-Surge-Global-Demand-Hopes-Soar/6951e6064342f77179dbaf3d</guid><description>Crude oil prices climbed as China announced its intention to broaden fiscal spending in 2026, signaling potential demand improvement. This comes amid stalled Ukraine war resolution efforts and ongoing concerns about a global oil supply glut from OPEC+ production. Despite heading for a fifth monthly decline, China's anticipated continued crude stockpiling is expected to absorb surplus supply, providing support for prices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:12:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e6064342f77179dbaf3c_1766975141876.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹8,700 Crore Unlock: Ventive Hospitality Shares Poised to Hit Market!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Massive-8700-Crore-Unlock-Ventive-Hospitality-Shares-Poised-to-Hit-Market/6951e52b4342f77179dbadba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Massive-8700-Crore-Unlock-Ventive-Hospitality-Shares-Poised-to-Hit-Market/6951e52b4342f77179dbadba</guid><description>On Monday, December 29, Ventive Hospitality Ltd. will see its one-year shareholder lock-in expire, freeing up 122.1 million shares, equivalent to 52% of its equity, for trading. This release of shares, valued at ₹8,791 crore based on Friday's closing price, could significantly influence the stock's trajectory. The company's shares closed at ₹720 on Friday, marking a 12% increase from its IPO price of ₹643.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:12:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e52b4342f77179dbadb9_1766974845834.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Small Business Credit EXPLODES: ₹46 Lakh Crore Hits Market as First-Timers Flock In!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Small-Business-Credit-EXPLODES-46-Lakh-Crore-Hits-Market-as-First-Timers-Flock-In/6951e5944342f77179dbae41</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Small-Business-Credit-EXPLODES-46-Lakh-Crore-Hits-Market-as-First-Timers-Flock-In/6951e5944342f77179dbae41</guid><description>India's small business credit market is experiencing robust growth, with total exposure reaching ₹46 lakh crore as of September 2025, according to the CRIF–SIDBI Small Business Spotlight Report. A significant trend is the rise of first-time borrowers, with 23.3% new to credit and 12% new to enterprise borrowing. This expansion, a 16.2% year-on-year increase, is fueled by policy support and government schemes, reaching deeper into smaller cities and benefiting sole proprietors. NBFCs are playing an increasingly vital role, especially in under-penetrated markets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:12:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e5944342f77179dbae40_1766975043545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Movers Alert: Coforge Acquisition, Vedanta Bid, Timex OFS &amp; More Stocks in Focus Today!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Movers-Alert-Coforge-Acquisition-Vedanta-Bid-Timex-OFS-and-More-Stocks-in-Focus-Today/6951e3784342f77179dbabad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Movers-Alert-Coforge-Acquisition-Vedanta-Bid-Timex-OFS-and-More-Stocks-in-Focus-Today/6951e3784342f77179dbabad</guid><description>Indian stock markets are watching several key companies today, December 29. Coforge plans a major acquisition of Encora for Rs 17,032.6 crore. Vedanta secured a critical mineral block, while Timex Group India's promoter will sell an 8.93% stake via OFS. Other stocks like Sigachi Industries, Viceroy Hotels, Lloyds Enterprises, Suzlon Energy, and Solarworld Energy Solutions are also in focus due to various corporate developments, including fundraisings and new contract wins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:03:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e3784342f77179dbabac_1766974573920.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GDP Secrets Revealed? New Data Could Rewrite Economic Picture by FY28!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Secrets-Revealed-New-Data-Could-Rewrite-Economic-Picture-by-FY28/6951e32b4342f77179dbab33</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Secrets-Revealed-New-Data-Could-Rewrite-Economic-Picture-by-FY28/6951e32b4342f77179dbab33</guid><description>India's upcoming Gross Domestic Product (GDP) series, set for release in February 2026 with a 2022-23 base year, may be revised again by fiscal year 2028. Officials are considering incorporating findings from the vital Debt and Investment Survey. This survey is key for estimating household investments and could capture significant post-pandemic shifts in savings and behavior, potentially leading to updated GDP figures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:01:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e32b4342f77179dbab32_1766974326584.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Mixed: Nikkei Dips, US Futures Flat - What Indian Investors MUST Watch Before Opening Bell!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Mixed-Nikkei-Dips-US-Futures-Flat-What-Indian-Investors-MUST-Watch-Before-Opening-Bell/6951e0b24342f77179dba8fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Mixed-Nikkei-Dips-US-Futures-Flat-What-Indian-Investors-MUST-Watch-Before-Opening-Bell/6951e0b24342f77179dba8fc</guid><description>Indian markets are poised for a mixed opening as global cues present a varied picture. GIFT Nifty signals a slight gain, while Friday saw the NSE Nifty 50 and BSE Sensex close lower. Asian markets traded cautiously, with Japan's Nikkei down, while US futures showed muted movement. Investors will monitor crude oil prices, which edged higher, and FII/DII data, showing net selling by foreign investors and strong buying by domestic ones on December 26, 2025. Gold prices remain near all-time highs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:50:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951e0b24342f77179dba8fb_1766973755872.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wakefit's Profit Leap: Mattress Giant Bets Big on Quick Commerce &amp; Home Decor for Explosive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Wakefits-Profit-Leap-Mattress-Giant-Bets-Big-on-Quick-Commerce-and-Home-Decor-for-Explosive-Growth/6951dfdf4342f77179dba83b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Wakefits-Profit-Leap-Mattress-Giant-Bets-Big-on-Quick-Commerce-and-Home-Decor-for-Explosive-Growth/6951dfdf4342f77179dba83b</guid><description>Wakefit has achieved a remarkable turnaround, moving from losses in FY25 to a profit of ₹35.5 Cr in the first half of FY26. The company is now strategically expanding into quick commerce and the home decor market, aiming to drive sustainable profitable growth through its asset-light omnichannel model. These bold moves are designed to capture more customer wallet share and enhance long-term value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:46:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951dfdf4342f77179dba83a_1766973476477.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BYD Set to Overtake Tesla: The 2025 EV Sales Crown Shifts! 👑</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/BYD-Set-to-Overtake-Tesla-The-2025-EV-Sales-Crown-Shifts/6951deb04342f77179dba6fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/BYD-Set-to-Overtake-Tesla-The-2025-EV-Sales-Crown-Shifts/6951deb04342f77179dba6fd</guid><description>Chinese auto giant BYD is on track to surpass Tesla as the world's largest electric vehicle seller in 2025. Based on sales data, BYD has sold 2.07 million EVs by the end of November, while Tesla's estimated full-year sales are projected to be around 1.65 million, a decline from the previous year. Factors like the expiration of US tax credits and increasing competition are impacting Tesla's performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:44:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951deb04342f77179dba6fc_1766973202462.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin's Wild 2025: From Record Highs to Shocking Crashes – What Investors NEED to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoins-Wild-2025-From-Record-Highs-to-Shocking-Crashes-What-Investors-NEED-to-Know/6951db454342f77179dba46d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoins-Wild-2025-From-Record-Highs-to-Shocking-Crashes-What-Investors-NEED-to-Know/6951db454342f77179dba46d</guid><description>Bitcoin experienced extreme volatility in 2025, beginning near $93,400 and dropping to a Q1 low of $76,198. By October, it hit a record $126,198, driven by institutional interest and ETFs. However, profit-taking and global market shifts led to a sharp correction, ending the year around $88,086, nearly 31% below its peak. Analysts predict continued volatility in 2026 but expect growing institutional adoption and infrastructure to stabilize the market long-term.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:26:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951db454342f77179dba46c_1766972382723.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Breakout Alert! Top Analyst Picks Engineers India, NMDC, Titan for HUGE Gains - Targets Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Breakout-Alert-Top-Analyst-Picks-Engineers-India-NMDC-Titan-for-HUGE-Gains-Targets-Revealed/6951da644342f77179dba36c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Breakout-Alert-Top-Analyst-Picks-Engineers-India-NMDC-Titan-for-HUGE-Gains-Targets-Revealed/6951da644342f77179dba36c</guid><description>Angel One analyst Rajesh Bhosale has identified Engineers India, NMDC, and Titan Company as top stock picks with a bullish outlook. Engineers India shows a bullish breakout from a descending triangle pattern, with a target of ₹220. NMDC has broken out of a year-long consolidation with an inverse head and shoulders pattern, targeting ₹92. Titan Company is in a strong uptrend, breaking multi-month highs with a target of ₹4,200. All recommendations include specific buy ranges, stop losses, and positive technical indicators like RSI and volume surges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:26:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6951da644342f77179dba36b_1766972077139.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>