<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:44:31 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Dabur Restrained by Court Over 'Cool King' Packaging</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dabur-Restrained-by-Court-Over-Cool-King-Packaging/698196b269d815649b72dcc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dabur-Restrained-by-Court-Over-Cool-King-Packaging/698196b269d815649b72dcc3</guid><description>The Delhi High Court has permanently restrained Dabur India Limited from selling its 'Cool King Thanda Tael' product, ruling its packaging infringes upon the distinctive trade dress of Emami Limited's Navratna Ayurvedic Oil. The court found Dabur's design to be a deliberate imitation, leading to potential consumer confusion and upholding Emami's market-leading position in the cooling oil segment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India-EU FTA: Geopolitics Fuels Historic Trade Breakthrough</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Geopolitics-Fuels-Historic-Trade-Breakthrough/6981965069d815649b72db68</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Geopolitics-Fuels-Historic-Trade-Breakthrough/6981965069d815649b72db68</guid><description>After years of stalled negotiations, the India-European Union Free Trade Agreement (FTA) was finalized on January 27, 2026. Driven by geopolitical shifts and supply chain imperatives, this landmark pact represents a strategic recalibration, not merely an economic one. It promises substantial tariff liberalization covering nearly all bilateral trade, unlocks significant market access for key sectors in both economies, and introduces robust regulatory disciplines. The agreement is poised to reshape global trade dynamics and presents profound opportunities and complexities for the legal services market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Legal AI Adoption Accelerates: Lawttorney.ai Claims 50K Users Amidst Industry Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Legal-AI-Adoption-Accelerates-Lawttorneyai-Claims-50K-Users-Amidst-Industry-Shift/6981961269d815649b72da38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Legal-AI-Adoption-Accelerates-Lawttorneyai-Claims-50K-Users-Amidst-Industry-Shift/6981961269d815649b72da38</guid><description>Law firms are grappling with escalating litigation, complex compliance, and client demands, driving a significant integration of AI into practice. Lawttorney.ai, an AI legal platform, highlights this trend with reported metrics of over 50,000 users and 1.78 million prompts processed. The platform emphasizes operational impact, citing significant time savings in research and drafting, alongside a strong stance on data safety. These developments occur as AI transitions from experimental tools to foundational legal infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IndiGo Fortifies Operations Post-Disruption, Eyes Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Fortifies-Operations-Post-Disruption-Eyes-Growth/6981952b69d815649b72d859</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Fortifies-Operations-Post-Disruption-Eyes-Growth/6981952b69d815649b72d859</guid><description>Following a major operational disruption in December 2025 that led to widespread flight cancellations and regulatory scrutiny, IndiGo has made strengthening its internal systems and operational resilience a key priority for 2026. The Indian budget carrier is simultaneously pursuing fleet expansion, including the deployment of its new Airbus A321XLR aircraft for longer routes, and is set to increase capacity by approximately 10% in the March quarter, buoyed by steady aircraft deliveries. This strategic pivot aims to solidify its market dominance amidst a growing Indian aviation sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:29:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981952b69d815649b72d858_1770100158725.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US-India Trade Deal: Tariffs Cut, Geopolitics Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-India-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Cut-Geopolitics-Shift/6981949869d815649b72d601</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-India-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Cut-Geopolitics-Shift/6981949869d815649b72d601</guid><description>The United States has immediately slashed tariffs on Indian imports from 25% to 18%, reversing a year of escalating trade friction. The accord mandates India cease Russian oil purchases and boost U.S. product procurement over $500 billion, aiming to mend trade ties and foster deeper economic cooperation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:28:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981949869d815649b72d600_1770100041754.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Steel PSUs to Hike Capex 44% Amid Infra Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Steel-PSUs-to-Hike-Capex-44percent-Amid-Infra-Push/6981950969d815649b72d775</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Steel-PSUs-to-Hike-Capex-44percent-Amid-Infra-Push/6981950969d815649b72d775</guid><description>India's public sector steel companies are set for a significant capital expenditure surge, with total spending projected to reach ₹25,125 crore in FY27, a 44% jump from the previous year. Steel Authority of India Limited (SAIL) and National Mineral Development Corporation (NMDC) are leading this investment drive, collectively boosting their planned outlays by 50%. This expansion is fueled by robust expectations for the domestic steel industry, underpinned by government infrastructure initiatives and anticipated economic recovery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BPCL Bets Big on Petrochemicals Amid Sector Capex Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BPCL-Bets-Big-on-Petrochemicals-Amid-Sector-Capex-Divergence/6981945e69d815649b72d4aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/BPCL-Bets-Big-on-Petrochemicals-Amid-Sector-Capex-Divergence/6981945e69d815649b72d4aa</guid><description>State-run Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd. (BPCL) is significantly increasing its capital expenditure for the upcoming fiscal year by 35% to ₹25,000 crore, driven by an aggressive expansion into petrochemicals. This strategic move places it against the trend of peers like Indian Oil Corporation (IOC) and ONGC, which are trimming their investment budgets. While overall state-run oil company capex is projected for a marginal rise, spending on refining and marketing is set to decline, with petrochemicals emerging as the clear growth area. BPCL's petrochemical investment alone is nearly tripling.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981945e69d815649b72d4a9_1770099924988.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PG Electroplast Surges; Bajaj, Adani Earnings Eyed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PG-Electroplast-Surges-Bajaj-Adani-Earnings-Eyed/6981905e69d815649b72ca17</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PG-Electroplast-Surges-Bajaj-Adani-Earnings-Eyed/6981905e69d815649b72ca17</guid><description>PG Electroplast saw its shares climb following a robust third-quarter performance, reporting a 57% year-on-year net profit increase. The market's attention now shifts to the crucial earnings disclosures from NBFC leader Bajaj Finance and conglomerate Adani Enterprises, scheduled for release today. This anticipation occurs against a backdrop of positive sentiment stemming from a new India-US trade agreement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:23:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981905e69d815649b72ca16_1770099807233.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Roars Back with 25% January Sales Jump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Roars-Back-with-25percent-January-Sales-Jump/6981941a69d815649b72d378</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Roars-Back-with-25percent-January-Sales-Jump/6981941a69d815649b72d378</guid><description>Bajaj Auto initiated 2026 with significant momentum, posting a 25.3% increase in total vehicle sales for January, reaching 477,422 units compared to 381,040 units in the prior year. This performance, which surpassed analyst estimates, was propelled by balanced growth in both domestic sales and international exports. The company's two-wheeler division saw a 24% rise in total sales, while its commercial vehicle segment experienced a substantial 35% surge. Year-to-date figures, however, reveal a divergence, with export growth offsetting a marginal decline in domestic volumes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Lifts Courier Export Cap, Fuels E-commerce Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Lifts-Courier-Export-Cap-Fuels-E-commerce-Growth/6981932a69d815649b72d171</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Lifts-Courier-Export-Cap-Fuels-E-commerce-Growth/6981932a69d815649b72d171</guid><description>The Indian government has eliminated the Rs 10 lakh value cap on courier exports and enhanced processes for handling returned shipments. This significant policy shift, announced in the Union Budget 2026, aims to empower startups, small businesses, and artisans by enabling higher-value direct-to-consumer (D2C) sales on global e-commerce platforms. Industry stakeholders anticipate improved ease of doing business and increased competitiveness against international rivals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:21:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981932a69d815649b72d170_1770099685737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AWL Agri Business Reports Revenue Growth, Profit Dips 34.5% Amid Stake Change</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/AWL-Agri-Business-Reports-Revenue-Growth-Profit-Dips-345percent-Amid-Stake-Change/6981926069d815649b72cf34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/AWL-Agri-Business-Reports-Revenue-Growth-Profit-Dips-345percent-Amid-Stake-Change/6981926069d815649b72cf34</guid><description>AWL Agri Business (formerly Adani Wilmar) posted Q3 FY26 results showing consolidated revenue climb 10.5% YoY to ₹18,602.67 Cr. However, consolidated PAT plummeted 34.5% YoY to ₹269.03 Cr. Nine-month revenue rose 17.2% but PAT fell 27.4%. The company also saw Wilmar International become the majority shareholder (56.94%) and fully utilized IPO proceeds. Acquisitions in G.D. Foods and Omkar Chemical were also noted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:19:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981926069d815649b72cf33_1770099549480.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>eMudhra Q3 FY26: Revenue Surges 35.6%, Eyes Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/eMudhra-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Surges-356percent-Eyes-Global-Expansion/6981923a69d815649b72ce43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/eMudhra-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Surges-356percent-Eyes-Global-Expansion/6981923a69d815649b72ce43</guid><description>eMudhra reported a robust Q3 FY26, with total income up 35.6% YoY to ₹1,911 Mn and adjusted PAT growing 37.6% YoY to ₹334 Mn. The company highlighted strong operational progress, including live US data centers, planned UAE expansion, and leveraging global regulatory tailwinds like NIS2 and DORA. Key wins were secured in the US, Europe, and BFSI sectors, signaling continued growth in cybersecurity and paperless transformation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:18:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981923a69d815649b72ce42_1770099422714.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Tariffs Slashed, Markets Surge on New Accord</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Slashed-Markets-Surge-on-New-Accord/6981909569d815649b72cb48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Slashed-Markets-Surge-on-New-Accord/6981909569d815649b72cb48</guid><description>India and the United States have finalized a comprehensive trade agreement that reduces US tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from a previous high of 50%. The pact is poised to boost Indian exports, reduce trade friction, and potentially reshape energy procurement dynamics. This development immediately injected significant optimism into financial markets, propelling India's benchmark Nifty 50 index up by nearly 3% and strengthening the Indian rupee by over 1% against the US dollar.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:16:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981909569d815649b72cb47_1770099302866.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Pru AMC Hits Record High Amid India-US Trade Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Pru-AMC-Hits-Record-High-Amid-India-US-Trade-Boost/6981914769d815649b72cc8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Pru-AMC-Hits-Record-High-Amid-India-US-Trade-Boost/6981914769d815649b72cc8d</guid><description>ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company (AMC) shares climbed to a fresh intraday high of ₹3,128.25 on Tuesday, a 7 percent jump, propelled by positive market sentiment following the finalization of the India-US trade deal. The stock has now appreciated 44 percent from its IPO price of ₹2,165. The AMC reported a strong Q3FY26 with profit after tax up 45.1 percent year-on-year to ₹917 crore, and its mutual fund AUM growing 23.2 percent year-on-year to ₹10.8 trillion, maintaining its position as the second-largest player with a 13.3 percent market share.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:14:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981914769d815649b72cc8c_1770099179521.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Spurs Markets, Offers Exporter Relief</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Spurs-Markets-Offers-Exporter-Relief/69818f7169d815649b72c52f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Spurs-Markets-Offers-Exporter-Relief/69818f7169d815649b72c52f</guid><description>India and the United States have finalized a trade agreement that drastically reduces US tariffs on Indian goods from a peak of 50% to 18%, with the removal of specific penalties. This development triggered a sharp surge in Indian equity markets, with the Nifty and Sensex indices climbing over 5% on February 3, 2026. The pact is expected to provide substantial relief to export-oriented sectors like textiles, auto ancillaries, gems, and jewellery, while also influencing currency markets and strategic energy procurement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818f7169d815649b72c52e_1770098837650.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kotak Targets India's 55% GVA Services Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Kotak-Targets-Indias-55percent-GVA-Services-Sector/6981902869d815649b72c8e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Kotak-Targets-Indias-55percent-GVA-Services-Sector/6981902869d815649b72c8e7</guid><description>Kotak Mahindra Asset Management Company has introduced the Kotak Services Fund, an open-ended equity scheme targeting India's vital services sector. The fund, which opens for its New Fund Offer (NFO) from February 4 to February 18, aims to capitalize on a sector contributing approximately 55% to India's Gross Value Added (GVA) and employing over 31.5% of the workforce. Leveraging a Growth at Reasonable Price (GARP) strategy and a bottom-up approach, the fund will invest across market capitalizations, focusing on companies exhibiting strong fundamentals and scalability. This launch aligns with structural economic trends of increasing incomes and widespread digital adoption reshaping consumer and business services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:05:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sancode Technologies Gets Odisha Nod for ₹1650 Cr Semiconductor Unit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sancode-Technologies-Gets-Odisha-Nod-for-1650-Cr-Semiconductor-Unit/6981900469d815649b72c79a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sancode-Technologies-Gets-Odisha-Nod-for-1650-Cr-Semiconductor-Unit/6981900469d815649b72c79a</guid><description>Sancode Technologies' subsidiary, Sancode Semi, has secured 'in-principal' approval from Odisha's High-Level Clearance Authority for a ₹1,650 crore Outsourced Semiconductor Assembly and Test (OSAT) unit. Proposed in Khordha district, this marks a strategic move into India's burgeoning semiconductor ecosystem, pending further regulatory clearances and compliance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Surge Defies Trade Deals Amidst Technical Turmoil</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Surge-Defies-Trade-Deals-Amidst-Technical-Turmoil/69818fdc69d815649b72c69b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Surge-Defies-Trade-Deals-Amidst-Technical-Turmoil/69818fdc69d815649b72c69b</guid><description>Indian gold and silver prices surged Tuesday, defying positive trade pacts with the US and EU. MCX silver jumped 7.42% and gold 3.55%, driven by technical factors, margin requirement adjustments by CME, and speculation around US monetary policy, overriding typical safe-haven demand dips.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:04:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Zen Tech Surges on Bullish Choice Equities Call: Rs 2150 Target Set</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Zen-Tech-Surges-on-Bullish-Choice-Equities-Call-Rs-2150-Target-Set/69818e8e69d815649b72c3be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Zen-Tech-Surges-on-Bullish-Choice-Equities-Call-Rs-2150-Target-Set/69818e8e69d815649b72c3be</guid><description>Choice Institutional Equities reiterates a BUY on Zen Tech, setting a Rs 2,150 target. The firm highlights strong order momentum, with INR 1,427 Cr secured, and anticipates steady near-term growth driven by an expanding order book and favorable trade agreements. Management's pragmatic approach to revenue guidance is seen as a positive reset.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818e8e69d815649b72c3bd_1770098632916.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Choice Equities Initiates BUY on Mahindra Lifespace, Eyes Rs 500 Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Choice-Equities-Initiates-BUY-on-Mahindra-Lifespace-Eyes-Rs-500-Target/69818e7769d815649b72c2c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Choice-Equities-Initiates-BUY-on-Mahindra-Lifespace-Eyes-Rs-500-Target/69818e7769d815649b72c2c7</guid><description>Choice Institutional Equities has issued a strong BUY recommendation for Mahindra Lifespace Developers, setting a price target of Rs 500. The brokerage cited robust year-over-year growth in pre-sales (up 71.3%) and average selling price (up 28.4%) as key factors. Upcoming project approvals and new launches in Q4FY26 are expected to further bolster performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:00:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818e7769d815649b72c2c6_1770098454181.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zee Entertainment Slashes Jobs Amid Revenue Slump, Eyes 20% EBITDA</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Entertainment-Slashes-Jobs-Amid-Revenue-Slump-Eyes-20percent-EBITDA/69818e0a69d815649b72c15b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Entertainment-Slashes-Jobs-Amid-Revenue-Slump-Eyes-20percent-EBITDA/69818e0a69d815649b72c15b</guid><description>Zee Entertainment Enterprises is intensifying its focus on manpower cost optimization, having already reduced its workforce by 951 employees between FY23 and FY25. This strategic move comes as the broadcast giant grapples with a shrinking pay-TV subscriber base and declining advertising revenue. The company is targeting an 18-20% EBITDA margin by FY26, a significant leap from its current 10.1% in 9M FY26. Deputy CEO Mukund Galgali cited overlaps in linear and digital operations as the genesis for this restructuring.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Drug Duty Cuts Offer Targeted Relief</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Budget-2026-Drug-Duty-Cuts-Offer-Targeted-Relief/69818dfd69d815649b72c0b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Budget-2026-Drug-Duty-Cuts-Offer-Targeted-Relief/69818dfd69d815649b72c0b5</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 has greenlit import duty exemptions for seven rare disease drugs and seventeen anti-cancer medications, a move championed by patient groups for offering direct financial relief on prohibitively expensive treatments. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced the measure, continuing a government strategy to lower customs duties on critical imported medicines. While this is projected to reduce out-of-pocket expenses by an estimated 10-15% for individuals bearing the cost, concerns remain that it may not fully address the high base prices of these life-saving therapies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Surges on Central Bank Buys &amp; Geopolitical Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-on-Central-Bank-Buys-and-Geopolitical-Fears/69818d2569d815649b72bef4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Surges-on-Central-Bank-Buys-and-Geopolitical-Fears/69818d2569d815649b72bef4</guid><description>Indian gold prices saw a notable upward revision on February 3, 2026, with 24K gold reaching ₹148,230 per 10 grams, a gain of ₹5,340. This rise is attributed to sustained purchasing by central banks globally and ongoing geopolitical tensions, which bolster gold's standing as a safe-haven asset. MCX gold futures also reflected this positive sentiment, advancing nearly 4%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:56:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818d2569d815649b72bef3_1770098106904.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta Pledges Entire Promoter Stake in VEDL for $350M Debt Facility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Vedanta-Pledges-Entire-Promoter-Stake-in-VEDL-for-350M-Debt-Facility/6981895069d815649b72b3f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Vedanta-Pledges-Entire-Promoter-Stake-in-VEDL-for-350M-Debt-Facility/6981895069d815649b72b3f9</guid><description>Vedanta Resources Limited has disclosed creating encumbrances on its entire 56.38% promoter stake in Vedanta Limited (VEDL) as part of a new US$350 million facility. While no new pledges were created beyond existing ones, the move underscores the group's continuing reliance on debt financing and share-backed arrangements for financial obligations and repayment. The funds are earmarked for existing debt and general corporate purposes for the VRL Group.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:54:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981895069d815649b72b3f8_1770097984763.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UBS Warns: Silver's Wild Ride Makes Long-Term Bets Risky</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/UBS-Warns-Silvers-Wild-Ride-Makes-Long-Term-Bets-Risky/69818d1269d815649b72be19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/UBS-Warns-Silvers-Wild-Ride-Makes-Long-Term-Bets-Risky/69818d1269d815649b72be19</guid><description>Silver prices experienced extraordinary volatility, including a 38% intraday collapse, rarely seen in modern markets. UBS Chief Investment Office advises extreme caution, stating it is too early for long-term exposure. The metal entered the sell-off from an overstretched position, volatility has surged to unprecedented levels, and key demand drivers are weakening.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Ignites Market Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Ignites-Market-Surge/69818c2369d815649b72bc60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Ignites-Market-Surge/69818c2369d815649b72bc60</guid><description>Indian equities experienced a powerful two-session rally, adding nearly ₹24 lakh crore in investor wealth. The surge, driven by the India-US trade deal reducing tariffs, propelled benchmark indices like the Sensex and Nifty to significant gains. This broad-based advance saw all Sensex constituents trading higher, with Reliance Industries leading the pack. The market's positive momentum overrides previous Budget Day jitters, according to market strategists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:52:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818c2369d815649b72bc5f_1770097841854.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: US Slashes Tariffs, Boosts 'Made in India' Exports</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-US-Slashes-Tariffs-Boosts-Made-in-India-Exports/69818bc169d815649b72bb36</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-US-Slashes-Tariffs-Boosts-Made-in-India-Exports/69818bc169d815649b72bb36</guid><description>The United States has significantly reduced tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, a move lauded by Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman as a substantial boost for the 'Made in India' initiative. This development, part of a new bilateral trade agreement, also sees India committing to lower trade barriers for American products and increase imports across key sectors like energy and agriculture. The deal aims to foster mutual economic benefits and strengthen ties between the two democratic giants.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818bc169d815649b72bb35_1770097718081.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alkosign Shuts 42% Turnover Luggage Unit Amidst Deep Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Alkosign-Shuts-42percent-Turnover-Luggage-Unit-Amidst-Deep-Losses/69818b3069d815649b72b969</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Alkosign-Shuts-42percent-Turnover-Luggage-Unit-Amidst-Deep-Losses/69818b3069d815649b72b969</guid><description>Alkosign Limited has approved the closure of its Luggage Business Unit, effective February 2, 2026, citing intense market competition and continuous losses. This unit contributed 42.78% of the company's consolidated turnover in FY25. The closure is also attributed to declining OEM outsourcing and the cancellation of the Baggit license. The move aims to refocus on core business activities for enhanced financial sustainability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:46:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818b3069d815649b72b968_1770097592549.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Star Navigates Q3 with Steady Revenue, Faces Inventory Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Blue-Star-Navigates-Q3-with-Steady-Revenue-Faces-Inventory-Headwinds/698189ce69d815649b72b647</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Blue-Star-Navigates-Q3-with-Steady-Revenue-Faces-Inventory-Headwinds/698189ce69d815649b72b647</guid><description>Blue Star posted a 4% revenue growth in Q3 FY26, maintaining stable EBITDA margins. However, reported profit after tax declined 39% due to a one-time labor code provision. Dealer inventory levels have risen to 5-6 weeks, driven by stocking ahead of the January 2026 Bureau of Energy Efficiency (BEE) energy label transition. Commercial refrigeration demand remains subdued, contrasting with strong execution in Electro-Mechanical Projects (EMPS) driven by data center and building sector demand. Management anticipates a seasonal pickup in summer, but near-term visibility is tempered by cost inflation and the BEE norm shift.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:44:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698189ce69d815649b72b646_1770097467034.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Elana Holdings Boosts Asian Hotels (North) Stake to 41.16% via Preferential Allotment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Elana-Holdings-Boosts-Asian-Hotels-North-Stake-to-4116percent-via-Preferential-Allotment/69818a3f69d815649b72b7a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Elana-Holdings-Boosts-Asian-Hotels-North-Stake-to-4116percent-via-Preferential-Allotment/69818a3f69d815649b72b7a8</guid><description>Elana Holdings Pte. Ltd. has substantially increased its stake in Asian Hotels (North) Limited to 24.68% through a preferential allotment. The acquisition, adding 10.85% of the expanded equity base, brings Elana and its Person Acting in Concert (PAC), Ms. Shreya Agarwal, to a combined 41.16% holding. This move significantly alters the ownership structure of the hotel company.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:42:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69818a3f69d815649b72b7a7_1770097327277.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Elana Holdings Seals 24.68% Asian Hotels Stake; Open Offer Exemption</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Elana-Holdings-Seals-2468percent-Asian-Hotels-Stake-Open-Offer-Exemption/6981896269d815649b72b4a4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Elana-Holdings-Seals-2468percent-Asian-Hotels-Stake-Open-Offer-Exemption/6981896269d815649b72b4a4</guid><description>Elana Holdings Pte. Ltd. acquired a significant 24.68% stake in Asian Hotels (North) Limited for ₹330 per share through a preferential issue. The transaction, occurring Jan 28-30, 2026, grants Elana a substantial minority holding, crucially exempting it from a mandatory SEBI open offer due to regulatory compliance. This strategic move reshapes Asian Hotels' ownership structure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:42:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981896269d815649b72b4a3_1770097210304.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chola Investment: Q3 Strength Amid Stock Correction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Chola-Investment-Q3-Strength-Amid-Stock-Correction/6981759d69d815649b727a15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Chola-Investment-Q3-Strength-Amid-Stock-Correction/6981759d69d815649b727a15</guid><description>Cholamandalam Investment (Chola) reported strong Q3 FY26 performance, driven by sustained AUM growth and expanding net interest margins. Despite a recent stock correction exceeding 10%, the company's fundamentals remain robust, supported by stable asset quality and a well-diversified product mix. Analysts note the company's strategic initiatives and healthy capital position as key drivers for future upside potential, even as market conditions present short-term headwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:38:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981759d69d815649b727a14_1770097016129.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SAIL: Volume Surge Meets Margin Pressure; Analysts Hold View</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SAIL-Volume-Surge-Meets-Margin-Pressure-Analysts-Hold-View/69817ae569d815649b728b01</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SAIL-Volume-Surge-Meets-Margin-Pressure-Analysts-Hold-View/69817ae569d815649b728b01</guid><description>Steel Authority of India Ltd. (SAIL) navigated the challenging pricing environment in Q3 FY26 with robust volume growth, yet faced margin compression. Revenue increased 3% quarter-on-quarter to ₹27,400 crore, driven by a 4% rise in sales volumes. However, a 1% dip in net sales realization per tonne and increased raw material costs led to a 9% sequential decline in EBITDA to ₹2,300 crore. IDBI Capital maintained its 'Hold' rating and a target price of ₹151, citing steady volume prospects against near-term margin pressures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:34:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69817ae569d815649b728b00_1770096868565.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GreenX Wealth Fund Surges Stake in Vivid Mercantile to 7.82%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/GreenX-Wealth-Fund-Surges-Stake-in-Vivid-Mercantile-to-782percent/6981876a69d815649b72a919</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/GreenX-Wealth-Fund-Surges-Stake-in-Vivid-Mercantile-to-782percent/6981876a69d815649b72a919</guid><description>GreenX Wealth Multihorizons Opportunity Fund, an SEBI-registered AIF, has significantly increased its stake in Vivid Mercantile Limited, a BSE-listed firm. The fund acquired an additional 7.42% through open market transactions, raising its total holding to 7.82% of the company's total share capital. This disclosure was made in compliance with SEBI takeover regulations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:32:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981876a69d815649b72a918_1770096725075.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Subros Posts Mixed Q3; EV Growth Fuels Revenue Despite Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Subros-Posts-Mixed-Q3-EV-Growth-Fuels-Revenue-Despite-Margin-Squeeze/698186f569d815649b72a78d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Subros-Posts-Mixed-Q3-EV-Growth-Fuels-Revenue-Despite-Margin-Squeeze/698186f569d815649b72a78d</guid><description>Subros Ltd. posted mixed Q3 FY26 results with revenue rising 15% year-on-year, supported by new business awards. However, higher material costs and product mix shifts compressed EBITDA margins to 8.6%. The auto component maker is aggressively pursuing electric compressor localization, securing a Rs 1,280 crore order for EVs and HEVs. Despite significant EV potential, a moderate outlook for PV/CV segments and ongoing margin headwinds remain key concerns for investors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:32:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698186f569d815649b72a78c_1770096618719.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US-India Trade Deal: $500B Claim Under Scrutiny, Tariffs Cut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-India-Trade-Deal-500B-Claim-Under-Scrutiny-Tariffs-Cut/69817e1369d815649b7296ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-India-Trade-Deal-500B-Claim-Under-Scrutiny-Tariffs-Cut/69817e1369d815649b7296ea</guid><description>The United States and India have finalized a trade agreement, leading to a reduction in US reciprocal tariffs on Indian goods from 25% to 18%. While President Trump claimed India committed to over $500 billion in US product purchases, New Delhi's response focused solely on the tariff cut, raising questions about the $500 billion figure's scale and credibility. The market reacted positively, with Indian equities surging, anticipating benefits for key export sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:27:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69817e1369d815649b7296e9_1770096430286.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shadowfax IPO Concludes: Logistics Giant Raises ₹1,907 Crore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Shadowfax-IPO-Concludes-Logistics-Giant-Raises-1907-Crore/6981860469d815649b72a60d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Shadowfax-IPO-Concludes-Logistics-Giant-Raises-1907-Crore/6981860469d815649b72a60d</guid><description>Shadowfax Technologies Limited has successfully completed an initial public offer aggregating ₹1,907.269 crore. The offering comprised both a fresh issuance of shares and an offer for sale by existing shareholders. Leading legal advisory firms Cyril Amarchand Mangaldas, Shardul Amarchand Mangaldas &amp; Co, JSA Advocates &amp; Solicitors, and Linklaters provided counsel on this substantial transaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981860469d815649b72a60c_1770096302662.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Subros Ltd: EV Push Fuels Growth Amidst Margin Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Subros-Ltd-EV-Push-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Margin-Pressure/6981859469d815649b72a504</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Subros-Ltd-EV-Push-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Margin-Pressure/6981859469d815649b72a504</guid><description>Subros Ltd posted robust Q3 FY26 revenue growth of 15.43% year-on-year, driven by increased volumes and new business awards, particularly in the electric mobility sector. However, EBITDA margins compressed by 65 basis points due to higher commodity costs and unfavorable currency movements, further impacted by new labor laws. The company secured a significant Rs 1,280 crore order for electric compressors and is expanding EV-related capacities. While diversification into CVs and railways continues, the auto components sector outlook is positive. The stock trades at approximately 23 times FY27 estimated earnings, considered fair but with limited near-term upside due to margin pressures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:23:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981859469d815649b72a503_1770096196539.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Sparks Market Rally, Boosts Exports</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Market-Rally-Boosts-Exports/6981844269d815649b72a338</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Market-Rally-Boosts-Exports/6981844269d815649b72a338</guid><description>Indian equity markets surged Tuesday following a landmark India-US trade agreement that reduced US tariffs on Indian goods from 50% to 18%. The pact, effective immediately, is expected to unlock significant opportunities for export-focused industries. The Sensex and Nifty opened sharply higher, with major gainers seen across sectors like Adani Enterprises and Adani Ports. Analysts anticipate accelerated earnings growth and a positive shift in foreign investor sentiment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981844269d815649b72a337_1770096076559.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Epic Energy Forges Key Deal to Enter Lithium-ion Battery Recycling Space</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Epic-Energy-Forges-Key-Deal-to-Enter-Lithium-ion-Battery-Recycling-Space/69817c2c69d815649b72927e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Epic-Energy-Forges-Key-Deal-to-Enter-Lithium-ion-Battery-Recycling-Space/69817c2c69d815649b72927e</guid><description>Epic Energy Limited inks a strategic collaboration with REFNIC (Zetrance Tech) to bolster its lithium-ion battery recycling and second-life initiatives. Operating through its SPV, SUN LLP, the partnership will see REFNIC handle design and engineering for a new shredding facility and second-life battery assembly plant in Wada, Maharashtra. This move targets sustainable energy systems and circular economy solutions for end-of-life batteries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 05:11:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69817c2c69d815649b72927d_1770095468399.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>