<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:43:42 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Markets Diverge: Cyclical Stocks Lead Amidst IT Weakness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Markets-Diverge-Cyclical-Stocks-Lead-Amidst-IT-Weakness/6983ef5fbf48f011a29ac4b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Markets-Diverge-Cyclical-Stocks-Lead-Amidst-IT-Weakness/6983ef5fbf48f011a29ac4b0</guid><description>Indian markets showed cautious consolidation on Wednesday, February 4, 2026, with the Nifty 50 index inching up to 25,779.5. A significant divergence emerged, with auto, metal, and energy sectors attracting buying interest, contrasted by a sharp decline in the IT index due to global tech weakness. Mid and small-cap stocks continued their recovery, bolstering market breadth. Investors are advised to focus on selective stock picking amid mixed global cues and profit-booking pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:16:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983ef5fbf48f011a29ac4af_1770255111637.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent Ltd. Beats EBITDA Estimates, But Fashion Woes Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Ltd-Beats-EBITDA-Estimates-But-Fashion-Woes-Linger/6983eee2bf48f011a29ac3c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trent-Ltd-Beats-EBITDA-Estimates-But-Fashion-Woes-Linger/6983eee2bf48f011a29ac3c2</guid><description>Trent Ltd. posted a robust third-quarter performance, with EBITDA rising 27.6% to ₹1,081 crore, surpassing market expectations. This growth was fueled by contributions from beauty, personal care, innerwear, and footwear segments, which now account for over 21% of the topline. The Star hypermarket business also saw its own brands contributing 74% to its revenue, prompting plans for accelerated expansion. However, the company's fashion portfolio experienced marginally negative like-for-like growth due to a shift in the festive season. Despite a 5% rise in its stock price on Wednesday ahead of the results, Trent shares remain significantly below their October 2024 peak, trading over 40% lower.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:14:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983eee2bf48f011a29ac3c1_1770254234617.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GAIL Battles Regulator Over Tariff: Future Capex Squeeze?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GAIL-Battles-Regulator-Over-Tariff-Future-Capex-Squeeze/6983edf6bf48f011a29ac296</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GAIL-Battles-Regulator-Over-Tariff-Future-Capex-Squeeze/6983edf6bf48f011a29ac296</guid><description>GAIL (India) Limited is contesting the Petroleum and Natural Gas Regulatory Board's (PNGRB) recent tariff order for its integrated pipeline network. The regulator approved a 12% increase to ₹65.69 per mmBtu, falling short of GAIL's requested ₹78. GAIL argues the PNGRB's exclusion of future capital and operational expenditures, coupled with a miscalculation of transmission losses and revenue sharing from capacity utilization, jeopardizes its financial model and could lead to higher consumer costs long-term. This dispute highlights a critical tension between regulatory price control and the substantial investment needed for India's energy infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:10:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983edf6bf48f011a29ac295_1770253975749.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ambani: India to slash energy imports; Reliance eyes AI dominance.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Ambani-India-to-slash-energy-imports-Reliance-eyes-AI-dominance/6983ed89bf48f011a29ac106</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Ambani-India-to-slash-energy-imports-Reliance-eyes-AI-dominance/6983ed89bf48f011a29ac106</guid><description>Reliance Industries Chairman Mukesh Ambani projected India will import less than 20% of its energy within a decade. Addressing a JioBlackRock event, he detailed Reliance's pivot to becoming an AI-native deeptech firm, anticipating a tenfold productivity boost. Ambani also stressed that sustained law and order and social harmony are critical for India's long-term economic expansion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:08:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983ed89bf48f011a29ac105_1770254401830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI's Rs 10 Lakh SIFs: A New Bridge for Sophisticated Investors?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SEBIs-Rs-10-Lakh-SIFs-A-New-Bridge-for-Sophisticated-Investors/6983ed7cbf48f011a29ac0ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SEBIs-Rs-10-Lakh-SIFs-A-New-Bridge-for-Sophisticated-Investors/6983ed7cbf48f011a29ac0ad</guid><description>SEBI has launched Specialised Investment Funds (SIFs) with a minimum investment of ₹10 lakh, aiming to bridge the gap between mutual funds and Portfolio Management Services (PMS). These funds, operational since April 2025, saw over 20,000 folios by December 2025, with many AMCs adopting long-short strategies. Despite their launch, early performance data indicates SIFs are lagging benchmarks, and liquidity can be more restricted than traditional mutual funds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:08:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983ed7cbf48f011a29ac0ac_1770253807337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: High-Tech Vision Ignores Farmer Income Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Budget-2026-High-Tech-Vision-Ignores-Farmer-Income-Crisis/6983ed05bf48f011a29abf52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Budget-2026-High-Tech-Vision-Ignores-Farmer-Income-Crisis/6983ed05bf48f011a29abf52</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 emphasizes technological advancement in agriculture, focusing on AI-driven development and support for high-value crops like coconut and cashew. While this signals a long-term modernization strategy, it largely sidesteps the immediate income distress faced by farmers grappling with volatile markets, rising input costs, and inadequate procurement mechanisms. The budget's vision for future farming offers little tangible relief for cultivators currently struggling with poor market prices, particularly for nutri-cereals, pulses, and oilseeds, where Minimum Support Price (MSP) realization remains inconsistent.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 01:06:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983ed05bf48f011a29abf51_1770253685300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pivots to US Energy: Trade Deal Fuels New Supply Chains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Pivots-to-US-Energy-Trade-Deal-Fuels-New-Supply-Chains/6983e23abf48f011a29ab87f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Pivots-to-US-Energy-Trade-Deal-Fuels-New-Supply-Chains/6983e23abf48f011a29ab87f</guid><description>India's energy import strategy is undergoing a significant shift, with state-owned companies preparing to boost purchases from the United States under a new bilateral trade agreement. This pivot comes as crude oil and natural gas imports from Russia are expected to decline sharply. While the trade deal offers India reduced tariffs and enhanced energy security, it introduces potential economic challenges, including increased freight costs and forgone discounts, as New Delhi recalibrates its global energy sourcing to balance geopolitical alignments and market economics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:20:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983e23abf48f011a29ab87e_1770250973049.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>