<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:35:36 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Raymond's Q3 Revenue Soars 18%; Aerospace &amp; Auto Drive Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Raymonds-Q3-Revenue-Soars-18percent-Aerospace-and-Auto-Drive-Growth/6980c1d1c680f8b0a9f5cc51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Raymonds-Q3-Revenue-Soars-18percent-Aerospace-and-Auto-Drive-Growth/6980c1d1c680f8b0a9f5cc51</guid><description>Raymond Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26 with total income up 18% YoY to INR 580 crores, boosted by its Aerospace &amp; Defense and Precision Technology &amp; Auto Components divisions. The company remains debt-free with a net cash surplus and has outlined INR 1,000 crores in future capex over five years for expansion in Andhra Pradesh. Management expressed optimism driven by global supply chain shifts and localization efforts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ansal Properties Loses Key Officials Amidst Insolvency Process</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ansal-Properties-Loses-Key-Officials-Amidst-Insolvency-Process/6980c125c680f8b0a9f5c8fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ansal-Properties-Loses-Key-Officials-Amidst-Insolvency-Process/6980c125c680f8b0a9f5c8fa</guid><description>Ansal Properties and Infrastructure Ltd. is grappling with significant personnel exits, including its Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, amid ongoing Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP). Dy. GM Architect resigns after 31 years, citing distress and pending dues, raising employee relations concerns for the NCLT-managed entity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:24:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980c125c680f8b0a9f5c8f9_1770045892176.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Corona Remedies Retains Strong CARE A+ Rating Amid Facility Reduction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Corona-Remedies-Retains-Strong-CARE-A-Rating-Amid-Facility-Reduction/6980c127c680f8b0a9f5c958</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Corona-Remedies-Retains-Strong-CARE-A-Rating-Amid-Facility-Reduction/6980c127c680f8b0a9f5c958</guid><description>Corona Remedies Limited's credit profile remains robust as CARE Ratings reaffirms its 'CARE A+; Stable' rating on bank facilities aggregating ₹95 crore. The long-term facilities saw a reduction, suggesting potential debt repayment or reduced financing needs. The 'CARE A1' short-term rating highlights strong liquidity, with a stable outlook indicating continued credit quality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:22:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bhageria Industries Posts 41% Revenue Jump Amid Profit Decline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Bhageria-Industries-Posts-41percent-Revenue-Jump-Amid-Profit-Decline/6980c0b2c680f8b0a9f5c6a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Bhageria-Industries-Posts-41percent-Revenue-Jump-Amid-Profit-Decline/6980c0b2c680f8b0a9f5c6a6</guid><description>Bhageria Industries reported a robust 41.00% YoY revenue growth to ₹241.93 Crores for Q3 FY26. However, standalone PAT declined 7.09% YoY to ₹12.02 Crores, with EPS falling to ₹2.75. Consolidated revenue rose 41.78% to ₹241.54 Crores, but consolidated PAT dipped 4.77% to ₹10.84 Crores. The company also approved incorporating a wholly-owned subsidiary for mineral investments and shifting its registered office.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:21:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980c0b2c680f8b0a9f5c6a5_1770045692689.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bhageria Revenue Surges 41%, Profit Dips Amidst Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Bhageria-Revenue-Surges-41percent-Profit-Dips-Amidst-Margin-Pressures/6980c0cec680f8b0a9f5c752</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Bhageria-Revenue-Surges-41percent-Profit-Dips-Amidst-Margin-Pressures/6980c0cec680f8b0a9f5c752</guid><description>Bhageria Industries reported a strong 41% YoY revenue jump to ₹241.93 Cr for Q3 FY26. However, standalone profit after tax (PAT) declined 7.09% to ₹12.02 Cr, indicating margin compression. Consolidated revenue also rose over 41%, while PAT saw a 4.77% dip. The company also greenlit a proposal for a wholly-owned subsidiary to explore the mineral business.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Interarch Building Solutions Posts 44% Revenue Surge; Expands Capacity, Plans ₹100 Cr QIP</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Interarch-Building-Solutions-Posts-44percent-Revenue-Surge-Expands-Capacity-Plans-100-Cr-QIP/6980bee8c680f8b0a9f5c11b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Interarch-Building-Solutions-Posts-44percent-Revenue-Surge-Expands-Capacity-Plans-100-Cr-QIP/6980bee8c680f8b0a9f5c11b</guid><description>Interarch Building Solutions reported a strong Q3 FY26 with revenue leaping 43.7% YoY to ₹522.52 Cr and PAT rising 32.2% to ₹372.64 Cr. The company announced aggressive expansion plans, including new land acquisition and Phase 2 of its AP plant, backed by a proposed ₹100 Cr QIP. An Income Tax search occurred, though management expects no material impact.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980bee8c680f8b0a9f5c11a_1770045507822.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Artemis Medicare Q3: 17.7% Revenue Growth, ₹700 Cr Fundraise, QoQ Profit Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Artemis-Medicare-Q3-177percent-Revenue-Growth-700-Cr-Fundraise-QoQ-Profit-Dips/6980c017c680f8b0a9f5c546</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Artemis-Medicare-Q3-177percent-Revenue-Growth-700-Cr-Fundraise-QoQ-Profit-Dips/6980c017c680f8b0a9f5c546</guid><description>Artemis Medicare Services reported Q3 FY26 standalone revenue growth of 17.73% YoY to ₹26,712.34 lakhs. However, net profit after tax declined 24.88% QoQ to ₹2,251.28 lakhs, impacted by an exceptional item. The board approved a ₹700 crore fundraising plan. Consolidated revenue also saw a 17.20% YoY jump. No future guidance was issued.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NCLT Okays Jash Engineering Merger, Typo Delays Final Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCLT-Okays-Jash-Engineering-Merger-Typo-Delays-Final-Order/6980bfe2c680f8b0a9f5c419</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCLT-Okays-Jash-Engineering-Merger-Typo-Delays-Final-Order/6980bfe2c680f8b0a9f5c419</guid><description>Jash Engineering Limited has secured sanction from the NCLT, Indore Bench, for its merger with Shivpad Engineers Private Limited. The approval, under the Companies Act, 2013, comes with a caveat: a typographical error in the NCLT order's 'Appointed Date' necessitates obtaining a corrected copy before stock exchange submission. This move signals consolidation, though specific financial synergies remain undisclosed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jaro Education Soars 42% Revenue, Returns to Profit; Targets Margin Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Jaro-Education-Soars-42percent-Revenue-Returns-to-Profit-Targets-Margin-Push/6980bf03c680f8b0a9f5c246</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Jaro-Education-Soars-42percent-Revenue-Returns-to-Profit-Targets-Margin-Push/6980bf03c680f8b0a9f5c246</guid><description>Jaro Education reported a strong Q3 FY'26 with revenue soaring 42% YoY to INR 61.80 cr and a return to profitability. The company posted INR 7.03 cr PAT. Nine-month figures show 13.29% revenue growth to INR 203 cr. Management targets 20-25% FY'26 revenue growth, aiming to restore EBITDA margins to ~30% and PAT margins to 19-20% via strategic expansion and ARPU growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:16:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980bf03c680f8b0a9f5c245_1770045370297.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Growth Engine Ignites, Markets Temper Reaction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Growth-Engine-Ignites-Markets-Temper-Reaction/6980b805c680f8b0a9f5ac25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Growth-Engine-Ignites-Markets-Temper-Reaction/6980b805c680f8b0a9f5ac25</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Union Budget 2026 outlines a strategy focused on accelerating economic growth through increased capital expenditure, domestic manufacturing incentives, and sector-specific development, though equity markets showed immediate caution following the announcement. Key proposals include significant boosts to the semiconductor and electronics sectors, infrastructure development via new rail corridors and freight networks, and reforms aimed at deepening bond markets and liberalizing foreign investment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b805c680f8b0a9f5ac24_1770045272363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CONCOR Volumes Soar, But Realization Pressures Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/CONCOR-Volumes-Soar-But-Realization-Pressures-Linger/6980ba24c680f8b0a9f5b352</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/CONCOR-Volumes-Soar-But-Realization-Pressures-Linger/6980ba24c680f8b0a9f5b352</guid><description>Container Corporation of India (CONCOR) posted a 4.5% revenue increase to INR 2,307 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by an 11% surge in total volumes to 1.4 million TEUs. However, blended realization per TEU dipped 6% year-on-year, primarily due to a significant 17% decline in domestic segment realization. Despite this margin pressure, a prominent brokerage maintains a 'BUY' rating with a revised target price of INR 580, anticipating strong future growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:13:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980ba24c680f8b0a9f5b351_1770045210306.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dixon Tech: Analyst Sticks to BUY Amid Smartphone Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Tech-Analyst-Sticks-to-BUY-Amid-Smartphone-Woes/6980bb11c680f8b0a9f5b701</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Tech-Analyst-Sticks-to-BUY-Amid-Smartphone-Woes/6980bb11c680f8b0a9f5b701</guid><description>Motilal Oswal maintains a BUY rating on Dixon Technologies, setting a ₹16,700 target price despite 3QFY26 headwinds from weak smartphone demand due to high memory prices and inventory. The firm acknowledges a 46% stock correction has priced in near-term risks, while Dixon advances backward integration and ECMS approvals, albeit facing Vivo JV delays.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:10:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980bb11c680f8b0a9f5b700_1770045049925.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PG Electroplast Hits 50% Profit Growth, Confirms FY26 Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PG-Electroplast-Hits-50percent-Profit-Growth-Confirms-FY26-Outlook/6980bddec680f8b0a9f5bf4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PG-Electroplast-Hits-50percent-Profit-Growth-Confirms-FY26-Outlook/6980bddec680f8b0a9f5bf4c</guid><description>PG Electroplast Ltd's third quarter performance saw net profit climb 50% year-on-year to ₹60.3 crore on revenue growth of 45.9% to ₹1,412 crore. The company subsequently reaffirmed its full-year FY26 guidance, projecting consolidated revenues of ₹5,700–5,800 crore (17–19% growth) and net profits of ₹300–310 crore (3–7% growth), signaling robust demand visibility and effective execution. This performance has bolstered investor confidence in the company's operational capacity and market position.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:10:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980bddec680f8b0a9f5bf4b_1770045043835.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Equitas SFB: Motilal Oswal Reiterates BUY on Strong Q3 Results</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Equitas-SFB-Motilal-Oswal-Reiterates-BUY-on-Strong-Q3-Results/6980bb24c680f8b0a9f5b7a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Equitas-SFB-Motilal-Oswal-Reiterates-BUY-on-Strong-Q3-Results/6980bb24c680f8b0a9f5b7a7</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Securities maintained a BUY rating on Equitas Small Finance Bank (ESFB), setting a target price of INR 80, following the bank's strong third-quarter fiscal year 2026 results. ESFB reported an approximate INR 900 million PAT, a 36% year-on-year increase, beating estimates by 27%. Net Interest Income rose 10.1% QoQ to INR 8.5 billion, with Net Interest Margins expanding to 6.72%. The bank also proactively managed asset quality by selling INR 548.5 million in NPA assets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:08:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980bb24c680f8b0a9f5b7a6_1770044895165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kajaria Ceramics: Flat Q3 Revenue, Fraud Impact; BUY Rating Held</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kajaria-Ceramics-Flat-Q3-Revenue-Fraud-Impact-BUY-Rating-Held/6980bc00c680f8b0a9f5bad6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kajaria-Ceramics-Flat-Q3-Revenue-Fraud-Impact-BUY-Rating-Held/6980bc00c680f8b0a9f5bad6</guid><description>Kajaria Ceramics (KJC) posted flat year-over-year revenue of INR 1,168 crore for Q3 FY26, hindered by subdued demand and intense competition, alongside stagnant tile volumes. Despite this, EBITDA margins improved YoY to 17.2%, though QoQ saw a dip. Reported Profit After Tax (PAT) was impacted by INR 396 million in extraordinary items, including a INR 194 million fraud loss at a subsidiary and INR 183 million in new labor code provisions. Motilal Oswal reiterates a BUY rating with a INR 1,057 price target, considering the stock attractive after a substantial correction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:07:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980bc00c680f8b0a9f5bad5_1770044850638.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KEC International: Margin Headwinds Temper Strong Order Book</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Margin-Headwinds-Temper-Strong-Order-Book/6980bc17c680f8b0a9f5bb5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Margin-Headwinds-Temper-Strong-Order-Book/6980bc17c680f8b0a9f5bb5f</guid><description>KEC International reported in-line results for Q3 FY26, with revenue up 12% year-on-year to ₹6,001 crore. While order inflows for 9MFY26 remained strong at ₹193 billion, leading to a backlog of ₹367 billion, anticipated delays in claim settlements are expected to impact margins. Consequently, earnings estimates for FY26-28 have been reduced by 15%, 8%, and 8% respectively. Motilal Oswal maintains a BUY rating with a revised target price of ₹890.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:04:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980bc17c680f8b0a9f5bb5e_1770044664546.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KPIT Tech Q3 Revenue Trails; Analyst Sees 29% Upside</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/KPIT-Tech-Q3-Revenue-Trails-Analyst-Sees-29percent-Upside/6980bc7dc680f8b0a9f5bd05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/KPIT-Tech-Q3-Revenue-Trails-Analyst-Sees-29percent-Upside/6980bc7dc680f8b0a9f5bd05</guid><description>KPIT Technologies posted USD 181 million in 3QFY26 revenue, a 1.5% sequential increase that missed analyst forecasts. While the commercial vehicle segment surged 10.5%, passenger car revenue dipped 1.2%. EBIT margins contracted to 15.6%, also underperforming expectations. Despite these short-term metrics, Motilal Oswal maintains a BUY rating with a ₹1,350 target, projecting 12% EPS CAGR and highlighting a 33x FY28E EPS valuation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal Lifts Five Star Finance to Buy, Eyes ₹590 Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Motilal-Oswal-Lifts-Five-Star-Finance-to-Buy-Eyes-590-Target/6980bb3fc680f8b0a9f5b8c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Motilal-Oswal-Lifts-Five-Star-Finance-to-Buy-Eyes-590-Target/6980bb3fc680f8b0a9f5b8c6</guid><description>Motilal Oswal reiterated a 'Buy' rating on Five Star Business Finance, raising the price target to ₹590. The brokerage highlighted the company's 3QFY26 performance, which met expectations with PAT growing 1% YoY and NII up 12% YoY. Motilal Oswal projects a 21% CAGR in AUM and 15% in PAT over FY26-28E, forecasting RoA/RoE of 6.9%/16% by FY28E.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:01:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980bb3fc680f8b0a9f5b8c5_1770044512283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Colgate Turns Around Revenue, But Volume Woes Persist</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Colgate-Turns-Around-Revenue-But-Volume-Woes-Persist/6980ba3dc680f8b0a9f5b3a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Colgate-Turns-Around-Revenue-But-Volume-Woes-Persist/6980ba3dc680f8b0a9f5b3a7</guid><description>Colgate-Palmolive India achieved a 2% year-over-year revenue increase to INR 14.9 billion in Q3 FY26, marking a return to growth after three quarters of decline. This performance, primarily fueled by price adjustments rather than volume expansion, saw toothpaste volumes contract by approximately 2%. Despite these challenges, brokerage Motilal Oswal maintains a 'BUY' rating, citing the stock's 25% correction over the past year and attractive forward valuations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:58:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980ba3dc680f8b0a9f5b3a6_1770044323280.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CONCOR Volumes Soar, But Realization Pressures Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/CONCOR-Volumes-Soar-But-Realization-Pressures-Linger/6980ba65c680f8b0a9f5b4fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/CONCOR-Volumes-Soar-But-Realization-Pressures-Linger/6980ba65c680f8b0a9f5b4fd</guid><description>Container Corporation of India (CONCOR) posted a 4.5% revenue increase to INR 2,307 crore in Q3 FY26, driven by an 11% surge in total volumes to 1.4 million TEUs. However, blended realization per TEU dipped 6% year-on-year, primarily due to a significant 17% decline in domestic segment realization. Despite this margin pressure, a prominent brokerage maintains a 'BUY' rating with a revised target price of INR 580, anticipating strong future growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:57:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980ba65c680f8b0a9f5b4fc_1770044242250.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LT Foods: Analyst Bullish on Growth, Q3 Performance Impresses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LT-Foods-Analyst-Bullish-on-Growth-Q3-Performance-Impresses/6980b973c680f8b0a9f5b117</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/LT-Foods-Analyst-Bullish-on-Growth-Q3-Performance-Impresses/6980b973c680f8b0a9f5b117</guid><description>Motilal Oswal forecasts a 16-20% CAGR for LT Foods from FY25-FY28, maintaining a 'BUY' rating with a INR 500 target. The company reported a 23.5% year-on-year revenue increase in Q3FY26, largely due to a 35% surge in its Basmati and Specialty Rice segment, which saw 15% volume growth. However, Organic and Ready-to-Cook segments experienced a decline.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:54:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b973c680f8b0a9f5b116_1770044087249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Marri Retail Eyes Rs 522 Cr IPO for Retail Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Marri-Retail-Eyes-Rs-522-Cr-IPO-for-Retail-Expansion/6980b955c680f8b0a9f5b01d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Marri-Retail-Eyes-Rs-522-Cr-IPO-for-Retail-Expansion/6980b955c680f8b0a9f5b01d</guid><description>Hyderabad-based Marri Retail has filed preliminary documents for an Initial Public Offering (IPO), aiming to raise Rs 522 crore through a fresh issuance and promoter stake sale. The funds are earmarked for expanding its footprint with 10 new apparel stores and three new jewellery outlets, alongside debt reduction and operational enhancements. The retailer reported Rs 1,301.4 crore in revenue and Rs 84.2 crore in profit for the six months ending September 2025, with apparel and jewellery contributing nearly equally to its top line.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:54:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b955c680f8b0a9f5b01c_1770044077009.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SIAM Forecasts Cautious PV Growth Amidst Economic Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/SIAM-Forecasts-Cautious-PV-Growth-Amidst-Economic-Headwinds/6980b931c680f8b0a9f5af85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/SIAM-Forecasts-Cautious-PV-Growth-Amidst-Economic-Headwinds/6980b931c680f8b0a9f5af85</guid><description>The Society of Indian Automobile Manufacturers (SIAM) anticipates a moderate 5-6% growth in domestic passenger vehicle (PV) sales for both FY26 and FY27, projecting total sales to reach 4.83 million units by FY27. This forecast balances underlying demand drivers like new model launches with significant macroeconomic and geopolitical challenges, including persistent inflation and rising input costs. While Q3 FY26 saw a robust 20.6% surge in PV sales, the industry remains vigilant regarding global uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:50:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b931c680f8b0a9f5af84_1770043840217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharat Wire Ropes Q3 Profit Dives 31% Amidst Rising Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Wire-Ropes-Q3-Profit-Dives-31percent-Amidst-Rising-Costs/6980b82fc680f8b0a9f5acf5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bharat-Wire-Ropes-Q3-Profit-Dives-31percent-Amidst-Rising-Costs/6980b82fc680f8b0a9f5acf5</guid><description>Bharat Wire Ropes reported a 31.1% YoY drop in Q3 net profit to ₹1,024.6 Lakhs, with revenue declining 18% to ₹13,281.80 Lakhs. Increased employee benefit expenses, including ₹188.35 Lakhs from new Labour Codes, alongside higher finance costs and depreciation, impacted quarterly profitability. For nine months, profit saw a marginal 0.56% YoY increase, and EPS improved YoY for both periods.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:47:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b82fc680f8b0a9f5acf4_1770043648233.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Two-Wheeler Market Roars Ahead in January 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Two-Wheeler-Market-Roars-Ahead-in-January-2026/6980b7e0c680f8b0a9f5ab1d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Two-Wheeler-Market-Roars-Ahead-in-January-2026/6980b7e0c680f8b0a9f5ab1d</guid><description>India's two-wheeler sector kicked off 2026 with impressive momentum, as leading manufacturers posted significant year-on-year sales increases in January. Hero MotoCorp and TVS Motor Company spearheaded this growth, with strong performances also reported by Royal Enfield and Suzuki Motorcycle India. Key drivers included resurgent scooter sales, expanding export markets, and a notable uptick in electric vehicle adoption, setting a positive tone for the industry.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b7e0c680f8b0a9f5ab1c_1770043533491.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AB Lifestyle Brands Posts 21% EBITDA Surge, Margin Expansion in Q3</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/AB-Lifestyle-Brands-Posts-21percent-EBITDA-Surge-Margin-Expansion-in-Q3/6980b44cc680f8b0a9f59e48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/AB-Lifestyle-Brands-Posts-21percent-EBITDA-Surge-Margin-Expansion-in-Q3/6980b44cc680f8b0a9f59e48</guid><description>Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Ltd. reported a strong Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 10% YoY to ₹2343 Cr. EBITDA surged 21% YoY to ₹431 Cr, driven by an 180 bps margin expansion to 18.4%. Normalized PAT grew 66% YoY to ₹100 Cr. The nine-month period saw revenue increase 6% YoY to ₹6222 Cr and EBITDA grow 12% YoY to ₹1054 Cr. The company added over 50 net stores and launched a new brand.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b44cc680f8b0a9f59e47_1770043476472.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chalet Hotels Q3 Revenue Zooms 27%; 9-Month Profit Inflated By Tax Adjustments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Chalet-Hotels-Q3-Revenue-Zooms-27percent-9-Month-Profit-Inflated-By-Tax-Adjustments/6980b501c680f8b0a9f5a21e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Chalet-Hotels-Q3-Revenue-Zooms-27percent-9-Month-Profit-Inflated-By-Tax-Adjustments/6980b501c680f8b0a9f5a21e</guid><description>Chalet Hotels reported strong Q3 FY26 operational growth with revenue up 27.07% YoY to ₹5,817 Cr and EBITDA rising 29.0%. PAT grew 28.5%. However, the 9-month PAT surge of 2483% was heavily influenced by significant tax reversals, masking core performance. Consolidated liquidity remains a concern with a current ratio of 0.63, though debt levels improved.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:42:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b501c680f8b0a9f5a21d_1770043366680.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget: Capex Surge Fuels Growth, State Borrowing a Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Capex-Surge-Fuels-Growth-State-Borrowing-a-Concern/6980b594c680f8b0a9f5a42b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Capex-Surge-Fuels-Growth-State-Borrowing-a-Concern/6980b594c680f8b0a9f5a42b</guid><description>The Union Budget FY27 signals a commitment to growth via a substantial increase in capital expenditure, projected at ₹12.2 lakh crore, a 9% rise from the previous year, aiming to drive infrastructure development. While fiscal deficit is targeted at 4.3% of GDP, a slight reduction from 4.4%, and the debt-to-GDP ratio is set to decline to 55.6%, concerns linger regarding the impact of significant state borrowing on GSec yields. The Budget eschews broad tax cuts, emphasizing targeted incentives for high-tech sectors and manufacturing, with an eye on execution efficiency for its ambitious development agenda.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b594c680f8b0a9f5a42a_1770043295233.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Reel on Fed Nomination Shock</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Reel-on-Fed-Nomination-Shock/6980b660c680f8b0a9f5a8ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Reel-on-Fed-Nomination-Shock/6980b660c680f8b0a9f5a8ca</guid><description>Global financial markets experienced a sharp, synchronized downturn as investors reacted to a surprise nomination for the Federal Reserve chairmanship. The event exposed vulnerabilities created by extensive leverage and a concentration of capital in popular trades, leading to cascading liquidations across gold, silver, equities, and cryptocurrencies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:40:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b660c680f8b0a9f5a8c9_1770043189629.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Bets Big on Infrastructure in 2026-27 Budget</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Bets-Big-on-Infrastructure-in-2026-27-Budget/6980b610c680f8b0a9f5a6f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Bets-Big-on-Infrastructure-in-2026-27-Budget/6980b610c680f8b0a9f5a6f1</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 earmarks a record ₹12.2 lakh crore for public capital expenditure, signaling a robust strategy to drive economic growth through infrastructure development and sustainability initiatives. This significant allocation aims to reduce transaction costs, boost productivity, and address climate concerns, positioning India for long-term resilience and competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:40:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b610c680f8b0a9f5a6f0_1770043115444.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India Sales Surge Amidst Margin Squeeze &amp; Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Sales-Surge-Amidst-Margin-Squeeze-and-Competition/6980b5f1c680f8b0a9f5a630</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Sales-Surge-Amidst-Margin-Squeeze-and-Competition/6980b5f1c680f8b0a9f5a630</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India Limited (HMIL) has posted strong sales figures for its Venue and Creta models, with the latter crossing 2 lakh sales in 2025 and the Venue garnering 80,000 bookings. Despite facing margin headwinds from rising input costs and plant ramp-up expenses, HMIL achieved an 8% revenue increase to ₹17,973.5 crore in Q3 FY26 and saw its net profit climb 6.3%. The company remains optimistic, leveraging strong rural demand and export performance, though it navigates increasing competition and an evolving market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:36:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b5f1c680f8b0a9f5a62f_1770043007600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Mfg PMI Rebounds Amidst Faltering Confidence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Mfg-PMI-Rebounds-Amidst-Faltering-Confidence/6980b570c680f8b0a9f5a3a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Mfg-PMI-Rebounds-Amidst-Faltering-Confidence/6980b570c680f8b0a9f5a3a8</guid><description>India's manufacturing Purchasing Managers' Index (PMI) climbed to 55.4 in January, signaling sector expansion fueled by robust new orders, increased output, and hiring. Despite this operational strength, business confidence hit a three-and-a-half-year low, with firms anticipating minimal future growth. Manufacturers grappled with rising input costs, though subdued factory-gate price inflation offered slight margin relief. The domestic market remained the primary sales driver, while export order growth decelerated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b570c680f8b0a9f5a3a7_1770042870241.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exide FY26 Q3 Profit Up 5.2%, Eyes EV Battery Growth Amid ROCE Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Exide-FY26-Q3-Profit-Up-52percent-Eyes-EV-Battery-Growth-Amid-ROCE-Dip/6980b4a8c680f8b0a9f5a098</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Exide-FY26-Q3-Profit-Up-52percent-Eyes-EV-Battery-Growth-Amid-ROCE-Dip/6980b4a8c680f8b0a9f5a098</guid><description>Exide Industries reported a 5.2% YoY rise in Q3 FY26 PAT to ₹258 Cr, on ₹3,812 Cr revenue, up 4.7%. While EBITDA remained stable, a dip in core business ROCE from 11.8% to 7.4% warrants attention. The company highlighted growth drivers including automotive sector recovery, solar targets, and strategic OEM wins, while advancing its lithium-ion battery plant for future EV demand.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b4a8c680f8b0a9f5a097_1770042703897.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Posts Strong Q3 Growth, Margins Expand Significantly</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Aditya-Birla-Lifestyle-Brands-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Margins-Expand-Significantly/6980b481c680f8b0a9f59f9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Aditya-Birla-Lifestyle-Brands-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Margins-Expand-Significantly/6980b481c680f8b0a9f59f9c</guid><description>Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands (ABL) reported strong Q3 FY26 results. Consolidated revenue grew 10% YoY to ₹2343 Cr, while normalized PAT surged 66% YoY to ₹100 Cr. EBITDA climbed 21% to ₹431 Cr, driving EBITDA margins up 180 bps to 18.4%. The Emerging Business segment showed remarkable margin expansion. Over 50 net stores were added.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:31:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b481c680f8b0a9f59f9b_1770042676430.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ather Energy IPO Funds Flowing, Factory Start Delayed 3 Months</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ather-Energy-IPO-Funds-Flowing-Factory-Start-Delayed-3-Months/6980b405c680f8b0a9f59c2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ather-Energy-IPO-Funds-Flowing-Factory-Start-Delayed-3-Months/6980b405c680f8b0a9f59c2c</guid><description>Ather Energy is deploying its IPO funds as planned, utilizing Rs. 813.95 crore by December 31, 2025, for its Maharashtra factory, R&amp;D, and debt repayment. However, the production start for the new facility is delayed to October 2026 from July 2026, attributed to environmental clearance timing. The company holds Rs. 1812.05 crore unutilized in fixed deposits, maintaining prudent treasury management.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:29:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b405c680f8b0a9f59c2b_1770042556437.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PB Fintech Profit Surges 160%; QIP Plan Rattles Stock</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PB-Fintech-Profit-Surges-160percent-QIP-Plan-Rattles-Stock/6980b426c680f8b0a9f59cfc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PB-Fintech-Profit-Surges-160percent-QIP-Plan-Rattles-Stock/6980b426c680f8b0a9f59cfc</guid><description>PB Fintech Ltd. announced a significant financial uplift, with third-quarter net profit soaring 160% year-over-year to Rs 189 crore and revenue climbing 37.1% to Rs 1,771 crore. Despite these robust figures, the company's stock saw a 3.45% decline following the announcement of a potential Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) to raise capital, introducing dilution concerns among investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PG Electroplast Q3: Revenue Surges 46%, Margins Squeeze Amidst Capex Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PG-Electroplast-Q3-Revenue-Surges-46percent-Margins-Squeeze-Amidst-Capex-Push/6980b31bc680f8b0a9f5989d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PG-Electroplast-Q3-Revenue-Surges-46percent-Margins-Squeeze-Amidst-Capex-Push/6980b31bc680f8b0a9f5989d</guid><description>PG Electroplast Limited posted a strong 45.9% YoY revenue growth to ₹1,412.1 crore in Q3 FY2026, driven by its product business. However, EBITDA margins narrowed to 8.9% from 9.5% YoY. For the nine-month period, revenue grew 20.7%, but PAT declined 10.5% YoY. The company plans significant capex of ₹700-750 crore for FY2026, leading to a shift from net cash to net debt.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:26:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b31bc680f8b0a9f5989c_1770042377618.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Surges on Strong Q3 Earnings, Margin Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Aditya-Birla-Lifestyle-Brands-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Earnings-Margin-Expansion/6980b3a1c680f8b0a9f59a60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Aditya-Birla-Lifestyle-Brands-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Earnings-Margin-Expansion/6980b3a1c680f8b0a9f59a60</guid><description>Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Limited (ABLBL) reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue climbing 10% YoY to ₹2343 Cr and EBITDA soaring 21% to ₹431 Cr. EBITDA margins expanded significantly by 180 bps to 18.4%, driven by strong performance in Lifestyle Brands and Emerging Business segments, including a 16% retail LTL growth. The company added over 90 stores in the quarter, signalling continued expansion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NAM India Hits Record Profit, Seals DWS Partnership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NAM-India-Hits-Record-Profit-Seals-DWS-Partnership/6980b38dc680f8b0a9f599ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/NAM-India-Hits-Record-Profit-Seals-DWS-Partnership/6980b38dc680f8b0a9f599ec</guid><description>Nippon Life India Asset Management (NAM India) reported record quarterly operating profit and PAT for Q3 FY26, with revenue up 20% YoY and PAT soaring 37%. The company crossed ₹1 trillion in Gold &amp; Silver ETF AUM and announced a strategic collaboration with DWS Group for its AIF subsidiary. Management targets 15% expense growth, prioritizing specialized product profitability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Corona Remedies Posts 15% Revenue Jump, PAT Surges 23.7% In Q3</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Corona-Remedies-Posts-15percent-Revenue-Jump-PAT-Surges-237percent-In-Q3/6980b163c680f8b0a9f59269</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Corona-Remedies-Posts-15percent-Revenue-Jump-PAT-Surges-237percent-In-Q3/6980b163c680f8b0a9f59269</guid><description>Corona Remedies reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue up 15% YoY to ₹342.42 Cr and PAT soaring 23.7% YoY to ₹55.56 Cr. Nine-month figures also show strong double-digit growth. Management guidance points to sustained 15% revenue and 20% PAT expansion, backed by strategic field force strengthening and brand portfolio growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:24:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980b163c680f8b0a9f59268_1770042136078.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>