<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:49:02 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Reva's IPO: Margin Risk Looms in COCO Store Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Revas-IPO-Margin-Risk-Looms-in-COCO-Store-Shift/699d298b04a25a58c84e775b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Revas-IPO-Margin-Risk-Looms-in-COCO-Store-Shift/699d298b04a25a58c84e775b</guid><description>PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery's upcoming IPO is marked by a strategic shift from a cost-efficient shop-in-shop model to capital-intensive Company-Owned Company-Operated (COCO) stores. This transition, while aimed at brand building, introduces significant economic risks including higher overheads and longer stabilization periods. The company's sharp focus on diamond jewellery, a differentiator, also presents vulnerability due to discretionary demand sensitivity and the escalating threat from lab-grown diamonds, unlike its diversified peers. Valuations appear demanding, pricing in a smooth execution of this operational pivot.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:31:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d298b04a25a58c84e775a_1771908047441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Flair Writing Expands Pencil Output by 84M Units at Subsidiary</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Flair-Writing-Expands-Pencil-Output-by-84M-Units-at-Subsidiary/699d298804a25a58c84e7744</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Flair-Writing-Expands-Pencil-Output-by-84M-Units-at-Subsidiary/699d298804a25a58c84e7744</guid><description>Flair Writing Industries has commenced manufacturing wooden pencils at its subsidiary, Flomaxe Stationery Private Limited in Surat, adding an estimated annual capacity of 84 million pieces. This strategic move bolsters its creative product portfolio and backward integration, aiming to capture a larger share of the substantial wooden pencil market. The facility will also produce complementary items like erasers and sharpeners, enhancing the company's stationery offerings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d298804a25a58c84e7743_1771907566625.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Creative Newtech Partners Kaspersky to Expand India Cybersecurity Offerings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Creative-Newtech-Partners-Kaspersky-to-Expand-India-Cybersecurity-Offerings/699d298804a25a58c84e772e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Creative-Newtech-Partners-Kaspersky-to-Expand-India-Cybersecurity-Offerings/699d298804a25a58c84e772e</guid><description>Creative Newtech Limited has teamed up with global cybersecurity firm Kaspersky to distribute its product suite across North, West, and East India. The move leverages the rapidly expanding Indian cybersecurity market, projected to reach $20.5 billion by 2030, and aims to enhance Creative Newtech's technology solutions portfolio.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d298804a25a58c84e772d_1771907578167.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>D&amp;H India: Indo Thai Securities Ups Stake to 9.43% via Rights Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DandH-India-Indo-Thai-Securities-Ups-Stake-to-943percent-via-Rights-Issue/699d298704a25a58c84e7718</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DandH-India-Indo-Thai-Securities-Ups-Stake-to-943percent-via-Rights-Issue/699d298704a25a58c84e7718</guid><description>Indo Thai Securities Ltd and its Persons Acting in Concert (PACs) have significantly increased their stake in D&amp;H India Ltd to 9.43% by acquiring 8,84,186 equity shares through a recent rights issue. This move surpasses the 5% regulatory disclosure threshold, marking a substantial shift in D&amp;H India's ownership structure and signalling increased investor interest in the industrial fan and blower manufacturer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Markets Plunge: Tariffs, AI Fears Spark Steep Opening Drop</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Plunge-Tariffs-AI-Fears-Spark-Steep-Opening-Drop/699d27cb04a25a58c84e748a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Plunge-Tariffs-AI-Fears-Spark-Steep-Opening-Drop/699d27cb04a25a58c84e748a</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks experienced a sharp downturn Tuesday morning, with the Sensex falling over 500 points and the Nifty down over 140. This selloff was triggered by escalating US tariff uncertainties and growing concerns over artificial intelligence impacting traditional IT services. IT stocks were significant laggards, exacerbating the broader market decline amidst a cautious global outlook.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:23:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d27cb04a25a58c84e7489_1771907518353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Faces Scrutiny After ₹590 Cr Fraud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Faces-Scrutiny-After-590-Cr-Fraud/699d27c804a25a58c84e7473</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Faces-Scrutiny-After-590-Cr-Fraud/699d27c804a25a58c84e7473</guid><description>A ₹590 crore fraud at IDFC First Bank's Chandigarh branch has triggered significant analyst downgrades and target price cuts. While viewed as an operational lapse, the event exposes risks to government deposit stability and could delay margin recovery, impacting the bank's near-term valuation despite confidence in its long-term growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:23:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d27c804a25a58c84e7472_1771907288936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Northern Arc Capital: D2C Surge Meets NBFC Funding Realities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Northern-Arc-Capital-D2C-Surge-Meets-NBFC-Funding-Realities/699d276b04a25a58c84e7384</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Northern-Arc-Capital-D2C-Surge-Meets-NBFC-Funding-Realities/699d276b04a25a58c84e7384</guid><description>Motilal Oswal initiated coverage on Northern Arc Capital with a 'Buy' rating and a ₹360 target, citing a strong shift to Direct-to-Customer (D2C) lending and diversified fee income. The D2C portfolio has surged, now comprising 56% of assets under management, aiming for 70% by FY28. Despite these growth drivers and robust historical asset quality, the company operates within an NBFC sector facing funding access hurdles and elevated credit risk in unsecured segments. Its market capitalization stands around ₹40.5 billion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:22:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d276b04a25a58c84e7383_1771907208739.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Tests 91 Mark Amid Trade Jitters, RBI Support Under Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Tests-91-Mark-Amid-Trade-Jitters-RBI-Support-Under-Scrutiny/699d274b04a25a58c84e7331</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Tests-91-Mark-Amid-Trade-Jitters-RBI-Support-Under-Scrutiny/699d274b04a25a58c84e7331</guid><description>The Indian rupee opened weaker, pressured by global trade policy uncertainty and regional currency weakness. Despite an intraday gain on Monday, importer demand and hedging activities pushed it back, highlighting sustained dollar demand. Traders are closely watching the 91-per-dollar level, a historical point for Reserve Bank of India intervention. The rupee's specific vulnerability at this psychological threshold suggests a reliance on central bank support, potentially masking deeper domestic flow imbalances that could challenge its stability against persistent dollar strength.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:21:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d274b04a25a58c84e7330_1771907170527.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NMP 2.0: Will PSU Asset Sales Fuel Growth or Face Execution Hurdles?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/NMP-20-Will-PSU-Asset-Sales-Fuel-Growth-or-Face-Execution-Hurdles/699d273c04a25a58c84e72fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/NMP-20-Will-PSU-Asset-Sales-Fuel-Growth-or-Face-Execution-Hurdles/699d273c04a25a58c84e72fd</guid><description>The government's National Monetisation Pipeline 2.0 aims to raise ₹16.72 lakh crore by FY30 through PSU asset sales and equity dilution. While building on NMP 1.0's partial success, the plan faces significant execution risks, market volatility, and scrutiny over its impact on core PSU valuations. Key entities like GAIL and Coal India are slated for stake sales, but analyst sentiment and operational challenges present headwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:21:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d273c04a25a58c84e72fc_1771907006564.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Stocks Plummet as AI Fears, Trade Tensions Grip Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-Plummet-as-AI-Fears-Trade-Tensions-Grip-Market/699d270004a25a58c84e7292</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-Plummet-as-AI-Fears-Trade-Tensions-Grip-Market/699d270004a25a58c84e7292</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks tanked Tuesday, led by IT stocks, as AI disruption anxieties and evolving US trade policies fueled a broad sell-off. The Nifty IT Index fell over 3%, with major players like TCS and Infosys experiencing sharp declines. Investors are weighing the existential threat of AI automation against geopolitical trade uncertainties, impacting sector valuations and market sentiment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:20:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d270004a25a58c84e7291_1771906976834.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Stock Rebounds Amid Fraud Probe &amp; Governance Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Stock-Rebounds-Amid-Fraud-Probe-and-Governance-Scrutiny/699d264d04a25a58c84e715e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Stock-Rebounds-Amid-Fraud-Probe-and-Governance-Scrutiny/699d264d04a25a58c84e715e</guid><description>IDFC First Bank shares experienced a modest rebound, trading up approximately 1% on Tuesday after a significant 16% drop on Monday following the disclosure of a Rs 590-crore fraud. The bank emphasized the incident's isolated nature, confined to specific Haryana government accounts at one branch. Management assured investors of sufficient buffers to absorb the impact, which is estimated at around 1% of net worth. Four employees have been suspended, and a forensic audit by KPMG is underway. Despite near-term volatility, the stock has gained 18% over the past year, outperforming the Nifty 50.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:17:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d264d04a25a58c84e715d_1771906744252.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks Plummet on AI Fears, Valuations Tested</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Plummet-on-AI-Fears-Valuations-Tested/699d264a04a25a58c84e7147</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Plummet-on-AI-Fears-Valuations-Tested/699d264a04a25a58c84e7147</guid><description>Indian IT shares experienced a significant sell-off Tuesday, with the Nifty IT index dropping 2.84%, driven by escalating fears of AI-driven disruption to legacy modernization services following Anthropic's new tool claims. Major players like Infosys and TCS saw substantial stock price erosion. While the immediate reaction suggests deep concern, current valuations for some industry leaders appear compressed relative to their strategic AI investments and global peers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:17:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d264a04a25a58c84e7146_1771907113905.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ePlane Taps NVIDIA AI For India's Air Taxi Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ePlane-Taps-NVIDIA-AI-For-Indias-Air-Taxi-Race/699d22ff04a25a58c84e6df1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ePlane-Taps-NVIDIA-AI-For-Indias-Air-Taxi-Race/699d22ff04a25a58c84e6df1</guid><description>The ePlane Company is collaborating with NVIDIA to accelerate the development of its e200x electric air taxi. Leveraging NVIDIA's Omniverse Software, ePlane will create a sophisticated digital twin for advanced simulations and validation. The partnership also aims to integrate NVIDIA's safety-critical computing platforms into the aircraft, enabling real-time autonomous decision-making and predictive maintenance, potentially fast-tracking India's urban air mobility sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:03:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d22ff04a25a58c84e6df0_1771907078378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABB India: Order Boom Meets Valuation Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-India-Order-Boom-Meets-Valuation-Headwinds/699d22fa04a25a58c84e6dda</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-India-Order-Boom-Meets-Valuation-Headwinds/699d22fa04a25a58c84e6dda</guid><description>ABB India reported its highest quarterly order inflows in five years, surging 52% to ₹4,100 crore, prompting JPMorgan to raise its price target to ₹6,001. However, the stock trades at a premium valuation of approximately 72-76 times trailing earnings, raising concerns despite robust demand drivers like data centers and infrastructure. Fourth-quarter profit margins contracted significantly to 15.4% from 19.5% due to cost pressures and provisions, impacting overall profitability despite revenue growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d22fa04a25a58c84e6dd9_1771906093566.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-France Tax Treaty: Dual Impact for French Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-France-Tax-Treaty-Dual-Impact-for-French-Investors/699d20ad04a25a58c84e6b79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-France-Tax-Treaty-Dual-Impact-for-French-Investors/699d20ad04a25a58c84e6b79</guid><description>India and France have overhauled their three-decade-old tax treaty, creating a bifurcated dividend tax structure. French firms with over 10% stake in Indian entities now face a 5% dividend tax, down from 10%. Conversely, minority shareholders will see their tax rate increase from 10% to 15%. India has also broadened its authority to tax capital gains on share sales, irrespective of stake size. The contentious Most Favoured Nation (MFN) clause has been scrapped, aligning with India's push for fiscal sovereignty and stricter tax enforcement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:53:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d20ad04a25a58c84e6b78_1771906199201.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's $62B Forward Book Imperils Reserve Goals Amid Debt Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-62B-Forward-Book-Imperils-Reserve-Goals-Amid-Debt-Surge/699d204604a25a58c84e6a9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-62B-Forward-Book-Imperils-Reserve-Goals-Amid-Debt-Surge/699d204604a25a58c84e6a9c</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's efforts to accumulate foreign exchange reserves face headwinds from a substantial $62 billion short forward book, necessitating dollar purchases. This comes as India plans a record ₹17.2 trillion in sovereign debt issuance for fiscal year 2027, potentially straining bond yields and the rupee. While reserves hit all-time highs, the central bank navigates complex liquidity management and market stability challenges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:51:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d204604a25a58c84e6a9b_1771905469953.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC Navigates Tax Squeeze: Volume vs. Profitability Under Fire</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Navigates-Tax-Squeeze-Volume-vs-Profitability-Under-Fire/699d202d04a25a58c84e6a7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Navigates-Tax-Squeeze-Volume-vs-Profitability-Under-Fire/699d202d04a25a58c84e6a7c</guid><description>ITC's cigarette business is under pressure from significant tax increases effective February 2026. Brokerages like CLSA and Kotak Institutional Equities have adjusted price targets and ratings, citing potential EBIT declines due to the need for steep price hikes that could impact volumes. While the company appears to prioritize market share protection through staggered price increases, heightened competition from players like Godfrey Phillips India is a key concern. Analyst sentiment remains divided, with a mixed outlook for the stock's performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:51:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d202d04a25a58c84e6a7b_1771905208113.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nomura Boosts Indian Ports: Adani's Scale Dominance Challenged?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Nomura-Boosts-Indian-Ports-Adanis-Scale-Dominance-Challenged/699d202a04a25a58c84e6a65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Nomura-Boosts-Indian-Ports-Adanis-Scale-Dominance-Challenged/699d202a04a25a58c84e6a65</guid><description>Nomura initiated coverage on JSW Infrastructure with a 'Buy' rating and target of ₹340, while upgrading Adani Ports &amp; SEZ to 'Buy' with a ₹1,850 target. The brokerage favors Indian private ports for their expansion potential, but market intelligence reveals significant scale disparities. Adani Ports, the sector's dominant player by capacity and market share, contrasts with JSW Infrastructure, which faces a steep climb to match its larger rival's operational footprint. While both companies are set to benefit from India's increasing trade volumes and a modal shift towards waterways, aggressive capacity additions across the sector introduce risks of oversupply and pricing pressure, making execution and competitive positioning critical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:51:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d202a04a25a58c84e6a64_1771905995741.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amber Enterprises: High Growth Priced In Amidst Valuation Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-High-Growth-Priced-In-Amidst-Valuation-Jitters/699d202904a25a58c84e6a4b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Amber-Enterprises-High-Growth-Priced-In-Amidst-Valuation-Jitters/699d202904a25a58c84e6a4b</guid><description>Brokerage firm Geojit Investments has initiated coverage on Amber Enterprises India with a 'Buy' rating and a target price of ₹9,156, projecting a 20% upside. The optimistic outlook is driven by anticipated market share gains in the room air conditioner (RAC) segment and expansion in the high-margin PCB business, supported by backward integration. However, the stock currently trades at a significant one-year forward Price-to-Earnings (P/E) multiple of 55x, nearing its historical high, raising concerns about its already elevated valuation and the execution risks associated with ambitious expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d202904a25a58c84e6a4a_1771905241575.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India C&amp;I Green Power: Cost Savings Fuel Demand Amidst Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-CandI-Green-Power-Cost-Savings-Fuel-Demand-Amidst-Hurdles/699d1f0304a25a58c84e681d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-CandI-Green-Power-Cost-Savings-Fuel-Demand-Amidst-Hurdles/699d1f0304a25a58c84e681d</guid><description>India's commercial and industrial sector is accelerating its shift to green energy, spurred by substantial cost savings from open access and private Power Purchase Agreements (PPAs). Driven by tariff arbitrage, sustainability mandates, and demand from data centers, renewable energy capacity for C&amp;I customers is projected to surge, contributing significantly to India's clean energy goals. However, this rapid expansion faces headwinds from grid infrastructure limitations, inconsistent state-level policy implementation, and potential impacts on utility revenues, posing risks to sustained growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:46:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d1f0304a25a58c84e681c_1771904965379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks: AI Fears Linger Despite CLSA's Optimism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-AI-Fears-Linger-Despite-CLSAs-Optimism/699d1ec704a25a58c84e67d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-AI-Fears-Linger-Despite-CLSAs-Optimism/699d1ec704a25a58c84e67d6</guid><description>Despite CLSA's assessment that AI disruption fears in India's IT sector are overstated, the market remains subdued. Brokerage CLSA has cut price targets across major IT players, including Infosys, TCS, and HCL Tech, citing persistent valuation de-ratings. This reflects broader investor skepticism regarding long-term growth visibility in an environment increasingly shaped by AI's potential to structurally alter business models, increase cyclicality, and compress margins in managed services. The Nifty IT index has seen significant declines in early 2026, indicating that concerns over AI's impact and macroeconomic pressures are currently outweighing positive management commentary.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:45:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d1ec704a25a58c84e67d5_1771905018605.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cement Sector: Volume Rebound Meets Cost Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Sector-Volume-Rebound-Meets-Cost-Headwinds/699d1ec404a25a58c84e67bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Sector-Volume-Rebound-Meets-Cost-Headwinds/699d1ec404a25a58c84e67bf</guid><description>The Indian cement industry posted a 6-7% volume increase in Q3 FY26, driven by construction and infra demand. Despite this, profitability is pressured by soaring energy costs and sequential realisations dips. January saw a 1.5-2% price hike, with further increases planned for February, though companies monitor pet-coke prices. Outlook remains positive for FY27, buoyed by infrastructure capex, yet high valuations for leaders contrast with opportunities in turnaround plays.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:45:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d1ec404a25a58c84e67be_1771905255076.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jane Street Sued Over Terraform Collapse Claims</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jane-Street-Sued-Over-Terraform-Collapse-Claims/699d1d5a04a25a58c84e6655</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jane-Street-Sued-Over-Terraform-Collapse-Claims/699d1d5a04a25a58c84e6655</guid><description>Terraform Labs' liquidation administrator has filed a lawsuit against major trading firm Jane Street Group LLC, alleging the firm used non-public information to front-run trades and profit from the crypto ecosystem's collapse. The suit, filed in Manhattan federal court, seeks damages and names Jane Street co-founder Robert Granieri and employees Bryce Pratt and Michael Huang as defendants. This action follows similar allegations against another trading firm, Jump Trading, and occurs amidst heightened regulatory scrutiny of crypto market practices following multi-billion dollar failures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:39:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d1d5a04a25a58c84e6654_1771904489625.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mphasis: Growth Hopes Clash With AI Disruption Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mphasis-Growth-Hopes-Clash-With-AI-Disruption-Fears/699d1bf704a25a58c84e5f85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mphasis-Growth-Hopes-Clash-With-AI-Disruption-Fears/699d1bf704a25a58c84e5f85</guid><description>Motilal Oswal maintains a positive outlook on Mphasis, forecasting robust revenue and profit growth driven by BFSI resilience and strong TCV wins. However, the firm cautions that artificial intelligence disruption and valuation ceilings may limit immediate stock re-rating. Current market indicators reflect bearish technical momentum and underperformance relative to peers and broader indices, contrasting with the brokerage's long-term 'Buy' rating and Rs 3,400 target price.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:33:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d1bf704a25a58c84e5f84_1771904918262.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Plunges 20% on ₹590 Cr Fraud; Governance Questions Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Plunges-20percent-on-590-Cr-Fraud-Governance-Questions-Emerge/699d196c04a25a58c84e49fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Plunges-20percent-on-590-Cr-Fraud-Governance-Questions-Emerge/699d196c04a25a58c84e49fb</guid><description>IDFC First Bank disclosed a ₹590 crore fraud at its Chandigarh branch, attributing it to employee collusion. While the bank asserts limited balance sheet risk, the market reacted severely with a near 20% stock price decline on high volume. The incident has prompted a forensic audit by KPMG and a suspension of business ties by the Haryana government, prompting renewed scrutiny over the bank's operational integrity and valuation premium.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:22:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d196c04a25a58c84e49fa_1771903821799.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>YES BANK Q3 Profit Surges 55.4% to ₹952 Cr on Strong NII Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/YES-BANK-Q3-Profit-Surges-554percent-to-952-Cr-on-Strong-NII-Growth/699d18e804a25a58c84e490e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/YES-BANK-Q3-Profit-Surges-554percent-to-952-Cr-on-Strong-NII-Growth/699d18e804a25a58c84e490e</guid><description>YES BANK reported a robust Q3FY26, with net profit surging 55.4% year-on-year to ₹952 crore. This strong performance was driven by a 10.9% rise in Net Interest Income and a 14.3% jump in Operating Profit. The bank also demonstrated sustained improvements in asset quality, with GNPA at 1.5%, and robust capital ratios. Strategic initiatives in digital banking and retail segments continue to fuel its growth trajectory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:20:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d18e804a25a58c84e490d_1771903338951.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Sector Cuts: AI Hype Meets De-rating Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Sector-Cuts-AI-Hype-Meets-De-rating-Reality/699d18af04a25a58c84e48bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Sector-Cuts-AI-Hype-Meets-De-rating-Reality/699d18af04a25a58c84e48bf</guid><description>Brokerage firm CLSA has reduced price targets for eight major Indian IT companies, including Infosys, TCS, and Wipro. Despite these adjustments, the firm largely maintains 'outperform' ratings, citing strong AI positioning and positive management commentary. However, a deep dive reveals that while AI's potential is undeniable, persistent sector-wide de-rating and elevated valuations for some mid-caps signal underlying pressures that may overshadow the optimistic outlook. The market is grappling with the conflict between future AI-driven growth and current macroeconomic constraints.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:19:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d18af04a25a58c84e48be_1771904452931.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PayPal Takeover Buzz: Network Value vs. Leadership Chaos</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PayPal-Takeover-Buzz-Network-Value-vs-Leadership-Chaos/699d18a904a25a58c84e48a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PayPal-Takeover-Buzz-Network-Value-vs-Leadership-Chaos/699d18a904a25a58c84e48a5</guid><description>PayPal Holdings is reportedly drawing preliminary takeover interest following a substantial stock price decline, sparking a near 10% intraday surge. The digital payments firm, currently valued around $40.9 billion, is engaging with banks amid unsolicited approaches. This development coincides with a significant leadership transition, as HP CEO Enrique Lores prepares to take the helm on March 1st, inheriting a mandate to navigate competitive pressures and evolving market dynamics, including the disruptive potential of artificial intelligence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:19:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d18a904a25a58c84e48a4_1771903270839.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ETF Pricing Gaps Widen Amidst SEBI Review</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/ETF-Pricing-Gaps-Widen-Amidst-SEBI-Review/699d17cf04a25a58c84e4762</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/ETF-Pricing-Gaps-Widen-Amidst-SEBI-Review/699d17cf04a25a58c84e4762</guid><description>Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) in India, particularly in gold, silver, and international categories, are exhibiting substantial deviations between their market prices and indicative Net Asset Values (iNAVs). This pricing disconnect, driven by robust demand against limited liquidity and regulatory caps, poses risks of investors overpaying or selling at a discount. The Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has initiated a review of the ETF pricing framework, proposing changes to base price determination and price band rationalization to enhance market efficiency and investor protection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d17cf04a25a58c84e4761_1771904231267.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Power Unit Secures 558 MW Tamil Nadu PPA at Rs 5.910/Unit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Unit-Secures-558-MW-Tamil-Nadu-PPA-at-Rs-5910Unit/699d16cb04a25a58c84e4648</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Power-Unit-Secures-558-MW-Tamil-Nadu-PPA-at-Rs-5910Unit/699d16cb04a25a58c84e4648</guid><description>Adani Power's subsidiary, Moxie Power Generation Ltd. (MPGL), has secured a significant win with a Letter of Award (LoA) from Tamil Nadu Power Distribution Corporation Limited (TNPDCL). The agreement is for the supply of 558 MW of power for five years at a tariff of Rs 5.910 per unit, set to begin April 1, 2026. This deal shores up Adani Power's revenue visibility, with over 95% of its operating capacity now tied to medium to long-term contracts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d16cb04a25a58c84e4647_1771902772515.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ORSL Secures Large EPC Contract for 10 TPD CBG Project in Madhya Pradesh</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ORSL-Secures-Large-EPC-Contract-for-10-TPD-CBG-Project-in-Madhya-Pradesh/699d16c904a25a58c84e4632</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ORSL-Secures-Large-EPC-Contract-for-10-TPD-CBG-Project-in-Madhya-Pradesh/699d16c904a25a58c84e4632</guid><description>Organic Recycling Systems Limited (ORSL) has landed a significant large-scale EPC contract from Shreyam Manek Agro Products Pvt. Ltd. for an integrated Compressed Bio-Gas (CBG) and biofertilizer project in Damoh, Madhya Pradesh. This deal, part of ORSL's ambitious ₹500-600 Cr plan for 10 such projects in MP over three years, underscores the company's expanding role in India's renewable energy sector and its engagement in state-led energy transition initiatives.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:11:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d16c904a25a58c84e4631_1771903342038.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Purple Finance Open Offer: ₹970 Cr Bid at ₹55/Share for 26% Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Purple-Finance-Open-Offer-970-Cr-Bid-at-55Share-for-26percent-Stake/699d15d704a25a58c84e4573</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Purple-Finance-Open-Offer-970-Cr-Bid-at-55Share-for-26percent-Stake/699d15d704a25a58c84e4573</guid><description>Allied Commodities Private Limited and Mr. Sandeep Jindal are launching an open offer for Purple Finance Limited, seeking to acquire 26% of its voting capital for approximately ₹970.65 crore at ₹55 per share. The offer, open from April 8 to April 22, 2026, aims for substantial stake and joint control, potentially altering the company's board composition. However, it hinges on Reserve Bank of India (RBI) approval, with potential withdrawal rights for acquirers and no withdrawal option for tendering shareholders.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:07:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d15d704a25a58c84e4572_1771903100923.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Britannia, Smartworks: Margin Gains &amp; Real Estate Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Britannia-Smartworks-Margin-Gains-and-Real-Estate-Surge/699d11e204a25a58c84e42c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Britannia-Smartworks-Margin-Gains-and-Real-Estate-Surge/699d11e204a25a58c84e42c8</guid><description>Britannia Industries reported resilient Q3 FY26 performance, marked by significant gross margin expansion to 43.3% driven by stable commodity prices, offsetting a revenue growth miss. Strategic shifts toward LUPs and digital channels signal future margin accretion. Smartworks Coworking achieved substantial footprint growth to 1.53 crore sq ft and an 86% surge in adjusted EBITDA, benefiting from strong demand in India's flexible workspace market and a focus on enterprise clients. Its robust revenue visibility and attractive valuations underscore its expansion trajectory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:50:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d11e204a25a58c84e42c7_1771901580772.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Mineral Pivot: Pax Silica &amp; Resource Deals Face Geopolitical Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indias-Mineral-Pivot-Pax-Silica-and-Resource-Deals-Face-Geopolitical-Headwinds/699d113d04a25a58c84e40e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indias-Mineral-Pivot-Pax-Silica-and-Resource-Deals-Face-Geopolitical-Headwinds/699d113d04a25a58c84e40e1</guid><description>India's strategic move to join the US-led Pax Silica initiative and secure critical mineral supply chains through agreements with Brazil and others marks a significant geopolitical realignment. While aiming to counter China's overwhelming control over vital resources essential for AI and advanced technologies, this pivot introduces considerable complexities. India faces the dual challenge of high diversification costs and the imperative to transition from a resource holder to a processing powerhouse, all while navigating volatile global markets and potential supply chain vulnerabilities. The nation's ambitious goals are underscored by robust domestic initiatives but remain subject to significant geopolitical and economic headwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:47:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d113d04a25a58c84e40e0_1771902232772.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anthropic Offers $350B Liquidity Amidst AI Market Tumult</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-Offers-350B-Liquidity-Amidst-AI-Market-Tumult/699d113104a25a58c84e40ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-Offers-350B-Liquidity-Amidst-AI-Market-Tumult/699d113104a25a58c84e40ca</guid><description>AI leader Anthropic is enabling current and former employees to sell shares, setting a secondary market valuation at $350 billion. This move comes as the company recently closed a funding round at $380 billion post-money. While offering employee liquidity, the transaction occurs against a backdrop of intense market volatility attributed to AI advancements, which has triggered significant losses across various sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:47:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d113104a25a58c84e40c9_1771901520193.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tax Overhaul: Credit Cards Face New Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Overhaul-Credit-Cards-Face-New-Scrutiny/699d112e04a25a58c84e40b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Overhaul-Credit-Cards-Face-New-Scrutiny/699d112e04a25a58c84e40b3</guid><description>New draft Income-tax Rules, effective April 1, 2026, mandate reporting for non-cash credit card payments over ₹10 lakh annually and cash payments exceeding ₹1 lakh. PAN linkage becomes mandatory for new cards. Employer-paid credit card expenses will be taxed as perquisites unless exclusively for official duties, requiring detailed documentation. This regulatory shift aims to boost financial transparency and align spending with income.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:47:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d112e04a25a58c84e40b2_1771901406166.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Investor Biases Sabotage SIP Returns Amidst Market Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Investor-Biases-Sabotage-SIP-Returns-Amidst-Market-Consolidation/699d112d04a25a58c84e409c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Investor-Biases-Sabotage-SIP-Returns-Amidst-Market-Consolidation/699d112d04a25a58c84e409c</guid><description>Common investor behavioral and planning errors are compromising the effectiveness of Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) in India's consolidating markets. Instead of leveraging rupee-cost averaging, investors often halt SIPs during downturns, misjudge risk, or fail to increase contributions, leading to significant erosion of potential long-term returns. These psychological pitfalls, including herd mentality and loss aversion, are more detrimental than market volatility itself. While SIP inflows remain robust, consistent discipline is key to realizing their intended wealth-building potential.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:47:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d112d04a25a58c84e409b_1771901612798.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fears Tank Cybersecurity Stocks; Deeper Analysis Reveals Enduring Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fears-Tank-Cybersecurity-Stocks-Deeper-Analysis-Reveals-Enduring-Demand/699d112c04a25a58c84e4085</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fears-Tank-Cybersecurity-Stocks-Deeper-Analysis-Reveals-Enduring-Demand/699d112c04a25a58c84e4085</guid><description>Cybersecurity stocks experienced a sharp sell-off, with major players like CrowdStrike and Zscaler dropping up to 11% on February 23, 2026, following Anthropic's launch of a new AI code security tool. Analysts, however, largely view this reaction as panic-driven. Emerging insights indicate that AI, while introducing new threats, is increasingly seen as a catalyst for, rather than a replacement of, essential cybersecurity services, potentially expanding the market significantly.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:47:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d112c04a25a58c84e4084_1771901357025.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MS Cautious on Navin, SRF Amid Price Fears; Analysts Divided</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/MS-Cautious-on-Navin-SRF-Amid-Price-Fears-Analysts-Divided/699d112a04a25a58c84e406e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/MS-Cautious-on-Navin-SRF-Amid-Price-Fears-Analysts-Divided/699d112a04a25a58c84e406e</guid><description>Morgan Stanley reiterated 'Underweight' ratings for Navin Fluorine and SRF, citing R-32 refrigerant price declines of ~25% which could impact earnings by 8-13% per $1/kg margin drop. Refrigerants form a third of earnings. Despite this caution, a strong majority of analysts maintain 'Buy' ratings for both companies, with divergent price targets and valuations. Navin Fluorine, trading at a higher P/E, has significantly outperformed SRF and the sector over the past year. SRF faces segment headwinds despite chemical strength, while Navin Fluorine shows robust recent performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:47:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d112a04a25a58c84e406d_1771901359252.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Navigates Western Demands: Market vs. Alliance Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Navigates-Western-Demands-Market-vs-Alliance-Strategy/699d112804a25a58c84e4057</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Navigates-Western-Demands-Market-vs-Alliance-Strategy/699d112804a25a58c84e4057</guid><description>At the Munich Security Conference, the EU and US revealed divergent strategies for engaging India: the EU seeks market access for trade, while the US prioritizes geopolitical alignment against China. India, however, is adeptly leveraging this competition to maintain its strategic autonomy and enhance its global standing. While the EU targets trade and market penetration, exemplified by its comprehensive free trade agreement, the US focuses on defense and technology partnerships to counterbalance Beijing. This dual approach empowers New Delhi, allowing it to extract concessions while preserving its policy independence, positioning India as a key player shaping the emerging global order.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:47:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d112804a25a58c84e4056_1771901362207.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>