<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:27:06 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Budget 2026: Trade Reforms Boost Logistics Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Budget-2026-Trade-Reforms-Boost-Logistics-Sector/697f196747db7081af62e5e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Budget-2026-Trade-Reforms-Boost-Logistics-Sector/697f196747db7081af62e5e6</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 targets accelerated trade through a year-end rollout of a single-window system for cargo clearance approvals, alongside extending Customs advance decision validity from three to five years. These measures, coupled with duty exemptions on fish caught by Indian vessels, aim to significantly streamline logistics, bolster the maritime sector, and enhance business certainty.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:16:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f196747db7081af62e5e5_1769937369350.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Bond Market Boosted by New Tools</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Bond-Market-Boosted-by-New-Tools/697f16a947db7081af62e2de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Bond-Market-Boosted-by-New-Tools/697f16a947db7081af62e2de</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Budget 2026 proposes significant measures to invigorate India's bond markets. A new market-making framework and the introduction of Total Return Swaps for corporate bonds seek to address persistent liquidity issues. Additionally, substantial incentives are earmarked for municipal bond issuances, aiming to fund urban infrastructure development.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:04:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f16a947db7081af62e2dd_1769936694034.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Health Sector: Pharma, Med Tourism Set for Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Boosts-Health-Sector-Pharma-Med-Tourism-Set-for-Growth/697f15dc8fda2bdba6e254ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Boosts-Health-Sector-Pharma-Med-Tourism-Set-for-Growth/697f15dc8fda2bdba6e254ba</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 prioritizes the healthcare sector with substantial allocations and strategic initiatives. Key announcements include a Rs 10,000 crore 'Biopharma Shakti' program over five years to bolster domestic biologics and biosimilars, the development of five regional medical tourism hubs, and a significant push for Ayurveda through new institutes and upgraded facilities. These measures aim to enhance India's global standing in biopharmaceuticals and medical tourism, while also strengthening traditional medicine practices and the allied health workforce.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f15dc8fda2bdba6e254b9_1769936493240.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Infrastructure Boost, Trading Tax Hike Sparks Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Infrastructure-Boost-Trading-Tax-Hike-Sparks-Market-Volatility/697f15c08fda2bdba6e2543e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Infrastructure-Boost-Trading-Tax-Hike-Sparks-Market-Volatility/697f15c08fda2bdba6e2543e</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman presented India's Union Budget 2025-26 on Sunday, February 1, 2026, prioritizing infrastructure development with a record capital expenditure allocation of ₹11.21 lakh crore, set to rise to ₹12.2 lakh crore for FY27. While the budget offers consumer relief through reduced taxes on overseas travel and education, it significantly increases the Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on equity futures and options trading from 0.02%-0.1% to 0.05%-0.15%, triggering an immediate market sell-off. Fiscal deficit targets remain firm, projected at 4.3% of GDP for FY27, indicating a focus on balancing growth with financial prudence. The new Income Tax Act, 2025, is slated for implementation from April 1, 2026.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f15c08fda2bdba6e2543d_1769936473985.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Capex to Rs 12.2 Lakh Crore for FY27</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Boosts-Capex-to-Rs-122-Lakh-Crore-for-FY27/697f15ac8fda2bdba6e25406</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Boosts-Capex-to-Rs-122-Lakh-Crore-for-FY27/697f15ac8fda2bdba6e25406</guid><description>India's Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced a significant increase in capital expenditure to ₹12.2 lakh crore for FY2026-27, a jump from ₹11.2 lakh crore previously, underscoring a sustained infrastructure-led growth strategy. The budget prioritizes urban development in cities exceeding five lakh population and outlines key initiatives in waterways, rail infrastructure, and private investment mobilization. This push is set against a backdrop of a projected 7.4% GDP growth for the current fiscal year and an inflation target near 2%.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:00:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f15ac8fda2bdba6e25405_1769936423089.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Health Budget: Jobs, Biopharma Boom, and Hubs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Health-Budget-Jobs-Biopharma-Boom-and-Hubs/697f153d8fda2bdba6e252eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Health-Budget-Jobs-Biopharma-Boom-and-Hubs/697f153d8fda2bdba6e252eb</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 unveils a significant healthcare push, allocating ₹10,000 crore over five years to the Biopharma Shakti initiative to bolster domestic manufacturing and research. The budget also champions medical tourism through the development of five regional hubs, aims to train 1 lakh allied health professionals and 1.5 lakh caregivers, and proposes substantial upgrades to traditional medicine infrastructure, including the WHO Global Centre for Traditional Medicine.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:58:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f153d8fda2bdba6e252ea_1769936283972.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Rs 1.7L Cr Fertilizer Subsidy Amid Global Price Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Budget-2026-Rs-17L-Cr-Fertilizer-Subsidy-Amid-Global-Price-Strain/697f152f8fda2bdba6e252b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Budget-2026-Rs-17L-Cr-Fertilizer-Subsidy-Amid-Global-Price-Strain/697f152f8fda2bdba6e252b6</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 earmarks ₹1.7 lakh crore for fertilizer subsidies, a slight increase over the revised estimate for the previous fiscal. This allocation aims to cushion farmers from escalating global input costs driven by geopolitical tensions and supply chain disruptions. The Fertilizer Association of India (FAI) is pressing for policy reforms, including customs duty rationalization and the integration of urea under the nutrient-based subsidy (NBS) framework. Concurrently, a new digital e-bill system is being implemented to streamline subsidy disbursals, signaling a move towards greater operational efficiency.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f152f8fda2bdba6e252b5_1769936273232.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Banks Tank on Budget's Record Borrowing Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Tank-on-Budgets-Record-Borrowing-Surge/697f13018fda2bdba6e25073</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Tank-on-Budgets-Record-Borrowing-Surge/697f13018fda2bdba6e25073</guid><description>Public sector banks across India experienced a significant sell-off on Sunday, February 1, 2026, following Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Union Budget announcement. The government's record ₹17.2 lakh crore gross market borrowing target for fiscal year 2026-2027, substantially exceeding expectations, is driving bond yields higher and expected to inflict Mark-to-Market (MTM) portfolio losses on these lenders. This abrupt reversal follows a strong 2025 rally for the Nifty PSU Bank index.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f13018fda2bdba6e25072_1769935755673.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Boosts IT Sector: Safe Harbour Margin Raised to 15.5%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Budget-2026-Boosts-IT-Sector-Safe-Harbour-Margin-Raised-to-155percent/697f12998fda2bdba6e24f59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Budget-2026-Boosts-IT-Sector-Safe-Harbour-Margin-Raised-to-155percent/697f12998fda2bdba6e24f59</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced sweeping changes to the IT services Safe Harbour regime in Budget 2026. The eligibility threshold surged to ₹2,000 crore from ₹300 crore, and a unified 15.5% margin was set for all IT services. Automated approvals will streamline compliance for a wider range of Indian IT companies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f12998fda2bdba6e24f58_1769935735598.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharat Vistaar: India Launches AI for Farm Decisions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Bharat-Vistaar-India-Launches-AI-for-Farm-Decisions/697f12798fda2bdba6e24ecd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Bharat-Vistaar-India-Launches-AI-for-Farm-Decisions/697f12798fda2bdba6e24ecd</guid><description>The Indian Union Budget 2026 unveiled Bharat Vistaar, an AI-powered initiative designed to revolutionize agricultural decision-making for farmers. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced the platform, which integrates the nation's agri-stack portals and ICAR's agricultural practices with AI systems. Bharat Vistaar aims to provide real-time soil and weather data, expert advice, and streamlined access to government schemes, fostering more sustainable and informed farming operations across India. Early implementations include AI-enabled chatbots assisting thousands of extension workers and incorporating local knowledge to create a dynamic information repository.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:46:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f12798fda2bdba6e24ecc_1769935612236.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Plunge on Budget Tax Hikes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Plunge-on-Budget-Tax-Hikes/697f1099691065341e44a46c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Plunge-on-Budget-Tax-Hikes/697f1099691065341e44a46c</guid><description>Indian equity markets experienced a sharp sell-off on February 1, 2026, following the Union Budget 2026 announcements. The benchmark Sensex plummeted over 1,500 points, and the Nifty 50 fell around 500 points. Key triggers included an increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options, alongside a shift in buyback taxation to capital gains for all shareholders. Market participants reacted negatively to the increased transaction costs and changed tax structure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:44:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f1099691065341e44a46b_1769935116252.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Tax Overhaul: Budget 2026 Simplifies Rules Amid Market Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Tax-Overhaul-Budget-2026-Simplifies-Rules-Amid-Market-Dip/697f107f691065341e44a3ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Tax-Overhaul-Budget-2026-Simplifies-Rules-Amid-Market-Dip/697f107f691065341e44a3ff</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman unveiled the Income Tax Act, 2025, effective April 1, 2026, aiming to cut tax sections by half and ease compliance. The budget also introduced staggered filing deadlines and targeted relief measures. However, immediate market reaction saw indices decline, partly attributed to increased Securities Transaction Tax on derivatives trading.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:38:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f107f691065341e44a3fe_1769935084412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Launches Foreign Asset Amnesty: Compliance Boost Ahead</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Launches-Foreign-Asset-Amnesty-Compliance-Boost-Ahead/697f0f96691065341e44a264</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Launches-Foreign-Asset-Amnesty-Compliance-Boost-Ahead/697f0f96691065341e44a264</guid><description>The Indian government has initiated a six-month foreign asset disclosure scheme, providing a one-time opportunity for taxpayers to regularize undeclared overseas assets. This initiative aims to encourage voluntary compliance by offering reduced penalties and immunity from prosecution. The scheme targets both individuals who have entirely failed to disclose foreign assets and those who have partially complied, offering different tiers of resolution. Experts view this as a pragmatic step to improve data visibility and align India with global transparency standards, potentially enhancing investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:35:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0f96691065341e44a263_1769934909158.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: 80C Limit Static, New Tax Law Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-80C-Limit-Static-New-Tax-Law-Looms/697f0f40691065341e44a19b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-80C-Limit-Static-New-Tax-Law-Looms/697f0f40691065341e44a19b</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 has maintained the status quo on Section 80C, keeping the investment deduction limit at Rs 1.5 lakh. This decision offers continuity but offers no new avenues for tax relief amidst rising living costs. Concurrently, the Income Tax Act, 2025, is slated to take effect from April 1, 2026, promising simplified rules. This fiscal update subtly reinforces the government's direction towards the new tax regime, limiting the appeal of traditional tax-saving instruments for many.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:34:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0f40691065341e44a19a_1769934876338.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Tax Slabs Static, Rebate Boosts New Regime</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Tax-Slabs-Static-Rebate-Boosts-New-Regime/697f0f19691065341e44a117</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Tax-Slabs-Static-Rebate-Boosts-New-Regime/697f0f19691065341e44a117</guid><description>Despite taxpayer expectations for relief, Union Budget 2026 has kept income tax slabs static for FY 2025-26. However, the new tax regime receives a boost with an expanded Section 87A rebate, making income up to ₹12 lakh effectively tax-free, alongside a maintained standard deduction of ₹75,000 for salaried individuals. This policy approach prioritizes fiscal stability and reform over broad-based tax reductions, continuing the shift towards the simplified new tax system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:32:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0f19691065341e44a116_1769934746054.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget Eyes Biopharma Hub; Stocks Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Budget-Eyes-Biopharma-Hub-Stocks-Rise/697ef18d46be08bbe62fca24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Budget-Eyes-Biopharma-Hub-Stocks-Rise/697ef18d46be08bbe62fca24</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Union Budget 2026 announced a ₹10,000 crore "Biopharma Shakti" program over five years, aiming to establish India as a biopharmaceutical manufacturing hub. This strategic allocation spurred immediate gains across the sector, with Biocon Ltd. leading the surge. The move signals robust government backing for advanced pharmaceutical capabilities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:32:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef18d46be08bbe62fca23_1769934599409.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Stocks Surge Ahead of Budget 2026 Amid Geopolitical Alerts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Stocks-Surge-Ahead-of-Budget-2026-Amid-Geopolitical-Alerts/697ef21a46be08bbe62fcae7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Defence-Stocks-Surge-Ahead-of-Budget-2026-Amid-Geopolitical-Alerts/697ef21a46be08bbe62fcae7</guid><description>Investor optimism fueled a significant surge in India's defence sector stocks on Sunday, February 1, 2026, propelling the Nifty India Defence index up by 1.6%. This ascent, occurring in an otherwise subdued market, is largely attributed to expectations of heightened government spending in the upcoming Union Budget 2026-27. Factors such as escalating global geopolitical tensions, a strategic push for force modernization, and the continuation of the indigenisation policy are reinforcing investor confidence in domestic defence manufacturers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef21a46be08bbe62fcae6_1769934589619.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TVS Motor January 2026 Sales Surge 29% on EV, 3W Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-January-2026-Sales-Surge-29percent-on-EV-3W-Boom/697f0e26691065341e449f58</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/TVS-Motor-January-2026-Sales-Surge-29percent-on-EV-3W-Boom/697f0e26691065341e449f58</guid><description>TVS Motor Company posted a robust 29% year-on-year sales increase for January 2026, driven by exceptional demand in its electric vehicle (EV) segment (+50%) and three-wheeler segment (+77%). Two-wheeler sales grew 28%, with domestic demand up 30%. The company's international business also saw a healthy 21% rise compared to January 2025.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:29:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0e26691065341e449f57_1769934544266.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Day Bloodbath: STT Hike Drains Indian Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Day-Bloodbath-STT-Hike-Drains-Indian-Markets/697f0b59691065341e44995f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Day-Bloodbath-STT-Hike-Drains-Indian-Markets/697f0b59691065341e44995f</guid><description>India's major stock indices, Nifty and Sensex, experienced a significant decline, shedding nearly 3% during a special Sunday Budget session. The downturn was primarily triggered by an increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives trading, impacting futures and options segments. Broader market indices also registered losses, with volatility surging over 10%. Defense stocks faced mixed reactions despite an increased capital outlay for the sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:28:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0b59691065341e44995e_1769934412323.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metals Plunge: Profit-Taking, Stronger Dollar Trigger Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metals-Plunge-Profit-Taking-Stronger-Dollar-Trigger-Sell-Off/697ef22e46be08bbe62fcb20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Metals-Plunge-Profit-Taking-Stronger-Dollar-Trigger-Sell-Off/697ef22e46be08bbe62fcb20</guid><description>Gold, silver, and industrial metals are experiencing a significant market correction. This downturn follows a period of historic rallies and is driven by a confluence of economic factors including investor profit-taking, a strengthened U.S. dollar alongside rising real yields, leverage-induced forced selling, and concerns over global economic growth affecting base metals. The CME's increase in margin requirements has further amplified selling pressure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:28:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef22e46be08bbe62fcb1f_1769934472569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget STT Hike Sparks Market Rout; Broker Stocks Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Budget-STT-Hike-Sparks-Market-Rout-Broker-Stocks-Plunge/697f0d3a691065341e449e44</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Budget-STT-Hike-Sparks-Market-Rout-Broker-Stocks-Plunge/697f0d3a691065341e449e44</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 announcements triggered a sharp market downturn, with the Sensex and Nifty plummeting. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's proposals to increase Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on Futures and Options, and to tax buybacks as capital gains, sent shockwaves through the financial sector. Brokerage and exchange stocks bore the brunt, experiencing significant price erosions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:26:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0d3a691065341e449e43_1769934313485.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Tax Reforms Simplify Compliance, Cut TCS</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Tax-Reforms-Simplify-Compliance-Cut-TCS/697f0c49691065341e449c9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Tax-Reforms-Simplify-Compliance-Cut-TCS/697f0c49691065341e449c9b</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 enacts the Income Tax Act, 2025, effective April 1, to simplify tax procedures and compliance. Key measures include reduced Tax Collected at Source (TCS) rates for education, medical remittances, and overseas travel, alongside an extended deadline for revised tax returns to March 31. Interest awarded by Motor Accident Claims Tribunals to individuals is now tax-exempt. While income tax slabs remain unchanged, simplified forms and rule-based tax deductions aim to ease the burden on ordinary taxpayers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:26:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0c49691065341e449c9a_1769934259349.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Union Budget Launches New Gandhi Scheme Amid Name Change Controversy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Union-Budget-Launches-New-Gandhi-Scheme-Amid-Name-Change-Controversy/697f0cbb691065341e449d89</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Union-Budget-Launches-New-Gandhi-Scheme-Amid-Name-Change-Controversy/697f0cbb691065341e449d89</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 introduced the Mahatma Gandhi Gram Swaraj Initiative, focusing on strengthening khadi, handloom, and handicrafts via global market access, branding, and skill development. This comes shortly after the government faced criticism for renaming the Mahatma Gandhi National Rural Employment Guarantee Act (MGNREGA) to the Viksit Bharat-Guarantee for Employment and Livelihood Mission (Rural) Bill. The initiative aims to invigorate rural economies and support artisans.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:23:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0cbb691065341e449d88_1769934188990.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: STT Hike Triggers Market Sell-off, BSE Faces Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-STT-Hike-Triggers-Market-Sell-off-BSE-Faces-Pressure/697f0beb691065341e449b7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-STT-Hike-Triggers-Market-Sell-off-BSE-Faces-Pressure/697f0beb691065341e449b7a</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026, presented on February 1, 2026, unveiled a robust capital expenditure plan and a strategic focus on manufacturing and infrastructure. However, the announcement of a tripling in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures trading triggered an immediate market correction, with benchmark indices and exchange stocks like BSE experiencing significant declines.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:20:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0beb691065341e449b79_1769933981454.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Europe Welcomes Five New Unicorns in January 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Europe-Welcomes-Five-New-Unicorns-in-January-2026/697f0c42691065341e449c68</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Europe-Welcomes-Five-New-Unicorns-in-January-2026/697f0c42691065341e449c68</guid><description>The European startup ecosystem has added five new "unicorns" – companies valued at over $1 billion – in January 2026. These include Belgium-based Aikido Security, Lithuanian-rooted Cast AI, French defense tech firm Harmattan AI, German ESG software provider Osapiens, and Ukrainian-founded edtech marketplace Preply. These funding rounds underscore continued strong venture capital appetite for innovative technology across diverse sectors, despite a generally cautious market.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:19:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0c42691065341e449c67_1769933972318.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026-27 Eyes Growth with Mega Capex Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-27-Eyes-Growth-with-Mega-Capex-Push/697f0b86691065341e449a49</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-27-Eyes-Growth-with-Mega-Capex-Push/697f0b86691065341e449a49</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman presented the Union Budget 2026-27 today, emphasizing 'Atmanirbharta' (self-reliance) and structural reforms. The fiscal plan significantly boosts capital expenditure to ₹12.2 lakh crore and raises the outlay for electronic manufacturing to ₹40,000 crore. Key initiatives include establishing three dedicated chemical parks, strengthening the Semiconductor Mission 2.0, and supporting critical mineral development in key states. The budget aims to accelerate economic growth, enhance productivity, and empower citizens.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0b86691065341e449a48_1769933816918.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Duty Exemptions Spur Manufacturing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Budget-2026-Duty-Exemptions-Spur-Manufacturing/697f0b68691065341e449994</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Budget-2026-Duty-Exemptions-Spur-Manufacturing/697f0b68691065341e449994</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Budget 2026 unveiled significant customs duty exemptions on specified parts for microwave oven manufacturing, aiming to reduce production costs and enhance local value addition. The measures extend to duty-free imports for leather and seafood export inputs, and duty exemptions for capital goods in Battery Energy Storage Systems, solar glass, and aviation components. These fiscal adjustments are positioned within a context of strong economic performance, with India's GDP projected to grow by 7.4% for the fiscal year ending March 31, 2026. The budget also continues exemptions for nuclear power project goods until 2035, signaling strategic long-term energy investments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0b68691065341e449993_1769933835160.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MIC Electronics Wins Contracts, Eyes Infrastructure Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MIC-Electronics-Wins-Contracts-Eyes-Infrastructure-Boom/697ef2f946be08bbe62fcd1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MIC-Electronics-Wins-Contracts-Eyes-Infrastructure-Boom/697ef2f946be08bbe62fcd1f</guid><description>MIC Electronics Ltd has landed significant contract wins, including a Rs 114.10 crore project for Nava Raipur and orders under the Amrit Bharat Scheme. These drive a 668% surge in Q3 FY26 net sales to Rs 90.23 crore, though 9MFY26 net profit experienced a slight dip. The company, a small-cap with a market cap over Rs 1,000 crore, boasts exceptional historical shareholder returns and maintains a substantial promoter stake.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef2f946be08bbe62fcd1e_1769933706744.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's UPI Shatters Records: January Transactions Top ₹28 Trillion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-UPI-Shatters-Records-January-Transactions-Top-28-Trillion/697ef27e46be08bbe62fcc14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-UPI-Shatters-Records-January-Transactions-Top-28-Trillion/697ef27e46be08bbe62fcc14</guid><description>UPI transactions reached a record ₹28.33 trillion and 21.7 billion in volume during January. National Payments Corporation of India data shows a 21% increase from December, highlighting robust growth in India's digital payment ecosystem. Daily transactions averaged 700 million.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef27e46be08bbe62fcc13_1769933702339.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Proposes Capital Gains Tax on Share Buybacks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Proposes-Capital-Gains-Tax-on-Share-Buybacks/697f0a67691065341e4497b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Proposes-Capital-Gains-Tax-on-Share-Buybacks/697f0a67691065341e4497b2</guid><description>The Indian Finance Minister has proposed a significant overhaul of share buyback taxation, mandating that proceeds be taxed as capital gains for all shareholder categories. Under the new framework, corporate promoters will face an effective tax rate of 22%, while non-corporate promoters will be taxed at 30%. This move aims to simplify the tax structure and eliminate previous arbitrage opportunities, potentially reshaping corporate capital allocation strategies and investor returns.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:14:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0a67691065341e4497b1_1769933595147.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paisalo Digital: Debt Overhaul Fuels Stock Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digital-Debt-Overhaul-Fuels-Stock-Surge/697ef31246be08bbe62fcd87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Paisalo-Digital-Debt-Overhaul-Fuels-Stock-Surge/697ef31246be08bbe62fcd87</guid><description>Paisalo Digital Limited has successfully completed the redemption of significant Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) and secured new capital at a reduced cost. This financial recalibration follows a Rs 188.5 crore capital raise at an 8.5% interest rate, aimed at expanding its "High Tech-High Touch" distribution model. The company's stock has responded positively, trading up from its 52-week low, reflecting investor confidence in its debt management and growth strategy.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef31246be08bbe62fcd86_1769933516942.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Pauses: Circuit Breakers Stabilize Amid Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Pauses-Circuit-Breakers-Stabilize-Amid-Volatility/697ef33346be08bbe62fce21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Pauses-Circuit-Breakers-Stabilize-Amid-Volatility/697ef33346be08bbe62fce21</guid><description>Exchanges employ market-wide circuit breakers to manage extreme price swings, temporarily halting trading to allow for reassessment and prevent panic. Activated by significant declines in benchmark indices like the S&amp;P 500, these pauses aim to restore order and facilitate informed decision-making. This mechanism is particularly relevant in the current uncertain economic environment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:10:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef33346be08bbe62fce20_1769933433414.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Tax Overhaul, Relief for Accident Victims; Markets Volatile</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Tax-Overhaul-Relief-for-Accident-Victims-Markets-Volatile/697f09ee691065341e449713</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Tax-Overhaul-Relief-for-Accident-Victims-Markets-Volatile/697f09ee691065341e449713</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 ushers in the Income Tax Act 2025, set to take effect April 1, 2026, aiming for simpler compliance and reduced litigation. Significant relief is provided to accident victims with full tax exemption on tribunal-awarded interest. Tax Collected at Source (TCS) on foreign remittances for travel, education, and medical needs has been reduced to 2%. The deadline for revising income tax returns is extended to March 31. While tax slabs remain largely unchanged under the new regime, a rebate ensures effective tax-free income up to Rs 12.75 lakh for salaried individuals. However, market volatility ensued, partly due to an increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT).</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:10:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f09ee691065341e449712_1769933424627.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Sports Sector with Decade-Long Khelo India Mission</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Boosts-Sports-Sector-with-Decade-Long-Khelo-India-Mission/697f0973691065341e449616</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Boosts-Sports-Sector-with-Decade-Long-Khelo-India-Mission/697f0973691065341e449616</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced a significant expansion of the Khelo India program in Budget 2026, launching a decade-long mission to overhaul India's sports ecosystem. The initiative aims to move beyond talent identification to foster integrated development pathways, enhance coaching, and leverage sports science. Simultaneously, a dedicated program will bolster domestic sports goods manufacturing, positioning India as a global hub for quality equipment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:08:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0973691065341e449615_1769933280215.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Eicher Motors January Sales Jump 14%, YTD Growth Hits 25% on Strong Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Eicher-Motors-January-Sales-Jump-14percent-YTD-Growth-Hits-25percent-on-Strong-Demand/697ef37146be08bbe62fced4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Eicher-Motors-January-Sales-Jump-14percent-YTD-Growth-Hits-25percent-on-Strong-Demand/697ef37146be08bbe62fced4</guid><description>Eicher Motors posted a robust 14% YoY increase in January sales, selling 1,04,322 motorcycles. Year-to-date, the company achieved a significant 25% growth, surpassing 1 million units globally. Domestic sales climbed 16% in January, while exports saw a 30% YTD surge. Performance is driven by &lt;350cc models, with new product launches and innovative marketing collaborations bolstering the outlook.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:07:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef37146be08bbe62fced3_1769933274210.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC Bank Caps Infinia Card Redemptions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-Bank-Caps-Infinia-Card-Redemptions/697ef3e546be08bbe62fcfb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-Bank-Caps-Infinia-Card-Redemptions/697ef3e546be08bbe62fcfb2</guid><description>HDFC Bank has implemented new monthly redemption limits for its Infinia metal credit cardholders, effective February 1, 2026. Cardholders can now redeem reward points a maximum of five times per month. This move follows earlier reports of tighter restrictions and aims to control the value extracted from the loyalty program, while the earning structure remains unchanged.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:06:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef3e546be08bbe62fcfb1_1769933176933.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Foreign Investment Caps to Lure Global Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Boosts-Foreign-Investment-Caps-to-Lure-Global-Capital/697f0830691065341e449491</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Boosts-Foreign-Investment-Caps-to-Lure-Global-Capital/697f0830691065341e449491</guid><description>India's government is set to significantly increase equity investment limits for non-residents, aiming to attract global capital and deepen market liquidity. The proposed changes allow individuals residing outside India to hold up to 10% equity in listed companies, with an aggregate limit for all such investors raised to 24%. This policy shift is expected to benefit key sectors including manufacturing, infrastructure, financial services, and consumption.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0830691065341e449490_1769932963828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Chip Mission: Dixon, Syrma Stocks Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Boosts-Chip-Mission-Dixon-Syrma-Stocks-Surge/697ef45e46be08bbe62fd077</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Boosts-Chip-Mission-Dixon-Syrma-Stocks-Surge/697ef45e46be08bbe62fd077</guid><description>The Indian government significantly amplified its commitment to domestic chip manufacturing by announcing 'India Semiconductor Mission 2.0' with a Rs 40,000 crore outlay in the Union Budget 2026. This move, aimed at bolstering industry-led research and training, immediately saw shares of key electronics manufacturing players Dixon Technologies and Syrma SGS Technology jump over 4% in intraday trading. The increased allocation signals a strong governmental push for self-reliance in the critical technology sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:05:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ef45e46be08bbe62fd076_1769933141141.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Electronics: Budget 2026 Eyes Global Supply Chains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Boosts-Electronics-Budget-2026-Eyes-Global-Supply-Chains/697f0811691065341e44940d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Boosts-Electronics-Budget-2026-Eyes-Global-Supply-Chains/697f0811691065341e44940d</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026, presented on February 1, 2026, signals a robust policy shift towards integrated electronics manufacturing. Key initiatives include the launch of India Semiconductor Mission (ISM) 2.0 and a substantial increase in the Electronics Components Manufacturing Scheme (ECMS) outlay to ₹40,000 crore. These measures aim to deepen domestic value addition, fortify supply chains, and position India as a significant player in the global electronics ecosystem. The announcements saw an immediate positive response in electronics stocks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:03:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f0811691065341e44940c_1769932979766.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Textile Stocks Rally on Budget, EU FTA Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Textile-Stocks-Rally-on-Budget-EU-FTA-Hopes/697f07a1691065341e449312</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Textile-Stocks-Rally-on-Budget-EU-FTA-Hopes/697f07a1691065341e449312</guid><description>Textile sector shares experienced a significant intraday surge on Sunday, February 1, 2026, driven by Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Budget 2026 proposals for the sector and the finalization of a Free Trade Agreement with the European Union. The budget outlined an integrated textile program and mega textile parks, while the FTA promises zero import tariffs into the EU, addressing past market share losses and competitive disadvantages. This news propelled stocks like Kitex Garments, Trident, and KPR Mill higher, though many equities remain below their 52-week peaks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:02:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f07a1691065341e449311_1769932862792.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>