<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:55:22 +0000</pubDate><item><title>PSU Banks: FPIs' Contrarian Bet Amidst Broader Indian Equity Exodus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-FPIs-Contrarian-Bet-Amidst-Broader-Indian-Equity-Exodus/69970308d25eafd9cd00a8fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-FPIs-Contrarian-Bet-Amidst-Broader-Indian-Equity-Exodus/69970308d25eafd9cd00a8fb</guid><description>Foreign portfolio investors are strategically pivoting towards Indian public sector banks (PSUs), accumulating stakes despite a broader exit from Indian equities totaling $19 billion in 2025. This divergence is fueled by attractive relative valuations and improving growth prospects within the PSU banking segment. Several PSU banks, including Union Bank of India and Indian Bank, have recently hit new 52-week highs, signaling strong performance that contrasts with overall FPI sentiment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:33:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69970308d25eafd9cd00a8fa_1771504710569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Owl Fund Freeze Sparks Private Credit Systemic Risk Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Blue-Owl-Fund-Freeze-Sparks-Private-Credit-Systemic-Risk-Fears/69970306d25eafd9cd00a8e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Blue-Owl-Fund-Freeze-Sparks-Private-Credit-Systemic-Risk-Fears/69970306d25eafd9cd00a8e4</guid><description>Asset manager Blue Owl Capital has permanently restricted redemptions from a retail-focused private debt fund, prompting economist Mohamed El-Erian to signal potential systemic stress akin to pre-2008 crises. This move shines a spotlight on the inherent liquidity challenges within the rapidly expanding private credit sector, particularly its increasing accessibility to individual investors. Concerns mount over opaque valuations and the 'market for lemons' dynamic, suggesting a looming significant valuation correction for certain assets as liquidity tightens across the globe. The incident underscores regulatory scrutiny of private market accessibility for retail participants.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:33:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69970306d25eafd9cd00a8e3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Omnitech IPO: Size Cut, Financial Volatility Raise Investor Eyebrows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Omnitech-IPO-Size-Cut-Financial-Volatility-Raise-Investor-Eyebrows/69970303d25eafd9cd00a8cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Omnitech-IPO-Size-Cut-Financial-Volatility-Raise-Investor-Eyebrows/69970303d25eafd9cd00a8cd</guid><description>Omnitech Engineering is launching a Rs 583 crore Initial Public Offering (IPO) on February 25, a significant reduction from its initial Rs 850 crore plan. The company, grappling with inconsistent financial performance and carrying Rs 382.9 crore in debt, aims to fund new manufacturing facilities and debt repayment. Investor scrutiny will center on valuation, growth sustainability, and the management's ability to navigate market volatility against a backdrop of cautious capital markets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:33:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69970303d25eafd9cd00a8cc_1771504522673.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Nippon Electricals Posts Strong Sales, Profit Growth; Eyes EV Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Nippon-Electricals-Posts-Strong-Sales-Profit-Growth-Eyes-EV-Expansion/6997021cd25eafd9cd00a7a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Nippon-Electricals-Posts-Strong-Sales-Profit-Growth-Eyes-EV-Expansion/6997021cd25eafd9cd00a7a2</guid><description>India Nippon Electricals Limited (INEL) reported a strong Q3 FY26 with revenue jumping 26.6% year-on-year to ₹2,718 million and net profit soaring 55.6% to ₹249 million. Despite a dip in EBITDA margins, PAT margins improved significantly. The company also highlighted its strategic move into Electric Vehicle (EV) components and a new technical partnership with Borg Warner for Electronic Fuel Injection (EFI ECU) control units, signaling a clear focus on future growth areas.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:29:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997021cd25eafd9cd00a7a1_1771504307165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HCLTech's AI Pivot: IP Focus Meets Valuation Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTechs-AI-Pivot-IP-Focus-Meets-Valuation-Headwinds/69970129d25eafd9cd00a5c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HCLTechs-AI-Pivot-IP-Focus-Meets-Valuation-Headwinds/69970129d25eafd9cd00a5c5</guid><description>HCL Technologies Chairperson Roshni Nadar Malhotra advocates for India's tech sector to transition from a scale-driven model to one centered on intellectual property and intelligence, driven by AI. HCLTech aims to lead this shift by building domestic capabilities and focusing on IP ownership, an 'asset-light' strategy in AI services. Despite recent outperformance, the company faces premium valuations and mixed analyst sentiment, with several downgrades to 'Hold' reflecting concerns over technical indicators and execution risks in a rapidly evolving AI landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:25:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69970129d25eafd9cd00a5c4_1771504115627.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nilekani's AI Diffusion Vision Meets Reality: Hurdles Emerge for India's Tech Leadership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nilekanis-AI-Diffusion-Vision-Meets-Reality-Hurdles-Emerge-for-Indias-Tech-Leadership/699700e6d25eafd9cd00a54c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nilekanis-AI-Diffusion-Vision-Meets-Reality-Hurdles-Emerge-for-Indias-Tech-Leadership/699700e6d25eafd9cd00a54c</guid><description>Infosys Chairman Nandan Nilekani envisions India leading global AI diffusion, leveraging its digital public infrastructure (DPI) experience. However, achieving this vision faces significant headwinds. A critical 'diffusion gap' persists between advanced AI capabilities and widespread societal adoption, exacerbated by India's shortage of skilled AI professionals, data privacy concerns, and increasing market concentration in AI infrastructure. While companies like Infosys are investing heavily, and the Indian government backs the IndiaAI Mission, translating potential into tangible, inclusive benefits remains a complex execution challenge. Analysts offer a mixed outlook, with 'Hold' ratings predominating, reflecting cautious optimism alongside scrutiny of margin pressures and the pace of real-world AI impact.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:24:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699700e6d25eafd9cd00a54b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Statiq's $18M Boost: India EV Charging Focus Shifts to Profitability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Statiqs-18M-Boost-India-EV-Charging-Focus-Shifts-to-Profitability/699700e3d25eafd9cd00a535</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Statiqs-18M-Boost-India-EV-Charging-Focus-Shifts-to-Profitability/699700e3d25eafd9cd00a535</guid><description>Statiq secured $18 million in a blended equity-debt round led by Tenacity Ventures, marking a potential turning point for India's EV infrastructure sector after a funding drought. The capital infusion will accelerate Statiq’s expansion of its full-stack charging network, with a strong emphasis on unit economics and operational reliability, crucial factors for investor confidence in the current market. This move indicates a sector-wide demand for profitable, scalable EV charging solutions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:24:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699700e3d25eafd9cd00a534.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra Midcap Fund's Sustained Alpha: Strategy &amp; Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Mahindra-Midcap-Funds-Sustained-Alpha-Strategy-and-Risks/699700c5d25eafd9cd00a4b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Mahindra-Midcap-Funds-Sustained-Alpha-Strategy-and-Risks/699700c5d25eafd9cd00a4b9</guid><description>Mahindra Manulife Mid Cap Fund has achieved an 8-year XIRR of 22.3%, exceeding the Nifty Midcap 150 TRI's 21.1% and demonstrating superior performance across multiple timeframes. The fund's strategy, focusing on sectors like financial services, has yielded results with lower volatility than its benchmark. This success occurs as midcap funds see a substantial rise in investor assets, now representing 13% of total equity AUM, highlighting a significant market trend and the fund's position within it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:23:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699700c5d25eafd9cd00a4b8_1771504018618.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PFC-REC Merger: Powerhouse Formation Meets Integration Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PFC-REC-Merger-Powerhouse-Formation-Meets-Integration-Scrutiny/699700b7d25eafd9cd00a49e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PFC-REC-Merger-Powerhouse-Formation-Meets-Integration-Scrutiny/699700b7d25eafd9cd00a49e</guid><description>A high-level committee has been formed to oversee the merger of PFC and REC, intended to create a ₹11.5 lakh crore financing behemoth crucial for large-scale power and digital infrastructure projects, including AI data centers. This strategic consolidation, following board approvals and budget proposals, aims to enhance capital deployment and streamline sector financing. However, the process will involve detailed operational integration and faces scrutiny due to the mixed historical outcomes of previous public sector bank mergers and performance disparities between PFC and REC.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:23:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699700b7d25eafd9cd00a49d_1771503912026.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Info Edge Beats Estimates: Recruitment Surges, Dividend Hiked Amid AI Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Info-Edge-Beats-Estimates-Recruitment-Surges-Dividend-Hiked-Amid-AI-Challenges/699700aed25eafd9cd00a485</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Info-Edge-Beats-Estimates-Recruitment-Surges-Dividend-Hiked-Amid-AI-Challenges/699700aed25eafd9cd00a485</guid><description>Info Edge (India) Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26, with revenue climbing 14% year-on-year to ₹765 crores and operating profits up 13% to ₹297 crores, driven by its dominant recruitment business. The company also announced a significant increase in its dividend payout ratio to up to 65% of PAT. However, challenges persist in the education segment due to AI impact and continued operating losses in real estate. Management outlined strategies to leverage AI across its platforms and expand its blue-collar jobs venture, JobHai.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:23:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699700aed25eafd9cd00a484_1771503925459.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alicon Castalloy Revenue Up 10%, Profit Falls QoQ Amid Global Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Alicon-Castalloy-Revenue-Up-10percent-Profit-Falls-QoQ-Amid-Global-Woes/699700a8d25eafd9cd00a46f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Alicon-Castalloy-Revenue-Up-10percent-Profit-Falls-QoQ-Amid-Global-Woes/699700a8d25eafd9cd00a46f</guid><description>Alicon Castalloy reported a 10% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹430 crore in Q3 FY26. However, sequential profit after tax (PAT) fell sharply by 76% to ₹3.3 crore due to higher employee costs, succession expenses, and operational issues, including a cybersecurity incident at a key customer and losses in its European entity. The company maintained a robust order book of ₹9,100 crore and sees potential in new orders, including for an eAxle housing from a German OEM.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:23:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699700a8d25eafd9cd00a46e_1771503934046.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABB India's Orders Soar 52%, But Profits Dip on High Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-Indias-Orders-Soar-52percent-But-Profits-Dip-on-High-Costs/6996fff7d25eafd9cd00a34e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-Indias-Orders-Soar-52percent-But-Profits-Dip-on-High-Costs/6996fff7d25eafd9cd00a34e</guid><description>ABB India reported stellar order growth of 52% year-on-year in Q4 CY2025, hitting a five-year high, and achieved record full-year orders and revenues for CY2025. However, profitability faced headwinds, with Profit After Tax (PAT) declining 18.4% in Q4 and 11.0% for the full year due to rising material and labor costs. The company announced a dividend of ₹29.59 per share, signaling confidence despite margin pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:20:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996fff7d25eafd9cd00a34d_1771503740792.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Winzo Faces ED Freeze Over Alleged Algorithmic Fraud in Gaming</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Winzo-Faces-ED-Freeze-Over-Alleged-Algorithmic-Fraud-in-Gaming/6996fff6d25eafd9cd00a338</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Winzo-Faces-ED-Freeze-Over-Alleged-Algorithmic-Fraud-in-Gaming/6996fff6d25eafd9cd00a338</guid><description>The Enforcement Directorate (ED) has provisionally attached $55.69 million (approximately ₹505 crore) in overseas bank accounts held by Winzo's entities in the US and Singapore. This action is part of a money laundering probe alleging that the real-money gaming platform systematically defrauded users by employing AI-driven bots and limiting fund withdrawals. The total proceeds of crime are estimated at ₹3,522.05 crore, with over ₹1,194 crore now attached or frozen. These developments occur as India enacts stringent regulations banning real-money gaming.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:20:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996fff6d25eafd9cd00a337_1771503764574.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Prudential Faces ₹984 Cr Tax Demand, Plans Appeal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Prudential-Faces-984-Cr-Tax-Demand-Plans-Appeal/6996ff09d25eafd9cd00a24d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Prudential-Faces-984-Cr-Tax-Demand-Plans-Appeal/6996ff09d25eafd9cd00a24d</guid><description>ICICI Prudential Life Insurance is facing a massive ₹984.13 crore tax demand, including a ₹492.06 crore penalty, from CGST authorities for the period July 2017 to July 2022. While the company maintains there's 'no impact at this stage' and plans to appeal the unfavorable order, this significant liability raises concerns about future profitability and operational costs for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:16:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996ff09d25eafd9cd00a24c_1771503512956.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apollo Infratech Profits Plummet 45% on Industry Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apollo-Infratech-Profits-Plummet-45percent-on-Industry-Headwinds/6996ff06d25eafd9cd00a237</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Apollo-Infratech-Profits-Plummet-45percent-on-Industry-Headwinds/6996ff06d25eafd9cd00a237</guid><description>Apollo Infratech reported a challenging Q3 FY26, with revenue falling 21% YoY to ₹434 crore and adjusted EBITDA plummeting 45% to ₹48 crore. Margins compressed by over 500 basis points, hit by higher production costs, a shift in product mix away from profitable items, and one-time marketing expenses. Despite near-term industry headwinds and customer cash flow issues, the company sees long-term potential driven by government infrastructure spending.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:16:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996ff06d25eafd9cd00a236_1771503482243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UltraTech Cement's Top Rating Affirmed on Strong Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UltraTech-Cements-Top-Rating-Affirmed-on-Strong-Growth/6996fe92d25eafd9cd00a19f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UltraTech-Cements-Top-Rating-Affirmed-on-Strong-Growth/6996fe92d25eafd9cd00a19f</guid><description>India Ratings has affirmed UltraTech Cement's highest credit rating ('IND AAA/Stable'), citing strong business leadership and healthy financials. The company reported a significant 19% year-on-year revenue growth in 9MFY26, driven by capacity expansion and strategic acquisitions. Management remains focused on cost efficiencies and market consolidation, with a stable outlook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:14:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996fe92d25eafd9cd00a19e_1771503353877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Scores Top Global Sustainability Ranking Amid Governance Worries</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Hindustan-Zinc-Scores-Top-Global-Sustainability-Ranking-Amid-Governance-Worries/6996fe1bd25eafd9cd00a137</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Hindustan-Zinc-Scores-Top-Global-Sustainability-Ranking-Amid-Governance-Worries/6996fe1bd25eafd9cd00a137</guid><description>Hindustan Zinc Limited (HZL) has achieved a significant feat, securing a place in the Top 1% globally in the S&amp;P Global Sustainability Yearbook 2026 for the Metals &amp; Mining industry. This marks its ninth year of inclusion and third consecutive year in the elite top percentile, highlighting strong environmental, social, and governance (ESG) practices. The company is pushing for 70% renewable energy by FY28 and Net Zero emissions by 2050. However, this recognition comes amidst ongoing concerns regarding substantial brand fee payments to its promoter Vedanta Limited and recent regulatory penalties, raising questions about corporate governance. The company's financial performance in FY25 remained robust, with revenue up 18% and profit up 33% year-on-year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:12:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996fe1bd25eafd9cd00a136_1771503259214.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors to Meet Investors, Discuss Future Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-to-Meet-Investors-Discuss-Future-Strategy/6996fd2bd25eafd9cd00a06b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-to-Meet-Investors-Discuss-Future-Strategy/6996fd2bd25eafd9cd00a06b</guid><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Limited has scheduled physical group meetings with analysts and institutional investors for February 24 and February 26, 2026. These engagements are key opportunities for the company to share its strategic direction, discuss future growth drivers, and provide an outlook on its performance in the dynamic Indian automotive market, especially its burgeoning electric vehicle segment. The meetings signal proactive communication with the investment community.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:08:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996fd2bd25eafd9cd00a06a_1771503088029.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Breakout Stocks Defy Market Sell-off Amid Geopolitical Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Breakout-Stocks-Defy-Market-Sell-off-Amid-Geopolitical-Jitters/6996fcbcd25eafd9cd009fe4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Breakout-Stocks-Defy-Market-Sell-off-Amid-Geopolitical-Jitters/6996fcbcd25eafd9cd009fe4</guid><description>Indian equity markets reversed early gains on February 19, 2026, succumbing to broad-based selling pressure and wiping out over ₹4 lakh crore in investor wealth. The Nifty 50 fell 1.41% and the Sensex 1.48%. Despite the downturn, select stocks exhibited strong price-volume breakouts, indicating resilience and independent momentum. Newgen Software Technologies surged over 13%, Tata Investment Corporation gained over 6%, and Oil India rose more than 5%, showcasing pockets of strength against prevailing market headwinds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:06:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996fcbcd25eafd9cd009fe3_1771502939078.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Constronics Infra Promoter Pledges Shares Amidst Regulatory Disclosure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Constronics-Infra-Promoter-Pledges-Shares-Amidst-Regulatory-Disclosure/6996fcabd25eafd9cd009fcd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Constronics-Infra-Promoter-Pledges-Shares-Amidst-Regulatory-Disclosure/6996fcabd25eafd9cd009fcd</guid><description>Constronics Infra Limited announced that its promoter, Mr. Vishnu Vardhan, has pledged 1,319,748 equity shares on February 17, 2026. This transaction, disclosed to the BSE on February 19, 2026, falls under SEBI's (Securities and Exchange Board of India) PIT (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations. While the specific reason for the pledge was not detailed, such actions can signal a promoter's need for liquidity or financial leverage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:06:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996fcabd25eafd9cd009fcc_1771502910569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan buys US firm, revenue jumps 31%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-buys-US-firm-revenue-jumps-31percent/6996fb80d25eafd9cd009e77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-buys-US-firm-revenue-jumps-31percent/6996fb80d25eafd9cd009e77</guid><description>Anupam Rasayan India Limited reported a strong Q3 FY26 with a 31% year-on-year revenue jump to ₹512 crore. The company also announced a significant strategic move to acquire US-based specialty chemicals firm Jayhawk Fine Chemicals, aiming for immediate EPS accretion and enhanced global presence. Management highlighted robust growth drivers from pipeline molecules and expanding portfolios.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:01:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996fb80d25eafd9cd009e76_1771502598364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Home Loans: Tenure Creep Exposes Hidden Interest Burden</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/India-Home-Loans-Tenure-Creep-Exposes-Hidden-Interest-Burden/6996fb51d25eafd9cd009e0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/India-Home-Loans-Tenure-Creep-Exposes-Hidden-Interest-Burden/6996fb51d25eafd9cd009e0b</guid><description>Indian banks increasingly extend home loan tenures instead of raising EMIs when interest rates climb, a practice that significantly inflates total repayment costs over the loan's extended life. While this avoids immediate monthly financial strain, borrowers often overlook the compounded interest from additional years. Proactive monitoring and strategic prepayments are crucial for borrowers to mitigate this "silent squeeze" and avoid prolonged debt burdens. The Reserve Bank of India's (RBI) monetary policy directly influences these cycles, with recent rate cuts in 2025 offering a potential window for optimization before future hikes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:00:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996fb51d25eafd9cd009e0a_1771502556474.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Texmaco Rail, RVNL Forge JV for Mega Rail Solutions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Texmaco-Rail-RVNL-Forge-JV-for-Mega-Rail-Solutions/6996fb11d25eafd9cd009dad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Texmaco-Rail-RVNL-Forge-JV-for-Mega-Rail-Solutions/6996fb11d25eafd9cd009dad</guid><description>Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering and Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL) have formed a strategic joint venture. This partnership combines Texmaco's manufacturing scale with RVNL's project execution expertise to deliver advanced rail solutions, rolling stock, and infrastructure projects for India and the world. The venture aims to boost 'Aatmanirbhar Bharat' and position India as a global rail hub.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:59:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996fb11d25eafd9cd009dac_1771502501631.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Ignites Critical Minerals Race: Magnet Production Set to Launch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Ignites-Critical-Minerals-Race-Magnet-Production-Set-to-Launch/6996fb09d25eafd9cd009d96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Ignites-Critical-Minerals-Race-Magnet-Production-Set-to-Launch/6996fb09d25eafd9cd009d96</guid><description>India is poised to commence domestic permanent magnet production by year-end, a significant move to bolster self-reliance in critical minerals. Supported by substantial government outlays for manufacturing and exploration, this initiative positions India to reduce import dependence and vie for a stronger global market presence. Four states have been identified for critical mineral processing units, alongside the establishment of Centers of Excellence to drive innovation and skill development. The national mission aims to strengthen the entire value chain from exploration to advanced processing, seeking to convert resource potential into strategic advantage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:59:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996fb09d25eafd9cd009d95_1771502546452.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Globe Civil Projects Posts Strong Q3 Growth, But Debt Soars.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Globe-Civil-Projects-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-But-Debt-Soars/6996faa1d25eafd9cd009d14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Globe-Civil-Projects-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-But-Debt-Soars/6996faa1d25eafd9cd009d14</guid><description>Globe Civil Projects Limited reported a strong financial performance for Q3 and the full fiscal year 2025. Revenue and profit saw significant year-on-year growth. However, the company's balance sheet reveals a sharp increase in borrowings and a substantial drop in cash reserves, signalling potential financial strain despite a growing order book and strategic expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:57:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996faa1d25eafd9cd009d13.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bhatia Retail Posts Strong Growth, Expands Stores, Stays Debt-Free</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bhatia-Retail-Posts-Strong-Growth-Expands-Stores-Stays-Debt-Free/6996f8b1d25eafd9cd009bcd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bhatia-Retail-Posts-Strong-Growth-Expands-Stores-Stays-Debt-Free/6996f8b1d25eafd9cd009bcd</guid><description>Bhatia Communications &amp; Retail (India) Limited announced impressive financial results for Q3 FY26, reporting a 38% year-on-year revenue jump to ₹176.12 Cr and a 37% rise in net profit to ₹4.91 Cr. Diluted Earnings Per Share (EPS) climbed 44% to ₹0.36. The company highlighted its expanding store network, now at 291 locations, and a strong, debt-free balance sheet with positive cash flow, signaling robust operational performance and strategic growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f8b1d25eafd9cd009bcc_1771501883390.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sudarshan Chemical Acquisition Loss, Eyes Q4 Comeback</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Sudarshan-Chemical-Acquisition-Loss-Eyes-Q4-Comeback/6996f8afd25eafd9cd009bb7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Sudarshan-Chemical-Acquisition-Loss-Eyes-Q4-Comeback/6996f8afd25eafd9cd009bb7</guid><description>Sudarshan Chemical Industries saw its Q3 FY26 performance hit by a INR 38 Crore EBITDA loss in its acquired Heubach business, driven by global demand slowdown and customer destocking. The company is now focusing on reducing inventory to improve cash flow, with management expecting a recovery in Q4 FY26.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:49:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f8afd25eafd9cd009bb6_1771501891941.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tilaknagar Industries Soars on Imperial Blue Deal, Eyes Profit Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Tilaknagar-Industries-Soars-on-Imperial-Blue-Deal-Eyes-Profit-Boost/6996f7c0d25eafd9cd009b1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Tilaknagar-Industries-Soars-on-Imperial-Blue-Deal-Eyes-Profit-Boost/6996f7c0d25eafd9cd009b1f</guid><description>Tilaknagar Industries (TI) reported a massive 90.5% year-on-year revenue jump in Q3 FY26, reaching ₹664 crore, driven by its recent acquisition of the Imperial Blue (IB) business. The company aims to significantly boost IB's margins and expand its own consolidated profitability over the next 2-3 years. Despite strong growth and ambitious targets for debt reduction, TI faces challenges from Telangana receivables and the impact of Maharashtra's new liquor policy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f7c0d25eafd9cd009b1e_1771501610361.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pace Digitek Bags Rs 89 Cr Railtel Order for Coach Surveillance System</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pace-Digitek-Bags-Rs-89-Cr-Railtel-Order-for-Coach-Surveillance-System/6996f5e3d25eafd9cd0099f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pace-Digitek-Bags-Rs-89-Cr-Railtel-Order-for-Coach-Surveillance-System/6996f5e3d25eafd9cd0099f0</guid><description>Pace Digitek Limited has received an advance letter of award from RailTel Corporation of India for a Rs 890.69 million (approx. ₹89 crore) project. The contract involves installing IP-based video surveillance systems in LHB coaches, including a three-year warranty and a five-year maintenance contract. This marks a significant win for the company, which is set to execute the project within eight months.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:37:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f5e3d25eafd9cd0099ef_1771501194524.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RPP Infra Projects: Large Orders, Margin Squeeze Fear</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RPP-Infra-Projects-Large-Orders-Margin-Squeeze-Fear/6996f5e1d25eafd9cd0099da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RPP-Infra-Projects-Large-Orders-Margin-Squeeze-Fear/6996f5e1d25eafd9cd0099da</guid><description>RPP Infra Projects has won a substantial ₹52.17 crore domestic work order from Tamil Nadu's Water Resources Department for flood mitigation, bolstering its order book to approximately ₹3,964 crore. Despite the influx of new business, the company faces scrutiny over its profitability, evidenced by a sharp decline in net profit in Q3 FY26, and an operating margin that has hit an eight-quarter low. The stock trades at a P/E of 10x, below the industry average of 17x, suggesting market caution regarding execution capabilities and potential margin pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:37:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f5e1d25eafd9cd0099d9_1771501164071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sunrakshakk Transforms: FMCG Pivot Fuels Massive Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sunrakshakk-Transforms-FMCG-Pivot-Fuels-Massive-Revenue-Surge/6996f582d25eafd9cd00994d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Sunrakshakk-Transforms-FMCG-Pivot-Fuels-Massive-Revenue-Surge/6996f582d25eafd9cd00994d</guid><description>Sunrakshakk Industries, formerly A.K. Spintex, has reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with revenue jumping 517% year-on-year to ₹164 Crores. This massive growth is powered by its strategic shift from textiles to an FMCG-led manufacturing model, with FMCG now making up 82% of its business. While overall EBITDA margins saw a minor dip, the company has ambitious plans to reach ₹1000 Crores in revenue by FY28, supported by recent funding and capacity expansions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:35:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f582d25eafd9cd00994c_1771501078900.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Disrupts IT Valuations, Banking Sees Cautious Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Disrupts-IT-Valuations-Banking-Sees-Cautious-Growth/6996f4f7d25eafd9cd0098ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Disrupts-IT-Valuations-Banking-Sees-Cautious-Growth/6996f4f7d25eafd9cd0098ce</guid><description>Artificial intelligence is creating a complex duality for the IT sector, driving increased technology spending while simultaneously pressuring valuations due to potential disruption of traditional service models. Companies must carefully navigate this shift to identify future winners. In banking, credit growth appears robust, though partially fueled by a shift from bond markets, necessitating a closer look at underlying demand. Foreign investor sentiment remains a key concern, tethered to global economic dynamics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:33:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6996f4f7d25eafd9cd0098cd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Sons Seeks Chairman Extension Amid TCS AI Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Sons-Seeks-Chairman-Extension-Amid-TCS-AI-Pivot/6996f40fd25eafd9cd00981e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Sons-Seeks-Chairman-Extension-Amid-TCS-AI-Pivot/6996f40fd25eafd9cd00981e</guid><description>Tata Sons is seeking shareholder approval for N Chandrasekaran's reappointment as executive chairman, a move requiring a policy exception, to ensure leadership continuity for the group's ambitious $120 billion capital expenditure plans. Concurrently, Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) will present its artificial intelligence strategy to the board, addressing market concerns over tech stock volatility and evolving AI-driven business models. This strategic balancing act occurs against a backdrop of mixed financial performance, highlighting the group's dual focus on stable governance and future technological adaptation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:29:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f40fd25eafd9cd00981d_1771500702252.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Retirees Face Yield Dilemma: YES Bank Tops FD Rates Amidst Market Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Retirees-Face-Yield-Dilemma-YES-Bank-Tops-FD-Rates-Amidst-Market-Caution/6996f32bd25eafd9cd009723</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Retirees-Face-Yield-Dilemma-YES-Bank-Tops-FD-Rates-Amidst-Market-Caution/6996f32bd25eafd9cd009723</guid><description>Fixed deposit interest rates for senior citizens have declined following RBI rate cuts, though YES Bank is currently offering a leading 7.75%. This spread highlights a significant gap compared to other private banks like HDFC (up to 6.95%) and ICICI (up to 7.10%). However, YES Bank's attractive deposit yield is juxtaposed against its high Price-to-Earnings ratio (around 21.0-21.4, significantly above the sector average of 10.69) and predominantly 'Sell' analyst ratings, signaling a strategic risk for depositors. The current environment, marked by a high credit-to-deposit ratio and evolving deposit composition, necessitates careful evaluation of safety, liquidity, and return beyond headline rates, particularly given the ₹5 lakh insurance limit per bank.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:25:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f32bd25eafd9cd009722_1771500465547.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JioHotstar Bets on AI Chatbots to Conquer India's Streaming Fatigue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/JioHotstar-Bets-on-AI-Chatbots-to-Conquer-Indias-Streaming-Fatigue/6996f2d8d25eafd9cd00969b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/JioHotstar-Bets-on-AI-Chatbots-to-Conquer-Indias-Streaming-Fatigue/6996f2d8d25eafd9cd00969b</guid><description>JioHotstar is deploying OpenAI's ChatGPT to combat content discovery fatigue, a critical move for retention and engagement in India's maturing streaming market. The partnership integrates conversational AI for personalized recommendations, aiming to unlock deeper user interaction beyond passive consumption and drive monetization. This strategy aligns with broader industry shifts towards 'intelligence' over sheer content volume.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:24:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f2d8d25eafd9cd00969a_1771500376077.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ester Industries Eyes Growth with Key Re-appointments, Big Deals Up For Vote</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Ester-Industries-Eyes-Growth-with-Key-Re-appointments-Big-Deals-Up-For-Vote/6996f2b3d25eafd9cd009623</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Ester-Industries-Eyes-Growth-with-Key-Re-appointments-Big-Deals-Up-For-Vote/6996f2b3d25eafd9cd009623</guid><description>Ester Industries Limited is asking shareholders to approve the reappointment of its Managing Director, Mr. Arvind Singhania, for another three years. The company also needs approval for significant business deals with its joint venture, Ester Loop Infinite Technologies Private Limited (ELITe), worth up to ₹1,463 Crores. Guarantees from its holding company and promoter, totalling ₹760 Crores, are also on the ballot. This comes as the company reported a net loss in FY24 but has shown a strong recovery in FY25.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:23:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f2b3d25eafd9cd009622_1771500320874.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hinduja Global Solutions: Mixed Results, AI Push, and Tax Evasion Storm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hinduja-Global-Solutions-Mixed-Results-AI-Push-and-Tax-Evasion-Storm/6996f2afd25eafd9cd00960d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hinduja-Global-Solutions-Mixed-Results-AI-Push-and-Tax-Evasion-Storm/6996f2afd25eafd9cd00960d</guid><description>Hinduja Global Solutions (HGS) posted a modest 1.1% YoY revenue growth to ₹1,075.4 Cr in Q3 FY2026, but its continuing operations reported a significant loss before tax. A gain from discontinued operations turned the total Profit After Tax (PAT) positive. Amidst this, the company faces serious allegations of ₹2,500 crore tax evasion. HGS is transforming into an AI-led digital operations company, prioritizing margin expansion and adding new logos, while competitors show stronger growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:23:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f2afd25eafd9cd00960c_1771500328594.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sidh Automobiles MD, CFO Quit Abruptly, Sparking Leadership Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sidh-Automobiles-MD-CFO-Quit-Abruptly-Sparking-Leadership-Fears/6996f234d25eafd9cd0094f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sidh-Automobiles-MD-CFO-Quit-Abruptly-Sparking-Leadership-Fears/6996f234d25eafd9cd0094f5</guid><description>Sidh Automobiles Limited has announced the sudden resignations of its Managing Director, Mr. Anil Sharma, and Chief Financial Officer, Mr. Jignesh Keshav Barot, both effective February 19, 2026. The company cited personal and unavoidable circumstances for these departures. This simultaneous exit of two key leaders raises concerns about leadership stability within the Non-Banking Financial Company (NBFC), especially following a recent period of financial losses and revenue decline.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:21:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f234d25eafd9cd0094f4_1771500183457.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fortis Promoter Boosts Japan Lawsuit vs Daiichi Sankyo</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Fortis-Promoter-Boosts-Japan-Lawsuit-vs-Daiichi-Sankyo/6996f224d25eafd9cd0094c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Fortis-Promoter-Boosts-Japan-Lawsuit-vs-Daiichi-Sankyo/6996f224d25eafd9cd0094c2</guid><description>Fortis Healthcare's promoter, Northern TK Venture Pte Ltd (NTK), has filed an updated claim against Japan's Daiichi Sankyo Company Limited in the Tokyo District Court. This amendment specifically targets blocking actions by Daiichi Sankyo that could hinder NTK's acquisition activities and corporate exercises related to Fortis Healthcare and Malar Hospitals. NTK is pursuing claims totaling over INR 109 billion for tortious damages and defamation, underscoring the significant financial and strategic implications of this ongoing legal battle.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:21:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f224d25eafd9cd0094c1_1771500199970.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cosmo First Sales Jump 28%, But Margins Face Import Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Cosmo-First-Sales-Jump-28percent-But-Margins-Face-Import-Pressure/6996f1aad25eafd9cd0093ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Cosmo-First-Sales-Jump-28percent-But-Margins-Face-Import-Pressure/6996f1aad25eafd9cd0093ea</guid><description>Cosmo First Limited reported a strong 28% year-on-year sales increase to ₹899 Crores for Q3 FY26, driven by higher volumes. However, EBITDA saw a modest 19% rise to ₹103 Crores, impacted by lower margins in core BOPP and BOPET film businesses due to increased imports, US tariffs, and inventory losses. The company is now focusing on scaling its specialty chemical and consumer businesses, utilizing recent capex, and reducing its net debt of ₹1,215 Crores.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:19:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6996f1aad25eafd9cd0093e9_1771500101127.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>