<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:59:06 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Sterlite Tech's Rally Masks Profitability Void Amidst Growth Hype</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Sterlite-Techs-Rally-Masks-Profitability-Void-Amidst-Growth-Hype/699bf61aee97f501b0eb3377</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Sterlite-Techs-Rally-Masks-Profitability-Void-Amidst-Growth-Hype/699bf61aee97f501b0eb3377</guid><description>Sterlite Technologies (STL) shares have surged, reaching multi-year highs on robust demand signals from FTTx, 5G, and data center buildouts. The company boasts a healthy order book of over ₹5,300 crore. However, this rally unfolds against a backdrop of negative trailing twelve-month profitability, negative returns on equity, and a significantly lower market capitalization compared to global peers like Corning and Prysmian. While recent US tariff adjustments offer some clarity, they contributed to Q3 FY26 EBITDA margin compression to 10.3%. Analysts remain divided, with some forecasting significant downside despite the current momentum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:39:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf61aee97f501b0eb3376_1771828870901.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Inc. Faces Heightened Risk: Fraud, GST Scrutiny, and AI Disruption</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Inc-Faces-Heightened-Risk-Fraud-GST-Scrutiny-and-AI-Disruption/699bf5caee97f501b0eb32e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Inc-Faces-Heightened-Risk-Fraud-GST-Scrutiny-and-AI-Disruption/699bf5caee97f501b0eb32e7</guid><description>A surge in regulatory scrutiny and operational risks is reshaping India Inc. IDFC First Bank disclosed a significant ₹590 crore fraud, triggering government business cessation and a sharp stock decline. The Goods and Services Tax (GST) regime is enforcing stricter compliance with severe penalties, including asset freezes and arrests. Meanwhile, the IT sector faces structural challenges from AI, leading to downgrades and valuation concerns, though defense stocks show resilience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:38:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf5caee97f501b0eb32e6_1771828870481.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariffs Evolving: Markets Brace for Policy Ambiguity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Tariffs-Evolving-Markets-Brace-for-Policy-Ambiguity/699bf5b3ee97f501b0eb327f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Tariffs-Evolving-Markets-Brace-for-Policy-Ambiguity/699bf5b3ee97f501b0eb327f</guid><description>Recent US legal rulings have fundamentally altered the approach to trade tariffs, moving away from unilateral "tweet-driven" impositions towards more institutionalized, investigatory processes. While this moderates the risk of sudden, sweeping duties, it introduces a new layer of complexity and sustained uncertainty for global exporters and currency markets. The US dollar faces structural headwinds amid evolving trade dynamics and uncertain fiscal outlooks, prompting caution despite a generally positive outlook for emerging market currencies in 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:37:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf5b3ee97f501b0eb327e_1771828840520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HAL Shares Tumble 4% as IAF Grounds Tejas Fighter Fleet</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HAL-Shares-Tumble-4percent-as-IAF-Grounds-Tejas-Fighter-Fleet/699bf595ee97f501b0eb3248</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HAL-Shares-Tumble-4percent-as-IAF-Grounds-Tejas-Fighter-Fleet/699bf595ee97f501b0eb3248</guid><description>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd. (HAL) shares dropped as much as 4% on Monday after the Indian Air Force reportedly grounded its fleet of around 30 Tejas fighter jets. The grounding follows a recent runway incident involving a Tejas LCA, prompting extensive technical scrutiny. This event adds to existing investor concerns, following recent stock declines related to the AMCA project and analyst downgrades.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:37:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf595ee97f501b0eb3247_1771828831870.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Insurers Brace for 5-Year Moratorium Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurers-Brace-for-5-Year-Moratorium-Shift/699bf53dee97f501b0eb312e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurers-Brace-for-5-Year-Moratorium-Shift/699bf53dee97f501b0eb312e</guid><description>India's Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority (IRDAI) has mandated a reduction in the health insurance moratorium period from eight years to five. This pivotal change shields policyholders from claim repudiation due to non-disclosure of pre-existing conditions after 60 months of continuous coverage, barring fraud. The move shifts insurer focus from retrospective claim disputes to prospective risk assessment and underwriting, impacting profitability and operational strategies across the sector. Major players like SBI Life, HDFC Life, and ICICI Lombard face evolving risk landscapes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:35:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf53dee97f501b0eb312d_1771828855252.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Clean Max IPO: High Growth, High Price?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Clean-Max-IPO-High-Growth-High-Price/699bf537ee97f501b0eb3116</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Clean-Max-IPO-High-Growth-High-Price/699bf537ee97f501b0eb3116</guid><description>Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions, India's largest C&amp;I renewable energy provider, launched its ₹3,100 crore IPO on February 23, 2026. Despite strong operational capacity (2.8 GW operational, 3.17 GW contracted) and a recent return to profitability in FY25, the IPO is priced at a premium. Valuations are steep, with reported P/E multiples exceeding 600x and EV/EBITDA around 16x, prompting mixed analyst views. While Anand Rathi suggests a long-term "Subscribe" rating, the high valuation and significant leverage (net debt ₹5,938 crore in FY25) present risks that may temper listing gains. The company's focus on the rapidly expanding C&amp;I renewable segment, particularly data centers and AI infrastructure, offers substantial growth potential, but investors must weigh this against current pricing and debt levels.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:35:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf537ee97f501b0eb3115_1771828636846.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPL Plunges 15% on Restructuring; Leverage Fears Dominate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/UPL-Plunges-15percent-on-Restructuring-Leverage-Fears-Dominate/699bf535ee97f501b0eb30ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/UPL-Plunges-15percent-on-Restructuring-Leverage-Fears-Dominate/699bf535ee97f501b0eb30ff</guid><description>UPL Ltd. shares plummeted by as much as 15% following the announcement of a significant group restructuring aimed at creating a pure-play crop protection entity. Investors are raising alarms over the company's substantial debt load and potential for shareholder dilution, concerns that analysts suggest are not adequately addressed by the proposed changes. Despite the strategic rationale for simplification, the market's reaction points to persistent anxieties regarding financial leverage and execution risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:35:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf535ee97f501b0eb30fe_1771828700322.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lenskart Valuation Debate: Growth vs. Stretched Multiples</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Lenskart-Valuation-Debate-Growth-vs-Stretched-Multiples/699bf52fee97f501b0eb30e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Lenskart-Valuation-Debate-Growth-vs-Stretched-Multiples/699bf52fee97f501b0eb30e6</guid><description>Lenskart Solutions reported a near 70x surge in Q3 FY26 net profit and robust revenue growth, prompting an initiation of coverage with a BUY rating and INR 600 target price. However, its market capitalization and premium valuation multiples are under scrutiny when compared to peers and considering significant operational and regulatory risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:35:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf52fee97f501b0eb30e5_1771828656673.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bombay HC Lifts Stay on Anil Ambani Actions; Banks Can Pursue Fraud Claims</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Bombay-HC-Lifts-Stay-on-Anil-Ambani-Actions-Banks-Can-Pursue-Fraud-Claims/699bf439ee97f501b0eb2fa6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Bombay-HC-Lifts-Stay-on-Anil-Ambani-Actions-Banks-Can-Pursue-Fraud-Claims/699bf439ee97f501b0eb2fa6</guid><description>The Bombay High Court's division bench has set aside a prior interim order, permitting banks and auditor BDO India LLP to proceed with actions against Anil Ambani under the RBI's 2024 Master Directions on fraud classification. This ruling, which branded the single judge's decision as "perverse," clears a significant legal hurdle for lenders, enabling them to pursue alleged financial irregularities based on a 2020 forensic audit report. The reversal potentially intensifies financial pressure on Ambani's group entities, which have a history of substantial debt and insolvency proceedings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:31:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf439ee97f501b0eb2fa5_1771828453809.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TIL Limited Announces ₹200 Cr Rights Issue and Tulip Compression Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TIL-Limited-Announces-200-Cr-Rights-Issue-and-Tulip-Compression-Acquisition/699bf431ee97f501b0eb2f8b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TIL-Limited-Announces-200-Cr-Rights-Issue-and-Tulip-Compression-Acquisition/699bf431ee97f501b0eb2f8b</guid><description>TIL Limited's Board has approved a significant strategic move, planning to raise up to ₹200 crore via a rights issue. Concurrently, the company will acquire a 60% stake in Tulip Compression Private Limited (TCPL) for ₹119.01 crore. This acquisition aims to bolster TIL's presence in the growing CNG, LNG, and Hydrogen infrastructure sector, leveraging TCPL's expertise and TIL's manufacturing capabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:31:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf431ee97f501b0eb2f8a_1771828456706.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Threat Looms: Indian IT Faces Valuation Reckoning</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Threat-Looms-Indian-IT-Faces-Valuation-Reckoning/699bf33fee97f501b0eb2e22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Threat-Looms-Indian-IT-Faces-Valuation-Reckoning/699bf33fee97f501b0eb2e22</guid><description>Jefferies has sounded a stark warning for India's IT sector, flagging Artificial Intelligence as a significant structural disruptor that could reshape business models. The brokerage noted that Indian IT stocks trade at a substantial premium to global peers like Accenture, despite exhibiting lower earnings growth. This valuation disconnect, coupled with AI's potential to shrink managed services revenue (a key segment), has led to earnings estimate cuts and price target reductions across major players. Analysts project a potential further derating of 30-65% if growth falters, highlighting the sector's ongoing challenges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:27:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf33fee97f501b0eb2e21_1771828152502.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Surges Amid Tariff Fears; Volatility Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-Amid-Tariff-Fears-Volatility-Looms/699bf33aee97f501b0eb2e0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-Amid-Tariff-Fears-Volatility-Looms/699bf33aee97f501b0eb2e0b</guid><description>Silver experienced a significant price surge on February 23, 2026, driven by heightened global tariff disputes and renewed geopolitical uncertainties, bolstering its safe-haven appeal. A weakening U.S. dollar further supported this upward momentum. Analysts forecast continued volatility, with MCX Silver March prices expected to fluctuate, influenced by Federal Reserve monetary policy expectations and robust industrial demand, though risks of sharp corrections remain prominent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:27:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf33aee97f501b0eb2e0a_1771828212429.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Prices Surge Amid Geopolitical Fire and Fed Policy Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Surge-Amid-Geopolitical-Fire-and-Fed-Policy-Uncertainty/699bf1dbee97f501b0eb2c7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Surge-Amid-Geopolitical-Fire-and-Fed-Policy-Uncertainty/699bf1dbee97f501b0eb2c7c</guid><description>Gold prices remain elevated, buoyed by persistent geopolitical risks in the Middle East and strong structural demand, particularly evident in the tight physical silver market. However, a divergence in Federal Reserve policy outlook—with some officials signaling potential rate hikes alongside expectations for cuts—introduces significant volatility. This complex interplay between high-stakes diplomacy and shifting monetary policy signals has led to sharp price swings, with analysts maintaining bullish long-term outlooks despite near-term uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:21:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf1dbee97f501b0eb2c7b_1771827836872.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Split: Banks Surge as Nifty Stalls Amid Tariff Ruling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Split-Banks-Surge-as-Nifty-Stalls-Amid-Tariff-Ruling/699bf1daee97f501b0eb2c65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Split-Banks-Surge-as-Nifty-Stalls-Amid-Tariff-Ruling/699bf1daee97f501b0eb2c65</guid><description>The Indian equity market is experiencing a pronounced bifurcation. The benchmark Nifty index is locked in a tight trading band, indicating indecision, while the Bank Nifty continues its ascent, outperforming broader indices and reaching multi-year highs against Nifty. This divergence occurs as global markets react positively to a Supreme Court ruling on Trumpera tariffs, potentially catalyzing a breakout from Nifty's consolidation. Stock recommendations like KEI Industries and Punjab National Bank highlight this sector-specific strength, with PNB leading a resurgent PSU banking sector. KEI Industries trades with a P/E of approximately 48x, while PNB has a P/E of 19x, reflecting sector-specific valuations and momentum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:21:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf1daee97f501b0eb2c64_1771827838140.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Defense Tech Surge: Valuations Soar Amidst Tech Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Defense-Tech-Surge-Valuations-Soar-Amidst-Tech-Shift/699bf164ee97f501b0eb2bb8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Defense-Tech-Surge-Valuations-Soar-Amidst-Tech-Shift/699bf164ee97f501b0eb2bb8</guid><description>India's defense sector is rapidly transitioning from traditional hardware to technology-intensive solutions, focusing on embedded systems, AI, and digital engineering. This shift is powering significant revenue growth and strategic market positioning for companies like Avantel, Cyient, AXISCADES, and Apollo Micro Systems. However, the sector's accelerated growth is accompanied by elevated valuations, with P/E ratios for many players significantly exceeding broader market averages, raising scrutiny over sustainability and execution risks in this policy-driven market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:19:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf164ee97f501b0eb2bb7_1771827675007.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dixon Tech: Geopolitics Aids JVs, Chip Costs Challenge OEM Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Tech-Geopolitics-Aids-JVs-Chip-Costs-Challenge-OEM-Margins/699bf15dee97f501b0eb2ba1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Tech-Geopolitics-Aids-JVs-Chip-Costs-Challenge-OEM-Margins/699bf15dee97f501b0eb2ba1</guid><description>Dixon Technologies is caught between conflicting market dynamics. JPMorgan maintains an 'overweight' stance, targeting ₹13,700, anticipating growth from eased Chinese equipment import rules benefiting joint ventures like Longcheer and HKC, projecting a 43% earnings CAGR. Conversely, Morgan Stanley reiterates an 'underweight' rating, citing severe headwinds from a dramatic surge in memory chip costs, particularly DRAM, which is expected to compress margins in Dixon's high-concentration low-to-mid tier smartphone OEM segment. The company's substantial market capitalization of approximately ₹65,000 crore and a P/E ratio around 60x suggest high investor expectations for seamless execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:19:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bf15dee97f501b0eb2ba0_1771827692252.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GAMCO Shareholders Greenlight Complify Trade Amalgamation with 99.99% Vote</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GAMCO-Shareholders-Greenlight-Complify-Trade-Amalgamation-with-9999percent-Vote/699befefee97f501b0eb2ab9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GAMCO-Shareholders-Greenlight-Complify-Trade-Amalgamation-with-9999percent-Vote/699befefee97f501b0eb2ab9</guid><description>GAMCO Limited shareholders overwhelmingly approved the amalgamation of Complify Trade Pvt. Ltd. at an EOGM on February 20, 2026. The resolution passed with a remarkable 99.99% of votes in favour, signaling strong shareholder confidence in the company's strategic consolidation move. This approval paves the way for Complify Trade to merge with GAMCO, aiming to streamline operations and achieve potential synergies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:13:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699befefee97f501b0eb2ab8_1771827289192.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lincoln Pharma Q3 FY26 Profit Surges 38% to ₹28.6 Cr; Revenue Up 13.5%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lincoln-Pharma-Q3-FY26-Profit-Surges-38percent-to-286-Cr-Revenue-Up-135percent/699bef01ee97f501b0eb29de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lincoln-Pharma-Q3-FY26-Profit-Surges-38percent-to-286-Cr-Revenue-Up-135percent/699bef01ee97f501b0eb29de</guid><description>Lincoln Pharmaceuticals reported a strong Q3 FY26 with net profit jumping 37.7% year-on-year to ₹28.60 crore, fueled by a 13.49% rise in revenue to ₹166.32 crore. The company is strategically expanding into niche therapeutic areas and regulated international markets, supported by increased R&amp;D investments and the commencement of its Cepha block facility. Despite a dip in 9-month EPS, the results underscore the company's growth momentum and focus on higher-margin products.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:09:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bef01ee97f501b0eb29dd_1771827056859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Textiles Rally on US Tariff Cut, But Cautious Outlook Prevails</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indian-Textiles-Rally-on-US-Tariff-Cut-But-Cautious-Outlook-Prevails/699bee92ee97f501b0eb2928</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indian-Textiles-Rally-on-US-Tariff-Cut-But-Cautious-Outlook-Prevails/699bee92ee97f501b0eb2928</guid><description>Indian textile stocks rallied Monday following a US announcement that significantly reduces tariffs on Indian goods, effectively reversing punitive measures imposed earlier. Trident, Welspun Living, Alok Industries, and Arvind saw share price increases. While the tariff reduction is seen as a positive catalyst for improved export competitiveness and potential new trade discussions, market strategists anticipate a relief rally rather than a sustained surge, citing ongoing global demand uncertainties and competitive pressures within the sector. The move marks a significant shift from the challenging trade environment of 2025, when tariffs reached as high as 50%.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:07:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bee92ee97f501b0eb2927_1771827004867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Banks Hit Record High Amidst Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Hit-Record-High-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/699bee31ee97f501b0eb2882</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Banks-Hit-Record-High-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/699bee31ee97f501b0eb2882</guid><description>The Nifty PSU Bank index surged to a record 9,840.25, capping a significant rally fueled by robust Q3 FY26 earnings and improved asset quality. Major PSU lenders like SBI, Bank of Baroda, and Indian Bank touched all-time highs. However, the sector's rapid ascent has compressed valuation gaps, raising questions about sustainability. Concurrently, a regulatory crackdown in Haryana has de-empaneled IDFC First Bank and AU Small Finance Bank due to alleged fraud, highlighting distinct performance trajectories within the BFSI sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:05:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bee31ee97f501b0eb2881_1771826856006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Narayana Hrudayalaya Rallies Amid Expansion, But Net Profit Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Narayana-Hrudayalaya-Rallies-Amid-Expansion-But-Net-Profit-Dips/699bee10ee97f501b0eb2845</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Narayana-Hrudayalaya-Rallies-Amid-Expansion-But-Net-Profit-Dips/699bee10ee97f501b0eb2845</guid><description>Narayana Hrudayalaya has acquired 3.3 acres in Bengaluru for business expansion, including a Global Capability Center. The move fuels a stock rally, supported by a 44% year-on-year increase in EBITDA to ₹440 crore for Q3. However, net profit dropped 34% YoY to ₹126.78 crore, raising questions about the impact of aggressive expansion on profitability. Analysts maintain a 'Buy' stance with a median target of ₹2,045, yet valuation metrics suggest a premium for future growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:05:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bee10ee97f501b0eb2844_1771826881190.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Monika Alcobev Lists on BSE SME, Eyes 20% Revenue CAGR Post IPO</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Monika-Alcobev-Lists-on-BSE-SME-Eyes-20percent-Revenue-CAGR-Post-IPO/699bed97ee97f501b0eb2757</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Monika-Alcobev-Lists-on-BSE-SME-Eyes-20percent-Revenue-CAGR-Post-IPO/699bed97ee97f501b0eb2757</guid><description>Monika Alcobev Limited successfully listed on the BSE SME platform on July 23, 2025, after its IPO was subscribed 4.08 times. The luxury alcohol importer aims for ~20% revenue CAGR over the next four years, leveraging the IPO funds for growth. However, challenges from high duties and state taxes could pressure margins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:03:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bed97ee97f501b0eb2756_1771826723182.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gaudium IVF IPO Subscribes: First Fertility Firm Taps Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Gaudium-IVF-IPO-Subscribes-First-Fertility-Firm-Taps-Market/699bed40ee97f501b0eb2674</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Gaudium-IVF-IPO-Subscribes-First-Fertility-Firm-Taps-Market/699bed40ee97f501b0eb2674</guid><description>Gaudium IVF's Rs 165 crore initial public offering achieved full subscription on its second day of bidding, with bids exceeding the shares on offer. The company becomes the first pure-play fertility services provider to list in India, a sector poised for significant growth. Investor interest was robust across retail and non-institutional categories. The IPO, priced between ₹75-₹79, values the company at approximately ₹575 crore and aims to fund expansion and debt repayment. Despite a premium valuation and a challenging regulatory environment, Gaudium IVF's strong margins and market position are key investor focal points.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:01:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bed40ee97f501b0eb2673_1771826638148.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Reviews PMS Rules Amidst Record AUM Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SEBI-Reviews-PMS-Rules-Amidst-Record-AUM-Surge/699bed2fee97f501b0eb265d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SEBI-Reviews-PMS-Rules-Amidst-Record-AUM-Surge/699bed2fee97f501b0eb265d</guid><description>India's portfolio management services (PMS) sector has nearly doubled its Assets Under Management (AUM) to ₹10.5 trillion by January 31, 2026, fueled by a 17% CAGR since FY21. This expansion, marked by a 50% rise in client count and an increase in registered managers, has prompted the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) to initiate a comprehensive review of its PMS regulations, targeting proposed changes by June 2026. The review aims to adapt the framework to evolving market dynamics while ensuring investor safeguards. This surge underscores a significant shift towards sophisticated wealth management solutions, particularly among high-net-worth individuals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:01:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bed2fee97f501b0eb265c_1771826583384.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Partners Tripura Group for India's First Integrated Zinc Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindustan-Zinc-Partners-Tripura-Group-for-Indias-First-Integrated-Zinc-Hub/699becadee97f501b0eb257c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hindustan-Zinc-Partners-Tripura-Group-for-Indias-First-Integrated-Zinc-Hub/699becadee97f501b0eb257c</guid><description>Hindustan Zinc (HZL) has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Tripura Group to establish a manufacturing unit within its Zinc Park in Bhilwara, Rajasthan. This collaboration aims to create India's first integrated downstream industrial hub for zinc-based products, fostering 'Make-in-India' manufacturing and supporting MSME growth. The initiative is a key step towards unlocking downstream value and building a competitive metal value chain.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:59:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699becadee97f501b0eb257b_1771826515824.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HZL Gains Edge as India Eases Mining Waste Rules</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HZL-Gains-Edge-as-India-Eases-Mining-Waste-Rules/699bec37ee97f501b0eb246e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HZL-Gains-Edge-as-India-Eases-Mining-Waste-Rules/699bec37ee97f501b0eb246e</guid><description>India's government has exempted tailings recycling within existing mine leases from fresh environmental clearances (EC), a move welcomed by Hindustan Zinc Ltd (HZL). This regulatory relief is expected to streamline operations, reduce delays, and promote resource optimization. HZL, a leader in zinc-lead-silver production with a market cap of approximately ₹2.49 lakh crore, currently boasts a strong return on equity of ~77.69% and a TTM P/E ratio around 21.1, reflecting investor confidence. The policy aligns with India's push for critical minerals to fuel its energy transition, potentially enhancing HZL's financial and ESG standing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:57:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bec37ee97f501b0eb246d_1771826385432.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Balrampur Chini Secures First Institutional PLA Order from Lucknow Cantonment Board</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Balrampur-Chini-Secures-First-Institutional-PLA-Order-from-Lucknow-Cantonment-Board/699bec2fee97f501b0eb2457</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Balrampur-Chini-Secures-First-Institutional-PLA-Order-from-Lucknow-Cantonment-Board/699bec2fee97f501b0eb2457</guid><description>Balrampur Chini Mills' bio-based venture, Balrampur Bioyug, has landed its first institutional order from the Lucknow Cantonment Board. This includes compostable garbage bags, PLA bottles, and pens, signaling market confidence ahead of its 80,000 TPA PLA plant commissioning in October 2026. The order marks a significant step in BCML's strategy to become a leader in India's burgeoning bio-plastics sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:57:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bec2fee97f501b0eb2456_1771826334471.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Rally on Tariff Relief, but Trade Risks Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Rally-on-Tariff-Relief-but-Trade-Risks-Linger/699bebcaee97f501b0eb239d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Rally-on-Tariff-Relief-but-Trade-Risks-Linger/699bebcaee97f501b0eb239d</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks opened higher on Monday, February 23, 2026, with the BSE Sensex gaining over 500 points and the Nifty 50 advancing above 25,700. The rupee appreciated 21 paise to 90.73 against the dollar, supported by falling crude oil prices and a weaker greenback. Record foreign exchange reserves further bolstered sentiment. However, a US Supreme Court ruling striking down tariffs, followed by President Trump's escalation to a 15% global tariff, introduces persistent trade policy uncertainty and potential volatility, evidenced by continued FII outflows.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:55:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bebcaee97f501b0eb239c_1771826409249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haryana Govt Cuts AU SFB; Analysts Cite Limited Impact</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Haryana-Govt-Cuts-AU-SFB-Analysts-Cite-Limited-Impact/699bebbaee97f501b0eb2383</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Haryana-Govt-Cuts-AU-SFB-Analysts-Cite-Limited-Impact/699bebbaee97f501b0eb2383</guid><description>AU Small Finance Bank has been de-empanelled by the Haryana government for handling its financial business. This development, citing suspected fraudulent activities, led to an immediate drop in the bank's stock price. However, global brokerage firm Jefferies has maintained its 'Buy' rating with a price target of ₹1,220, citing that deposits linked to the Haryana government represent a minimal 0.4% of the bank's total deposits and that preliminary findings indicate no direct financial loss or fraudulent activity towards the bank. The bank has initiated an internal review and placed certain employees on leave.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:55:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bebbaee97f501b0eb2382_1771826306155.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Sons Board Meeting: Chairman, Listing Fate Hang in Balance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Tata-Sons-Board-Meeting-Chairman-Listing-Fate-Hang-in-Balance/699be698ee97f501b0eb20fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Tata-Sons-Board-Meeting-Chairman-Listing-Fate-Hang-in-Balance/699be698ee97f501b0eb20fa</guid><description>The Tata Sons board meets this week, with a potential third term for Chairman N Chandrasekaran on the agenda. A critical discussion point is the Reserve Bank of India's mandate for Tata Sons to list on the stock market by September 2025, a requirement stemming from its classification as an 'upper layer' non-banking financial company. This impending listing, coupled with a mixed performance across Tata group equities in early 2026, sets the stage for significant strategic re-evaluation. While Tata Steel and Voltas have surged, others like Tejas Networks and TCS have retreated, creating a complex backdrop for group-wide decisions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:33:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699be698ee97f501b0eb20f9_1771824922475.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Block Deal Boosts Cohance Lifesciences Amidst Deepening Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Block-Deal-Boosts-Cohance-Lifesciences-Amidst-Deepening-Woes/699be692ee97f501b0eb20e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Block-Deal-Boosts-Cohance-Lifesciences-Amidst-Deepening-Woes/699be692ee97f501b0eb20e0</guid><description>Cohance Lifesciences shares saw a sharp jump of over 8% on February 23, 2026, driven by a substantial block deal valued at ₹235.6 crore. This short-term rally occurred despite a stark 76.1% year-on-year decline in Q3 FY26 net profit and a 19.5% revenue drop. Technical analysts maintain a cautious "sell on rise" outlook, underscoring persistent concerns over the company's financial health and operational challenges, including regulatory hurdles.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699be692ee97f501b0eb20df_1771824920862.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DEE Piping Systems Secures INR 173 Cr Orders, Bolstering Order Book</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DEE-Piping-Systems-Secures-INR-173-Cr-Orders-Bolstering-Order-Book/699be078ee97f501b0eb1ddb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DEE-Piping-Systems-Secures-INR-173-Cr-Orders-Bolstering-Order-Book/699be078ee97f501b0eb1ddb</guid><description>DEE Piping Systems has announced a significant boost to its order book, securing new contracts aggregating approximately INR 173 Crores. The wins include substantial domestic orders and international contracts for its Thai subsidiary, reinforcing the company's position in critical piping solutions. These orders are expected to contribute meaningfully to future revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:07:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699be078ee97f501b0eb1dda_1771823373236.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Gains on Tariff Relief, but Trade Uncertainty Lingers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Gains-on-Tariff-Relief-but-Trade-Uncertainty-Lingers/699bdfa8ee97f501b0eb1ce4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Gains-on-Tariff-Relief-but-Trade-Uncertainty-Lingers/699bdfa8ee97f501b0eb1ce4</guid><description>The Indian Rupee appreciated 21 paise to 90.73 against the US dollar on February 23, 2026, buoyed by a US Supreme Court ruling invalidating emergency tariffs and a subsequent drop in the dollar index. This short-term relief, coupled with falling crude oil prices and robust domestic equity markets (Sensex at 83,283, Nifty 50 near 25,700), provided a positive start. However, renewed US tariff announcements to 15% and sustained foreign institutional investor outflows (₹934.61 crore on Feb 20) introduce significant headwinds, casting doubt on the durability of these gains amidst persistent global trade uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:03:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bdfa8ee97f501b0eb1ce3_1771823151226.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Plunges 20% Amidst ₹590 Cr Fraud; Block Deals Exceed ₹1390 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Plunges-20percent-Amidst-590-Cr-Fraud-Block-Deals-Exceed-1390-Cr/699bdf23ee97f501b0eb1bbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Plunges-20percent-Amidst-590-Cr-Fraud-Block-Deals-Exceed-1390-Cr/699bdf23ee97f501b0eb1bbb</guid><description>IDFC First Bank's stock experienced its sharpest single-day decline since March 2020, plummeting almost 20% after disclosing a ₹590 crore fraud in its Chandigarh branch involving Haryana government accounts. Over 2.7% of its equity, valued at ₹1,390 crore, changed hands in significant block deals at ₹67 per share, while the bank suspended four employees and appointed KPMG for a forensic audit. The Haryana government has subsequently de-empaneled the bank from handling its business.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:01:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bdf23ee97f501b0eb1bba_1771823090720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India GST Crackdown Intensifies: New Tech, Higher Stakes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/India-GST-Crackdown-Intensifies-New-Tech-Higher-Stakes/699bdf20ee97f501b0eb1ba4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/India-GST-Crackdown-Intensifies-New-Tech-Higher-Stakes/699bdf20ee97f501b0eb1ba4</guid><description>India's Goods and Services Tax (GST) compliance has entered a new era of aggressive enforcement, moving far beyond routine filings. Authorities are leveraging sophisticated AI and data analytics to flag discrepancies and combat evasion, escalating consequences for businesses. For listed companies, this translates into significant reputational and financial risks, demanding a robust approach to regulatory oversight and disclosure. Penalties now extend to credit freezes, bank account seizures, and potential arrests, making proactive compliance a critical imperative.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:01:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bdf20ee97f501b0eb1ba3_1771823000861.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CIE India Surges on Domestic Demand, But Margins Show Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CIE-India-Surges-on-Domestic-Demand-But-Margins-Show-Strain/699bdf16ee97f501b0eb1b8a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CIE-India-Surges-on-Domestic-Demand-But-Margins-Show-Strain/699bdf16ee97f501b0eb1b8a</guid><description>CIE Automotive India's third quarter saw revenue climb 13.4% year-over-year to ₹2,393 crore and net profit rise 10.4% to ₹204.3 crore, buoyed by robust domestic demand. However, EBITDA margins contracted slightly to 14%, indicating cost pressures. The company maintains a net debt-free status and a P/E ratio significantly below its sector average, even as analysts reiterate 'Buy' ratings with price targets suggesting further upside.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:01:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bdf16ee97f501b0eb1b89_1771822994769.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Valiant Communications: Kill Switch Equipment Evaluated by Indian Armed Forces</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valiant-Communications-Kill-Switch-Equipment-Evaluated-by-Indian-Armed-Forces/699bdf13ee97f501b0eb1b73</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valiant-Communications-Kill-Switch-Equipment-Evaluated-by-Indian-Armed-Forces/699bdf13ee97f501b0eb1b73</guid><description>Valiant Communications Limited announced the successful completion of an evaluation for its Hardware-Based Network Isolation (Kill) Switch Equipment with the Indian Armed Forces (Classified). This marks a significant step for the company's cybersecurity offerings, designed for mission-critical operational environments to enhance cyber resilience and ensure operational continuity during cyber incidents. The company already has a global presence with over 110 countries featuring its installations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:01:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bdf13ee97f501b0eb1b72_1771822997239.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fashion's Climate Bill: Profit Risk Spurs Industry Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Fashions-Climate-Bill-Profit-Risk-Spurs-Industry-Overhaul/699bde4cee97f501b0eb19b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Fashions-Climate-Bill-Profit-Risk-Spurs-Industry-Overhaul/699bde4cee97f501b0eb19b4</guid><description>The global fashion industry risks substantial profit erosion, potentially losing up to 67% of operating margins by 2040 if climate change mitigation efforts lag. A new report highlights escalating costs from carbon pricing, volatile raw materials like cotton, and energy dependence as primary financial drivers. The findings compel a strategic pivot towards decarbonisation and resilience, shifting the paradigm from mere environmental compliance to a competitive imperative for long-term survival and growth. Early integration of sustainability is key to navigating these financial headwinds and unlocking future market opportunities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:57:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bde4cee97f501b0eb19b3_1771822795722.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPL Stock Drops 12% on Restructuring Plan Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/UPL-Stock-Drops-12percent-on-Restructuring-Plan-Uncertainty/699bde39ee97f501b0eb1996</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/UPL-Stock-Drops-12percent-on-Restructuring-Plan-Uncertainty/699bde39ee97f501b0eb1996</guid><description>UPL Limited's stock plunged 12% to near the ₹600 level on the Bombay Stock Exchange Monday, driven by investor concerns over a sweeping corporate restructuring. The plan consolidates crop protection units, but ambiguities in financial impact and execution timelines have overshadowed strategic intent. This adds to existing sector headwinds, including weak global demand and pricing challenges, further pressuring the company's valuation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:57:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bde39ee97f501b0eb1995_1771822765973.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Tumbles Below $65K Amid Tariff Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Tumbles-Below-65K-Amid-Tariff-Fears/699bddcdee97f501b0eb18aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Bitcoin-Tumbles-Below-65K-Amid-Tariff-Fears/699bddcdee97f501b0eb18aa</guid><description>Bitcoin experienced a significant downturn, falling below $65,000 as new US global tariff announcements sparked a risk-off sentiment. Over $458 million in crypto positions were liquidated, primarily long trades, pushing the Fear and Greed Index to extreme lows not seen since 2018. While short-term bias remains bearish, this extreme pessimism historically precedes accumulation phases. Gold prices rallied as a safe-haven asset, contrasting with Bitcoin's performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:55:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bddcdee97f501b0eb18a9_1771822724879.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>