<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 01:49:17 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Netweb Technologies Launches India's Smallest AI Supercomputer with NVIDIA</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Netweb-Technologies-Launches-Indias-Smallest-AI-Supercomputer-with-NVIDIA/699518363ec8b0ccb20d77fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Netweb-Technologies-Launches-Indias-Smallest-AI-Supercomputer-with-NVIDIA/699518363ec8b0ccb20d77fb</guid><description>Netweb Technologies India Ltd. has launched its new 'Make in India' AI supercomputing systems, including the world's smallest, Tyrone Camarero Spark. Partnering with NVIDIA, these systems aim to significantly boost India's AI capabilities for millions of developers and support large-scale model training.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 01:39:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699518363ec8b0ccb20d77fa.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Buffett Pivots: Berkshire Sells Amazon, Buys NYT in Portfolio Shake-up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Buffett-Pivots-Berkshire-Sells-Amazon-Buys-NYT-in-Portfolio-Shake-up/699515b53ec8b0ccb20d766b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Buffett-Pivots-Berkshire-Sells-Amazon-Buys-NYT-in-Portfolio-Shake-up/699515b53ec8b0ccb20d766b</guid><description>Berkshire Hathaway executed a substantial portfolio overhaul in the fourth quarter of 2025. Holdings in e-commerce giant Amazon.com Inc. were slashed by nearly 75%, alongside continued reductions in Apple and Bank of America. Concurrently, The New York Times Co. saw a significant investment increase, acquiring over 5 million shares. Positions in energy firm Chevron Corp. and insurer Chubb Ltd. were also bolstered, signaling a strategic shift in Buffett's investment focus away from mega-cap tech.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 01:28:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699515b53ec8b0ccb20d766a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Prices Dip on Iran Talks, But Geopolitical Risks Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Dip-on-Iran-Talks-But-Geopolitical-Risks-Linger/6995156c3ec8b0ccb20d7636</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Dip-on-Iran-Talks-But-Geopolitical-Risks-Linger/6995156c3ec8b0ccb20d7636</guid><description>Crude oil futures saw a decline as diplomatic talks between the U.S. and Iran showed signs of progress, reducing the immediate geopolitical risk premium. West Texas Intermediate traded near $62 a barrel, while Brent crude hovered around $67. This relief rally occurred despite Iran's military drills near the Strait of Hormuz and ongoing US military deployments, highlighting the market's current focus on de-escalation over persistent regional vulnerabilities. Analyst consensus forecasts modest price declines for 2026, yet the market may be underestimating the potential for renewed volatility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 01:27:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6995156c3ec8b0ccb20d7635.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amazon's $200B AI Spend: Prove-It Time for Cloud Giant</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazons-200B-AI-Spend-Prove-It-Time-for-Cloud-Giant/699515693ec8b0ccb20d761f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Amazons-200B-AI-Spend-Prove-It-Time-for-Cloud-Giant/699515693ec8b0ccb20d761f</guid><description>Amazon's nine-day stock decline ended Tuesday, but the underlying investor concern remains: the company's projected $200 billion capital expenditure for 2026, primarily for AI infrastructure. This aggressive outlay, far exceeding prior estimates, has ignited debate over free cash flow and payback periods, pushing the company into a critical "prove it" phase. While management asserts confidence in long-term returns from its AWS dominance, the sheer scale of investment raises questions about sustainability and competitive positioning against peers like Microsoft, Alphabet, and Meta, who are also engaged in a colossal AI infrastructure buildout.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 01:27:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699515693ec8b0ccb20d761e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India FMCG Prices Rise Amid Margin Squeeze, Weak Rupee</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-FMCG-Prices-Rise-Amid-Margin-Squeeze-Weak-Rupee/69950e7c3ec8b0ccb20d7338</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-FMCG-Prices-Rise-Amid-Margin-Squeeze-Weak-Rupee/69950e7c3ec8b0ccb20d7338</guid><description>India's Fast-Moving Consumer Goods (FMCG) sector is implementing price increases of up to 5% on select products this quarter. This move comes after months of price restraint and is driven by escalating commodity costs and a depreciating rupee, which are squeezing company margins. While revenue growth has been observed, the ability to fully pass on cost increases remains a challenge, indicating continued pressure on profitability for major players like Dabur India, Hindustan Unilever, and Tata Consumer Products.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:57:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69950e7c3ec8b0ccb20d7337.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Mega-Refinery Woes: Investors Favor Coastal Sites</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Mega-Refinery-Woes-Investors-Favor-Coastal-Sites/69950e6c3ec8b0ccb20d7310</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Mega-Refinery-Woes-Investors-Favor-Coastal-Sites/69950e6c3ec8b0ccb20d7310</guid><description>Key overseas investors Adnoc and Saudi Aramco are reportedly disengaging from India's decade-stalled Ratnagiri Refinery and Petrochemicals (RRPCL) project. Adnoc has withdrawn, while Aramco seeks revised terms amid persistent land acquisition issues in Maharashtra. This signals a strategic shift as capital is increasingly directed towards more viable, coastal projects like Bharat Petroleum Corporation's proposed Andhra Pradesh refinery, supported by robust Indian petrochemical demand growth. ONGC's Gujarat refinery project also advances, highlighting a move towards diversified and more geographically advantageous energy infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:57:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69950e6c3ec8b0ccb20d730f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bank Stocks Gain: Mid-Caps Offer Value Amidst IT Sell-off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-Stocks-Gain-Mid-Caps-Offer-Value-Amidst-IT-Sell-off/69950e103ec8b0ccb20d71fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-Stocks-Gain-Mid-Caps-Offer-Value-Amidst-IT-Sell-off/69950e103ec8b0ccb20d71fc</guid><description>As IT stocks exhibit volatility, Dalal Street investors are increasingly shifting capital towards the banking sector. This trend favors mid-sized private banks like Karnataka Bank and Dhanlaxmi Bank, which trade at significant discounts to their larger, premium-valued peers such as HDFC Bank and Kotak Mahindra Bank. While regulatory support and specific loan growth in areas like gold and SME lending offer upside, potential margin pressures and asset quality nuances require careful investor scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:55:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69950e103ec8b0ccb20d71fb.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EU Defense Pivot: India Firms Gain Strategic Edge Amidst Global Re-arming</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EU-Defense-Pivot-India-Firms-Gain-Strategic-Edge-Amidst-Global-Re-arming/69950dff3ec8b0ccb20d71c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/EU-Defense-Pivot-India-Firms-Gain-Strategic-Edge-Amidst-Global-Re-arming/69950dff3ec8b0ccb20d71c7</guid><description>Europe is dramatically increasing defense spending, aiming for 3.5% of GDP by 2030 under the ReARM plan, aiming to reduce reliance on U.S. and Chinese suppliers. A new India-EU security and defense partnership, signed January 2026, creates significant opportunities for Indian defense firms. Companies such as Solar Industries, Premier Explosives, and Dynamatic Technologies are positioned to benefit from critical supply shortages in munitions, missiles, and aerospace components, as Europe seeks scalable production and diversified sourcing. The pact aims to integrate Indian capabilities into European defense initiatives, offering a strategic advantage beyond mere trade.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:55:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69950dff3ec8b0ccb20d71c6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Chip Ambitions: Ancillary Stocks Face Valuation Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Chip-Ambitions-Ancillary-Stocks-Face-Valuation-Test/69950df83ec8b0ccb20d71af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Chip-Ambitions-Ancillary-Stocks-Face-Valuation-Test/69950df83ec8b0ccb20d71af</guid><description>India's drive to become a global semiconductor hub, backed by government incentives like Semiconductor Mission 2.0, is creating significant demand for ancillary industries. While companies such as Navin Fluorine, SRF, KEI Industries, and L&amp;T Technology Services stand to benefit, their high valuations and operational challenges present a complex investment picture. Navin Fluorine and SRF face input cost volatility and intense global competition, while KEI Industries is exposed to commodity price fluctuations. L&amp;T Technology Services grapples with sector-wide IT slowdowns and past margin pressures. The sustainability of growth for these firms hinges on successful execution amidst a shifting global trade environment and the actual pace of domestic fab development.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:55:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69950df83ec8b0ccb20d71ae_1771376243737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kedia's SME Gamble: Sattrix Valuation vs. Innovators Facade Turnaround</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kedias-SME-Gamble-Sattrix-Valuation-vs-Innovators-Facade-Turnaround/69950de73ec8b0ccb20d7195</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kedias-SME-Gamble-Sattrix-Valuation-vs-Innovators-Facade-Turnaround/69950de73ec8b0ccb20d7195</guid><description>Veteran investor Vijay Kedia has acquired an 8% stake in Sattrix Information Security Ltd., a BSE SME microcap, near its all-time high at a premium valuation of approximately 70x P/E. This aggressive move contrasts with his longer-term, value-oriented holding in Innovators Facade Systems, which shows a compelling profit turnaround and a more modest P/E ratio around 20-25x. The investment highlights the high-risk, high-reward dynamics of SME microcaps, particularly Sattrix's elevated valuation against the broader IT sector's median P/E of 22-27x, amidst ongoing growth in the Indian cybersecurity market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:55:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69950de73ec8b0ccb20d7194_1771376482353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's UPI Boom: Scale Achieved, Profitability &amp; Rural Reach Hurdles Remain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-UPI-Boom-Scale-Achieved-Profitability-and-Rural-Reach-Hurdles-Remain/69950d743ec8b0ccb20d70c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-UPI-Boom-Scale-Achieved-Profitability-and-Rural-Reach-Hurdles-Remain/69950d743ec8b0ccb20d70c9</guid><description>India's UPI ecosystem has achieved monumental scale, processing billions of transactions, largely driven by fintech giants PhonePe, Google Pay, and Paytm's aggressive $3B+ investment. While this has shifted front-end digital payment control from banks to private players, reaching the RBI's one billion user target necessitates deep penetration into rural "Bharat." This expansion demands substantial further investment in infrastructure and education, amidst persistent digital divides and questions regarding sustainable revenue models.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:53:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69950d743ec8b0ccb20d70c8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FC-16 Sparks Rural-Urban Fiscal Divide Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FC-16-Sparks-Rural-Urban-Fiscal-Divide-Fears/69950d713ec8b0ccb20d70b2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FC-16-Sparks-Rural-Urban-Fiscal-Divide-Fears/69950d713ec8b0ccb20d70b2</guid><description>The 16th Finance Commission's report proposes ₹7.91 lakh crore for local bodies (2026-31), with a 55:45 rural-urban split, marking an 11-percentage point reduction for rural Panchayati Raj Institutions (PRIs) compared to the 15th FC. While increasing overall grants, the focus on performance-based criteria and urbanization incentives, coupled with significant state matching contributions for performance grants, raises concerns about deepening fiscal disparities and the untapped potential of rural local bodies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:53:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69950d713ec8b0ccb20d70b1_1771376179177.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stable Money Raises $25M, Eyes Profitability by 2028</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Stable-Money-Raises-25M-Eyes-Profitability-by-2028/69950abe3ec8b0ccb20d6f87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Stable-Money-Raises-25M-Eyes-Profitability-by-2028/69950abe3ec8b0ccb20d6f87</guid><description>Stable Money, a fixed-income investment fintech, has secured $25 million in a Pre-Series C round, valuing the company at $175 million. The firm manages ₹5,000 crore in assets and aims for profitability by early 2028, focusing on growing its fixed deposit and bond products. The funding will support product expansion, hiring, and new initiatives, with significant user acquisition occurring in Tier-II and Tier-III cities. Partnership expansion to 20 institutions is planned to drive threefold asset growth in 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:41:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69950abe3ec8b0ccb20d6f86.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Gold Imports Dip as Silver Surge Exacerbates Trade Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Gold-Imports-Dip-as-Silver-Surge-Exacerbates-Trade-Gap/699507d93ec8b0ccb20d6e3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Gold-Imports-Dip-as-Silver-Surge-Exacerbates-Trade-Gap/699507d93ec8b0ccb20d6e3d</guid><description>India's trade balance is facing pressure as precious metal import trends diverge. Gold import volumes dropped 18.29% to 522.38 tonnes in April-December 2025, despite a 24.62% price increase. Conversely, silver imports surged 128.95% in value to $7.77 billion, driven by a 56.07% volume increase and a 46.69% price hike. This divergence contributed to a wider trade deficit, which grew to $96.58 billion for the April-December period. Silver's industrial utility is a key factor in its robust demand, contrasting with gold's primary role as an investment asset.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:29:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699507d93ec8b0ccb20d6e3c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Property Surge: Capital Gains Outpace Rents, Yields Shrink</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Property-Surge-Capital-Gains-Outpace-Rents-Yields-Shrink/699507d43ec8b0ccb20d6e26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Property-Surge-Capital-Gains-Outpace-Rents-Yields-Shrink/699507d43ec8b0ccb20d6e26</guid><description>India's property market exhibited a significant divergence in Q4 2025, with capital values increasing by 2.2% nationally while rental demand contracted by 2.4% quarter-on-quarter. This trend indicates a market prioritizing capital appreciation over rental income, resulting in substantial yield compression. Chennai recorded the highest gross rental yields at 4.16%, but the broader market dynamic suggests an adjustment where rental returns diminish relative to property value growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:29:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699507d43ec8b0ccb20d6e25.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys Navigates AI 'Surgery': Costs, Skills &amp; Market Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Navigates-AI-Surgery-Costs-Skills-and-Market-Scrutiny/699502383ec8b0ccb20d6c2f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Navigates-AI-Surgery-Costs-Skills-and-Market-Scrutiny/699502383ec8b0ccb20d6c2f</guid><description>Infosys Chairman Nandan Nilekani framed the AI transition as a profound "root-and-branch surgery," demanding fundamental shifts in organizational models and workforce skills beyond mere automation. This complex integration of non-deterministic AI into structured business processes creates significant friction and necessitates extensive reskilling. Despite strategic AI investments, Infosys faces market scrutiny due to cautious revenue guidance and historical underperformance relative to peers, raising concerns about potential workforce stratification and operational costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:05:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699502383ec8b0ccb20d6c2e_1771373244551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Overhauls ECB Rules: Wider Access, Market Pricing, New Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Overhauls-ECB-Rules-Wider-Access-Market-Pricing-New-Risks/699502333ec8b0ccb20d6c15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Overhauls-ECB-Rules-Wider-Access-Market-Pricing-New-Risks/699502333ec8b0ccb20d6c15</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has significantly revised its External Commercial Borrowing (ECB) regulations, effective February 16, 2026. This overhaul broadens borrower and lender eligibility, removes the all-in-cost ceiling for pricing, and clarifies end-use rules for sectors like real estate and manufacturing. While aiming to boost capital access and reduce financing friction, the changes also necessitate enhanced risk management for entities navigating increased foreign currency debt and currency volatility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:05:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699502333ec8b0ccb20d6c14_1771373231537.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>