<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:43:15 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Alka India to AUDROC; Approves ₹355 Cr Preferential Issue &amp; Higher Limits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Alka-India-to-AUDROC-Approves-355-Cr-Preferential-Issue-and-Higher-Limits/69a11e86fa7d0695d1ab3bde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Alka-India-to-AUDROC-Approves-355-Cr-Preferential-Issue-and-Higher-Limits/69a11e86fa7d0695d1ab3bde</guid><description>Alka India Limited has proposed a name change to AUDROC Limited, pending approvals. The company also sanctioned a ₹354.96 crore preferential share issuance and significantly increased its borrowing and investment limits to ₹5,000 crore each. A material subsidiary, Vintage FZE (India) Private Limited, is being divested for ₹0.90 lakh. These moves signal a strategic shift and increased financial flexibility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:33:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11e86fa7d0695d1ab3bdd_1772167186104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC Ruling Shields Civil Disputes from Criminal Overtones</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-Ruling-Shields-Civil-Disputes-from-Criminal-Overtones/69a11e85fa7d0695d1ab3bc8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-Ruling-Shields-Civil-Disputes-from-Criminal-Overtones/69a11e85fa7d0695d1ab3bc8</guid><description>The Supreme Court has definitively quashed a First Information Report (FIR) stemming from a stalled joint venture, reinforcing that purely civil disputes do not warrant criminal prosecution. This ruling, rooted in the principle that dishonest intent must be present from the transaction's inception, aims to prevent the misuse of criminal law for settling contractual defaults and signals a judicial pushback against opportunistic litigation, thereby strengthening the sanctity of commercial agreements. The decision highlights an 11-year delay in lodging the FIR as a key indicator of the dispute's civil nature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11e85fa7d0695d1ab3bc7_1772167004687.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NTT Data Bets Big on India: 5K Hires, $1.5B Data Center Push Amidst AI Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NTT-Data-Bets-Big-on-India-5K-Hires-15B-Data-Center-Push-Amidst-AI-Boom/69a11dbffa7d0695d1ab3a1d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/NTT-Data-Bets-Big-on-India-5K-Hires-15B-Data-Center-Push-Amidst-AI-Boom/69a11dbffa7d0695d1ab3a1d</guid><description>Japanese technology firm NTT Data intends to add 5,000 employees in India by 2026, focusing on software, consulting, and IT support. This aggressive hiring occurs as the broader Indian IT sector faces significant workforce restructuring due to AI adoption, with major players reporting stalled hiring. Concurrently, NTT Data is investing $1.5 billion to build four new data centers in India, aiming to address the nation's data infrastructure deficit and capture growth from escalating AI investments. This move positions NTT Data against competitors like TCS, which is also embarking on massive data center infrastructure projects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:29:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11dbffa7d0695d1ab3a1c_1772166777183.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Loan Surge: Muthoot's Operational Edge Trumps Manappuram's High P/E</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Loan-Surge-Muthoots-Operational-Edge-Trumps-Manappurams-High-PE/69a11dabfa7d0695d1ab3a03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Loan-Surge-Muthoots-Operational-Edge-Trumps-Manappurams-High-PE/69a11dabfa7d0695d1ab3a03</guid><description>The gold loan sector is expanding rapidly, with loans against gold surging 42% to ₹15.6 lakh crore, fueled by a significant rise in gold prices. Jefferies maintains a 'Buy' on Muthoot Finance, citing its superior operational efficiency and reasonable valuation (P/E of ~16x), while rating Manappuram Finance 'Hold' due to its high valuation (P/E of ~64x) and execution challenges. Regulatory easing on branch expansion is poised to benefit larger players, highlighting a divergent growth trajectory for key NBFCs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:29:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11dabfa7d0695d1ab3a02_1772166714795.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GDP Overhaul: Growth Revised Upward, Policy Pivot Ahead</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Overhaul-Growth-Revised-Upward-Policy-Pivot-Ahead/69a11d6afa7d0695d1ab3966</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-GDP-Overhaul-Growth-Revised-Upward-Policy-Pivot-Ahead/69a11d6afa7d0695d1ab3966</guid><description>India's statistical agency is set to release a revised GDP series on February 27, 2026, shifting the base year to 2022-23. This recalibration is projected to boost the current fiscal year's growth estimate to 7.6% from 7.4%, reflecting structural economic evolution and potentially influencing monetary policy. The updated figures are also anticipated to clarify India's trajectory towards becoming the world's fourth-largest economy, offering a more accurate snapshot of its resilience amidst global trade volatility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:28:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11d6afa7d0695d1ab3965_1772167076487.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India GDP Leaps to 8.3%, Base Year Shift Dominates Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Leaps-to-83percent-Base-Year-Shift-Dominates-Outlook/69a11d21fa7d0695d1ab391b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Leaps-to-83percent-Base-Year-Shift-Dominates-Outlook/69a11d21fa7d0695d1ab391b</guid><description>India's Q3 FY26 GDP is projected at a robust 8.3%, propelled by strong domestic demand and GST reforms. However, a forthcoming base year revision introduces significant data uncertainty, while falling inflation is tempering nominal GDP growth, signaling potential pressure on corporate pricing power. The economy faces global headwinds and contracting government capital expenditure, amidst a banking sector liquidity squeeze.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:27:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11d21fa7d0695d1ab391a_1772166555576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CLSA Sees 37% Upside for Tata Motors CV Post-Demerger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CLSA-Sees-37percent-Upside-for-Tata-Motors-CV-Post-Demerger/69a118e7fa7d0695d1ab35ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CLSA-Sees-37percent-Upside-for-Tata-Motors-CV-Post-Demerger/69a118e7fa7d0695d1ab35ae</guid><description>Brokerage CLSA initiated coverage on Tata Motors Commercial Vehicles (TMCV) with an 'outperform' rating and a ₹673 price target, signaling a potential 37% surge. The firm anticipates a commercial vehicle upcycle in India and the EU, bolstered by synergies from the Iveco acquisition and EV adoption. Projections indicate robust free cash flow generation, aiding balance sheet deleveraging by FY2028, despite debt from the €3.8 billion Iveco deal. TMCV shares closed at ₹491.35 on Thursday, up 2.4%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:09:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a118e7fa7d0695d1ab35ad_1772165654946.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gravita India: Diversification Drive Meets Valuation Hurdle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gravita-India-Diversification-Drive-Meets-Valuation-Hurdle/69a118e3fa7d0695d1ab3597</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gravita-India-Diversification-Drive-Meets-Valuation-Hurdle/69a118e3fa7d0695d1ab3597</guid><description>Gravita India is aggressively diversifying into value-added copper and lithium-ion recycling following strategic acquisitions and plant expansions. While analyst consensus remains strongly 'Buy' with ambitious price targets, the company's elevated P/E ratio, trading at a premium to peers and the broader sector, signals potential valuation concerns and execution risks for its complex growth agenda.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:09:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a118e3fa7d0695d1ab3596_1772165524220.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Inc. Redesigns Benefits Amid Cost Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Inc-Redesigns-Benefits-Amid-Cost-Surge/69a118e3fa7d0695d1ab3580</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Inc-Redesigns-Benefits-Amid-Cost-Surge/69a118e3fa7d0695d1ab3580</guid><description>Indian employers are aggressively recalibrating employee benefit structures due to persistent healthcare cost inflation, projected at 9.9% for 2026. This seismic shift sees companies implementing cost-control measures like co-payments and enhancing sum insured for health plans. Parental coverage is moving towards shared funding, while Outpatient Department (OPD) benefits and flexible plans are expanding to meet workforce expectations. Despite growing technology adoption in benefits management, employee feedback highlights gaps in flexibility and perceived adequacy of coverage. These strategic adjustments signal a critical evolution in corporate welfare and risk management.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:09:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a118e3fa7d0695d1ab357f_1772165522792.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GAIL Stock Dips Amidst Divergent Analyst Views on Guidance Cut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GAIL-Stock-Dips-Amidst-Divergent-Analyst-Views-on-Guidance-Cut/69a118e2fa7d0695d1ab3569</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/GAIL-Stock-Dips-Amidst-Divergent-Analyst-Views-on-Guidance-Cut/69a118e2fa7d0695d1ab3569</guid><description>GAIL (India) Ltd. shares opened lower on February 27, 2026, following Kotak Institutional Equities' reiterated 'Sell' rating and ₹145 price target. The brokerage cited a reduced FY26/27E marketing PBT guidance to ₹3,500 crore, down from ₹4,000 crore, amid rising Henry Hub gas prices and customer offtake adjustments. Concerns also linger over the petrochemical business, capital expenditure, and new fertilizer plant investments, revealing the company's capital allocation strategy in a volatile energy market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:09:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a118e2fa7d0695d1ab3568_1772165750334.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Road Sector: Decade-Low Pace Meets Resilient Tolls</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Road-Sector-Decade-Low-Pace-Meets-Resilient-Tolls/69a11832fa7d0695d1ab3459</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Road-Sector-Decade-Low-Pace-Meets-Resilient-Tolls/69a11832fa7d0695d1ab3459</guid><description>India's road development is projected to hit a decade-low construction pace in FY2027, driven by a significant slowdown in project awards by authorities like NHAI and MoRTH. This erosion of developer order books, exacerbated by monsoon disruptions and land acquisition hurdles, is leading to intense competition and high bidding discounts. Despite the bleak outlook for new projects, existing operational road assets are demonstrating resilience, with stable and growing toll collections supported by consistent traffic growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:06:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11832fa7d0695d1ab3458_1772165475127.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Razorpay Legal Victory: SC Sets Higher Bar for Fintech PMLA Cases</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Razorpay-Legal-Victory-SC-Sets-Higher-Bar-for-Fintech-PMLA-Cases/69a117eafa7d0695d1ab33a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Razorpay-Legal-Victory-SC-Sets-Higher-Bar-for-Fintech-PMLA-Cases/69a117eafa7d0695d1ab33a6</guid><description>The Supreme Court has dismissed the Enforcement Directorate's appeal, upholding a High Court decision that quashed money laundering proceedings against Razorpay. This landmark judgment establishes a precedent requiring proof of intent, not mere negligence, for prosecuting payment gateways under the Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA). The ruling provides crucial regulatory clarity, potentially de-risking the fintech sector and encouraging further investment amidst robust market growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:04:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a117eafa7d0695d1ab33a5_1772165208447.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wardwizard Promoter's 1.16% Shares Invoked; Stake Falls to 7.88%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Wardwizard-Promoters-116percent-Shares-Invoked-Stake-Falls-to-788percent/69a11799fa7d0695d1ab332c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Wardwizard-Promoters-116percent-Shares-Invoked-Stake-Falls-to-788percent/69a11799fa7d0695d1ab332c</guid><description>Promoter Yatin Sanjay Gupte of Wardwizard Innovations &amp; Mobility Limited has seen 34.91 lakh shares (1.16% of total share capital) invoked by lender Blacksoil Capital Private Limited. This reduces his overall shareholding to 7.88% from 10.01%. The disclosure was filed under SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:03:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11799fa7d0695d1ab332b_1772165307950.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crompton Greaves: Strategic Bets vs. Market Skepticism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Crompton-Greaves-Strategic-Bets-vs-Market-Skepticism/69a11777fa7d0695d1ab3305</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Crompton-Greaves-Strategic-Bets-vs-Market-Skepticism/69a11777fa7d0695d1ab3305</guid><description>Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals is executing a strategic pivot, entering residential wires and scaling solar operations, while its core electrical durable and lighting segments show resilience. Despite a 7.3% YoY revenue increase in Q3 FY26, profitability faced headwinds from commodity costs, leading to a YoY profit decline. The company trades at a forward P/E of 23x FY28 earnings, significantly lower than peers, yet analysts maintain a strong 'Buy' consensus with substantial upside potential.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:03:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11777fa7d0695d1ab3304_1772165141561.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bandhan MF Crosses 5% in Arvind SmartSpaces After Share Buy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bandhan-MF-Crosses-5percent-in-Arvind-SmartSpaces-After-Share-Buy/69a116fffa7d0695d1ab323e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bandhan-MF-Crosses-5percent-in-Arvind-SmartSpaces-After-Share-Buy/69a116fffa7d0695d1ab323e</guid><description>Bandhan Mutual Fund's Small Cap Fund has acquired an additional 3,64,365 shares in real estate developer Arvind SmartSpaces Limited, pushing its total holding to over 5%. The move signals increased conviction from the fund manager in the company's prospects, though recent earnings pressure remains a key watchpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:01:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a116fffa7d0695d1ab323d_1772164973146.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fears Spark TCS Stock Slump, Pressuring SP Group's Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Fears-Spark-TCS-Stock-Slump-Pressuring-SP-Groups-Debt/69a11629fa7d0695d1ab311b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Fears-Spark-TCS-Stock-Slump-Pressuring-SP-Groups-Debt/69a11629fa7d0695d1ab311b</guid><description>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) shares have plunged nearly 29% over the past year, fueled by artificial intelligence disruption concerns within the IT sector. This sharp sell-off is now critically impacting Shapoorji Pallonji (SP) Group's substantial $3 billion+ private credit facility, specifically its Porteast debentures. The high loan-to-value ratio on these debentures, collateralized by SP Group's stake in Tata Sons (which holds TCS), is nearing covenant breach levels. This event underscores the fragility of private credit structures when linked to volatile public market assets amidst sector-wide technological anxieties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:57:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11629fa7d0695d1ab311a_1772164790982.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Glenmark Pharma USA to launch Sodium Phosphates Injection vials in April 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Glenmark-Pharma-USA-to-launch-Sodium-Phosphates-Injection-vials-in-April-2026/69a1159bfa7d0695d1ab3093</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Glenmark-Pharma-USA-to-launch-Sodium-Phosphates-Injection-vials-in-April-2026/69a1159bfa7d0695d1ab3093</guid><description>Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Inc., USA, is set to launch its Sodium Phosphates Injection USP vials in April 2026, entering a segment of the US market that generated $66.8 million in sales for the 12 months ending December 2025. This move aims to expand Glenmark's US institutional channel presence with bioequivalent and affordable treatment alternatives.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:55:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1159bfa7d0695d1ab3092_1772164819498.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zaggle Eyes Sports Deal: CSK Partnership Fuels Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Zaggle-Eyes-Sports-Deal-CSK-Partnership-Fuels-Expansion/69a114a9fa7d0695d1ab2fb5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Zaggle-Eyes-Sports-Deal-CSK-Partnership-Fuels-Expansion/69a114a9fa7d0695d1ab2fb5</guid><description>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited has formally entered the sports and entertainment sector through a one-year corporate expense card agreement with Chennai Super Kings Cricket Limited. This strategic move aims to expand Zaggle's reach into new-age corporate segments beyond its traditional enterprise client base. The partnership is supported by a robust third-quarter performance, which saw net profit surge 84.3% year-on-year to ₹36.3 crore and revenue climb 56% to ₹525.5 crore, driven by increased transaction volumes across its core businesses. Zaggle's stock closed up 7.05% on February 26, 2026, reflecting positive investor sentiment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a114a9fa7d0695d1ab2fb4_1772164387372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MDL: Order Surge Fuels Growth Amidst Capex Challenge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/MDL-Order-Surge-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Capex-Challenge/69a113b7fa7d0695d1ab2f00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/MDL-Order-Surge-Fuels-Growth-Amidst-Capex-Challenge/69a113b7fa7d0695d1ab2f00</guid><description>Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders (MDL) is aggressively expanding its order book, targeting ₹1 lakh crore by H1 FY27 through major submarine and destroyer contracts. To support this, MDL is investing significantly in infrastructure, including a new greenfield shipyard. While revenue grew 14.6% in Q3 FY26, margins saw a slight dip. The company's valuation is considered reasonable against a backdrop of strong sector tailwinds and analyst optimism, but potential execution risks on mega-contracts and substantial capex demand careful scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:47:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a113b7fa7d0695d1ab2eff_1772164349870.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Smartphone Market Brace for Record Decline, ASP Surge Amid AI Memory Crunch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Smartphone-Market-Brace-for-Record-Decline-ASP-Surge-Amid-AI-Memory-Crunch/69a11169fa7d0695d1ab2d1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Smartphone-Market-Brace-for-Record-Decline-ASP-Surge-Amid-AI-Memory-Crunch/69a11169fa7d0695d1ab2d1f</guid><description>The global smartphone market faces its steepest annual decline ever in 2026, with shipments predicted to fall 12.9% to 1.12 billion units due to an AI-driven memory shortage. This supply shock is structurally resetting the industry, pushing average selling prices up 14% to a record $523, while larger players like Apple and Samsung are poised to gain market share at the expense of smaller Android vendors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:37:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11169fa7d0695d1ab2d1e_1772163574790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SpiceJet Promoter Stake Shift Fuels Investor Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Promoter-Stake-Shift-Fuels-Investor-Concern/69a11165fa7d0695d1ab2d08</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SpiceJet-Promoter-Stake-Shift-Fuels-Investor-Concern/69a11165fa7d0695d1ab2d08</guid><description>SpiceJet's promoter, Ajay Singh, saw a significant stake invoked and partially sold by Authum Investment due to outstanding dues from Spice Healthcare. This event, coupled with the airline's persistent YTD share depreciation and negative P/E, signals ongoing financial strain. Investors are weighing this against a recovering but competitive Indian aviation sector, where peers like IndiGo boast strong financials and Akasa Air pursues aggressive expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:37:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11165fa7d0695d1ab2d07_1772163581130.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KVB Target Raised, But Valuation Gap Widens vs Peers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KVB-Target-Raised-But-Valuation-Gap-Widens-vs-Peers/69a11162fa7d0695d1ab2cf1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KVB-Target-Raised-But-Valuation-Gap-Widens-vs-Peers/69a11162fa7d0695d1ab2cf1</guid><description>Emkay Global boosted Karur Vysya Bank's (KVB) share price target to ₹390, citing its transformation into a differentiated franchise with consistent growth and strong profitability. Despite a retained 'Buy' rating, KVB's stock trades near its 52-week high, with an elevated valuation that warrants comparison against peers like City Union Bank and Federal Bank, which currently trade at lower multiples. While KVB's operational metrics remain robust, a review of analyst consensus and forward-looking risk factors highlights potential divergences in future stock performance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:37:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11162fa7d0695d1ab2cf0_1772163749415.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VBL Faces Margin Squeeze Amidst RIL's Campa Offensive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VBL-Faces-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-RILs-Campa-Offensive/69a11091fa7d0695d1ab2b63</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VBL-Faces-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-RILs-Campa-Offensive/69a11091fa7d0695d1ab2b63</guid><description>Varun Beverages (VBL) anticipates a rebound in CY26 after a challenging CY25, driven by favorable weather and international expansion. However, Reliance Industries' disruptive pricing for its Campa Cola brand presents a significant competitive threat, potentially impacting VBL's ability to sustain margins and market share. Analysts maintain a 'Strong Buy' consensus, citing VBL's market leadership and growth potential, though its valuation is approaching premium levels.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:33:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11091fa7d0695d1ab2b62_1772163344720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NPS MSF: High-Octane Equity Risks Retail Investor Retirement</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NPS-MSF-High-Octane-Equity-Risks-Retail-Investor-Retirement/69a11075fa7d0695d1ab2b47</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/NPS-MSF-High-Octane-Equity-Risks-Retail-Investor-Retirement/69a11075fa7d0695d1ab2b47</guid><description>The National Pension System's (NPS) Multiple Scheme Framework (MSF) now permits up to 100% equity allocation for new contributions, a significant departure from previous caps. This enhanced flexibility, however, places the onus of asset allocation and risk management squarely on individual subscribers, as MSF schemes lack the age-based automatic rebalancing found in traditional NPS plans. Experts warn that this shift, particularly for those nearing retirement, significantly amplifies the risk of sequence of return issues and market volatility, potentially jeopardizing long-term corpus security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:33:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11075fa7d0695d1ab2b46_1772163343130.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NBCC Seeks RERA Exemption Amidst Supertech Revival</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCC-Seeks-RERA-Exemption-Amidst-Supertech-Revival/69a10ff9fa7d0695d1ab2ad3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/NBCC-Seeks-RERA-Exemption-Amidst-Supertech-Revival/69a10ff9fa7d0695d1ab2ad3</guid><description>State-owned NBCC is petitioning the Supreme Court for an exemption from RERA registration to complete 11 Supertech housing projects requiring fund infusion. This move is necessitated by RERA's rules against diverting funds between projects, a step NBCC deems essential for revival. Despite a similar exemption granted in the Amrapali case, this request underscores the complex financial and regulatory hurdles in large-scale real estate turnarounds, potentially impacting NBCC's financial flexibility and execution timelines. The projects involve over 50,000 homes, with substantial investment needed to complete units awaiting delivery.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a10ff9fa7d0695d1ab2ad2_1772163389746.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Broker Picks: Valuations, Sector Trends Scrutinized</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Broker-Picks-Valuations-Sector-Trends-Scrutinized/69a10da3fa7d0695d1ab2989</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Broker-Picks-Valuations-Sector-Trends-Scrutinized/69a10da3fa7d0695d1ab2989</guid><description>Bajaj Broking Research has identified Colgate-Palmolive (India) and Varun Beverages as top buy recommendations. The market remains range-bound, with Nifty consolidating between 25,350-25,900, and Bank Nifty showing relative strength. Analyst sentiment leans positive for these stocks, citing technical breakouts and strong growth outlooks, but investors must consider competitive pressures and macroeconomic volatility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:21:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a10da3fa7d0695d1ab2988_1772162789957.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vishal Mega Mart Block Deal Upsized, Promoter Exit Raises Valuation Questions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Vishal-Mega-Mart-Block-Deal-Upsized-Promoter-Exit-Raises-Valuation-Questions/69a10a60fa7d0695d1ab27fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Vishal-Mega-Mart-Block-Deal-Upsized-Promoter-Exit-Raises-Valuation-Questions/69a10a60fa7d0695d1ab27fb</guid><description>Vishal Mega Mart is under scrutiny as promoter Samayat Services LLP has significantly increased its planned block deal size to ₹7,500 crore, selling 6.5% of its stake at a discount. This aggressive divestment by a major shareholder, following a substantial exit in June 2025, contrasts sharply with CEO Gunender Kapur's optimistic outlook on India's consumption growth. The move comes despite positive Q3 results and strong analyst 'Buy' ratings, raising questions about the company's premium valuation and the true strategic rationale behind the PE-backed promoter's capital realization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 03:07:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a10a60fa7d0695d1ab27fa_1772162335737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NFRA Steps Up Audit Scrutiny, Targets Big 6</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NFRA-Steps-Up-Audit-Scrutiny-Targets-Big-6/69a107fcfa7d0695d1ab25e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NFRA-Steps-Up-Audit-Scrutiny-Targets-Big-6/69a107fcfa7d0695d1ab25e9</guid><description>India's National Financial Reporting Authority (NFRA) is finalizing inspection reports for ten audit firms, with release scheduled by the end of the current fiscal year, March 31, 2026. These reviews encompass firm-wide Standard on Quality Control (SQC) compliance and cover 42 specific audit engagements across the selected firms, including members of the 'big 6'. This intensified regulatory action signals NFRA's commitment to fostering transparency and robust financial practices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:57:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a107fcfa7d0695d1ab25e8_1772161135409.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Boom Masks Deeptech Execution Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Boom-Masks-Deeptech-Execution-Gap/69a107adfa7d0695d1ab2589</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Boom-Masks-Deeptech-Execution-Gap/69a107adfa7d0695d1ab2589</guid><description>AI powered a 37% jump in India's deeptech funding to $2.3 billion in 2025, but a critical 85% of seed ventures fail to reach Series A. Investors are more selective, prioritizing proven execution over early-stage potential, highlighting a significant gap between innovation and commercialization. This trend contrasts with the global AI frenzy, where India's share remains small.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:55:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a107adfa7d0695d1ab2588_1772161357869.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks Target Affluent as Personal Loans Go Premium</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Target-Affluent-as-Personal-Loans-Go-Premium/69a10712fa7d0695d1ab24e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Target-Affluent-as-Personal-Loans-Go-Premium/69a10712fa7d0695d1ab24e4</guid><description>Indian banks are observing a marked shift in personal loan demographics, with affluent and mass-affluent segments increasingly borrowing. This trend, driven by the allure of instant digital approvals and a desire to preserve long-term investments, sees individuals leveraging credit for lifestyle enhancements and perceived investments. Banks are recalibrating their strategies, tightening underwriting for riskier segments while actively pursuing higher-value clients through technologically advanced, rapid loan processing. This pivot signals a strategic repositioning of unsecured lending towards premium customer bases, aiming to balance profitability with evolving risk appetites in a dynamic market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:53:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a10712fa7d0695d1ab24e3_1772161114431.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Uber India's Losses Surge 1600% as Competition Intensifies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Uber-Indias-Losses-Surge-1600percent-as-Competition-Intensifies/69a10712fa7d0695d1ab24cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Uber-Indias-Losses-Surge-1600percent-as-Competition-Intensifies/69a10712fa7d0695d1ab24cd</guid><description>Uber India's FY25 financials reveal a stark contrast between marginal revenue growth and a dramatic surge in losses. Total sales rose 2.3% to ₹3,849 crore, yet operating losses expanded over twelvefold to ₹1,052.3 crore, and net losses skyrocketed by 1,600% to ₹1,512 crore. This performance highlights significant cost pressures and intense market competition, particularly from rivals like Rapido, forcing increased driver incentives that compressed net revenue from ride-hailing to just ₹88 crore.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:53:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a10712fa7d0695d1ab24cc_1772160945015.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DEE Development Secures First ₹58 Cr Seamless Pipe Orders from New Gujarat Plant</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DEE-Development-Secures-First-58-Cr-Seamless-Pipe-Orders-from-New-Gujarat-Plant/69a10621fa7d0695d1ab23e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DEE-Development-Secures-First-58-Cr-Seamless-Pipe-Orders-from-New-Gujarat-Plant/69a10621fa7d0695d1ab23e0</guid><description>DEE Development Engineers has won its first contracts for seamless pipes, valued at ₹58 Crores, from its newly commissioned forged seamless pipe plant in Anjar, Gujarat. These orders, set for execution by December 2026, signify the initial business secured for this new vertical and mark a crucial step in the company's manufacturing expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a10621fa7d0695d1ab23df_1772160645833.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ONGC Bull Spread: Capped Gains vs. Capital Outlay</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/ONGC-Bull-Spread-Capped-Gains-vs-Capital-Outlay/69a10370fa7d0695d1ab21dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/ONGC-Bull-Spread-Capped-Gains-vs-Capital-Outlay/69a10370fa7d0695d1ab21dd</guid><description>A bull call spread strategy on Oil and Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC) has been proposed, involving the purchase of 285 strike calls and the sale of 300 strike calls for March expiry, at a net debit of ₹4 per share (₹9,000 per lot). This structure offers a maximum profit of ₹24,750 if ONGC closes at or above ₹300 on expiry, with a breakeven point at ₹289. The recommendation is supported by strong technical indicators and futures data, but the limited upside and significant margin requirement warrant careful investor scrutiny amidst broader market conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:37:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a10370fa7d0695d1ab21dc_1772160232452.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pilots Programmable CBDC for Food Subsidies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Pilots-Programmable-CBDC-for-Food-Subsidies/69a1035dfa7d0695d1ab21a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Pilots-Programmable-CBDC-for-Food-Subsidies/69a1035dfa7d0695d1ab21a2</guid><description>India has initiated a pilot project in Puducherry to disburse food subsidies via its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC), the e-rupee. This initiative leverages programmable digital tokens, directly credited to beneficiaries' wallets, intended for exclusive use on foodgrains. The move aims to enhance transparency and curb leakages within the Public Distribution System (PDS), building on previous digital reforms. While lauded for potential efficiency gains, it highlights the evolving role of CBDC in welfare delivery and potential challenges related to digital access and state control.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:37:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1035dfa7d0695d1ab21a1_1772160047609.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia CEO Bets on AI Agents to Use, Not Replace, Software</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-CEO-Bets-on-AI-Agents-to-Use-Not-Replace-Software/69a102e3fa7d0695d1ab20bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-CEO-Bets-on-AI-Agents-to-Use-Not-Replace-Software/69a102e3fa7d0695d1ab20bd</guid><description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang asserted that artificial intelligence agents will act as 'tool users,' integrating with and augmenting established enterprise software rather than supplanting it. This perspective contrasts with market fears of AI cannibalizing the software sector. The company's optimistic sales forecast, driven by strong AI demand, reinforces its dominant position. Huang cited examples like ServiceNow and SAP as software platforms AI agents will leverage to boost productivity. Nvidia's fiscal fourth-quarter revenue surged 73% to $68.13 billion, and first-quarter guidance was set significantly above expectations at $78 billion, signaling sustained AI hardware demand.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:35:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a102e3fa7d0695d1ab20bc_1772159860715.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MTAR Tech: AI Fuel Surge, But Valuation Woes Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MTAR-Tech-AI-Fuel-Surge-But-Valuation-Woes-Loom/69a102dbfa7d0695d1ab20a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MTAR-Tech-AI-Fuel-Surge-But-Valuation-Woes-Loom/69a102dbfa7d0695d1ab20a6</guid><description>MTAR Technologies shares have climbed over 160% in the past year, propelled by its crucial role in Bloom Energy's fuel cell solutions for AI data centers. Despite a 'Buy' rating and a ₹4,810 price target from Motilal Oswal, the company's valuation appears stretched. While revenue growth is robust, past profit stagnation and significant reliance on a single major customer present considerable risks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:35:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a102dbfa7d0695d1ab20a5_1772160020312.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dividends, Deals, and Disruptions: India Inc's Mixed Signals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dividends-Deals-and-Disruptions-India-Incs-Mixed-Signals/69a10145fa7d0695d1ab0555</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dividends-Deals-and-Disruptions-India-Incs-Mixed-Signals/69a10145fa7d0695d1ab0555</guid><description>Indian corporations are buzzing with activity as Indian Oil Corporation and IRFC consider dividends, while Rail Vikas Nigam secures significant orders. However, Hindalco faces acquisition delays due to US government shutdowns, and the IT sector grapples with AI-driven disruption fears, leading to sector-wide underperformance. Real estate and energy sectors show mixed but generally stable outlooks amidst evolving global and domestic conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:28:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a10145fa7d0695d1ab0554_1772159847080.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India GDP Surge vs. Tech Slump: Market Brace for Data</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Surge-vs-Tech-Slump-Market-Brace-for-Data/69a1013bfa7d0695d1ab0539</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GDP-Surge-vs-Tech-Slump-Market-Brace-for-Data/69a1013bfa7d0695d1ab0539</guid><description>Indian markets are poised for a subdued open on February 27, 2026, tracking weaker GIFT Nifty futures and global sentiment influenced by tech sector volatility. Investors await India's Q3 FY26 GDP data, with projections suggesting robust growth exceeding 8%, a significant counterpoint to international headwinds. However, lingering concerns over sustained tech sector performance and geopolitical tensions will shape trading dynamics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:28:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1013bfa7d0695d1ab0538_1772159486536.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jio Financial Fuels Credit Arm with Rs 2,000 Cr Premium Bet</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jio-Financial-Fuels-Credit-Arm-with-Rs-2000-Cr-Premium-Bet/69a10088fa7d0695d1ab0412</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Jio-Financial-Fuels-Credit-Arm-with-Rs-2000-Cr-Premium-Bet/69a10088fa7d0695d1ab0412</guid><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd (JFSL) has infused Rs 2,000 crore into its wholly-owned subsidiary, Jio Credit Ltd, purchasing shares at a significant Rs 585.70 premium. This strategic capital allocation aims to bolster Jio Credit's business growth and operations, underscoring JFSL's ambition to capture a substantial share of India's expanding credit market. The move diversifies JFSL's financial services portfolio beyond its asset management joint venture, positioning it as a formidable player in the competitive lending landscape.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:25:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a10088fa7d0695d1ab0411_1772159245411.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Fog Weighs on Indian Markets; DII Support Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Fog-Weighs-on-Indian-Markets-DII-Support-Key/69a10086fa7d0695d1ab03fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Geopolitical-Fog-Weighs-on-Indian-Markets-DII-Support-Key/69a10086fa7d0695d1ab03fb</guid><description>Indian equity markets are poised for a cautious opening on February 27, 2026, influenced by escalating geopolitical tensions between the US and Iran. Despite global risk aversion, robust buying by Domestic Institutional Investors (DIIs) provided support on the previous day, contrasting with Foreign Institutional Investor (FII) outflows. The market's trajectory hinges on the interplay of these flows against geopolitical developments and the underlying strength indicated by controlled inflation and a stable monetary policy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 02:25:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a10086fa7d0695d1ab03fa_1772159593509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>