<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:45 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Mass Market Struggles Amidst Premium Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Mass-Market-Struggles-Amidst-Premium-Shift/699c72c4ee97f501b0ebdf81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Mass-Market-Struggles-Amidst-Premium-Shift/699c72c4ee97f501b0ebdf81</guid><description>The Indian December quarter revealed persistent weakness in mass consumption across apparel, jewellery, and food, as consumers grapple with inflation and stagnant real wages. Despite tax cuts and festive periods, demand for entry-level and middle-class products remained muted. Retailers are increasingly focusing on premiumization strategies to offset volume declines. Companies like Shoppers Stop and Page Industries are seeing slower demand at entry price points, while Titan Company faces pressure in its sub-₹1 lakh jewellery segment. Westlife Foodworld reported flat growth in the quick-service restaurant sector. Experts emphasize that sustained recovery hinges on actual income growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cipla proposes Achin Gupta as MD &amp; GCEO; P.R. Ramesh for Director re-appointment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Cipla-proposes-Achin-Gupta-as-MD-and-GCEO-PR-Ramesh-for-Director-re-appointment/699c7244ee97f501b0ebdee3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Cipla-proposes-Achin-Gupta-as-MD-and-GCEO-PR-Ramesh-for-Director-re-appointment/699c7244ee97f501b0ebdee3</guid><description>Cipla is seeking shareholder approval for significant leadership changes. Achin Gupta is proposed as the new Managing Director &amp; Global Chief Executive Officer for a five-year term starting April 1, 2026. P. R. Ramesh is also proposed for re-appointment as an Independent Director. The company has outlined remuneration details and an e-voting period for shareholders to cast their votes on these crucial appointments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:29:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c7244ee97f501b0ebdee2_1771860677868.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Global Capital for Climate Risk With ILS Framework</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Eyes-Global-Capital-for-Climate-Risk-With-ILS-Framework/699c6fb9ee97f501b0ebdc89</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Eyes-Global-Capital-for-Climate-Risk-With-ILS-Framework/699c6fb9ee97f501b0ebdc89</guid><description>The International Financial Services Centres Authority (IFSCA) is advancing a proposal to the Indian government for a specialized insurance framework enabling investment in insurance-linked securities (ILS) like catastrophe bonds. This strategic move aims to broaden domestic risk-sharing mechanisms and attract global capital to GIFT City. The initiative is projected to be formalized within months, following consultations. It addresses India's increasing vulnerability to climate-related disasters by creating sophisticated tools for risk transfer to capital markets, a sector experiencing robust global growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:18:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6fb9ee97f501b0ebdc88_1771860043989.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Policy Shift: New CPI Data Meets Inflation Target Review Uncertainty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Policy-Shift-New-CPI-Data-Meets-Inflation-Target-Review-Uncertainty/699c6f76ee97f501b0ebdc1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Policy-Shift-New-CPI-Data-Meets-Inflation-Target-Review-Uncertainty/699c6f76ee97f501b0ebdc1e</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has introduced a new Consumer Price Index (CPI) series, using 2024 prices and tracking 358 items, aimed at better reflecting household consumption and reducing data volatility. This comes as the central bank prepares for a mandated five-year review of its flexible inflation targeting (FIT) regime, with the current 4% target and 2-6% tolerance band under scrutiny. Governor Sanjay Malhotra indicated that upcoming April projections will incorporate the new methodology. Separately, he clarified that observed changes in US securities holdings are due to valuation shifts, not a strategic reduction, highlighting the impact of currency fluctuations on reserves.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:17:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6f76ee97f501b0ebdc1d_1771860867365.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aditya Ispat Sells Core Steel Unit for ₹3.68 Cr to Related Party</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Aditya-Ispat-Sells-Core-Steel-Unit-for-368-Cr-to-Related-Party/699c6f72ee97f501b0ebdc07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Aditya-Ispat-Sells-Core-Steel-Unit-for-368-Cr-to-Related-Party/699c6f72ee97f501b0ebdc07</guid><description>Aditya Ispat Limited's board has greenlit the slump sale of its entire non-alloy steel manufacturing and trading business to Jai Bapji Ispat Private Limited, a related party, for ₹3.68 crore. This strategic divestment, representing 97.75% of FY25 turnover and 88.85% of net worth, is deemed crucial for the company's survival amidst high debt and eroding net worth. Shareholder approval via postal ballot is pending.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:17:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6f72ee97f501b0ebdc06_1771859957277.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Auctions G-Sec 2035 Amid Large Borrowing Program</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Auctions-G-Sec-2035-Amid-Large-Borrowing-Program/699c6d3dee97f501b0ebd9ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Auctions-G-Sec-2035-Amid-Large-Borrowing-Program/699c6d3dee97f501b0ebd9ba</guid><description>The Government of India is set to auction its 6.48% Government Security maturing in 2035, seeking to raise ₹32,000 crore with an option for an additional ₹2,000 crore. This issuance is a component of the Centre's extensive market borrowing program designed to finance fiscal requirements and maintain liquidity in the bond markets. The auction, scheduled for February 27, 2026, involves participation from Primary Dealers through the RBI's e-Kuber system. Analysts are monitoring this issuance in the context of substantial overall debt supply and the Reserve Bank of India's steady monetary policy stance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:07:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6d3dee97f501b0ebd9b9_1771860087950.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shree Salasar Eyes Capital Infusion; Board to Weigh Fund Raising Feb 26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Shree-Salasar-Eyes-Capital-Infusion-Board-to-Weigh-Fund-Raising-Feb-26/699c6b8aee97f501b0ebd840</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Shree-Salasar-Eyes-Capital-Infusion-Board-to-Weigh-Fund-Raising-Feb-26/699c6b8aee97f501b0ebd840</guid><description>Shree Salasar Investments Limited has called a board meeting for February 26, 2026, to explore proposals for raising capital. The company may issue equity shares, convertible or non-convertible securities, or warrants. Any approved plan will require shareholder consent, potentially impacting ownership and future strategic moves.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6b8aee97f501b0ebd83f_1771858938015.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Surge on Tariff Fears, Safe Haven Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Surge-on-Tariff-Fears-Safe-Haven-Demand/699c6986ee97f501b0ebd610</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Surge-on-Tariff-Fears-Safe-Haven-Demand/699c6986ee97f501b0ebd610</guid><description>Gold and silver prices surged Monday, reaching three-week highs, fueled by escalating global trade uncertainties following a US Supreme Court ruling and retaliatory tariff increases. Investors sought refuge in precious metals as safe-haven demand intensified, overshadowing concerns about broader economic growth slowdowns projected for 2026. Central bank accumulation and expectations of future interest rate adjustments also underpin the precious metals complex. Gold futures traded around $5,171.20, while silver futures neared $86.575.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:51:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6986ee97f501b0ebd60f_1771861080788.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market Downturn Exposes Bata, Whirlpool, Zee Weaknesses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Market-Downturn-Exposes-Bata-Whirlpool-Zee-Weaknesses/699c690cee97f501b0ebd541</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Market-Downturn-Exposes-Bata-Whirlpool-Zee-Weaknesses/699c690cee97f501b0ebd541</guid><description>The Nifty 50 experienced its worst January in over a decade in 2026, with a 3.10% decline. This downturn has amplified pre-existing challenges for Bata India and Whirlpool of India, characterized by stretched valuations, poor revenue growth, and intense competition. Zee Entertainment Enterprises, while trading at lower multiples, faces its own set of headwinds including historical sales stagnation and significant regulatory scrutiny concerning governance and alleged fund diversion, creating a persistent overhang. These specific company struggles contrast sharply with the previously perceived market rally, underscoring sector-specific vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:49:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c690cee97f501b0ebd540_1771858330675.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Halves Exporter Benefits Amid Budgetary Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Halves-Exporter-Benefits-Amid-Budgetary-Squeeze/699c68f2ee97f501b0ebd52a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Halves-Exporter-Benefits-Amid-Budgetary-Squeeze/699c68f2ee97f501b0ebd52a</guid><description>India has halved exporter benefits under the RoDTEP scheme, cutting rates and value caps by 50% as per a February 23, 2026, Directorate General of Foreign Trade notification. This move, linked to reduced FY27 budgetary allocation, is projected to increase exporters' operational costs, potentially squeezing margins and diminishing competitiveness. Experts warn this could deter smaller firms and impact order wins in price-sensitive global markets facing weak demand and supply disruptions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c68f2ee97f501b0ebd529_1771858333225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Strategic Capital Shifts Signal Sectoral Rebalancing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Strategic-Capital-Shifts-Signal-Sectoral-Rebalancing/699c67f5ee97f501b0ebd3fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Strategic-Capital-Shifts-Signal-Sectoral-Rebalancing/699c67f5ee97f501b0ebd3fc</guid><description>February 23, 2026, witnessed substantial stake adjustments across diverse market segments. Promoters rebalanced holdings in Edelweiss Financial Services, while institutional investors acquired stakes in Dudigital Global and Jasub Property Holdings increased its position in Cohance Lifesciences. These transactions reflect active capital deployment and a strategic reassessment of value across financial services, visa processing, pharmaceuticals, and media sectors. Asian Paints and Network 18 also experienced significant promoter-level and strategic entity share exchanges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:45:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c67f5ee97f501b0ebd3fb_1771858458806.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Russia Tech Pact Targets Rare Earth Dominance, Drives Self-Reliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Russia-Tech-Pact-Targets-Rare-Earth-Dominance-Drives-Self-Reliance/699c6776ee97f501b0ebd31a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Russia-Tech-Pact-Targets-Rare-Earth-Dominance-Drives-Self-Reliance/699c6776ee97f501b0ebd31a</guid><description>India's TEXMiN Foundation, part of IIT (ISM) Dhanbad, has signed an MoU with Russia's GIREDMET to collaborate on rare earth and critical mineral technologies. This strategic partnership aims to bolster India's self-reliance, focusing on areas like neodymium-iron-boron magnets and lithium-ion battery recycling. The collaboration aligns with India's National Critical Mineral Mission, seeking to accelerate technology translation from research to pilot-scale validation amidst increasing global supply chain scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:43:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6776ee97f501b0ebd319_1771858646835.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Bonds: Yields Test 6.8% Amid Record Supply &amp; Global Static</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/India-Bonds-Yields-Test-68percent-Amid-Record-Supply-and-Global-Static/699c66d9ee97f501b0ebd1da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/India-Bonds-Yields-Test-68percent-Amid-Record-Supply-and-Global-Static/699c66d9ee97f501b0ebd1da</guid><description>Invesco Mutual Fund projects a further steepening of India's yield curve, anticipating the 10-year benchmark to trade between 6.60%-6.80% in the coming months. This outlook is set against a backdrop of significant fiscal supply pressures, with total sovereign borrowing estimated around ₹30.5 trillion for FY27. While domestic spreads in certain segments remain attractive, the market faces substantial absorption challenges and increasing global economic headwinds, including a volatile rupee and varied central bank policies abroad. The Reserve Bank of India's (RBI) liquidity management and Open Market Operations (OMOs) are expected to be crucial in anchoring yields.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c66d9ee97f501b0ebd1d9_1771857771413.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cheesecake Factory Bakery Eyes India Amidst Stiff Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cheesecake-Factory-Bakery-Eyes-India-Amidst-Stiff-Competition/699c668aee97f501b0ebd184</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Cheesecake-Factory-Bakery-Eyes-India-Amidst-Stiff-Competition/699c668aee97f501b0ebd184</guid><description>The Cheesecake Factory Bakery is entering India through a licensing deal with The Gourmet Cafe, injecting an estimated $60 million to launch 55 outlets within five years. The first store opened in Bengaluru, with plans for national expansion. This move taps into India's rapidly growing premium dessert and cafe market, driven by increasing consumer spending and global brand interest, though it faces intense competition from established players and agile local brands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:39:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c668aee97f501b0ebd183_1771858138006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's MF AUM Surges, Signaling Maturing Investor Behavior</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-MF-AUM-Surges-Signaling-Maturing-Investor-Behavior/699c65b1ee97f501b0ebd032</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-MF-AUM-Surges-Signaling-Maturing-Investor-Behavior/699c65b1ee97f501b0ebd032</guid><description>The Indian mutual fund industry's Assets Under Management (AUM) reached ₹82 lakh crore, now comprising 32% of bank deposits. This growth, driven by a 20% year-on-year increase in MF AUM against a 12% rise in bank deposits, highlights a significant shift in household savings. Sustained SIP inflows, hitting ₹31,002 crore in January 2026, coupled with a 13% rise in unique investors to 6.02 crore, underscore a maturing investor mindset where volatility is increasingly used for cost averaging rather than triggering redemptions. This trend signals a long-term transition from traditional savings instruments to market-linked assets, supported by enhanced distribution channels.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:35:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c65b1ee97f501b0ebd031_1771857819439.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Allcargo Terminals signs promoter land lease MoU for Gurugram PFT</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Allcargo-Terminals-signs-promoter-land-lease-MoU-for-Gurugram-PFT/699c651fee97f501b0ebcf60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Allcargo-Terminals-signs-promoter-land-lease-MoU-for-Gurugram-PFT/699c651fee97f501b0ebcf60</guid><description>Allcargo Terminals Limited (ATL) has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with its promoter group entities, Allcargo Inland Park Private Limited (AIPPL) and TransIndia Real Estate Limited (TREL), to explore leasing land in Gurugram, Haryana. The proposed transaction aims to establish a Private Freight Terminal (PFT) or Inland Container Depot (ICD), with ATL paying an initial deposit of ₹5.00 crore. This move is expected to bolster the company's capacity for handling container volumes and contribute positively to its profitability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:33:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c651fee97f501b0ebcf5f_1771857338569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Carney's Asia Tour: Canada's Trade Diversification Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Carneys-Asia-Tour-Canadas-Trade-Diversification-Pivot/699c64acee97f501b0ebcedb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Carneys-Asia-Tour-Canadas-Trade-Diversification-Pivot/699c64acee97f501b0ebcedb</guid><description>Prime Minister Mark Carney's upcoming diplomatic mission to India, Australia, and Japan (Feb 26-Mar 7, 2026) signals Canada's strategic pivot to de-risk its economy. Amid rising geopolitical uncertainty and tariff risks, Ottawa seeks to diversify trade beyond traditional U.S. and EU markets, attract critical investment, and bolster supply chain resilience. The tour prioritizes advanced technologies like AI, clean energy, and critical minerals, aiming to forge new economic partnerships crucial for Canada's long-term prosperity and security.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:31:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c64acee97f501b0ebceda_1771859496932.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stablecoin Surge Fuels Treasury Bill Shortage Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Stablecoin-Surge-Fuels-Treasury-Bill-Shortage-Fears/699c6161ee97f501b0ebcbe8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Stablecoin-Surge-Fuels-Treasury-Bill-Shortage-Fears/699c6161ee97f501b0ebcbe8</guid><description>The stablecoin market, projected to hit $2 trillion by 2028, is expected to drive up to $1 trillion in new demand for U.S. Treasury bills. This influx, combined with Federal Reserve purchases, could create a $0.9 trillion shortfall in T-bill supply, forcing the Treasury to re-evaluate issuance strategies. Major issuers like Tether and Circle are already significant buyers, channeling crypto capital into U.S. debt, but this shift also introduces new market fragilities and regulatory considerations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6161ee97f501b0ebcbe7_1771857275411.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dishman Carbogen Amcis Rating Cut; Company Highlights Performance Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Dishman-Carbogen-Amcis-Rating-Cut-Company-Highlights-Performance-Gains/699c6160ee97f501b0ebcbd1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Dishman-Carbogen-Amcis-Rating-Cut-Company-Highlights-Performance-Gains/699c6160ee97f501b0ebcbd1</guid><description>Dishman Carbogen Amcis has clarified a credit rating downgrade by India Ratings to 'A' (long-term) and 'A1' (short-term) with a negative outlook. The company emphasized that the downgrade does not reflect its improving business and financial performance, pointing to enhanced net leverage and strengthening EBITDA margins. The rating agency cited persistently high debt levels and contracting margins as reasons for the revision.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c6160ee97f501b0ebcbd0_1771856381353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wipro Bets Big on AI, But Market Doubts Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Wipro-Bets-Big-on-AI-But-Market-Doubts-Linger/699c60daee97f501b0ebca9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Wipro-Bets-Big-on-AI-But-Market-Doubts-Linger/699c60daee97f501b0ebca9e</guid><description>Wipro's Chief Strategist Hari Shetty advocates for AI as a net job creator and opportunity for 'autonomous enterprises,' countering industry fears. Despite World Economic Forum estimates projecting 170 million new jobs globally, Wipro faces market skepticism due to slower deal conversion, persistent AI disruption concerns, and a mixed analyst outlook. Competitors like Infosys are surging on AI partnerships, while Wipro's stock trades near 52-week lows with mixed analyst ratings and a conservative growth forecast.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:14:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c60daee97f501b0ebca9d_1771856418748.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Export Quality Push: ₹25K Cr Mission Tackles Global Standards</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indias-Export-Quality-Push-25K-Cr-Mission-Tackles-Global-Standards/699c5fa1ee97f501b0ebc808</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/Indias-Export-Quality-Push-25K-Cr-Mission-Tackles-Global-Standards/699c5fa1ee97f501b0ebc808</guid><description>India has initiated a ₹25,060 crore Export Promotion Mission (EPM) designed to support exporters in meeting stringent international quality and regulatory standards, such as the EU's CBAM and REACH. This six-year initiative is critical for leveraging nine recent Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) and enhancing global competitiveness, particularly for micro and small enterprises. The program addresses the escalating costs of compliance and the necessity for high-quality benchmarks to secure market access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:09:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5fa1ee97f501b0ebc807_1771857514851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Power inks 702 MW wind turbine deal with Vayona Energy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Power-inks-702-MW-wind-turbine-deal-with-Vayona-Energy/699c5f99ee97f501b0ebc7ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Power-inks-702-MW-wind-turbine-deal-with-Vayona-Energy/699c5f99ee97f501b0ebc7ec</guid><description>Vayona Energy, backed by the Murguppa Group, has secured a significant contract to supply 195 SG 3.6-145 wind turbines to Tata Power Renewable Energy Ltd (TPREL). This deal will add 702 MW of renewable capacity across Karnataka, Maharashtra, and Tamil Nadu. Vayona operates two manufacturing plants and manages a portfolio exceeding 12 GW in assets. Prashant Jain, Executive Vice Chairman of Vayona Energy, highlighted the company's value for TPREL's trust and anticipation for expanded collaboration. This transaction underscores the robust growth and investment momentum within India's wind energy sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:09:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5f99ee97f501b0ebc7eb_1771855970985.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Telcos Brace for ARPU Surge Amidst Widening Investment Chasm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Telcos-Brace-for-ARPU-Surge-Amidst-Widening-Investment-Chasm/699c5f92ee97f501b0ebc7d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Telcos-Brace-for-ARPU-Surge-Amidst-Widening-Investment-Chasm/699c5f92ee97f501b0ebc7d4</guid><description>Indian telecom operators are set to see Average Revenue Per User (ARPU) climb 13-15% in FY27, fueled by anticipated headline tariff hikes and sustained data consumption growth. While Vodafone Idea (Vi) received a reprieve on its Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) dues, analysts highlight a significant and persistent gap in network investment compared to rivals Bharti Airtel and Reliance Jio. This disparity underscores a diverging outlook, with market leaders poised to leverage increased ARPU for further expansion, while Vi focuses on stabilization amidst financial constraints.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:09:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5f92ee97f501b0ebc7d3_1771855917865.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airtel Abandons Perplexity Partnership for Adobe Amidst Strategic Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Airtel-Abandons-Perplexity-Partnership-for-Adobe-Amidst-Strategic-Pivot/699c5f84ee97f501b0ebc7b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Airtel-Abandons-Perplexity-Partnership-for-Adobe-Amidst-Strategic-Pivot/699c5f84ee97f501b0ebc7b4</guid><description>Bharti Airtel concluded its 12-month Perplexity Pro free access partnership in January 2026, a surprising move given nearly three-fourths of its 360 million customers engaged with the offer. The telecom giant is now partnering with Adobe, indicating a significant shift in its digital services strategy. The collaboration with Perplexity, valued at ₹17,000 annually per user, provided access to advanced AI models and research tools. The reasons for the abrupt conclusion, despite strong user response, remain opaque, further highlighted by Perplexity AI's lack of comment and its CEO's absence from a key industry event.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:09:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5f84ee97f501b0ebc7b3_1771856084481.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Finance Allots ₹1000 Cr NCDs; 7-yr Debt at 8.66% Coupon</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Cholamandalam-Finance-Allots-1000-Cr-NCDs-7-yr-Debt-at-866percent-Coupon/699c5f08ee97f501b0ebc717</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Cholamandalam-Finance-Allots-1000-Cr-NCDs-7-yr-Debt-at-866percent-Coupon/699c5f08ee97f501b0ebc717</guid><description>Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company Limited has issued unsecured subordinated non-convertible securities worth ₹1000 crore. The fundraising, which includes a ₹500 crore green shoe option, aims to augment the company's capital base and support its growth strategy. These 7-year securities carry a fixed coupon rate of 8.66% per annum, providing long-term, predictable financing costs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:07:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5f08ee97f501b0ebc716_1771856258530.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Homes EGM: Shareholders vote on capital hike, RPTs amid debt crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Homes-EGM-Shareholders-vote-on-capital-hike-RPTs-amid-debt-crisis/699c5e1aee97f501b0ebc60e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Homes-EGM-Shareholders-vote-on-capital-hike-RPTs-amid-debt-crisis/699c5e1aee97f501b0ebc60e</guid><description>India Homes Limited (formerly India Steel Works Limited) convened an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on February 23, 2026. Key agenda items included proposals to increase authorized share capital and approve significant related party transactions, including a ₹100 crore land deal with the Executive Chairman. The meeting comes amid severe financial distress, marked by a soaring Debt-to-Equity ratio of 3.88 and a negative Debt Service Coverage Ratio of -0.24. Shareholders also voted on appointing a new independent director.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5e1aee97f501b0ebc60d_1771856314782.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Reset: India Faces Volatility Amid Policy Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Tariff-Reset-India-Faces-Volatility-Amid-Policy-Shifts/699c5d2fee97f501b0ebc4d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Tariff-Reset-India-Faces-Volatility-Amid-Policy-Shifts/699c5d2fee97f501b0ebc4d1</guid><description>The United States' tariff landscape is in flux following a Supreme Court decision on February 20, 2026, invalidating previous emergency levies. President Trump's administration quickly pivoted, announcing a new 15% global tariff effective February 24, 2026. This move replaces specific bilateral agreements and creates a dual impact: certain Indian sectors like textiles and machinery gain from lower overall rates compared to prior peaks, while others, particularly gems and jewelry, face renewed tariff burdens. The sudden policy pivot introduces significant uncertainty for India's export strategy, even as the nation navigates robust economic growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:59:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5d2fee97f501b0ebc4d0_1771855817269.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anthem Biosciences converts ₹275 Cr loan to equity in Neoanthem subsidiary</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Anthem-Biosciences-converts-275-Cr-loan-to-equity-in-Neoanthem-subsidiary/699c5c3aee97f501b0ebc3be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Anthem-Biosciences-converts-275-Cr-loan-to-equity-in-Neoanthem-subsidiary/699c5c3aee97f501b0ebc3be</guid><description>Anthem Biosciences executed a first amendment to its loan agreement with its subsidiary, Neoanthem Lifesciences, allowing an additional ₹275 crore of loan to be converted into equity. This move increases Neoanthem's equity funding from its parent and is part of a larger ₹550 crore financial assistance package. The company stated the transaction is on an arm's length basis and will not materially impact consolidated financials, though it's subject to future approvals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:55:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5c3aee97f501b0ebc3bd_1771855370297.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JTL Industries Acquires Powersol Metalcraft Stake for ₹8.1 Cr, Boosts Steel Operations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JTL-Industries-Acquires-Powersol-Metalcraft-Stake-for-81-Cr-Boosts-Steel-Operations/699c5acfee97f501b0ebc231</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JTL-Industries-Acquires-Powersol-Metalcraft-Stake-for-81-Cr-Boosts-Steel-Operations/699c5acfee97f501b0ebc231</guid><description>JTL Industries' Board of Directors has approved the acquisition of a 47.97% stake in Powersol Metalcraft Limited (PML) for ₹8.10 crore. The move will make PML, a manufacturer of hot-rolled steel sections, an associate company of JTL, bolstering JTL's strategic expansion and diversification efforts in the steel sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:49:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5acfee97f501b0ebc230_1771854678361.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nuvama's AA Rating Lifted, But Valuation and Risks Demand Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nuvamas-AA-Rating-Lifted-But-Valuation-and-Risks-Demand-Scrutiny/699c5a57ee97f501b0ebc136</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nuvamas-AA-Rating-Lifted-But-Valuation-and-Risks-Demand-Scrutiny/699c5a57ee97f501b0ebc136</guid><description>Nuvama Wealth Management received a long-term rating upgrade to AA with a stable outlook from ICRA. While this reflects operational scale and solid profitability, its Price-to-Earnings ratio appears high relative to some peers, and the company navigates intense competition, technological reliance, and evolving regulatory shifts. Analyst consensus remains bullish with significant upside targets, but a critical examination of inherent risks is imperative.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:47:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5a57ee97f501b0ebc135_1771855346417.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UP Secures ₹6,650 Cr Singapore Investment for Mega Projects</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UP-Secures-6650-Cr-Singapore-Investment-for-Mega-Projects/699c5970ee97f501b0ebbfe6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UP-Secures-6650-Cr-Singapore-Investment-for-Mega-Projects/699c5970ee97f501b0ebbfe6</guid><description>Uttar Pradesh Chief Minister Yogi Adityanath has secured ₹6,650 crore in investment commitments from Singapore-based Universal Success Group for three major projects: an international township near Jewar Airport (₹3,500 crore, 12,000 jobs), a logistics park on the Kanpur-Lucknow corridor (₹650 crore, 7,500 jobs), and a 40 MW hyperscale data center in Noida/Greater Noida (₹2,500 crore, 1,500 jobs). These ventures are slated to create approximately 20,000 jobs, aiming to bolster the state's economy and employment landscape. This development aligns with UP's ongoing efforts to attract foreign direct investment and enhance its position as a preferred business destination.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:43:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5970ee97f501b0ebbfe5_1771854432339.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bangladesh Eyes Adani Power Deal Renegotiation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Bangladesh-Eyes-Adani-Power-Deal-Renegotiation/699c596cee97f501b0ebbfcf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Bangladesh-Eyes-Adani-Power-Deal-Renegotiation/699c596cee97f501b0ebbfcf</guid><description>Bangladesh's newly elected administration is prioritizing the renegotiation of its substantial power purchase agreement with India's Adani Power Ltd. Officials cite high coal procurement costs and electricity tariffs as primary concerns, making contract revision a top agenda item for the government. The existing 25-year Power Purchase Agreement (PPA), established in 2017, has been a source of contention, marked by past supply disruptions due to unpaid bills and allegations of inflated costs. This move signals a potential recalibration of energy sourcing and bilateral ties.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:43:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c596cee97f501b0ebbfce_1771854441805.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manilam Industries IPO Fully Subscribed Amidst Sector Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Manilam-Industries-IPO-Fully-Subscribed-Amidst-Sector-Growth/699c5916ee97f501b0ebbeb5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Manilam-Industries-IPO-Fully-Subscribed-Amidst-Sector-Growth/699c5916ee97f501b0ebbeb5</guid><description>Manilam Industries India's initial public offering closed oversubscribed on its second day, attracting significant interest from non-institutional and retail investors. The company aims to raise nearly Rs 40 crore to fund capital expenditure, debt repayment, and working capital needs within the expanding Indian decorative laminates sector. While market conditions favor growth, the company faces competition from established players and operates on the SME platform, presenting distinct investment considerations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:41:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5916ee97f501b0ebbeb4_1771854433004.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Noida Airport Inauguration Signals UP's Economic Transformation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airport-Inauguration-Signals-UPs-Economic-Transformation/699c581dee97f501b0ebbca9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Noida-Airport-Inauguration-Signals-UPs-Economic-Transformation/699c581dee97f501b0ebbca9</guid><description>Noida International Airport is set for inauguration next month, a landmark ₹29,000 crore project developed by Zurich Airport International AG. The greenfield airport aims for an initial capacity of 12 million passengers annually, expanding to 70 million, and is strategically positioned as a major logistics and industrial catalyst for Uttar Pradesh. Beyond easing air traffic congestion at Delhi's Indira Gandhi International Airport, the project is anticipated to drive significant economic growth, trade expansion, and job creation in the region, aligning with the state's ambitious economic development goals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:37:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c581dee97f501b0ebbca8_1771854051968.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CIE India Q4 CY25 Sales Hit Record ₹15.4Bn; Costs Dent Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CIE-India-Q4-CY25-Sales-Hit-Record-154Bn-Costs-Dent-Margins/699c5803ee97f501b0ebbc87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CIE-India-Q4-CY25-Sales-Hit-Record-154Bn-Costs-Dent-Margins/699c5803ee97f501b0ebbc87</guid><description>CIE Automotive India reported record Q4 CY2025 sales of INR 15.4 billion, driven by strong domestic demand across vehicle segments. However, one-off costs and rising energy tariffs impacted EBITDA margins. The company is strategically expanding Indian capacity while navigating restructuring and competitive pressures in its European operations, particularly from Chinese EV makers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:37:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5803ee97f501b0ebbc86_1771854110152.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Signpost India Secures ₹450 Cr Kolkata Streetscape Advertising Rights</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Signpost-India-Secures-450-Cr-Kolkata-Streetscape-Advertising-Rights/699c5794ee97f501b0ebbb7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Signpost-India-Secures-450-Cr-Kolkata-Streetscape-Advertising-Rights/699c5794ee97f501b0ebbb7c</guid><description>Signpost India Limited has been awarded exclusive outdoor advertising rights for key streets in Kolkata under the 'Kolkata Streetscape Renaissance' Project. The 10+2 year contract with the Kolkata Municipal Corporation is set to generate approximately Rs. 450 crore in gross advertising revenue, marking a significant expansion for the company into a major metro city.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:35:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5794ee97f501b0ebbb7b_1771854696569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pace Digitek subsidiary secures ₹1,587 cr RIL battery pack order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pace-Digitek-subsidiary-secures-1587-cr-RIL-battery-pack-order/699c578bee97f501b0ebbb65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pace-Digitek-subsidiary-secures-1587-cr-RIL-battery-pack-order/699c578bee97f501b0ebbb65</guid><description>Pace Digitek's subsidiary, Lineage Power, has won a significant ₹1,587.10 million purchase order from Reliance Industries for Li-ion battery packs. The domestic order is slated for completion by August 31, 2026, marking a crucial win for the subsidiary in the burgeoning energy storage sector. This deal validates Lineage Power's manufacturing capabilities, bringing a major conglomerate into its client fold.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:35:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c578bee97f501b0ebbb64_1771854156181.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABSL AMC Launches BSE Top 10 Banks ETF</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ABSL-AMC-Launches-BSE-Top-10-Banks-ETF/699c5721ee97f501b0ebba7b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ABSL-AMC-Launches-BSE-Top-10-Banks-ETF/699c5721ee97f501b0ebba7b</guid><description>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC has launched the BSE Top 10 Banks ETF, an open-ended fund replicating the BSE Top 10 Banks Total Return Index. This ETF targets India's 10 largest banks by free-float market capitalization, aiming to capitalize on the banking sector's resilience and growth momentum. The fund's structure as a non-F&amp;O compliant index is designed to reduce stock-level dispersion. The New Fund Offer closes on February 25, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:33:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5721ee97f501b0ebba7a_1771853751533.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PVP Ventures Q3 Revenue Jumps 225%; Losses Persist Amidst ₹1,375 Cr GST Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVP-Ventures-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-225percent-Losses-Persist-Amidst-1375-Cr-GST-Demand/699c54b7ee97f501b0ebb7c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/PVP-Ventures-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-225percent-Losses-Persist-Amidst-1375-Cr-GST-Demand/699c54b7ee97f501b0ebb7c6</guid><description>PVP Ventures reported a Q3 FY26 net loss of ₹4.06 crore on consolidated income of ₹17.09 crore, despite a significant 225% YoY revenue jump. The company faces substantial risks including a ₹1,375 crore GST demand, SEBI penalties, and concerns over receivables from a financially weak related party, PHML. Negative reserves further highlight balance sheet stress.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:23:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c54b7ee97f501b0ebb7c5_1771853145821.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cistro Telelink NCLT nod for 40% capital cut to clear ₹2 Cr losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Cistro-Telelink-NCLT-nod-for-40percent-capital-cut-to-clear-2-Cr-losses/699c5457ee97f501b0ebb71d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Cistro-Telelink-NCLT-nod-for-40percent-capital-cut-to-clear-2-Cr-losses/699c5457ee97f501b0ebb71d</guid><description>Cistro Telelink Limited has secured National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) approval for a significant reduction in its paid-up equity share capital by approximately 40%. The capital will be reduced from ₹5.13 crore to ₹3.08 crore, amounting to ₹2.05 crore, to offset accumulated losses of ₹2.16 crore as of March 31, 2024. The move is aimed at cleaning up the balance sheet and potentially attracting future investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:21:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699c5457ee97f501b0ebb71c_1771853194288.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>