<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:38:28 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Chip Ambition: Design-Led ISM 2.0 Eyes Global Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Chip-Ambition-Design-Led-ISM-20-Eyes-Global-Hub/69872e90b81b2b81dcfc665f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Chip-Ambition-Design-Led-ISM-20-Eyes-Global-Hub/69872e90b81b2b81dcfc665f</guid><description>India's India Semiconductor Mission (ISM) 2.0 will prioritize domestic chip design capabilities and ecosystem strengthening, as announced by Union Minister Ashwini Vaishnaw. With a Rs 1,000 crore allocation for FY 2026-27, the mission aims to foster design startups, integrate the full semiconductor value chain, and develop advanced manufacturing at nodes as small as 2 nanometers. This strategic shift underscores India's ambition to leverage its talent pool for deep tech innovation and global market presence, building on the foundation of ISM 1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finkurve Financial's AUM Soars 118%, But Debt Levels Surge to 1.67x</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Finkurve-Financials-AUM-Soars-118percent-But-Debt-Levels-Surge-to-167x/69872e73b81b2b81dcfc654c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Finkurve-Financials-AUM-Soars-118percent-But-Debt-Levels-Surge-to-167x/69872e73b81b2b81dcfc654c</guid><description>Finkurve Financial Services reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with Assets Under Management (AUM) leaping 118.63% YoY to ₹833.15 Cr. Total income climbed 31.19% and PAT rose 23.86% to ₹6.98 Cr. However, the company's Debt-to-Equity ratio nearly doubled to 1.67, and Return on Equity/Assets declined, signaling potential leverage risks alongside aggressive expansion fuelled by recent fundraising and a 36% branch network increase.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nahar Poly Films Q3 Profit Surges 147% on Other Income, Revenue Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nahar-Poly-Films-Q3-Profit-Surges-147percent-on-Other-Income-Revenue-Dips/69872d82b81b2b81dcfc6363</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nahar-Poly-Films-Q3-Profit-Surges-147percent-on-Other-Income-Revenue-Dips/69872d82b81b2b81dcfc6363</guid><description>Nahar Poly Films reported a robust 147.3% year-on-year surge in standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹1,628.96 lakhs for Q3 FY26. This exceptional growth was primarily driven by a substantial 182% increase in 'Other Income' to ₹1,164.10 lakhs, alongside a 6.75% reduction in total expenses. However, revenue from operations saw a marginal 2.6% dip to ₹16,747.09 lakhs. Consolidated PAT also soared by 157.2% YoY. The company did not provide management guidance or future outlook.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finkurve Financial Surges 119% in AUM, But Margins and Leverage Rise Worry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Finkurve-Financial-Surges-119percent-in-AUM-But-Margins-and-Leverage-Rise-Worry/69872d1db81b2b81dcfc61ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Finkurve-Financial-Surges-119percent-in-AUM-But-Margins-and-Leverage-Rise-Worry/69872d1db81b2b81dcfc61ec</guid><description>Finkurve Financial Services reported a robust Q3 FY26 with Assets Under Management (AUM) soaring 119% YoY to ₹833.15 Cr and disbursements up 38% to ₹1,374 Cr. The company is strategically shifting its focus to retail gold loans, now comprising 93% of its loan book. However, Net Interest Margins compressed to 15.2% from 17.7% YoY, and Debt-to-Equity rose to 1.7x from 0.9x, signalling increased leverage and pressure on profitability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Star Delta Transformers Sees Revenue Surge 61%, Profit Declines Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Star-Delta-Transformers-Sees-Revenue-Surge-61percent-Profit-Declines-Sharply/69872d0ab81b2b81dcfc6126</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Star-Delta-Transformers-Sees-Revenue-Surge-61percent-Profit-Declines-Sharply/69872d0ab81b2b81dcfc6126</guid><description>Star Delta Transformers reported a robust 61.30% year-on-year revenue growth in Q3 FY26, reaching ₹53.30 Cr. However, Profit After Tax (PAT) declined 3.78% YoY to ₹2.06 Cr and a significant 48.11% QoQ to ₹2.06 Cr, leading to a sharp compression in PAT margins to 3.87% from 8.99% in the previous quarter. For the nine months, revenue grew 21.58% YoY while PAT rose 9.76% YoY.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nahar Poly Films PAT Surges 147% On Other Income, Revenue Dips</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nahar-Poly-Films-PAT-Surges-147percent-On-Other-Income-Revenue-Dips/69872cb3b81b2b81dcfc5fd0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nahar-Poly-Films-PAT-Surges-147percent-On-Other-Income-Revenue-Dips/69872cb3b81b2b81dcfc5fd0</guid><description>Nahar Poly Films announced a substantial 147.2% year-on-year jump in standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹1,628.96 lakhs for Q3 FY26, fueled by a striking 182.3% surge in 'Other Income'. However, revenue from operations declined 3.2% YoY to ₹16,747.09 lakhs. Consolidated PAT similarly surged 157.1% to ₹1,932.50 lakhs. Despite strong YoY profitability, both revenue and PAT saw a quarter-on-quarter decline, with no management guidance provided.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Diffusion Engineers Surges 27% Revenue, Orders Double Amid Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diffusion-Engineers-Surges-27percent-Revenue-Orders-Double-Amid-Expansion/69872c96b81b2b81dcfc5ee8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diffusion-Engineers-Surges-27percent-Revenue-Orders-Double-Amid-Expansion/69872c96b81b2b81dcfc5ee8</guid><description>Diffusion Engineers Limited reported a strong Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue up 27.31% YoY to ₹1,008.24 million and PAT surging 69.14% to ₹120.11 million. The company's order book nearly doubled to ₹1,934.08 million, driven by heavy engineering. Capacity expansions are on track, funded by internal accruals and IPO proceeds. A diversification move into Tejorup Sunmay Systems Pvt. Ltd. was also approved.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SEPC Posts Record Growth, But Auditor Flags Asset Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEPC-Posts-Record-Growth-But-Auditor-Flags-Asset-Risks/69872c1fb81b2b81dcfc5d66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEPC-Posts-Record-Growth-But-Auditor-Flags-Asset-Risks/69872c1fb81b2b81dcfc5d66</guid><description>SEPC Limited reported a substantial 114.1% YoY jump in consolidated revenue to ₹34,206.71 lakhs for Q3 FY26, with PAT soaring 236.7%. However, the strong top-line growth is overshadowed by a qualified review report from statutory auditors MSKA &amp; Associates LLP. The auditors raised significant concerns about the recoverability of Non-Current Contract Assets and Trade Receivables, as well as the recognition of Deferred Tax Assets, casting doubt on the reported financial health. Standalone performance showed a decline.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Destination Weddings Fuel Travel Insurance Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indian-Destination-Weddings-Fuel-Travel-Insurance-Boom/69872ba7b81b2b81dcfc5c1f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indian-Destination-Weddings-Fuel-Travel-Insurance-Boom/69872ba7b81b2b81dcfc5c1f</guid><description>The surge in Indian destination weddings is creating a structural shift in travel insurance. Policybazaar data reveals a significant rise in policy purchases linked to these events, driven by longer, multi-generational trips and an increased focus on comprehensive medical coverage and high sum insured values. This trend is expanding the market beyond traditional segments and highlighting evolving customer priorities.

PB Fintech, the parent company of Policybazaar, holds a dominant position in India's digital insurance marketplace and is well-positioned to capitalize on this evolving demand. The company's robust financial performance, with strong revenue and profit growth in Q3 FY26, reflects its operational strength amidst a growing Indian travel insurance market projected to reach over USD 4 billion by 2031.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fitch Lifts Biocon Biologics Outlook Amid Parent's Leverage Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Fitch-Lifts-Biocon-Biologics-Outlook-Amid-Parents-Leverage-Drive/69872b2ab81b2b81dcfc5a94</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Fitch-Lifts-Biocon-Biologics-Outlook-Amid-Parents-Leverage-Drive/69872b2ab81b2b81dcfc5a94</guid><description>Fitch Ratings has upgraded Biocon Biologics Limited's (BBL) outlook to Positive from Stable, affirming its 'BB-' Issuer Default Rating. This adjustment hinges on Biocon Limited's (BL) projected leverage reduction, fueled by recent equity issuance and improved EBITDA. Despite BBL's established biosimilar market presence, significant regulatory hurdles, U.S. pricing pressures, and limited manufacturing diversification pose ongoing risks. The company's parent, Biocon Ltd., has a market capitalization of approximately ₹59,228 Cr and trades with a high P/E ratio, reflecting investor sentiment on its growth prospects and valuation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MRP Agro Q3 Profit Plummets 44% YoY Amid Revenue Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/MRP-Agro-Q3-Profit-Plummets-44percent-YoY-Amid-Revenue-Slump/69872ab2b81b2b81dcfc5929</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/MRP-Agro-Q3-Profit-Plummets-44percent-YoY-Amid-Revenue-Slump/69872ab2b81b2b81dcfc5929</guid><description>MRP Agro Limited reported a significant year-on-year decline for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. Total revenue fell 47.6% to ₹2438.05 Lakhs from ₹4647.85 Lakhs in the prior year, while Profit After Tax (PAT) for the parent company dropped 44.1% to ₹191.64 Lakhs from ₹343.00 Lakhs. The company provided limited financial details, omitting Balance Sheet and Cash Flow statements, and offered no management guidance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HPCL Seals $3B LNG Deal for India's Energy Security</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/HPCL-Seals-3B-LNG-Deal-for-Indias-Energy-Security/69872a02b81b2b81dcfc56f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/HPCL-Seals-3B-LNG-Deal-for-Indias-Energy-Security/69872a02b81b2b81dcfc56f2</guid><description>Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Limited (HPCL) secured a critical 10-year, $3 billion Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG) supply agreement with Abu Dhabi's ADNOC Gas. This landmark deal aims to bolster India's long-term energy security, meeting the nation's escalating demand for natural gas. The pact, advised by Shardul Amarchand Mangaldas &amp; Co, signifies a strategic commitment to diversifying energy sources and integrating cleaner fuels into the domestic market.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:03:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing Gains From India Trade Pact, Supply Chain Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Boeing-Gains-From-India-Trade-Pact-Supply-Chain-Boost/698729e6b81b2b81dcfc55ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Boeing-Gains-From-India-Trade-Pact-Supply-Chain-Boost/698729e6b81b2b81dcfc55ee</guid><description>The recent India-US interim trade agreement promises substantial benefits for aircraft manufacturer Boeing and its supply chain partners. By removing tariffs on aircraft parts and fostering deeper integration, the pact is expected to enhance cost competitiveness and unlock new opportunities in India's rapidly growing aerospace sector. Boeing's long-standing advocacy for a zero-tariff approach in aerospace is now being realized, potentially bolstering its strategic position amidst global supply chain realignments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:02:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Poised As Key OEM Hub As Boeing, Airbus Boost Sourcing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Poised-As-Key-OEM-Hub-As-Boeing-Airbus-Boost-Sourcing/698729c3b81b2b81dcfc5540</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Poised-As-Key-OEM-Hub-As-Boeing-Airbus-Boost-Sourcing/698729c3b81b2b81dcfc5540</guid><description>The United States' interim trade agreement with India, which significantly reduces tariffs on aircraft parts, is catalyzing a strategic pivot by aerospace giants Boeing and Airbus to deepen their manufacturing ties with India. Both companies are scaling up their annual sourcing from the subcontinent, viewing India not just as a supplier but as a critical foreign original equipment manufacturer (OEM) base. This move taps into India's growing manufacturing capabilities and skilled workforce, aiming to de-risk global supply chains and meet surging aircraft demand. While India's aerospace sector stands to benefit, challenges remain in upscaling production and moving further up the value chain to meet these ambitious targets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Chip Design Leap: Qualcomm 2nm Chip Unveiled, Minister Eyes Global Leadership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Chip-Design-Leap-Qualcomm-2nm-Chip-Unveiled-Minister-Eyes-Global-Leadership/6987294ab81b2b81dcfc53cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Chip-Design-Leap-Qualcomm-2nm-Chip-Unveiled-Minister-Eyes-Global-Leadership/6987294ab81b2b81dcfc53cd</guid><description>India has taken a significant step in semiconductor manufacturing as Union Minister Ashwini Vaishnaw unveiled a 2-nanometer chip designed by Qualcomm within the country. This development positions India among nations leading cutting-edge chip design. The government's proactive training initiatives, with 67,000 engineers already skilled, are fueling this progress, setting the stage for the upcoming Semicon 2.0 mission focused on design and advanced manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Plans Bed Capacity Doubling; Q3 FY26 Revenue Up 19%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Plans-Bed-Capacity-Doubling-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Up-19percent/69872880b81b2b81dcfc51f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcare-Plans-Bed-Capacity-Doubling-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Up-19percent/69872880b81b2b81dcfc51f0</guid><description>Max Healthcare Institute Limited outlined a strategic roadmap for significant growth, targeting over 9,800 beds by FY29. The company reported a strong 19% YoY revenue increase to ₹7,524 Cr and a 30% jump in PAT to ₹1,244 Cr for 9M FY26, driven by capacity expansion and operational efficiency. Key priorities include M&amp;A, digital transformation, and organic bed additions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SRG Housing Finance Surges Past ₹900 Cr AUM, Profit Jumps 43%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SRG-Housing-Finance-Surges-Past-900-Cr-AUM-Profit-Jumps-43percent/69872862b81b2b81dcfc50fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SRG-Housing-Finance-Surges-Past-900-Cr-AUM-Profit-Jumps-43percent/69872862b81b2b81dcfc50fd</guid><description>SRG Housing Finance Limited (SRGHFL) reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with Gross Loan Assets (AUM) growing 33.42% YoY to ₹943.93 crore, nearing its ₹1,000 crore target. Profit After Tax (PAT) surged 43.03% YoY to ₹8.21 crore. Net Interest Income (NII) grew 40.87%, and Net Interest Margin (NIM) improved to 2.68%. Management highlighted network expansion and disciplined asset quality maintenance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hi-Tech Pipes Posts Revenue Surge, But Profits Slip; Signs Non-Compete Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Pipes-Posts-Revenue-Surge-But-Profits-Slip-Signs-Non-Compete-Deal/69872769b81b2b81dcfc4ed9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Pipes-Posts-Revenue-Surge-But-Profits-Slip-Signs-Non-Compete-Deal/69872769b81b2b81dcfc4ed9</guid><description>Hi-Tech Pipes Limited reported a significant 40.54% YoY revenue growth to ₹106,958.82 Lacs for Q3 FY26. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) declined by 9.19% to ₹1,738.70 Lacs, and EPS fell 22.22% YoY. Standalone revenues saw a 20.86% dip. The board also approved a Non-Compete Agreement with Hi-Tech Flow Solutions Limited to delineate business domains, stating no material impact.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SEPC Q3 PAT Soars 237%, But Auditor Flags Asset &amp; DTA Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEPC-Q3-PAT-Soars-237percent-But-Auditor-Flags-Asset-and-DTA-Risks/69872726b81b2b81dcfc4d42</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEPC-Q3-PAT-Soars-237percent-But-Auditor-Flags-Asset-and-DTA-Risks/69872726b81b2b81dcfc4d42</guid><description>SEPC Limited posted a stellar consolidated Q3 result with PAT surging 237.17% YoY to ₹1,495.96 Lakhs on 114.13% revenue growth. However, standalone PAT declined 22.95%. Statutory auditors issued qualified reports, citing uncertainties over ₹28,786 Lakhs in deferred tax assets and recoverability of ₹7,454 Lakhs in contract assets and receivables from stalled projects. The company continues on a going concern basis despite significant accumulated losses, supported by a rights issue and investor infusion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:51:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Archit Organosys Sees Profit Surge 140% YoY on Strong Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Archit-Organosys-Sees-Profit-Surge-140percent-YoY-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/6987270cb81b2b81dcfc4c57</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Archit-Organosys-Sees-Profit-Surge-140percent-YoY-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/6987270cb81b2b81dcfc4c57</guid><description>Archit Organosys Limited has announced a strong financial performance for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. Revenue surged 48.4% year-on-year to ₹3,839.81 Lakhs, while net profit witnessed a massive 140.6% jump to ₹243.48 Lakhs. For the nine-month period, revenue grew 26.7% and profit more than doubled. EBITDA margins also improved to 14.20%. The company noted the implementation of New Labour Codes and a provision for defined benefit obligations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:50:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987270cb81b2b81dcfc4c56_1770467814144.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hi-Tech Pipes Q3 Revenue Soars 40%, Profits Squeeze 9% On Rising Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Pipes-Q3-Revenue-Soars-40percent-Profits-Squeeze-9percent-On-Rising-Costs/698726f2b81b2b81dcfc4b67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Pipes-Q3-Revenue-Soars-40percent-Profits-Squeeze-9percent-On-Rising-Costs/698726f2b81b2b81dcfc4b67</guid><description>Hi-Tech Pipes reported a strong 40.55% YoY revenue growth in Q3 FY26 to ₹106,958.82 Lacs. However, profitability took a hit, with Profit After Tax (PAT) declining 9.2% YoY to ₹1,738.70 Lacs due to margin compression. For the nine months, revenue grew 16.53% while PAT saw a marginal 5.9% rise. The company also approved a Non-Compete Agreement and offered no forward guidance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:50:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698726f2b81b2b81dcfc4b66_1770467707839.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Prozone Realty: Consolidated Surge Masks Standalone Slump, Legal Clouds Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Prozone-Realty-Consolidated-Surge-Masks-Standalone-Slump-Legal-Clouds-Loom/69872677b81b2b81dcfc49d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Prozone-Realty-Consolidated-Surge-Masks-Standalone-Slump-Legal-Clouds-Loom/69872677b81b2b81dcfc49d7</guid><description>Prozone Realty reported a mixed financial performance for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Consolidated revenue from operations surged 29.8% YoY to ₹6,094.91 lakh, with net profit up 74.8% to ₹678.24 lakh for the quarter. However, standalone net profit plummeted 94.3% YoY to ₹5.54 lakh. The company faces significant headwinds from a legal dispute over a Nagpur project's NOC and an MCA rejection for its Deputy Managing Director's reappointment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:48:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69872677b81b2b81dcfc49d6_1770467618723.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ganesha Ecosphere PAT Crashes 84% YoY; Standalone Recovers QoQ</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ganesha-Ecosphere-PAT-Crashes-84percent-YoY-Standalone-Recovers-QoQ/69872604b81b2b81dcfc4886</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ganesha-Ecosphere-PAT-Crashes-84percent-YoY-Standalone-Recovers-QoQ/69872604b81b2b81dcfc4886</guid><description>Ganesha Ecosphere Limited reported a sharp 84.0% year-on-year drop in consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) for Q3 FY26, falling to ₹474.84 Lakhs from ₹2,970.65 Lakhs. Consolidated revenue also declined 10.2% YoY. Standalone revenue saw a modest 1.8% YoY increase, while its PAT dropped 18.6% YoY but surged 104.0% QoQ. The company noted an incremental impact from new Labour Codes. The nine-month period saw significant YoY PAT declines across both standalone (-48.3%) and consolidated (-81.1%) figures.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:46:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69872604b81b2b81dcfc4885_1770467424895.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SRG Housing Finance Posts Strong Growth, But Returns Dip Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SRG-Housing-Finance-Posts-Strong-Growth-But-Returns-Dip-Sharply/698725bbb81b2b81dcfc4739</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SRG-Housing-Finance-Posts-Strong-Growth-But-Returns-Dip-Sharply/698725bbb81b2b81dcfc4739</guid><description>SRG Housing Finance reported strong Q3 FY26 results, with Assets Under Management (AUM) soaring 33.43% YoY to ₹944 crore and Profit After Tax (PAT) jumping 43.03% to ₹8.21 crore. Disbursements rose 17.99% YoY. Net Interest Margins expanded, and Gross NPAs improved. However, a significant concern emerged with declining Return on Average Equity (RoAE) and Return on Average Assets (RoAA) YoY, signalling a potential dip in profitability quality despite topline growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:44:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698725bbb81b2b81dcfc4738_1770467251624.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nahar Capital Q3 Profit Plummets Amidst Alarming Financial Data Inconsistencies</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nahar-Capital-Q3-Profit-Plummets-Amidst-Alarming-Financial-Data-Inconsistencies/6987258eb81b2b81dcfc460f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nahar-Capital-Q3-Profit-Plummets-Amidst-Alarming-Financial-Data-Inconsistencies/6987258eb81b2b81dcfc460f</guid><description>Nahar Capital reported a sharp 26.3% YoY drop in standalone Net Profit for Q3 FY26, despite an 18.7% revenue increase. Consolidated income surged 198.5%, but net profit declined 6.6% over nine months. Critically, the company's filings reveal alarming inconsistencies in standalone Profit Before Tax and Net Profit calculations, raising serious concerns about financial reporting integrity for investors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:44:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987258eb81b2b81dcfc460e_1770467111324.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Tech Pact Fuels AI Ambitions Amidst Global Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-US-Tech-Pact-Fuels-AI-Ambitions-Amidst-Global-Competition/6987252cb81b2b81dcfc44bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-US-Tech-Pact-Fuels-AI-Ambitions-Amidst-Global-Competition/6987252cb81b2b81dcfc44bf</guid><description>A new interim trade agreement between India and the United States is set to significantly boost technology product trade, particularly in Graphics Processing Units (GPUs) and data center equipment. This pact supports India's ambitious AI mission, marked by substantial GPU procurements and projected investments exceeding $200 billion. While signaling India's growing role in global tech supply chains, the nation must navigate competitive pressures and infrastructure challenges to realize its AI powerhouse aspirations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:42:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987252cb81b2b81dcfc44be_1770466940317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Balkrishna Paper Mills Posts Huge Loss; Auditor Flags Going Concern Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balkrishna-Paper-Mills-Posts-Huge-Loss-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Risk/69872516b81b2b81dcfc43da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Balkrishna-Paper-Mills-Posts-Huge-Loss-Auditor-Flags-Going-Concern-Risk/69872516b81b2b81dcfc43da</guid><description>Balkrishna Paper Mills Ltd. reported a significant 162% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹171.08 Lakhs in Q3 FY26, but posted a net loss of ₹21.30 Lakhs. For the nine months, losses widened to ₹375.94 Lakhs. Critically, statutory auditors issued a qualified conclusion, highlighting a material uncertainty regarding the company's ability to continue as a going concern due to its substantially negative net worth of ₹(17,268.89) Lakhs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:42:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69872516b81b2b81dcfc43d9_1770466792320.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MGL Profit Dips 9% YoY As Margins Shrink Despite Revenue Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/MGL-Profit-Dips-9percent-YoY-As-Margins-Shrink-Despite-Revenue-Rise/698723a9b81b2b81dcfc415e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/MGL-Profit-Dips-9percent-YoY-As-Margins-Shrink-Despite-Revenue-Rise/698723a9b81b2b81dcfc415e</guid><description>Mahanagar Gas Limited (MGL) reported a 11.58% YoY revenue growth to ₹2,265.97 Crore in Q3 FY26, but Profit After Tax (PAT) declined 9.43% YoY to ₹201.97 Crore. Earnings Per Share (EPS) fell to ₹20.45. EBITDA margins compressed to 17.10% from 22.18% YoY. Despite volume growth, cost pressures are evident. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹12 per share but faces significant legal demands from GAIL and GST authorities.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:36:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698723a9b81b2b81dcfc415d_1770466574311.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stallion India inks Rajasthan MoU for ₹200cr HFO plant, eyes 35% growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Stallion-India-inks-Rajasthan-MoU-for-200cr-HFO-plant-eyes-35percent-growth/69872334b81b2b81dcfc3fea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Stallion-India-inks-Rajasthan-MoU-for-200cr-HFO-plant-eyes-35percent-growth/69872334b81b2b81dcfc3fea</guid><description>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Limited (SIFL) has inked a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Government of Rajasthan for a ₹200 crore Hydrofluoroolefin (HFO) manufacturing plant in Bhilwara. This strategic move targets next-generation, sustainable refrigerants and aims to bolster SIFL's product portfolio. The company anticipates commissioning its R32 project by October 2026, preceding the HFO plant's commencement in 2027. Management projects a robust 30-35% revenue CAGR over the next three years.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:34:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69872334b81b2b81dcfc3fe9_1770466442375.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Muthoot Finance Closes $600 Million Bond Sale to Fuel Lending Operations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Closes-600-Million-Bond-Sale-to-Fuel-Lending-Operations/698722cfb81b2b81dcfc3e9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Closes-600-Million-Bond-Sale-to-Fuel-Lending-Operations/698722cfb81b2b81dcfc3e9c</guid><description>Muthoot Finance Limited has successfully completed the issuance of $600 million in USD-denominated senior secured notes. The notes, bearing a 5.75% coupon and maturing in 2030, were drawn under its $4 billion global medium-term note program. Legal advisory services for the transaction were provided by Trilegal. The funds raised are designated for onward lending and other activities permissible by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:32:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698722cfb81b2b81dcfc3e9b_1770466198625.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SAB Events: CoC Approves Insolvency Resolution Plan, Path to Revival Opens</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/SAB-Events-CoC-Approves-Insolvency-Resolution-Plan-Path-to-Revival-Opens/698722bab81b2b81dcfc3dc1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/SAB-Events-CoC-Approves-Insolvency-Resolution-Plan-Path-to-Revival-Opens/698722bab81b2b81dcfc3dc1</guid><description>SAB Events &amp; Governance Now Media Limited announced a critical update from its postal ballot concluded Feb 7, 2026. The Committee of Creditors (CoC) has given the green light to the Binding Resolution Plan proposed by the Resolution Applicant. This significant approval marks a crucial step in the company's Pre-Packaged Insolvency Resolution Process (PPIRP) under the IBC, 2016, paving the way for potential revival from financial distress.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:32:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698722bab81b2b81dcfc3dc0_1770466229133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Simplex Castings Q3 Results: Revenue Soars 41%, But Margins Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Simplex-Castings-Q3-Results-Revenue-Soars-41percent-But-Margins-Squeeze/69872245b81b2b81dcfc3c28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Simplex-Castings-Q3-Results-Revenue-Soars-41percent-But-Margins-Squeeze/69872245b81b2b81dcfc3c28</guid><description>Simplex Castings Ltd. has reported a strong 41.40% year-on-year revenue jump to ₹148.14 Cr for the nine months ending December 2025 (9MFY26). However, profitability margins faced pressure, with EBITDA margin dipping to 17.90% and PAT margin to 10.18%. The company secured significant orders and completed a strategic fund raise, aiming for aggressive revenue CAGR while focusing on financial discipline and deleveraging.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:30:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69872245b81b2b81dcfc3c27_1770466079105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nahar Capital Consolidated Profit Surges 229%, Standalone Dips Amidst Non-Operational Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nahar-Capital-Consolidated-Profit-Surges-229percent-Standalone-Dips-Amidst-Non-Operational-Gains/698720fdb81b2b81dcfc397b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nahar-Capital-Consolidated-Profit-Surges-229percent-Standalone-Dips-Amidst-Non-Operational-Gains/698720fdb81b2b81dcfc397b</guid><description>Nahar Capital and Financial Services Ltd. reported a dramatic 229% year-on-year surge in consolidated net profit to ₹953.80 crore for Q3 FY2026, driven by a ₹2260.45 crore jump in 'Other Income' and fair value gains. However, standalone net profit fell 33% to ₹768.83 crore, with revenue showing marginal growth. The company provided no future outlook.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698720fdb81b2b81dcfc397a_1770465936197.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Myntra CTO Hire Signals Tech Push Amid Profit Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Myntra-CTO-Hire-Signals-Tech-Push-Amid-Profit-Surge/698720ddb81b2b81dcfc3878</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Myntra-CTO-Hire-Signals-Tech-Push-Amid-Profit-Surge/698720ddb81b2b81dcfc3878</guid><description>Myntra's appointment of ex-Google/Instacart executive Pramod Adiddam as CTO signals a strategic emphasis on technology and innovation. This leadership change coincides with a significant financial upswing, with net profit soaring 18 times to Rs 548 crore on 18% revenue growth to Rs 6,043 crore in FY25. The move aims to bolster platform capabilities and maintain competitive advantage in India's rapidly expanding fashion e-commerce sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:24:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698720ddb81b2b81dcfc3877_1770465896497.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Pact Boosts Tech Access, NVIDIA Poised for AI Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-US-Pact-Boosts-Tech-Access-NVIDIA-Poised-for-AI-Surge/69872063b81b2b81dcfc36d9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-US-Pact-Boosts-Tech-Access-NVIDIA-Poised-for-AI-Surge/69872063b81b2b81dcfc36d9</guid><description>India's Union Minister Piyush Goyal announced a strategic policy prioritizing domestic interests and critical technology access, underscored by a new US-India trade pact that eases ICT goods import and boosts AI hardware cooperation. This development aligns with India's aggressive expansion in semiconductor manufacturing, aiming to become a global hub. NVIDIA is positioned to benefit from increased demand for its AI chips, with analysts maintaining a "Strong Buy" consensus despite its premium valuation. The pact signifies a geopolitical shift, balancing protectionism with the need for advanced technology imports.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:22:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69872063b81b2b81dcfc36d8_1770465690115.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Meghmani Organics Posts Loss on TiO2 Woes, Standsalone Business Shines</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Meghmani-Organics-Posts-Loss-on-TiO2-Woes-Standsalone-Business-Shines/6987200cb81b2b81dcfc354c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Meghmani-Organics-Posts-Loss-on-TiO2-Woes-Standsalone-Business-Shines/6987200cb81b2b81dcfc354c</guid><description>Meghmani Organics reported a challenging Q3 FY26 with consolidated PAT turning negative, primarily driven by significant operational issues and losses in its Titanium Dioxide (TiO2) segment. The company temporarily shut down its TiO2 plant due to anti-dumping duty withdrawal and high costs. However, its standalone business, led by Crop Protection, demonstrated robust performance, with revenue growth and strong EBITDA margins, while Pigments faced capacity constraints. The company anticipates TiO2 recovery from Q2 FY27, contingent on regulatory actions and market conditions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:20:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987200cb81b2b81dcfc354b_1770465519066.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>A.K. Capital Services Surges 84% PAT on Strong Q3, Declares ₹22 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AK-Capital-Services-Surges-84percent-PAT-on-Strong-Q3-Declares-22-Dividend/69871fe9b81b2b81dcfc3464</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AK-Capital-Services-Surges-84percent-PAT-on-Strong-Q3-Declares-22-Dividend/69871fe9b81b2b81dcfc3464</guid><description>A. K. Capital Services Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 financial results, showcasing significant year-on-year growth. Standalone PAT surged 84.37% to ₹150.19 Cr, with margins improving across the board. Consolidated PAT grew 50.71% to ₹260.31 Cr. The company's strong performance also led the Board to declare a second interim dividend of ₹22 per share.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:20:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69871fe9b81b2b81dcfc3463_1770465371365.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SMS Pharma Q3 Profit Soars 36%, Invests ₹7 Cr in Unit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/SMS-Pharma-Q3-Profit-Soars-36percent-Invests-7-Cr-in-Unit/69871f76b81b2b81dcfc32e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/SMS-Pharma-Q3-Profit-Soars-36percent-Invests-7-Cr-in-Unit/69871f76b81b2b81dcfc32e5</guid><description>SMS Pharmaceuticals Limited has reported robust year-on-year growth for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Revenue surged 21.40% YoY to ₹21,044.70 Lakhs in Q3 FY26, while Net Profit after Tax jumped 35.87% YoY to ₹2,333.80 Lakhs. The company also approved an investment of up to ₹7 Crores in its subsidiary, SMS Peptides Private Limited, signaling expansion plans amidst strong operational performance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:18:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69871f76b81b2b81dcfc32e4_1770465195846.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ester Industries posts Q3 loss amid tariffs, sees hope in specialty films</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Ester-Industries-posts-Q3-loss-amid-tariffs-sees-hope-in-specialty-films/69871e84b81b2b81dcfc309f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Ester-Industries-posts-Q3-loss-amid-tariffs-sees-hope-in-specialty-films/69871e84b81b2b81dcfc309f</guid><description>Ester Industries Limited reported a challenging Q3 FY26 with a net loss of ₹12.4 Cr, a sharp decline from last year's profit, primarily due to US trade tariffs and predatory Chinese pricing impacting its BOPET Film segment margins. Despite a revenue dip of 2.1% YoY to ₹343.5 Cr, the company highlighted robust growth in its Specialty Polymer and rPET segments, signaling a strategic shift. Management remains optimistic, anticipating an improvement following potential trade deal finalization and anti-dumping investigations, while focusing on operational efficiency and sustainable solutions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:14:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69871e84b81b2b81dcfc309e_1770465077791.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>A K Capital Services posts 84% PAT jump, declares dividend; debt ratio at 2.88x</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/A-K-Capital-Services-posts-84percent-PAT-jump-declares-dividend-debt-ratio-at-288x/69871e1eb81b2b81dcfc2f12</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/A-K-Capital-Services-posts-84percent-PAT-jump-declares-dividend-debt-ratio-at-288x/69871e1eb81b2b81dcfc2f12</guid><description>A. K. Capital Services Limited reported a strong performance for Q3 FY26, with standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 84.4% year-on-year to ₹1,501.93 Lakhs, driven by significant margin expansion to 36.80%. Consolidated PAT rose 50.7% YoY to ₹2,603.06 Lakhs. The Board also declared a second interim dividend of ₹22 per share. However, the consolidated Debt/Equity ratio stands at a high 2.88 times.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:12:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69871e1eb81b2b81dcfc2f11_1770464930836.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>