<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:46:08 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Ind-Swift Labs Promoter Boosts Stake to 43.06% Via ₹617 Cr Warrant Conversion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ind-Swift-Labs-Promoter-Boosts-Stake-to-4306percent-Via-617-Cr-Warrant-Conversion/69a13ab7fa7d0695d1ab5d2d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Ind-Swift-Labs-Promoter-Boosts-Stake-to-4306percent-Via-617-Cr-Warrant-Conversion/69a13ab7fa7d0695d1ab5d2d</guid><description>Ind-Swift Laboratories Limited announced that Essix Biosciences Limited, a promoter group entity, has acquired 51,00,000 equity shares through the conversion of fully convertible warrants. The preferential allotment, valued at ₹617.10 crore, significantly increases the promoter group's combined stake to 43.06%. This move consolidates promoter ownership and may signal future strategic directions for the API and formulation manufacturer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:33:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a13ab7fa7d0695d1ab5d2c_1772174295334.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sarda Energy Secures SKS Power Amid SC Ruling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sarda-Energy-Secures-SKS-Power-Amid-SC-Ruling/69a13a52fa7d0695d1ab5c3e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sarda-Energy-Secures-SKS-Power-Amid-SC-Ruling/69a13a52fa7d0695d1ab5c3e</guid><description>The Supreme Court's affirmation of Sarda Energy's Rs 1950 crore acquisition of SKS Power Generation solidifies the doctrine of commercial wisdom for lenders. This ruling empowers Sarda Energy to integrate a significant thermal power asset, potentially reshaping its operational capacity and strategic footprint in India's evolving energy market. The decision also underscores a trend towards market-driven resolutions in the power sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:31:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a13a52fa7d0695d1ab5c3d_1772174051280.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Energy &amp; Gold Financier Surge Masks Cyclical Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/PSU-Energy-and-Gold-Financier-Surge-Masks-Cyclical-Risks/69a139b9fa7d0695d1ab5b39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/PSU-Energy-and-Gold-Financier-Surge-Masks-Cyclical-Risks/69a139b9fa7d0695d1ab5b39</guid><description>Indian Oil Corporation (IOC) and Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) reported substantial EBITDA growth in Q3 FY26, fueled by soaring refining margins and government compensation. Muthoot Finance also posted robust EBITDA gains, primarily from aggressive gold loan expansion and rising gold prices. However, these performances are underpinned by volatile commodity prices and subsidies, raising questions about long-term sustainability and presenting significant risks for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:29:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a139b9fa7d0695d1ab5b38_1772173930009.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver ETFs Plunge Amid Gold Rally: Geopolitics Fuels Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-ETFs-Plunge-Amid-Gold-Rally-Geopolitics-Fuels-Divergence/69a139b8fa7d0695d1ab5b22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-ETFs-Plunge-Amid-Gold-Rally-Geopolitics-Fuels-Divergence/69a139b8fa7d0695d1ab5b22</guid><description>Gold and silver futures advanced on Feb 27, 2026, driven by geopolitical uncertainty and tariff concerns. While precious metals saw initial gains on MCX and COMEX, recent ETF performance shows a stark contrast: gold ETFs gained 3% in February, whereas silver ETFs plunged 15.66%. This divergence highlights silver's heightened volatility and industrial demand linkage versus gold's steady safe-haven appeal amidst fluctuating macro conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:29:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a139b8fa7d0695d1ab5b21_1772173961920.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Block Slashes 40% Workforce, Embraces AI for Hyper-Efficiency</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Block-Slashes-40percent-Workforce-Embraces-AI-for-Hyper-Efficiency/69a139b6fa7d0695d1ab5b0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Block-Slashes-40percent-Workforce-Embraces-AI-for-Hyper-Efficiency/69a139b6fa7d0695d1ab5b0b</guid><description>Block Inc. has announced a drastic workforce reduction of over 4,000 employees, nearly halving its staff from over 10,000 to under 6,000. This strategic move, detailed by Chairman Jack Dorsey on February 27, 2026, is attributed to the transformative impact of internal AI tools enabling leaner, more efficient operations, even as the company reported a robust 24% year-over-year growth in gross profit and a 33% surge in its Cash App business for Q4 2025. The announcement signals a significant shift in operational philosophy, prioritizing AI-driven productivity over traditional headcount, and reverberates industry-wide concerns about AI's accelerating influence on employment and business models, particularly impacting global IT services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:29:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a139b6fa7d0695d1ab5b0a_1772174065698.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Physicswallah: Online Growth Meets Offline Challenge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Physicswallah-Online-Growth-Meets-Offline-Challenge/69a1358efa7d0695d1ab5725</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Physicswallah-Online-Growth-Meets-Offline-Challenge/69a1358efa7d0695d1ab5725</guid><description>JM Financial initiated coverage with a 'Buy' rating and ₹110 target, citing Physicswallah's robust online business and projected 28% revenue CAGR through FY28. The edtech firm boasts 4.37 million paying users, driving high-margin stability. However, the company's ambitious offline expansion faces persistent hurdles like real estate acquisition and faculty recruitment, a stark contrast to its digital success. This dichotomy raises questions about sustainable growth as the edtech sector navigates consolidation and a shift towards "phygital" models.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:11:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1358efa7d0695d1ab5724_1772172882677.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Urban Company: Analyst 'Buy' Amidst Growth, Profitability Puzzles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Urban-Company-Analyst-Buy-Amidst-Growth-Profitability-Puzzles/69a13518fa7d0695d1ab5613</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Urban-Company-Analyst-Buy-Amidst-Growth-Profitability-Puzzles/69a13518fa7d0695d1ab5613</guid><description>JM Financial has initiated coverage on Urban Company with a 'Buy' rating and a ₹125 target price, highlighting its dominant 60%+ share in India's burgeoning online home services market. Despite this bullish stance, the company faces significant challenges. Its high-frequency InstaHelp vertical continues to incur substantial losses, while the Native product line enters fiercely competitive segments like air conditioners. Furthermore, a large share unlock event in March 2026 poses a considerable risk to the stock's valuation, contrasting with other analysts' more cautious outlooks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:09:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a13518fa7d0695d1ab5612_1772172843083.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Investec Flags OMC Overvaluation, Favors RIL</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Investec-Flags-OMC-Overvaluation-Favors-RIL/69a13515fa7d0695d1ab55fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Investec-Flags-OMC-Overvaluation-Favors-RIL/69a13515fa7d0695d1ab55fc</guid><description>Brokerage Investec maintains a 'Sell' rating on state-owned Oil Marketing Companies (OMCs) like BPCL, HPCL, and IOC, arguing current valuations reflect an unrealistic earnings outlook. Despite strong near-term performance, stocks trade at a significant premium to historical averages. Conversely, Investec reiterates a 'Buy' on Reliance Industries, viewing it as the prime beneficiary of an anticipated refining upcycle amid rising crude prices and geopolitical tensions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:09:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a13515fa7d0695d1ab55fb_1772173095806.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Technical Breakouts Face Valuation Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Technical-Breakouts-Face-Valuation-Hurdles/69a13513fa7d0695d1ab55e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Technical-Breakouts-Face-Valuation-Hurdles/69a13513fa7d0695d1ab55e5</guid><description>Technical chart patterns suggest potential upside for Dr Reddy's Laboratories, Bharat Electronics (BEL), and Triveni Engineering. However, a deeper analysis reveals differing valuation metrics, sector-specific challenges, and competitive pressures that investors must weigh against these bullish technical signals. BEL, in particular, trades at a high multiple, pricing in significant future growth, while Dr Reddy's navigates a complex global pharma outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:09:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a13513fa7d0695d1ab55e4_1772172750046.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Depository Fee Cuts Spark EBITDA Fears, But Stocks Show Deeper Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Depository-Fee-Cuts-Spark-EBITDA-Fears-But-Stocks-Show-Deeper-Woes/69a13502fa7d0695d1ab55c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Depository-Fee-Cuts-Spark-EBITDA-Fears-But-Stocks-Show-Deeper-Woes/69a13502fa7d0695d1ab55c6</guid><description>Central Depository Services Ltd (CDSL) and National Securities Depository Ltd (NSDL) are set to experience a direct impact on their Earnings Before Interest, Tax, Depreciation, and Amortisation (EBITDA) following a regulatory mandated 20% reduction in KYC 'fetch' charges, effective April 1. Brokerages project a 5% to 6% hit to EBITDA. However, the market's reaction appears muted, with both stocks already trading significantly below their recent peaks, indicating existing headwinds may overshadow this specific development.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:09:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a13502fa7d0695d1ab55c5_1772172918926.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Suzlon's Diversification Gamble: Will New Energy Ventures Justify Bullish Targets?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Suzlons-Diversification-Gamble-Will-New-Energy-Ventures-Justify-Bullish-Targets/69a13415fa7d0695d1ab53f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Suzlons-Diversification-Gamble-Will-New-Energy-Ventures-Justify-Bullish-Targets/69a13415fa7d0695d1ab53f7</guid><description>ICICI Direct maintains a 'BUY' rating for Suzlon Energy with an unchanged target of INR 65, citing strong fundamentals and a robust order book. However, the company's 'Suzlon 2.0' strategy to diversify into solar and Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) introduces significant execution challenges and competitive pressures that may temper the optimistic outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:05:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a13415fa7d0695d1ab53f6_1772172831062.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Thomas Cook India Focuses on Maharashtra; CRISIL Upgrades Ratings to AA/Stable</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Thomas-Cook-India-Focuses-on-Maharashtra-CRISIL-Upgrades-Ratings-to-AAStable/69a13410fa7d0695d1ab53e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Thomas-Cook-India-Focuses-on-Maharashtra-CRISIL-Upgrades-Ratings-to-AAStable/69a13410fa7d0695d1ab53e0</guid><description>Thomas Cook India is targeting the Maharashtrian market with specialized Marathi Europe tours and actor Subodh Bhave as brand ambassador. This strategic regional push coincides with a significant credit rating upgrade by CRISIL to 'CRISIL AA/Stable' and 'CRISIL A1+', marking the highest rating for any travel and tourism company in India. The move signifies enhanced financial credibility and a focused approach to capturing a key demographic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:05:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a13410fa7d0695d1ab53df_1772172998540.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PNGS Reva Diamond IPO: Flat GMP Signals Caution Amidst IPO Market Chill</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PNGS-Reva-Diamond-IPO-Flat-GMP-Signals-Caution-Amidst-IPO-Market-Chill/69a133c9fa7d0695d1ab52e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PNGS-Reva-Diamond-IPO-Flat-GMP-Signals-Caution-Amidst-IPO-Market-Chill/69a133c9fa7d0695d1ab52e3</guid><description>PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery's Rs 380 crore IPO has finalized allotment, with an overall subscription rate of just 1.23 times. The grey market premium (GMP) is flat to negative, suggesting limited listing gains. Despite strong financials and a focus on diamond jewellery, significant revenue concentration in Maharashtra and execution risks associated with expanding to exclusive stores are key concerns. This debut occurs in a cautious IPO market environment in early 2026, where many recent listings have struggled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:03:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a133c9fa7d0695d1ab52e2_1772172346700.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Escape Plan Bags $25M to Capture Travel Retail Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Escape-Plan-Bags-25M-to-Capture-Travel-Retail-Market/69a133a7fa7d0695d1ab52c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Escape-Plan-Bags-25M-to-Capture-Travel-Retail-Market/69a133a7fa7d0695d1ab52c8</guid><description>Escape Plan, a travel products retail platform, has raised $25 million in Series A funding, spearheaded by Jungle Ventures with participation from Fireside Ventures and IndiGo Ventures. This capital injection will empower Escape Plan to bolster its brand, refine pricing, and expand distribution across India and select international markets. The company also plans significant investments in technology and product innovation to enhance its omni-channel capabilities and strengthen value chain control, positioning it for intensified competition in the growing travel accessories sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:03:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a133a7fa7d0695d1ab52c7_1772172335951.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FTAs Boost Investment Certainty, Signal New Trade Era</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FTAs-Boost-Investment-Certainty-Signal-New-Trade-Era/69a133a0fa7d0695d1ab52ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FTAs-Boost-Investment-Certainty-Signal-New-Trade-Era/69a133a0fa7d0695d1ab52ae</guid><description>India's new generation FTAs with EFTA and the UK signal a strategic pivot, moving beyond tariff cuts to integrate investment facilitation, services, and digital trade. The India-EFTA pact targets a substantial $100 billion FDI over 15 years, while the India-UK CETA streamlines market access for services and professionals. These agreements aim to reduce investor uncertainty and enhance India's position as a global manufacturing and sourcing hub, though their ultimate impact will depend on effective implementation and overcoming domestic regulatory complexities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:03:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a133a0fa7d0695d1ab52ad_1772172638083.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India C&amp;I Renewables Surge: Policy Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-CandI-Renewables-Surge-Policy-Risks-Loom/69a1333bfa7d0695d1ab51fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-CandI-Renewables-Surge-Policy-Risks-Loom/69a1333bfa7d0695d1ab51fd</guid><description>India's commercial and industrial (C&amp;I) renewable energy capacity is projected to grow by 17 GW, reaching 57 GW by FY28, fueled by tariff arbitrage and corporate sustainability goals. The Green Energy Open Access (GEOA) Rules facilitate this expansion by enabling direct sourcing of renewables. However, states face a critical balancing act between incentivizing C&amp;I adoption and preserving the financial health of distribution utilities (DISCOMs), creating potential policy instability that could impact tariffs and project viability. Energy-intensive sectors like steel, cement, and data centers are leading this transition, with private equity-backed developers expected to dominate new capacity additions due to attractive returns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 06:01:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1333bfa7d0695d1ab51fc_1772172389660.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MTNL Bonds Stay on Crisil's 'Watch Negative' Amid Payment Lapses, Widening Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/MTNL-Bonds-Stay-on-Crisils-Watch-Negative-Amid-Payment-Lapses-Widening-Losses/69a130c9fa7d0695d1ab5060</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/MTNL-Bonds-Stay-on-Crisils-Watch-Negative-Amid-Payment-Lapses-Widening-Losses/69a130c9fa7d0695d1ab5060</guid><description>Crisil Ratings has maintained Mahanagar Telephone Nigam Limited's (MTNL) long-term debt rating on 'Watch Negative'. This reflects past non-adherence to structured payment mechanisms for government-guaranteed bonds, despite recent improvements. MTNL's operating loss widened to ₹241 crore in 9MFY26 from ₹175 crore in 9MFY25, with revenue dropping to ₹547 crore. The BSNL service agreement, effective January 1, 2025, is impacting revenue recognition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a130c9fa7d0695d1ab505f_1772171632509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kirloskar Brothers ₹214 Cr Adani Power Pump Contract Boosts Order Book</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kirloskar-Brothers-214-Cr-Adani-Power-Pump-Contract-Boosts-Order-Book/69a13053fa7d0695d1ab4fd3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kirloskar-Brothers-214-Cr-Adani-Power-Pump-Contract-Boosts-Order-Book/69a13053fa7d0695d1ab4fd3</guid><description>Kirloskar Brothers Limited (KBL) has secured a substantial ₹214 crore contract from Adani Power Limited for supplying pump packages to thermal power projects across four Indian states. This order enhances KBL's revenue visibility for the next 18-24 months and strengthens its position in the critical power sector equipment supply chain.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:49:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a13053fa7d0695d1ab4fd2_1772171447581.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Struggles Amid FII Outflows; Peers Show Resilience</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Struggles-Amid-FII-Outflows-Peers-Show-Resilience/69a12e7efa7d0695d1ab4df1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Struggles-Amid-FII-Outflows-Peers-Show-Resilience/69a12e7efa7d0695d1ab4df1</guid><description>The Indian Rupee depreciated by 4 paise to 90.95 against the US dollar on Friday, February 27, 2026, driven by foreign institutional investor (FII) outflows and a decline in domestic equity markets. Despite a weaker dollar index and lower crude oil prices, the rupee failed to gain traction, highlighting persistent selling pressure and underperformance compared to other Asian currencies. Analysts point to structural issues and trade uncertainties as ongoing concerns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:41:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12e7efa7d0695d1ab4df0_1772171026813.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Foseco India Dividend Boosts Stock Amid Profit Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Foseco-India-Dividend-Boosts-Stock-Amid-Profit-Dip/69a12dfdfa7d0695d1ab4d3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Foseco-India-Dividend-Boosts-Stock-Amid-Profit-Dip/69a12dfdfa7d0695d1ab4d3d</guid><description>Foseco India's share price climbed significantly, propelled by a recommended dividend payout of ₹25 per share for FY25. This market reaction occurred despite the company reporting a 20.53% year-on-year decline in net profit for Q3 FY26, which fell to ₹15.53 crore from ₹19.54 crore in the prior year, even as revenue saw an 8.11% increase to ₹147.53 crore.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:39:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12dfdfa7d0695d1ab4d3c_1772171130194.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pet Firm Supertails Navigates Fire Disaster, Leverages Funding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Pet-Firm-Supertails-Navigates-Fire-Disaster-Leverages-Funding/69a12dfbfa7d0695d1ab4d26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Pet-Firm-Supertails-Navigates-Fire-Disaster-Leverages-Funding/69a12dfbfa7d0695d1ab4d26</guid><description>Bengaluru-based pet care startup Supertails faced a significant inventory loss due to a warehouse fire shortly after securing $30 million in funding. Demonstrating rapid operational recovery, the company established a new warehouse within 72 hours. Customer impact was minimized, with most orders fulfilled or in processing, and assurances given for sale price honors and refunds. The incident tests the company's resilience and operational risk management following a major investment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:39:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12dfbfa7d0695d1ab4d25_1772170929367.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto Faces Equity Sell-Off: Altcoins Show Resilience Amidst Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Crypto-Faces-Equity-Sell-Off-Altcoins-Show-Resilience-Amidst-Volatility/69a12d0dfa7d0695d1ab4c10</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Crypto-Faces-Equity-Sell-Off-Altcoins-Show-Resilience-Amidst-Volatility/69a12d0dfa7d0695d1ab4c10</guid><description>The cryptocurrency market experienced a broad decline, mirroring a sell-off in equities triggered by Nvidia's earnings report and heightened risk aversion. Bitcoin tested lower levels, though many altcoins like Cardano, Solana, Ethereum, and BNB showed upward momentum on a weekly basis, suggesting underlying demand persists. XRP continued its underperformance, struggling with regulatory headwinds and competitive pressures. The crypto market's correlation with traditional assets remains a dominant theme.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:35:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12d0dfa7d0695d1ab4c0f_1772170893393.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zen Technologies crosses 5% stake mark on Motilal Oswal fund buying</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Zen-Technologies-crosses-5percent-stake-mark-on-Motilal-Oswal-fund-buying/69a12d08fa7d0695d1ab4bf9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Zen-Technologies-crosses-5percent-stake-mark-on-Motilal-Oswal-fund-buying/69a12d08fa7d0695d1ab4bf9</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund's schemes have collectively increased their shareholding in Zen Technologies Ltd. to 5.0316%. This move signifies growing institutional interest and confidence in the defense technology firm's future prospects. The acquisition of an additional 55,352 shares on February 23, 2026, crosses the crucial 5% threshold for the fund house.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:35:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12d08fa7d0695d1ab4bf8_1772170607883.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UP Attracts ₹4 Lakh Crore in Foreign Investment Commitments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/UP-Attracts-4-Lakh-Crore-in-Foreign-Investment-Commitments/69a12c2cfa7d0695d1ab4a7c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/UP-Attracts-4-Lakh-Crore-in-Foreign-Investment-Commitments/69a12c2cfa7d0695d1ab4a7c</guid><description>Uttar Pradesh's Chief Minister's recent four-day tour to Japan and Singapore concluded with substantial investment commitments totaling ₹4 lakh crore. This figure comprises ₹1.5 lakh crore in signed MoUs and ₹2.5 lakh crore in fresh proposals. The drive is a significant push towards the state's ambition of becoming a $1 trillion economy by 2029-30. Key agreements were reached in sectors like semiconductors, green hydrogen, automotive, and data centers, with dedicated industrial zones planned for Japanese and Singaporean firms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:31:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12c2cfa7d0695d1ab4a7b_1772170412803.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aadhar Housing: AXDI Acquires 10.18% Stake from Blackstone Affiliate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aadhar-Housing-AXDI-Acquires-1018percent-Stake-from-Blackstone-Affiliate/69a12c20fa7d0695d1ab4a5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aadhar-Housing-AXDI-Acquires-1018percent-Stake-from-Blackstone-Affiliate/69a12c20fa7d0695d1ab4a5a</guid><description>AXDI LDII SPV 1 Ltd. has acquired a significant 10.18% stake in Aadhar Housing Finance Limited via an off-market transfer from BCP Topco VII Pte. Ltd., an affiliate of Blackstone. The transaction, completed on February 26, 2026, marks a shift as the acquirer is not part of the existing promoter group. This move introduces a new substantial shareholder and may influence the company's strategic direction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:31:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12c20fa7d0695d1ab4a59_1772170408932.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India to Invest ₹50,000 Crore in Coal-to-Chemicals Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-to-Invest-50000-Crore-in-Coal-to-Chemicals-Push/69a12ba4fa7d0695d1ab49ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-to-Invest-50000-Crore-in-Coal-to-Chemicals-Push/69a12ba4fa7d0695d1ab49ce</guid><description>Coal India Limited is embarking on a significant Rs 50,000 crore diversification strategy through three major coal gasification projects. These ventures will focus on producing downstream chemicals, including ammonium nitrate, and synthetic natural gas (SNG). The move aims to substantially reduce India's reliance on imported industrial feedstock and natural gas, marking a strategic pivot for the company toward integrated energy and chemicals production.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:29:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12ba4fa7d0695d1ab49cd_1772170461656.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Drishya Advisory Sells Harmony Capital Stake; Holding Drops to 0.50%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Drishya-Advisory-Sells-Harmony-Capital-Stake-Holding-Drops-to-050percent/69a12ab3fa7d0695d1ab48a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Drishya-Advisory-Sells-Harmony-Capital-Stake-Holding-Drops-to-050percent/69a12ab3fa7d0695d1ab48a1</guid><description>Drishya Advisory LLP has significantly reduced its stake in Harmony Capital Service Ltd., selling 3,50,000 shares and dropping its holding from 12.17% to a mere 0.50%. The transaction occurred via an Open Offer on February 24, 2026. This move marks a substantial shift in the company's shareholding structure, potentially signalling a change in strategic focus or investor participation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:25:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12ab3fa7d0695d1ab48a0_1772170007653.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Exchange India: Promoter Pledges 12 Cr Shares for ₹100 Cr Loan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Exchange-India-Promoter-Pledges-12-Cr-Shares-for-100-Cr-Loan/69a128d7fa7d0695d1ab4744</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Exchange-India-Promoter-Pledges-12-Cr-Shares-for-100-Cr-Loan/69a128d7fa7d0695d1ab4744</guid><description>Vizag Profiles Private Limited, a promoter of Steel Exchange India Limited, has pledged an additional 12 crore shares, representing 9.62% of the company's total capital, as collateral for a ₹100 crore loan facility. This action increases the total encumbered promoter holding to 19.32 crore shares (15.50% of total capital). The move follows a recent release of shares by the promoter group and comes amid ongoing fundraising efforts by the company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:17:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a128d7fa7d0695d1ab4743_1772169554746.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Exchange India: Trustee pledges 9.62% shares for Vizag Profiles debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Exchange-India-Trustee-pledges-962percent-shares-for-Vizag-Profiles-debt/69a1285afa7d0695d1ab46e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Steel-Exchange-India-Trustee-pledges-962percent-shares-for-Vizag-Profiles-debt/69a1285afa7d0695d1ab46e6</guid><description>Catalyst Trusteeship Limited, acting as Debenture Trustee for Vizag Profiles Private Limited, has disclosed a pledge of 120,000,000 equity shares, representing 9.62% of Steel Exchange India Ltd's (SEIL) total share capital. This move, effective February 26, 2026, is undertaken under SEBI's Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers (SAST) Regulations, highlighting potential control implications tied to Vizag Profiles' debenture obligations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:15:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1285afa7d0695d1ab46e5_1772169624148.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sai Life Sciences Hits New High Amidst Growth &amp; Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Hits-New-High-Amidst-Growth-and-Valuation-Concerns/69a126f0fa7d0695d1ab45c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sai-Life-Sciences-Hits-New-High-Amidst-Growth-and-Valuation-Concerns/69a126f0fa7d0695d1ab45c7</guid><description>Sai Life Sciences shares touched a record high, propelled by robust revenue growth and expanding margins in its integrated CRDMO model. The company has seen impressive compounded annual growth rates in revenue and profitability, supported by strong client relationships. Analysts maintain a "Strong Buy" consensus with significant upside potential. However, the stock's elevated valuation, heavy reliance on regulated export markets, and recent governance warnings warrant careful consideration amidst industry headwinds and intense competition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:09:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a126f0fa7d0695d1ab45c6_1772169085959.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UltraTech Cement: Aggressive Growth Meets Elevated Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UltraTech-Cement-Aggressive-Growth-Meets-Elevated-Valuation/69a1258afa7d0695d1ab43d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UltraTech-Cement-Aggressive-Growth-Meets-Elevated-Valuation/69a1258afa7d0695d1ab43d4</guid><description>Motilal Oswal reiterated a 'Buy' on UltraTech Cement with a ₹15,000 target, citing significant market share gains driven by aggressive capacity expansion and strategic acquisitions like Kesoram and ICEM. The company aims to boost domestic grey cement capacity to 235.4 mtpa by FY28. However, its current P/E ratio exceeds 50x, higher than the industry average, and current ROE remains moderate at around 9-10%, raising questions about the sustainability of projected earnings growth and valuation multiples. Despite sector tailwinds from infrastructure spending and a consensus 'Buy' rating, a wide range in analyst price targets suggests differing views on its future trajectory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a1258afa7d0695d1ab43d3_1772168898570.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Raptee Bets Big on Electric Motorcycles: 750K Unit Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Raptee-Bets-Big-on-Electric-Motorcycles-750K-Unit-Ambition/69a12556fa7d0695d1ab4380</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Raptee-Bets-Big-on-Electric-Motorcycles-750K-Unit-Ambition/69a12556fa7d0695d1ab4380</guid><description>Electric motorcycle startup Raptee is embarking on an ambitious expansion, securing 40 acres for a new plant near Cheyyar with a projected capacity of 750,000 units over eight years. This move coincides with the commercial launch and deliveries of its T30 model, differentiating itself with high-voltage technology adapted from electric cars and an eight-year battery warranty. The company has raised approximately $12.8 million to $29.5 million in various funding rounds and is actively seeking further investment to fuel this significant production scale-up.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:02:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12556fa7d0695d1ab437f_1772168929330.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Leela's Luxury Bet: High Valuation Meets Bullish Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Leelas-Luxury-Bet-High-Valuation-Meets-Bullish-Outlook/69a12499fa7d0695d1ab4293</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Leelas-Luxury-Bet-High-Valuation-Meets-Bullish-Outlook/69a12499fa7d0695d1ab4293</guid><description>Leela Palaces Hotels &amp; Resorts is projecting significant revenue and earnings growth for fiscal year 2027, underpinned by India's robust luxury travel demand and limited high-end hotel supply. The company, planning to expand its portfolio to at least 35 hotels, reported strong operational performance in the nine months ending December 31, 2025. Despite a generally optimistic analyst consensus and a 'Strong Buy' rating, Leela's market valuation, characterized by a high P/E ratio, presents a significant point of consideration against its recent stock performance and historical profit fluctuations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:59:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12499fa7d0695d1ab4292_1772168638154.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto's KTM AG Refinances EUR 550M Debt With International Consortium</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Autos-KTM-AG-Refinances-EUR-550M-Debt-With-International-Consortium/69a12423fa7d0695d1ab420e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Autos-KTM-AG-Refinances-EUR-550M-Debt-With-International-Consortium/69a12423fa7d0695d1ab420e</guid><description>KTM AG, a subsidiary of Bajaj Auto's Bajaj Mobility AG, has secured a EUR 550 million refinancing loan from an international banking consortium. This move strengthens KTM's financial foundation, replacing a previous EUR 450 million loan from Bajaj Auto International Holdings B.V. and completing its financial restructuring efforts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:57:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12423fa7d0695d1ab420d_1772168325815.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bihar MFI Bill Sparks 3-10% Drop in Lender Stocks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bihar-MFI-Bill-Sparks-3-10percent-Drop-in-Lender-Stocks/69a12003fa7d0695d1ab3f0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bihar-MFI-Bill-Sparks-3-10percent-Drop-in-Lender-Stocks/69a12003fa7d0695d1ab3f0a</guid><description>Microfinance lenders Utkarsh Small Finance Bank, Fusion Finance, and L&amp;T Finance saw significant stock declines of 3-10% on February 27, 2026. The trigger was Bihar's passage of a stringent Micro Finance Institutions Bill, mirroring Karnataka's prior legislation. The bill imposes mandatory state registration, interest rate caps, and borrower exposure limits, impacting companies with substantial operations in Bihar, which accounts for 15% of the national MFI market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:39:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a12003fa7d0695d1ab3f09_1772167303001.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Green Energy Growth Hindered by Grid Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Energy-Growth-Hindered-by-Grid-Strain/69a11f7dfa7d0695d1ab3e07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Energy-Growth-Hindered-by-Grid-Strain/69a11f7dfa7d0695d1ab3e07</guid><description>India's renewable energy expansion faces significant headwinds. Curtailment of solar output, estimated at 2.3 TWh in late 2025, stems from grid absorption limits and inflexible coal plants. Transmission delays are stranding 50 GW of capacity, causing project losses of up to Rs 700 crore. Accelerated investment in energy storage, particularly pumped hydro, and urgent transmission infrastructure upgrades are critical to de-risk investments and meet India's 500 GW non-fossil fuel target by 2030.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:37:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11f7dfa7d0695d1ab3e06_1772167241414.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Realty Stocks Tumble Amidst Demand Shift &amp; IT Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Realty-Stocks-Tumble-Amidst-Demand-Shift-and-IT-Headwinds/69a11f0ffa7d0695d1ab3ce5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Realty-Stocks-Tumble-Amidst-Demand-Shift-and-IT-Headwinds/69a11f0ffa7d0695d1ab3ce5</guid><description>Indian realty stocks have experienced a significant correction, with the Nifty Realty Index underperforming the broader market. This divergence from developers' positive sales guidance highlights underlying market shifts. Demand is moderating in volume terms, with a pronounced structural move towards premium housing and a contraction in the affordable segment. New property launches have also slowed, with the exception of the Mumbai Metropolitan Region. Furthermore, the downturn in the IT sector is creating a ripple effect, impacting potential homebuyer confidence and sales.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:35:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11f0ffa7d0695d1ab3ce4_1772167095613.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fuels Block's Growth Strategy: 4,000 Jobs Cut, Stock Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fuels-Blocks-Growth-Strategy-4000-Jobs-Cut-Stock-Soars/69a11f0ffa7d0695d1ab3cce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fuels-Blocks-Growth-Strategy-4000-Jobs-Cut-Stock-Soars/69a11f0ffa7d0695d1ab3cce</guid><description>Block Inc. is cutting over 4,000 jobs, nearly half its workforce, in a strategic AI-driven restructuring. This move, aimed at boosting efficiency and growth, saw its stock surge 25%. The company cited AI advancements enabling smaller teams to achieve greater output, signaling a departure from traditional layoff narratives.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:35:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11f0ffa7d0695d1ab3ccd_1772167302613.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godrej Properties: BUY Upgrade Amidst Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-BUY-Upgrade-Amidst-Margin-Pressures/69a11efdfa7d0695d1ab3c98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-BUY-Upgrade-Amidst-Margin-Pressures/69a11efdfa7d0695d1ab3c98</guid><description>Godrej Properties reported a 54.6% surge in Q3 FY26 booking value, supported by robust home sales and a growing project pipeline. Customer collections rose 39.5% to ₹4,282 crore. However, the company posted a negative EBITDA of ₹197 crore due to significant cost escalations. Despite this, Geojit Financial Services upgraded the stock to BUY with a ₹2,096 target price, based on projected FY28 book value. This upgrade overlooks near-term margin compression and the reliance on other income for profit growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:35:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11efdfa7d0695d1ab3c97_1772167060876.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alka India to AUDROC; Approves ₹355 Cr Preferential Issue &amp; Higher Limits</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Alka-India-to-AUDROC-Approves-355-Cr-Preferential-Issue-and-Higher-Limits/69a11e86fa7d0695d1ab3bde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Alka-India-to-AUDROC-Approves-355-Cr-Preferential-Issue-and-Higher-Limits/69a11e86fa7d0695d1ab3bde</guid><description>Alka India Limited has proposed a name change to AUDROC Limited, pending approvals. The company also sanctioned a ₹354.96 crore preferential share issuance and significantly increased its borrowing and investment limits to ₹5,000 crore each. A material subsidiary, Vintage FZE (India) Private Limited, is being divested for ₹0.90 lakh. These moves signal a strategic shift and increased financial flexibility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:33:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a11e86fa7d0695d1ab3bdd_1772167186104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>