<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:26:17 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Jeena Sikho Lifecare Skyrockets 92% Revenue, Eyes Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Jeena-Sikho-Lifecare-Skyrockets-92percent-Revenue-Eyes-Global-Expansion/698853e2b81b2b81dcfd4cee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Jeena-Sikho-Lifecare-Skyrockets-92percent-Revenue-Eyes-Global-Expansion/698853e2b81b2b81dcfd4cee</guid><description>Jeena Sikho Lifecare reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with revenues soaring 92% YoY to ₹221.66 Crore and PAT jumping 405% to ₹66.73 Crore. The company showcased strong operational growth, improved YoY margins, and announced significant capacity expansion plans, including international diversification, while maintaining a debt-free status.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:14:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698853e2b81b2b81dcfd4ced_1770542192454.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSBs' Record Profit Surge: FDI Hike, Growth Drivers Scrutinized</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSBs-Record-Profit-Surge-FDI-Hike-Growth-Drivers-Scrutinized/69885114b81b2b81dcfd4b01</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSBs-Record-Profit-Surge-FDI-Hike-Growth-Drivers-Scrutinized/69885114b81b2b81dcfd4b01</guid><description>Public Sector Banks (PSBs) are poised to achieve a historic combined profit exceeding ₹2 lakh crore in FY26, building on sustained growth and improved asset quality [cite: Input]. Credit expansion is robust at 12%, with deposit growth at 10% [cite: Input]. The government is exploring a hike in Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) limits for PSBs to 49%, a move aimed at bolstering capital access. Despite this strong performance, the sector faces scrutiny over competitive pressures, deposit mobilization challenges, and evolving regulatory landscapes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:02:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69885114b81b2b81dcfd4b00_1770541471106.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titan Eyes $2 Billion Watch Sales Post-EU Trade Deal, Swiss Luxury Boom Expected</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Eyes-2-Billion-Watch-Sales-Post-EU-Trade-Deal-Swiss-Luxury-Boom-Expected/6988509cb81b2b81dcfd49cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Eyes-2-Billion-Watch-Sales-Post-EU-Trade-Deal-Swiss-Luxury-Boom-Expected/6988509cb81b2b81dcfd49cb</guid><description>Titan Company anticipates a significant rise in Indian sales for luxury Swiss watches, driven by the India-EU Free Trade Agreement which lowers import duties. The Tata group firm aims to boost overall watch sales to $2 billion by FY30, heavily leaning on premiumization and expanding its Helios and Helios Luxe formats. This strategic push positions Swiss brands to become more competitive, potentially reshaping India's premium watch market.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:00:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988509cb81b2b81dcfd49ca_1770541339438.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Reshapes Global Aerospace: Delhi Ascends</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-US-Trade-Deal-Reshapes-Global-Aerospace-Delhi-Ascends/69884a0cb81b2b81dcfd4725</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-US-Trade-Deal-Reshapes-Global-Aerospace-Delhi-Ascends/69884a0cb81b2b81dcfd4725</guid><description>The India-U.S. trade agreement unlocks zero-duty access for Indian aerospace components into the American market, fundamentally altering global supply chain dynamics. This strategic shift elevates India to parity with established Asian and European hubs, driving increased sourcing by major OEMs like Boeing and Airbus. Concurrently, the pact is expected to stimulate substantial new aircraft orders from India's rapidly expanding aviation sector, projecting billions in future fleet expansion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:32:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69884a0cb81b2b81dcfd4724_1770539686416.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T's Strategic Pivot: Data Centers, Green Energy Fueling Future Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandTs-Strategic-Pivot-Data-Centers-Green-Energy-Fueling-Future-Growth/6988499bb81b2b81dcfd45c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandTs-Strategic-Pivot-Data-Centers-Green-Energy-Fueling-Future-Growth/6988499bb81b2b81dcfd45c2</guid><description>Infrastructure giant Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T) is making substantial investments in high-growth sectors. The company plans to commission 18 MW of data center capacity by March-end, bringing its total to 32 MW, backed by a Rs 1,000 crore capital expenditure. Concurrently, L&amp;T is advancing its green energy ambitions with an indigenous 4 MW electrolyzer stack upgrade to 8-10 MW, anticipating significant future orders. These strategic expansions in digital infrastructure and sustainable energy underscore a forward-looking diversification strategy, even as the company navigates a Q3 profit decline attributed to a one-time Rs 1,191 crore provision for new labor codes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:30:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988499bb81b2b81dcfd45c1_1770539522353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>E-Way Bill Surge: India's Economy Accelerates, Supply Chain Strain Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/E-Way-Bill-Surge-Indias-Economy-Accelerates-Supply-Chain-Strain-Looms/698843f2b81b2b81dcfd432d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/E-Way-Bill-Surge-Indias-Economy-Accelerates-Supply-Chain-Strain-Looms/698843f2b81b2b81dcfd432d</guid><description>India's e-way bill generation saw a significant surge in January, reaching 136.83 million, its second-highest monthly total. This robust growth, up 42.6% year-on-year, reflects strong consumption-led demand and improved economic activity. Experts interpret this as a positive sign for GST collections and overall economic health, aligning with optimistic GDP growth forecasts. However, the rapid increase also points to potential strain on supply chains and logistics networks, warranting a closer look at underlying sustainability and operational efficiency.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:06:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698843f2b81b2b81dcfd432c_1770538195419.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Air Taxi Vision Faces Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Air-Taxi-Vision-Faces-Hurdles/6988431cb81b2b81dcfd40fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Air-Taxi-Vision-Faces-Hurdles/6988431cb81b2b81dcfd40fc</guid><description>A recent report from the Confederation of Indian Industry (CII) proposes electric air taxis (eVTOLs) utilizing building rooftops to alleviate India's chronic traffic congestion. While the vision offers a path to rapid urban transit, significant regulatory voids, substantial infrastructure investment requirements, and the immaturity of the global advanced air mobility (AAM) sector present considerable obstacles to rapid implementation. The prospect faces a long road from concept to a functioning, scalable network, despite the Indian aviation sector's growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:02:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988431cb81b2b81dcfd40fb_1770538120852.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Karnataka's Auto Land Conversion: Efficiency Boost or New Discretion?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Karnatakas-Auto-Land-Conversion-Efficiency-Boost-or-New-Discretion/69884306b81b2b81dcfd405d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Karnatakas-Auto-Land-Conversion-Efficiency-Boost-or-New-Discretion/69884306b81b2b81dcfd405d</guid><description>Karnataka has launched an auto-conversion policy for land within the Greater Bengaluru Authority (GBA) region, eliminating the need for separate land conversion permits. This reform aims to expedite development, reduce bureaucratic delays, and tackle corruption, while also enabling 'B' Khata properties to transition to 'A' Khata status. The move is situated against a backdrop of surging property values and significant urbanization in Bengaluru, with broad implications for developers and property owners.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:02:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69884306b81b2b81dcfd405c_1770537877921.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trade Deal Boosts India Inc.; Q3 Earnings, Inflation Data in Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Deal-Boosts-India-Inc-Q3-Earnings-Inflation-Data-in-Focus/69884032b81b2b81dcfd3e5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Deal-Boosts-India-Inc-Q3-Earnings-Inflation-Data-in-Focus/69884032b81b2b81dcfd3e5c</guid><description>The Indian stock market is navigating a week dominated by the landmark India-US trade agreement, which significantly reduces tariffs and aims to boost bilateral commerce. Investors are also closely monitoring the ongoing Q3 earnings season, with major corporations such as Titan, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, and ONGC set to release their financial results. Crucial domestic economic data, including inflation and foreign exchange reserves, will provide further market direction. This confluence of events positions the market for an event-driven period, following a phase of consolidation post-budget and monetary policy announcements.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:50:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69884032b81b2b81dcfd3e5b_1770537127440.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Forges Mega-Lenders: PFC-REC Merger Fuels 'Viksit Bharat' Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Forges-Mega-Lenders-PFC-REC-Merger-Fuels-Viksit-Bharat-Ambition/69883acdb81b2b81dcfd3708</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Forges-Mega-Lenders-PFC-REC-Merger-Fuels-Viksit-Bharat-Ambition/69883acdb81b2b81dcfd3708</guid><description>The Indian government is orchestrating a significant restructuring of its financial sector to bolster lending capacity for the 'Viksit Bharat' initiative. This includes the proposed merger of Power Finance Corporation (PFC) and Rural Electrification Corporation (REC) and the formation of a High-Level Committee on Banking. This dual strategy aims to create large-scale financial institutions capable of meeting the substantial funding needs of India's future growth phases, emphasizing scale, efficiency, and robust credit disbursement.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:27:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69883acdb81b2b81dcfd3707_1770536123133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New Income Tax Rules Draft Released: CBDT Seeks Public Input for Simpler Compliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/New-Income-Tax-Rules-Draft-Released-CBDT-Seeks-Public-Input-for-Simpler-Compliance/69883ab3b81b2b81dcfd3604</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/New-Income-Tax-Rules-Draft-Released-CBDT-Seeks-Public-Input-for-Simpler-Compliance/69883ab3b81b2b81dcfd3604</guid><description>The Central Board of Direct Taxes (CBDT) has released draft income tax rules under the new Income Tax Act, 2025, set to take effect April 1, 2026. Aimed at enhancing ease of compliance, the CBDT is actively inviting suggestions from stakeholders across four key areas: simplifying language, reducing litigation, cutting compliance burdens, and identifying obsolete rules. This consultation phase precedes the final notification of the rules and forms.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:26:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69883ab3b81b2b81dcfd3603_1770535824075.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Fuels Market Surge; IT Stocks Falter Amid AI Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Reliance-Fuels-Market-Surge-IT-Stocks-Falter-Amid-AI-Fears/69883a93b81b2b81dcfd3568</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Reliance-Fuels-Market-Surge-IT-Stocks-Falter-Amid-AI-Fears/69883a93b81b2b81dcfd3568</guid><description>India's leading companies added a substantial ₹4.55 lakh crore in market capitalization last week, driven primarily by Reliance Industries amid a broad equity market rally. In stark contrast, technology giants Tata Consultancy Services and Infosys saw their valuations diminish, reflecting global anxieties surrounding artificial intelligence advancements and stretched valuations. This divergence signals a sector rotation, favoring diversified conglomerates over technology exporters.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:26:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69883a93b81b2b81dcfd3567_1770535947885.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HAL Out of AMCA Race; Defence Bets on Private Sector Power</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/HAL-Out-of-AMCA-Race-Defence-Bets-on-Private-Sector-Power/69883a1ab81b2b81dcfd33fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/HAL-Out-of-AMCA-Race-Defence-Bets-on-Private-Sector-Power/69883a1ab81b2b81dcfd33fa</guid><description>Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL) has been disqualified from India's ambitious fifth-generation fighter jet program, the Advanced Multirole Combat Aircraft (AMCA). This decision by the Aeronautical Development Agency (ADA) follows HAL's persistent delivery delays and capacity constraints, clearing the path for private sector consortia led by Tata Advanced Systems and Larsen &amp; Toubro to develop the crucial defense project. The move signals a significant strategic shift in India's defense manufacturing landscape.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:24:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69883a1ab81b2b81dcfd33f9_1770535572281.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trade Pact Inks Deal, But Inflation, Earnings Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Pact-Inks-Deal-But-Inflation-Earnings-Loom/698835e2b81b2b81dcfd313e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Pact-Inks-Deal-But-Inflation-Earnings-Loom/698835e2b81b2b81dcfd313e</guid><description>The Indian stock market is poised for an event-driven week, balancing optimism from a new India-US trade framework against persistent inflation concerns and a critical Q3 earnings season. While the trade agreement promises to reduce tariffs, investors are keenly awaiting domestic inflation data on February 12 and foreign exchange reserves on February 13. Key corporate results from Titan Company, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, ONGC, and others will also dictate stock-specific movements. Analysts suggest a consolidation phase, emphasizing implementation and spending pace, amidst global economic uncertainties and geopolitical developments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:06:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698835e2b81b2b81dcfd313d_1770534617198.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amira Foods Promoters Declared Fugitives in ₹1.2K Cr Fraud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Amira-Foods-Promoters-Declared-Fugitives-in-12K-Cr-Fraud/6988356eb81b2b81dcfd2fc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Amira-Foods-Promoters-Declared-Fugitives-in-12K-Cr-Fraud/6988356eb81b2b81dcfd2fc3</guid><description>Karan A Chanana and Anita Daing, promoters of Amira Pure Foods Pvt Ltd (APFPL), have been declared fugitive economic offenders by a Delhi court. This designation follows allegations of a ₹1,201.85 crore bank loan fraud. The court ordered the confiscation of ₹123 crore in assets, impacting the global operations of the rice brand. The accused are currently abroad and have refused to face prosecution in India.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:04:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988356eb81b2b81dcfd2fc2_1770534493744.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty Holds Support Amid Trade Deal Boost, Earnings Cloud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Holds-Support-Amid-Trade-Deal-Boost-Earnings-Cloud/698834f3b81b2b81dcfd2e71</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Holds-Support-Amid-Trade-Deal-Boost-Earnings-Cloud/698834f3b81b2b81dcfd2e71</guid><description>Indian equity markets displayed notable resilience following the India-US trade agreement, which saw tariffs reduced and provided a significant sentiment boost, leading to a strong rally. The Nifty 50 closed February 7, 2026, near its day's high. However, the index continues to exhibit a lower-high, lower-low pattern on charts, suggesting underlying technical weakness. The upcoming corporate earnings season introduces a layer of uncertainty, with broad EPS estimate cuts contrasting with specific sector resilience, creating a complex outlook.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:02:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698834f3b81b2b81dcfd2e70_1770534316569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Equities Lag: Value vs. Risk in Small-Cap Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Equities-Lag-Value-vs-Risk-in-Small-Cap-Push/69883480b81b2b81dcfd2d2f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Equities-Lag-Value-vs-Risk-in-Small-Cap-Push/69883480b81b2b81dcfd2d2f</guid><description>Indian equities recorded modest 8-10% gains in 2025, significantly underperforming global benchmarks that surged over 20%. Despite a decade-long winning streak, this relative lag signals underlying pressures. Analyst recommendations to pivot toward small and mid-cap stocks, citing attractive entry points after sharp corrections, are tempered by elevated valuations and persistent earnings misses. Concurrently, regulatory shifts, including the EU-India FTA and Budget 2026, alongside global AI investment trends, shape a complex outlook.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:00:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69883480b81b2b81dcfd2d2e_1770534228163.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sun Pharma Eyes Organic Growth, Keeps M&amp;A Discipline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sun-Pharma-Eyes-Organic-Growth-Keeps-MandA-Discipline/698833ffb81b2b81dcfd2bdc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Sun-Pharma-Eyes-Organic-Growth-Keeps-MandA-Discipline/698833ffb81b2b81dcfd2bdc</guid><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd. plans to maintain a disciplined approach to mergers and acquisitions, prioritizing organic business growth to enhance shareholder value. Chairman Dilip Shanghvi highlighted a focus on innovative medicines in the US market and strategic 'tuck-in' acquisitions for emerging markets. The company is also actively evaluating opportunities in the biosimilar segment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:58:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698833ffb81b2b81dcfd2bdb_1770534264754.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Malaysia Tech Pact: Strategic Trust Fuels Economic Transformation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Malaysia-Tech-Pact-Strategic-Trust-Fuels-Economic-Transformation/69883313b81b2b81dcfd2a2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Malaysia-Tech-Pact-Strategic-Trust-Fuels-Economic-Transformation/69883313b81b2b81dcfd2a2a</guid><description>India and Malaysia are escalating bilateral cooperation into cutting-edge sectors including digital technologies, artificial intelligence, and semiconductors. This strategic alliance is underpinned by a commitment to "economic transformation through strategic trust," fostering unprecedented speed and depth in mutual investments across digital economy, biotechnology, and IT. The partnership aims to bolster regional stability and economic resilience in emerging global dynamics, with specific measures to ease citizen mobility and enhance security cooperation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:54:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69883313b81b2b81dcfd2a29_1770533874098.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget: Growth Surge Amidst Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Growth-Surge-Amidst-Execution-Hurdles/69883242b81b2b81dcfd2869</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Growth-Surge-Amidst-Execution-Hurdles/69883242b81b2b81dcfd2869</guid><description>India's 2026-27 Union Budget signals an ambitious economic trajectory, projecting real GDP growth between 6.8% and 7.2% and substantial capital expenditure increases. While aiming for fiscal consolidation with a deficit target of 4.3% of GDP, the plan hinges on effective implementation amidst global volatility and internal execution risks. Sustained infrastructure investment and human capital development are core pillars, but the scale of the fiscal push necessitates vigilant oversight.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:50:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69883242b81b2b81dcfd2868_1770533656902.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SH Kelkar Posts Profit Turnaround Amidst Investment Push, US Deal Inked</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/SH-Kelkar-Posts-Profit-Turnaround-Amidst-Investment-Push-US-Deal-Inked/69883224b81b2b81dcfd2753</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/SH-Kelkar-Posts-Profit-Turnaround-Amidst-Investment-Push-US-Deal-Inked/69883224b81b2b81dcfd2753</guid><description>S H Kelkar &amp; Company Ltd has turned profitable for the nine months ending FY2026, reporting Rs. 67.4 crore profit against a prior-year loss. Revenue grew 10.4% YoY to Rs. 1,718 crore. However, EBITDA margins compressed YoY, with Q3 FY2026 at 9.7% from 11.9%. Management cites strategic investments in global growth centres, including securing its first US customer order, as drivers for long-term expansion. The company acknowledges potential near-term debt increases for these initiatives.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:50:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69883224b81b2b81dcfd2752_1770533544220.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rally Diverges: Reliance Soars as AI Fears Hit Indian IT</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rally-Diverges-Reliance-Soars-as-AI-Fears-Hit-Indian-IT/69882593b81b2b81dcfd232b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rally-Diverges-Reliance-Soars-as-AI-Fears-Hit-Indian-IT/69882593b81b2b81dcfd232b</guid><description>India's top-valued companies experienced a significant collective market capitalization increase of ₹4.55 trillion, fueled by a broad equity rally. Reliance Industries was the primary beneficiary, adding ₹1.41 trillion to its valuation. In stark contrast, the IT sector, including Tata Consultancy Services and Infosys, saw its market value diminish, predominantly due to escalating concerns surrounding artificial intelligence and its potential disruption to traditional software services, mirroring global tech market sentiment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:56:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69882593b81b2b81dcfd232a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anant Raj Partners Submer for India's AI Data Center Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anant-Raj-Partners-Submer-for-Indias-AI-Data-Center-Expansion/6988257cb81b2b81dcfd2213</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anant-Raj-Partners-Submer-for-Indias-AI-Data-Center-Expansion/6988257cb81b2b81dcfd2213</guid><description>Anant Raj Limited, via its subsidiary Anant Raj Cloud, has partnered with Spain's Submer Technologies to bolster AI infrastructure in India. The collaboration focuses on deploying AI-ready, high-density, and energy-efficient computing platforms, leveraging Submer's liquid-cooling tech. This move aims to support sovereign and enterprise AI workloads, driving India's digital economy and AI sovereignty goals, aligning with national initiatives like 'Digital India'.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:56:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988257cb81b2b81dcfd2212_1770530370569.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Motors Signals Price Hikes Amid Soaring Commodity Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Signals-Price-Hikes-Amid-Soaring-Commodity-Costs/69882410b81b2b81dcfd207d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-Signals-Price-Hikes-Amid-Soaring-Commodity-Costs/69882410b81b2b81dcfd207d</guid><description>Tata Motors is poised to increase passenger vehicle prices in the coming weeks, citing persistent pressure from rising commodity costs. Managing Director and CEO Shailesh Chandra confirmed the move, noting a significant impact on the company's cost structure. This follows similar concerns from Maruti Suzuki and Hyundai Motor India, indicating a sector-wide pricing adjustment trend due to escalating input expenses.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:50:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69882410b81b2b81dcfd207c_1770530048899.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jio Studios Confirms 'Dhurandhar 2' Will Dwarf First Film's Blockbuster Success</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Jio-Studios-Confirms-Dhurandhar-2-Will-Dwarf-First-Films-Blockbuster-Success/6988239fb81b2b81dcfd1f0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Jio-Studios-Confirms-Dhurandhar-2-Will-Dwarf-First-Films-Blockbuster-Success/6988239fb81b2b81dcfd1f0a</guid><description>Jio Studios' 'Dhurandhar' has shattered box office records, grossing ₹1,051.14 crore in India and a staggering ₹1,344.64 crore worldwide. The film's phenomenal 60-day theatrical run and global Netflix ranking signal a new era for Indian cinema. President Jyoti Deshpande confirmed that the sequel, 'Dhurandhar 2', is already shot and is poised to be significantly larger than its predecessor, featuring a five-language release.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:48:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6988239fb81b2b81dcfd1f09_1770529874885.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KKR's $2.5B Asia Bet: Betting on Growth Amidst US Credit Warnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KKRs-25B-Asia-Bet-Betting-on-Growth-Amidst-US-Credit-Warnings/69882338b81b2b81dcfd1dab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KKRs-25B-Asia-Bet-Betting-on-Growth-Amidst-US-Credit-Warnings/69882338b81b2b81dcfd1dab</guid><description>KKR is channeling $2.5 billion into its Asia private credit strategy, notably via its Asia Credit Opportunities Fund II (ACOF II), aiming for low-teen returns. This move contrasts sharply with cautionary voices like Jeffrey Gundlach regarding the U.S. private credit market, as KKR bets on Asia's structural growth drivers and its own deep regional expertise. The strategy emphasizes control and bespoke solutions in a market less developed than its Western counterparts, with India emerging as a prime target.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:46:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69882338b81b2b81dcfd1daa_1770529757049.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Agri Deal: Farmer Fears Amid Calibrated Opening</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-US-Agri-Deal-Farmer-Fears-Amid-Calibrated-Opening/69881d87b81b2b81dcfd1680</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-US-Agri-Deal-Farmer-Fears-Amid-Calibrated-Opening/69881d87b81b2b81dcfd1680</guid><description>India has finalized an interim trade agreement with the US, involving a "calibrated" opening of its agricultural markets. While tariffs on US products like DDGS, tree nuts, and fruits will be reduced, Indian farmer groups voice strong concerns over potential price drops for key crops such as soybean and maize. The deal also navigates complexities around genetically modified (GM) ingredients in imports, despite assurances of protection for sensitive domestic sectors like dairy. Simultaneously, India gains zero-duty access for its own agricultural exports to the US, and broader trade in energy and technology is set to expand.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:22:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69881d87b81b2b81dcfd167f_1770528422737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Mundra Port Sets Records, Bolstering India's Trade Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Mundra-Port-Sets-Records-Bolstering-Indias-Trade-Dominance/69881cb5b81b2b81dcfd14ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Mundra-Port-Sets-Records-Bolstering-Indias-Trade-Dominance/69881cb5b81b2b81dcfd14ed</guid><description>Adani Mundra Port achieved unprecedented operational highs in January 2026, setting new monthly records for automobile exports and liquid cargo throughput. These achievements highlight the port's increasing significance in supporting India's trade flows, driven by strong demand from key automakers and robust handling capacity for diverse cargo streams. This performance cements Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Limited's (APSEZ) position as a critical infrastructure provider.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:18:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69881cb5b81b2b81dcfd14ec_1770528224279.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shree Cements Bets on RMC Expansion, Eyes Q4 Volume Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shree-Cements-Bets-on-RMC-Expansion-Eyes-Q4-Volume-Surge/69881c91b81b2b81dcfd13e6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shree-Cements-Bets-on-RMC-Expansion-Eyes-Q4-Volume-Surge/69881c91b81b2b81dcfd13e6</guid><description>Shree Cements anticipates a significant rebound in Q4 FY26 cement volumes, targeting 9-9.5 million tonnes, driven by infrastructure growth and government spending. Concurrently, the company is aggressively expanding its ready-mix concrete (RMC) business, aiming to double its plant footprint to 45 units within eight months as a strategic move to enhance its position in the construction value chain. Management also confirmed a debt-free status with substantial cash reserves and outlined ongoing capacity expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:18:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69881c91b81b2b81dcfd13e5_1770528085088.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titan Names Gukesh 'Titan of Year', Unveils ₹70k Luxury Watch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Names-Gukesh-Titan-of-Year-Unveils-70k-Luxury-Watch/69881c17b81b2b81dcfd12b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Names-Gukesh-Titan-of-Year-Unveils-70k-Luxury-Watch/69881c17b81b2b81dcfd12b7</guid><description>Titan Company is amplifying its premiumisation strategy, appointing chess prodigy Gukesh Dommaraju as 'Titan of the Year 2026' and introducing a ₹69,995 limited-edition automatic watch. This initiative underscores Titan's pivot towards long-term brand building and associating high-end timepieces with global Indian achievers to capture a larger share of the rapidly expanding premium watch market.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:16:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69881c17b81b2b81dcfd12b6_1770527884944.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Pact Spurs Semiconductor, Data Center Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-US-Trade-Pact-Spurs-Semiconductor-Data-Center-Growth/69881421b81b2b81dcfd0fe3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-US-Trade-Pact-Spurs-Semiconductor-Data-Center-Growth/69881421b81b2b81dcfd0fe3</guid><description>India's semiconductor and data center ambitions are set for a significant boost following the interim trade framework agreement with the US. Pan IIT Alumni India highlights the deal as a catalyst for deeper tech collaboration and supply chain resilience, aligning with recent Union Budget measures. This strategic move aims to attract global investment and leverage India's manufacturing capabilities amidst shifting global supply chains.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:42:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69881421b81b2b81dcfd0fe2_1770525923723.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Veolia Secures Mumbai Water Deal, Eyes 60% Demand by 2030</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Veolia-Secures-Mumbai-Water-Deal-Eyes-60percent-Demand-by-2030/698813aeb81b2b81dcfd0ef1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Veolia-Secures-Mumbai-Water-Deal-Eyes-60percent-Demand-by-2030/698813aeb81b2b81dcfd0ef1</guid><description>Veolia Environnement is set to supply 60% of Mumbai's drinking water by 2030, with two major treatment facilities due online by 2029-2030. This partnership leverages Veolia's technological expertise and operational models to meet escalating urban demand in India's vast water sector. The contract underscores Veolia's ambition to more than double its Indian business by 2030, capitalizing on government initiatives and stringent environmental regulations driving market growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:40:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698813aeb81b2b81dcfd0ef0_1770525797168.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Doubles Deep Tech Startup Window, Boosts Capital Access</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Doubles-Deep-Tech-Startup-Window-Boosts-Capital-Access/69880a47b81b2b81dcfd0807</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Doubles-Deep-Tech-Startup-Window-Boosts-Capital-Access/69880a47b81b2b81dcfd0807</guid><description>India has significantly updated its startup framework, doubling the recognition period for deep tech companies to 20 years and increasing the revenue threshold for tax and grant benefits to ₹3 billion. This move aims to align policy with the long gestation periods of science-led ventures and bolster the nation's deep tech ecosystem through combined regulatory reform and public capital, including the ₹1 trillion RDI Fund. A new India Deep Tech Alliance, backed by major venture firms and Nvidia, also signals growing private sector commitment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:00:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69880a47b81b2b81dcfd0806_1770523377243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Century Enka Profits Soar 69% YoY on Margin Expansion Despite Revenue Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Century-Enka-Profits-Soar-69percent-YoY-on-Margin-Expansion-Despite-Revenue-Dip/6987fd28b81b2b81dcfd00a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Century-Enka-Profits-Soar-69percent-YoY-on-Margin-Expansion-Despite-Revenue-Dip/6987fd28b81b2b81dcfd00a1</guid><description>Century Enka reported a significant Q3-FY26 profit surge of 69.3% YoY to INR 237 Mn, fueled by a robust EBITDA margin expansion to 9.93%. This turnaround occurred despite a 16.6% YoY revenue decline to INR 4,117 Mn. For 9M-FY26, net profit grew 2.8% YoY to INR 614 Mn with improved margins. Management foresees better demand in Q4-FY26 but faces margin pressure from imports and rising raw material costs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:04:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987fd28b81b2b81dcfd00a0_1770519964454.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Profit Jumps 24.5% Amidst Rival Rally: NIM Pressure Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Profit-Jumps-245percent-Amidst-Rival-Rally-NIM-Pressure-Mounts/6987f63bb81b2b81dcfcfb87</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Profit-Jumps-245percent-Amidst-Rival-Rally-NIM-Pressure-Mounts/6987f63bb81b2b81dcfcfb87</guid><description>State Bank of India (SBI) reported a robust 24.5% year-on-year net profit growth in Q3 FY26, reaching a record high. This surge was driven by a 15.7% increase in advances, fueled by strong retail and SME loan growth. However, the bank, along with its rivals like Punjab National Bank (PNB), HDFC Bank, and Kotak Mahindra Bank, is navigating pressure on Net Interest Margins (NIMs) due to RBI's rate cut measures. SBI's Return on Assets (ROA) stood at 1.19%, trailing HDFC Bank and Kotak Mahindra Bank.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:34:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987f63bb81b2b81dcfcfb86_1770518281329.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Two-Wheeler Leaders Face Margin Squeeze Amidst Premium Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Two-Wheeler-Leaders-Face-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Premium-Valuations/6987f62cb81b2b81dcfcfb03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Two-Wheeler-Leaders-Face-Margin-Squeeze-Amidst-Premium-Valuations/6987f62cb81b2b81dcfcfb03</guid><description>Indian two-wheeler manufacturers TVS Motor, Hero MotoCorp, and Bajaj Auto have posted robust sales growth for the December 2025 quarter, driven by festive demand and policy tailwinds. TVS Motor led with a 27.5% sales volume increase and 37.1% revenue growth. However, rising commodity costs, one-time labor code expenses, and increasingly premium valuations, particularly for TVS Motor, present significant headwinds. While new model launches offer future promise, analysts signal caution regarding the sustainability of margins and the high multiples across the sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:34:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987f62cb81b2b81dcfcfb02_1770518171825.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>